<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="May" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>May you be my friend?</summary>
	<body>"May, want to be my friend?" is one of those movies that remind us that terror not always bears claws of steel in a hand or a mask on the face. Terror and madness are much more close to us the reality of our peaceful and even sometimes boring monotony. It may operates under the method: the beast sleeps within us. In each of us there is a possible psychopath and our neighbour of the second can hide a dark past or a double life. So, Lucky McKee, us it is effectively a story allegedly daily (However, hooked from the beginning) about a young man very similar to those many others that they swarm our around. The Raritan for the class, the shy girl from the grocery store, this strange sister of our friend, our prima of the people. This is why we boarded a commuter train, not a high-speed train with views to reruns of "The fresh Prince of Bell Air" and adolescents through and scenes unbearable with hormones surplus and deficit of neurons. In this train we are with well drawn characters and flesh and blood. Characters worked, attractive and even very daring. (The companion of May in the vet where he works has no waste) All of them revolve around the character of May, played with a lot of love and talent by Angela Bettis that succeeds in creating a character that shows compelling and original. The plot is as I say very interesting and surprising to a pace that breaks our expectations but that never disappoints us. The transformation that suffers from May and the hopeless desencadenación to a daunting destination, happens due to a range of features and very well explained and sound recognizable events that shape and mature the true face of terror.This is a film that takes runout to start before you begin where almost all the others of its kind, to then finish also well beyond where no other dare. Once Todd Solondz, known for achieving go too far with their jumps and shying away from the usual genres to invent his own, gave us "Welcome to the doll's House" (1996), (previous film to its acid and brilliant "Happyness" (1998) which has a lot to do with this.) In it, Mr Solondz, he addressed so raw and valiant, the drama of a girl ugly and traumatized, faced with the more stark reality. The biggest difference between them is, of course, that was not a horror film. Well, and to the point, do not expect conventional scenes, nor cats that are determined to lose, or efectistas sustitos, nor special effects because they do not need. This is a low-budget production but also it not noticeable. And he is not noticed, because it has a much more than correct picture, a heady, agonizing atmosphere an intelligent Assembly and a very real, and for this end, frighteningly real.This is a movie worth (of notable high for whom you write now) which is that friends, if "Amelie" had been a film of terror rather than a magical tale, that sweet francesita were no doubt called "May". And the magic, black magic, of course, very black.</body>
</review>
