<review author="Iñigo" title="Paradise now" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>How to put on the skin of a kamikaze</summary>
	<body>It is a relief that before such film that is the Palestinian issue in a somewhat linear way, positioned on one side and with the political or social issue as background, we get a work as "Paradise Now". The film of Hany Abu-Assad, offers the same way, social cracks and political notes of the Palestinian problem, but what raw material in it is human treatment (all applicable not only to that location, but the rest of the world) of the question.And it is appreciated that for many absurd controversy which has aroused in certain places (especially in the run-up to the Oscars), the film shows completely aseptic. And that is, precisely, the eldest of their ventures.Despite the fact that the protagonists agree with certain political or social positions, religion, beliefs or convictions, the direction and development not are positioned on any position in particular. They only try to deepen and immerse themselves in the head of the person who reaches such extremes, is for the reason that it is. And that is the purpose of the film: discover the reason for the actions of the kamikazes. Although it does not offer a final closed let us clear the why of this. We have to be able to get on your skin and try to understand it.Because, as much as some insist on demonstrating otherwise, there controversy or dispute the fact of wanting to understand the actions of someone, it kamikaze, rapist or child molester (e.g. the close of the also very correct "the woodsman"). Beware, this does not ever include the fact to justify them. I believe that we are mature enough to differentiate it.It is always interesting and productive to put in the shoes of someone, try to understand him and suffer their fears and feel their desires, by very atrocious to be the crime that has been committed. Logically, and as it happened, for example, in "The sinking", not everyone will be able to put in the shoes of a monster as Hitler (serve as a paradigm). Many feel nausea only think about it. And I can understand. But a person with moral concerns it will be very productive, and ultimately, and although it sounds exaggerated, empathy is based on that. In not making distinctions of any kind.It is high time that we realize that victims are not the only protagonists. The executioner, in some ways, is always a victim at the same time. Whatever its condemnation and reason. It should be digging in their past.To win as individuals in a society, we need to understand that everything has a reason. And nothing and no one can judge the life of another for free.And I repeat. Thus it would not justify (cannot be justified in any way the brutality of certain acts) nothing, but not punish, we would just the opposite effect. Correct (educate) is the more appropriate term. Ever since Cain, a punishment did improve anyone or dissuade him to commit a crime. Maybe we should put us in front of a mirror and observe. It would be interesting what would come to discover if we look at the proper depth.The truth is that the direction of Hany Abu-Assad helps a lot when dealing the film with the seriousness and objectivity that it deserves. Your camera is as sterile as possible, simply notes and still not determine or judge. While a very low budget, both the camera and the somewhat homely way of filming is evident, it is not necessary nothing more. If you know say with class and subtlety that is meant, as it is the case, there are no problems is that aspect.And interpretations are also quite successful. Without performing a job that attracts attention, Ali Suliman and, above all, a hesitant Kais Nashef does help us to put ourselves in your difficult place. And this work of containment and expression is really worthy.We can live, thanks to them, each and every one of the apparent remnants of a kamikaze, including their beliefs, their sectarian religion, family, social, political and educational environment. And we can feel very closely their fears, their wishes, their sense of guilt, his anxiety and concern, as well as doubts, their most internal conflicts, their constraints and his gruesome indecision, that it is, in essence, Genesis of the greatest terrors. And all those confronted feelings degenerate into emotional instability and lack of control of his person to avoid that their acts are, from that moment, entirely predictable. But it is something that not only them can happen to them.In short, a breath of fresh air to the vast majority of films that flooded us lately and who have no intention to be offensive, certain pamphleteering character that ends with bore the Viewer. Let us not forget that we are talking about film. And, personally, I prefer to understand it as a projection of vital feelings and spiritual concerns. Not as obvious and repetitive criticism.I'd rather live the cinema as a game in which the human mind and spirit are those who decide, and not the hands of a director that caresses the complacency and only feed the ego.The true value of the address is us are those who have the final decision in our power. He is the craftsman who produces quality Wicker, develops ideas and problems from which we are those who finished rooting our decision and our determination. That, in part, we are, also, part of his work. We are the last point in this long route of the film, which is that, really, any movie and any creator want reach.Even we ourselves can qualify us as a last bastion, so it is compression and reflection. That is, in essence, understand the cinema as art. And know that, first and foremost and in spite of this, the film exposes hard terrorism rather than none, precisely for all that I have mentioned earlier. Pulls all kinds of complex sectarian overland and fans than what they do, simply, is to generate crazy and useless injustices that lead not more than globalized fear and the desire to reach a non-existent glory.As reads the sentence of your poster: "24 hours at the head of a kamikaze". With its advantages and, obviously, its drawbacks.</body>
</review>
