<review author="Dragon negro" title="Arthur y los Minimoys" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Luc Besson can handle the action, and here proves again the film while maintaining a hectic pace without hardly rest.</summary>
	<body>Luc Besson directs this film based on his own books in what he says will be his last foray into film as director, although some rumors suggest it could return to after the cameras to direct its sequel. It tells us this film the story of Arthur, a boy who lives with his grandmother in a House away from the people whose parents have it rather abandoned and their only consolation is live fantasies thanks to the books of travel and inventions of his grandfather by Africa. But the tranquility will be threatened when she discovers that due to the debts of the grandmother to maintain the House they will be evicted within forty-eight hours. Arthur will put all his efforts in search of a treasure hidden by his grandfather, but doing so will have to travel to the tiny world of the Minimoys.La film blend live action with action in the form of drawings by computer totally coherently and perfectly complemented the one on the other. And it is precisely in is last where it generates all the more thrilling action and where Arthur will live great adventures, with an animation achieved every detail and a character design really achieved, you can see hair and freckles very well profiled in the face of the protagonists and the Princess is really beautiful, one of the most beautiful women's faces seen in animation.Luc Besson can handle the action, and here proves again the film while maintaining a hectic pace without hardly rest. At most we can blame you some slippage of script, especially that of the rope of the knife that fairly sings, but generally maintains a good level.Despite being directed to a child audience, Arthur and the Minimoys is perfectly enjoyable for all ages and is without doubt one of the film's animation of the year along with Monster House and Cars, failing even to see Happy Feet.</body>
</review>
