<review author="Dragon negro" title="La alianza del mal" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The argument does not look bad and could have worked well and even be a new lost boys, if not because the film makes water everywhere.</summary>
	<body>Go another translation of title in English too, because a time view the movie not be I where they have released such an Alliance, but well, let's get to the topic that is to comment on the film. The Covenant is the latest film from director Renny Harlin, a director who has come to make films so successful as the second part of the jungle of glass, Deep Blue Sea or the adventures of Ford Farlaine and lately seems to have lost the North with as mediocre as Driven, hunters minds films or the Exorcist: the beginning, and the latter do nothing but confirm that this guy is not that was before because it remains in its line of mediocre pulling bad.The plot of the film looks entry rather more than what we can then see, a group of four young friends who belong to families with a lineage of witchcraft and who have inherited magical powers. All goes well until they begin to happen strange things and discover that there is another boy just like them from a lost lineage and that he intends to steal their powers. This is basically the argument, that might have worked well and even be a new lost boys, if not because the film makes water everywhere.The four friends are a few chulitos and guaperas of very careful at a boarding school for people with pasta and they are dedicated to using his powers for anything less for something useful, osease cool, search match, jumping from cliffs, impress the girls and hesitation between them. The largest is which makes leading and sensible of the group, and which captures all the prominence, the other three appear rarely and only their characters are developed, is also the new and cute girl of course, he falls in love with the prota, all this with a cart of topicazos more, apart from some dialogues that directly cause embarrassment. But the best is the character that makes bad, all directly connected with him is worth. And is that it does anything that makes sense, if we think a little on the steps to get to where you want to see that they lack all logic and reason and that perfectly the writer could have sought a way more coherent and less topical portraying the antagonist and develop it.To all this nonsense, we add a final fight which found me the most ridiculous and charisma thing I've seen in a long time in the cinema with special effects used in the most clumsy and repetitive way imaginable.</body>
</review>
