<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Mentes en blanco" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pastiche sweetened halfway between the spasmodic and macabre thriller of the most bloody gore and competent narrative functionality of the film of intrigue.</summary>
	<body>Pastiche watered-down halfway between the spasmodic and macabre thriller of the most bloody gore and competent narrative film of intrigue functionality, although it comes rigged with predictable arguments, already old mounts and, above all, the ACE in the manga know that a surprising end to revive ninety minutes of visual laziness. Blank minds play this ambiguity in a remarkable way, everything must be said. It is sister with other products of a similar cut and come, as we see it, pieces of root of Saw (Oh, what school has opened this franchise) or (more distantly) usual suspects. In the Kingdom of the blind, the one-eyed man is King.There are players of worth (Kinnear, Caviezel, Stormarre) and it did not turn to a staff anonymous in other films of this nature. The script is thorough, alluring, puzzle animated conventions of the genre where premium (as said) the search for an ending which leaves us all flipados online Saw (I insist) or Seven to a well trabada events hilazón and more artisan work in purely theatrical characterization of the characters.Those of the men locked in a basement without having any pajolera idea of the how and the when sounds already known song. These times of creativity flat produce spirited clones. one accepts because, ultimately, it loves the cinema and recognizes that it is not always easy to film the silence of the Lambs (the masterpiece of the adult entertainment) or the aforementioned Seven, that to me feel me absolutely great. Both flashback and as much camera in hand produce hot flashes and dizziness. The construction of the final decoration, the Baroque puzzle show, uses a heavy process of creating parallel reality: none of these realities seduces us entirely.The final question: is it good? In its own way it is a masterpiece, but this way already has staff pinch fed up. We want quality film, but with so much and so diverse, scale that they arracimen on the products good in principle, but bored by viewed Bulletin Board. I am thinking now, leaves vu, which has the same ingredients of competent but lacking an appropriate dramatic tension film.Theatrical in abundance, surprising final, actors in racha, director of video clips (Simon Brand): unknown. And why, then I have the feeling that the film's worth and that take one a great time in the cinema?</body>
</review>
