<review author="Silvia" title="Nueve vidas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps not reach masterpiece owing to greater cohesion between the stories, but the advantage that the movie is that it makes sense that we we have a promising director when it comes to dive into the most intimate emotions of each.</summary>
	<body>Any person has a story to tell. In this film are nine stories: nine lives. In each episode, the finale is as an impact in the stomach, hit the conscience and leaves reflecting the Viewer. It is the narration, filmed in a single sequence of nine stories, nine fragments of life of nine women of ages, conditions and different personalities, but are essentially the same. Each one is a different situation, but that becomes its own emotional crossroads.Scraps of life of fifteen minutes each that make up a universal portrait of the female essence. A dive so deep in the woman's personality not could have got better that, as in this case, with close-ups that bring us closer to the characters, with a camera that accompanies and follows their movements and convert to the viewer at first-hand testimony of what is happening there. Sandra is an immigrant who spends his days locked up in prison and lives with the impotence of mired to embrace his little daughter. Diana (Robin Wright Penn), a pregnant woman who sees how his emotional stability stumbles to find with a past love. In the emotional reunion in the supermarket scene, affection seems to be reborn again between the couple, moreover, it is a feeling that not never left. Another parts shows the State of anxiety that suffers from a woman on the brink of a surgical operation, intense moment even manages to snatch a nervous smile to the Viewer. Love, pain, sex, death and loneliness, mingle in these stories being the expression of life itself. Although the set of stories is somewhat irregular, by the fact that some stories samples more developed than others, manages to keep up without just decay into the tape.With a mise en scene apparently sober but impeccable and a soft soundtrack like a caress, the director of things that say just by looking at her and son of writer Gabriel García Marquez once again as a wise connoisseur of feminine psychology confirms that has a special sensitivity to translate into images the human feeling. Perhaps not reach masterpiece owing to greater cohesion between the stories, but the advantage that the movie is that it makes sense that we we have a promising director when it comes to dive into the most intimate emotions of each.</body>
</review>
