<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Descubriendo el Cielo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film bizarre, chaotic and at times incoherent, but who nevertheless like.</summary>
	<body>Discovering the sky is a rare film. Quite rare. It is one of those that makes you constantly have the feeling that you're losing something, that there is something else in it that you are not able to see; But despite everything you like. It is somewhat similar to what years ago I happened with some X-files episodes, which I do not know anything, but I loved. I guess that it will have you had that feeling ever.It is a film that rides halfway between drama and science fiction, to grosso modo narrates as the angels of heaven needed a new advent to retrieve tables of Alliance and break the Covenant with men, in revenge for having abandoned these religion.It covers the passage of a great number of years, that since that it begins until it ends it's been about 20, and does so in a way a bit chaotic and sharp, but with some charm. It gives the feeling of lost long time in mundane scenes, while it is passed on tiptoe by others that are key to the development of the film. Also their interpreters are somewhat histriónicos, exaggerated in the fanfare and gestures, and we could even tell you that lack you verisimilitude to the characterization of the characters. But above all stands the performance of one of the greats of the screen (is my opinion, for taste colors), which is Stephen Fry, recalcitrant British ever there, multidisciplinary actor with a preference for comedy, and usually do exquisite and acid typically British humour gala that in real life. FRY is capable of making people laugh, but also of thrill, as he does at times in discovering the sky and years ago with his masterful interpretation of Oscar Wilde in Wilde, what in my opinion is the definitive interpretation of the great author, that own actor has acknowledged deep similarities, including homosexuality.But anyway, what they want to tell you; while I find more faults than virtues, to me has not disappointed, and at times I liked this movie. Though honestly, I don't know to explain to them why.</body>
</review>
