<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Blood creature" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More than worthy product, taking into account, that Yes, the limitations of any kind of the era, country and gender.</summary>
	<body>The truth is I didn't have too many references of the filipino horror film. And when I say that it did not have too many you could say almost none. I had always had the feeling that should be something akin to the New Zealander, with much viscera and offal everywhere. To satisfy final push that latent curiosity gave me see the special dedicated to him on this website.I got to do me with a copy of Blood criature, apparently and according to I have read of other members of this section, and other information that I got after devote some time to this, is who gave the kick-off.The fact that it was based on a short story by H.G. Wells was in a sense a small at least some quality assurance in the script. And the truth is that despite everything expected me a kind of grotesque then not proved to be such. Taking into account technical, economic and all limitations, Blood Criature turns out to be a pretty decent product, insofar as it considers it with "special criteria" to put it in some way. After a start that can brand intense, continuing a somewhat pesaroso development which again revitalize a quite movidito ending.The truth is that, or rather the monster causes hilarity, but as I said before, should take into account the constraints of all kinds of this production. The interpretation is almost the least, because the truth is that too much there is complexity in the characters.That Yes, as curious fact tell that I missed the introduction in which alert you that will ring a Bell before the abrupt scenes to prevent the sensitive stomach, and as I see on the criticisms of other colleagues and some websites it is a curious fact of the film. But the truth is that in the version I've seen it appears.Finally, as experience is not bad at all, but the truth is that it isn't that it is willing to delve into this genus. Although who knows, so I see two or three more and I just dazzling.</body>
</review>
