<review author="José A. Peig" title="Dentro del laberinto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are rubber puppets, but they have life, lyricism, freshness and a dimension that gives them a point more than the cliché reality. It is a full demonstration that can make poetry with a show of the Muppets.</summary>
	<body>There are films that are myths of past eras because they invoke them and we return to a State of being buried by the passage of time, but still latent. In our era, fairy tales are told in pictures. Thus we have reached the heart stories such as the Skywalker, the Goonies and the case of this Labyrinth, delicious entertainment film. In fact, it is the equivalent of Lewis Carroll (Alice in the country of wonders) films from masses. When this film came to billboards - in the eighty-six, if I am not mistaken - I would have about eight years. I left amazed cinema. It is a waste of magic and fantasy. Only films such as the adaptation of the neverending story made Petersen or return of the jedi (there, I was six years old, he won the mask of Vader.y everything else is history already) equalled her power of fascination. So, obviously, to a boy like me, belonging to the era ochentera. Today, from the prism of a different one and at more advanced ages era, do not happen to be mere films for children. However.Both films Star Wars and this production directed by Jim Henson(vaya_pérdida_prematura,_aquel_mago_de_las_marionetas) Lucasian resist the passage of time and with them I can return to the center of my innocence. And Labyrinth is not no masterpiece, but it is a marvel of design, ambience, humor, characterization of characters, music (heavenly David Bowie) and lyrical background. Not in vain, lies a love poem that floats eternally in a world governed by the Jarrett King, in love with heroin which he wanted to give the paradise of dreams for their fear and loyalty. The film is built on the myth of the labyrinth, allegory of the road to the interior of our secrets. The path of life is like a maze whose Center contains a reward. Who provides it? who will victorious in his adventure of countless dangers that leads to the city of the Goblins?. Sara retrieves his brother and found new friends. Jarret, become nocturnal bird notes distant Sara happiness through the window of your room. Jarrett returns, alone, to the Moon in search of other dreams to sell in exchange for love.Moreover, this new tale of Alice in the Wonderland country is a lesson of artisan illusionism, made with much love and vocation, demonstrating that the current infographics methods are not essential to recreate worlds fantastic and full of life. There are rubber puppets, but they have life, lyricism, freshness and a dimension that gives them a point more than the cliché reality. See Hagle or Ludo, perspire tenderness, they are endearing in their gestures. It is a full demonstration that can make poetry with a show of the Muppets.And also a demonstration that is not essential to be original to entertain. Just a product with its own personality. We have already mentioned; drink of Lewis Carroll. Also in "The wizard of Oz" and similar. But this "Labyrinth" has the personal required of a craftsman as skilled in visual and in the management of the typical profiles of a fantasy world. We remarquemos this, therefore to the nonsense of "Eragon" tale. We are not asking to "Eragon" (or any other similar products that also drink from previous and classic works) to be original, just demand a minimum of interest when it comes to revisit and/or inspired by the classics.Personality and charisma of an artist of the likes of David Bowie put the icing to a substantially child film, a joyful delight even for adults, although it has sections failed as the stupid final battle in the city of the elves, a complete anticlimax that breaks a development which, up to that point of the footage, handled, with perfect balancethe more child elements with some oniric dyes, humor, and the tension of the adventure passage, achieving a viewing stimulant for viewers of all ages. By innumerable dangers, me I have found its way to the Castle beyond the Goblin city there.</body>
</review>
