<review author="Caruco" title="Mentes en blanco" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a particularly memorable movie, but can be seen, especially by the curious surprise at the end.</summary>
	<body>Don't want to reveal too on the intricacies of "Unknown", a film that articulates its intrigue and the surprise outcome. In addition to making us wait until the last scene, almost until his last seconds, to give us other information to give a surprise turn of the screw to that seen until then.It is also the directorial debut of the Colombian Simon Brand, man hardened above all in the advertising world, in ads for Pepsi, Coca Cola or BMW; and in the music videos for singers like Enrique Iglesias, Britney Spears or Shakira. Which earned him that "Variety" magazine included as one of "40 most influential latinos in Hollywood".Although its realization is the opposite of what is espararía him, a dazzling and originalilla way to sell us the content, but also which is a sunset in grey, purely functional scene and it would seem that modest and subject to interpretations and the script, skillful, Matthew Waynee, also rookie.Making friends.The plot excuse places us in a warehouse and with five men stunned, tied or injured who have lost the memory because of an accident with chemicals deposited in the enclosure. As they recover the knowledge they should do the same with memory because they deducted that some of them are victims and the other hijackers.The grace is go making cabals on who one is, with the aggravating circumstance that nobody can trust no one: the abductees must fear for his life; and the hijackers to possible foreign aid in the form of agents of law and order.Among them was génera a logical distrust, but also the need to ally themselves to escape from this impasse, or rather, locked storage. While abroad, a couple of colleagues hijackers has been to collect the booty, followed closely by the police, as well as a woman who suffers, Eliza (Bridget Moynahan), well one of the retained is her husband.Best from home.So to expect the moment that everything come and the puzzle, with multiple tracks, some format? flash-back? (to return the memories), will acquire consistency.Freed from the nails of the passion of Christ, among its protagonists highlights Jim Caviezel, nicknamed "denim jacket" by his manner of dress, and which stands immediately in the leader of the group. Also a Greg Kinnear, who is impossible to see him as a "bad boy" and Barry Pepper, recent even his interpretración in "The three burials of MILTIADES Estrada" with Tommy Lee Jones.A part of the urgency of the characters in go regaining its identity, it is not "Unknown" is an especially memorable film. But it can be seen, especially by the curiosity of its surprise ending, but my advice is to not be be specially intrigue with icing lover, perhaps best that they see comfortably from home, when you arrive on DVD.</body>
</review>
