<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Eragon" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do not disappoint lovers of fantasy film (although it is not love her), but I must warn that you must not make the mistake of compare it with?"The Lord of the rings"</summary>
	<body>If we look at the image that fantastic and chivalric literature awarded to the imaginary dragons, perhaps, these not go well unemployed: evil, bloody, wild and lonely. Fortunately the molds can also be downed and it is precisely what did a teenager named Christopher Paolini when he published the novel Eragon that, years later, has been moved to the cinema.This is not a history of large battles (that there is any), nor of impossible love; It is simply the nice story of friendship between a farmer and a dragon. She is awesome (an exquisíta infographic work that deserves to be admired); He is a tender young which still may not be converted into an Elvish-sexual element (component which not only influences on libido but also at the box office).They emphasize its special effects (something to which the Americans we are accustomed) and a fairly consistent with the narrative music, making very complicit in it. The cast of actors that appears around the screen nothing has to envy to other types of films (John Malkovich, Jeremy Irons and Robert Carlyle). The narrative is dynamic but somewhat predictable (something which, unfortunately, happens quite often in this genre). Against him appear a little elaborate scenarios (above all, the room where he manages his Galbatorix Government: more than a real room seemed an After Hours of calle Gran Vía). Also, sometime suffers the lack of information: we do not understand why the King guard the egg Dragon if this can do so much damage, not is can destroy? We do not know. Nor is explains very well the initial battle that the authoritarian reign of evil begins. Appreciated, on the contrary, the detailed explanation on the relationship that keeps a rider with his dragon, relationship that stands out for its beauty and loyalty (some men should learn from the Dragons).In general, I think that the movie will not disappoint lovers of fantasy film (although it is not love her), but I must warn that you must not make the mistake of compare it with "The Lord of the rings", they belong to the same genre but the theme and the stroke are dististos. Moreover, it would be so stupid to expect that all novels were as "Don Quixote".</body>
</review>
