<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="El Polaquito" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A vision full of strength of the current Argentina, which invites reflection on the situation of a world in which half of the people died of hunger and the other half of obesity and heartbreaking.</summary>
	<body>I guess many of you will know that proverbial maxim which says that on many occasions, the lack of media sharpens the wits. Clear proof of this is the large number of titles that became leaders of box office and critical without having counted for its rather than strictly basic realization. And sometimes not even that. The Blair Witch Project and a long list are clear examples of this.Well something is what is happening from a few years ago in Argentine cinema. The deep economic crisis in the country has led to the appearance of films shot near "real-time", with little budget, but beautifully offset this section with scripts that exude pointedness, ingenuity and dynamism in some cases; either with distressing harshness portray the current reality of a country once rico who now suffers from years of pillaging continued by a corrupt political class like no other. The Polaquito belongs to this last class. The Polish is a child who lives in the surrounding suburbs to the central station of Buenos Aires, and earn the living singing tangos in wagons, while it suffers the oppression of a mafioso of neighborhood dedicated to exploit young people for their own benefit. His deep love for a prostitute with whom engaged in a relationship takes you to stand up to everything and decide that its future is not about doomed begging and exploitation. The film, based on real events, perfectly recreates the atmosphere of disillusionment and pessimism prevailing in some part of the current Argentine society, but simultaneously launches a message of hope for the country, a hope that necessarily passes by young people. Dantescas conditions in which they live and the lack of vital expectations of youth, before the impassivity of all is the leitmotif of the tape, made with mimbres scarce but full of strength, drive, and talent.The Polaquito is a heartbreaking cry, a call to an untenable situation that nobody does anything and condemned to ostracism and death to thousands of human beings. Now that the Argentina economy is growing at a frantic pace for three or four years, once past the doldrums, this film claimed that before the optimism of the ruling class, should bear in mind this part of society for which the only feasible objective when they get up every day, is to reach the night live.</body>
</review>
