<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Nueve reinas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An original history of scammers that combines the social denunciation with the entertainment, with a perfect Assembly between the two which makes it an important attraction for the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>Aware of that may sound repetitive to have read any other written mine on Argentine cinema, I again insist that the serious economic crisis in the country has served to spur the filmmakers, which has greatly exacerbated his wit and transmission capacity, on the basis of his argument in many cases something derived from that juncture. While at other times the issue is exposed harshly and leaving little room to smile (e.g. in El Polaquito), here is the issue with major bloating, so while frame in the dramatic genre, also has touches of comedy.Nine Queens narrates the story of two con men medium hair to them occurs a unique opportunity to sell a valuable collection of stamps to a mobster on the verge of being deported from the country. And it does so in a tone of extreme drama, using sometimes a subtle irony to glimpse the influence Spanish in the economic situation of the country. But it does without it note too, in specific details such as the fact that in many scenes showing own crisis scenarios (people agolpada against a bank intervened to try to recover their savings), appears just beside a Telefónica running a toda mecha Office. Or that the mafioso who are about to expel from the country by corrupt politicians and appropriating huge amounts of money also is, as they say, gallego.In addition to being a film denouncing the situation of the Argentina again, it is a tape that entertains, arouses curiosity by the original of the Wiles and tricks used to fleece the people, and that starts on many occasions the smile of the Viewer.Also at times resorted to symbolism, as in the scene (don't worry that what I am about to say has any relevance in the argument, it is not spoiler) that while travelling one of the protagonists in a subway car, a kid offers travelers prints in exchange for a donation, and the scammer raises the possibility of choosing between fifty pesos (about 15 euros) and a car of toy you just bought; the boy, after looking at the car, with bright eyes take the ticket: the need is higher than the whims of children of another child who has had to do more before time.But not all lights; Sometimes it gets a little predictable, and seems they wanted to give a touch of Hollywood, weighed part of this characteristic and charming Argentine pace. In any case, is a good film, which as usual, went through Spain with lower impact of the well-deserved. But that, unfortunately, is most common.</body>
</review>
