<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Arthur y los Minimoys" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Neither love nor uncomfortable the foray into the realm of digital one of the most curious filmmakers of the current scene animation.</summary>
	<body>Surprisingly, and to some extent like risk it on the European continent to titles of this draft. After the compliment we can criticize the lucrative desire which imposes on the creative of Luc Besson. Here is not only the director, so it is also logical that someone who invests money wants to retrieve it.Do judging by the employees, first quality ingredients, commercial success is assured: simple story combining adventure with a subtle idea of overcoming to the adversity story? everyday? framed in a world of fantasy that could well exist if not for the licenses that permitted the French filmmaker.He told us that love is equated to the four natural elements and pulled out the depths of Joan of arc side, but to prove it we had to endure too many minutes sitting in the armchair. Now drop the idea of a rotten creatures similar to Elves? are not talking about even the Invisibles - descoyuntan nothing makeshift dance floors where sound modern hits and confers the power of the omnipresence of an African tribe members. What mess.From a technical point of view convinced the wanderings of a real child by a fictional land although little improvised and built on too many references. Taking into account patterns and archetypes, comings and goings of Arthur worthy, throwing in lack more reckless passion and a touch of recklessness by the French filmmaker: good boy who meets a cake to resolve conflict finished without giving too many coherent explanations and girl that falls, lazarillo lucid and comic, bad very bad. Yes takes care instead of leaving the door open to future sequels? returns to his facet as a producer.This type is ready to throw hooks: nothing more bite, the networks we catch. When the film ends if wish you we too wonder: current winks, proliferation of elements who, for very natural that they seem, has an aura of unreality; the look of some of the bichejos, which reminds Mila Jojovich in the fifth element. A simple exercise of observation leads us to the hand of Luc Besson in this rural version of the tiny television creatures who are too far away to final consumers of this title: children born at the dawn of the new century.</body>
</review>
