<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Eragon" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Walk at home, so we catalogue this failed foray into the fantasy universe that seeks to follow in the footsteps of productions that ennoblecieron the gender.</summary>
	<body>In a glimpse of sincerity should indicate that his footage is not too extensive, something that eludes any desire to leave the room. It is also true that we must not refuse responsibilities leaving alone to our small accompanied by, because Yes, they become the only excuse when watching a film that reminds Dragonheart and makes great other samples of second category as dungeons &amp; dragons.Extravagant in sublime moments devoid of content but devoid of emotion, Eragon unconvincing because we have the feeling of watching something that already have told us, and, with more substance and better ways. We do not know very well what and who has done so, but a sense of déjà vu constant accompanies us in this work that is attached with pins.The filmmakers premieres, and Stefen December is, they seem to have confused great movies with stunning natural landscapes, two or three stars of name recognition and a plot which gives equal to be pointless, because it enhance already then with Visual effects, and scenes of lucha.23 years has Christopher Paolini, author of the legacy, even without completing a trilogy whose first books have reached figures millions of sales. Eragon is the introductory volume and, judging from the denouement of the film adaptation, will be the first of a series of films. Sure that the Legion of fans who have read the book will come flocking to the cinema: the first time is guaranteed but it is risky to rely on you to continue supporting a strictly commercial and dramatic bet.Do not know if the young writer outlines his characters with the same depth that the writers responsible for bringing words to images: 4 professionals have been necessary? would be - to deploy a catalogue of beings that respond to standardized patterns. The main roles are nothing more than schemes to the service of a hackneyed moralina adorned with predictable action at all times.Had not yet said: we liked the work of Peter Jackson at the head of the Lord of the rings, and it is not to compare, but how much damage has been done to those who venture into the difficult genre of fantasy.</body>
</review>
