<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Quinceañera" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After a touching and funny movie halo hides a portrait (one more, it must be said) of the Hispanic community in the illusory Californian society.</summary>
	<body>The working class, the Group of workers behind a country, has starred in some of the best dramatic romances in the history of the cinema. If we had doubt of the emotional hook that have these beings on the big screen here we have the classic love story between two young Hispanics conditioned, not by family or social conventions, but for the price of housing. Forget it, is the story.American friends really like the end happy, extrapolated in recent years to describe happy all the footage. This is the slice of life in spanglish in the dream of a future better. This escalation was a come better maintains active parents, elders of the community. On the contrary Quinceañera narrates the vicissitudes of second generation immigrants, the wishes of a teenager born in United States but anchored in marshy ground because of the inherited customs.The protagonist dreams of his coming-out, logic between the americanitas serving 15 years. The concrete fact item is the conglomeration of ideas arising from this interesting work about the clash of cultures and the necessary assimilation of uses unrelated to the life we had traditionally been. Tape makers add to the mix racial tensions and a nothing subtle critique of homophobia and religious prejudices.In line with ' Costumbrismo ' with pretensions of titles like my family, when I left cuba and goal! It suggests ways as a social portrait. As entertainment product also works. Not we left the film with heart in a fist or malaise, so it meets its main functions. Perhaps peca offer us a dulcificada image of what more or less Intuit, but this is the price of making a feature film that like everyone, most.The Sundance Festival usually every year an excellent crop of independent court and, in some form, offender in form and substance. Being sincere, all titles not them perceive the same way here in Europe. This may be the case of this film that managed to join jury and audience in the latest edition of the alternative event: real feat or new marketing strategy? I.e. pass by the known contest, and I cover of glory or what is the same, free advertising. Judge you.</body>
</review>
