<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Mia Sarah" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Seeing it have the feeling of being before a fable of another time, a quite sweetened tape which seems out of a chest that will return soon.</summary>
	<body>A newcomer in the direction can choose to risk in the staging or relax and play with a cluster of related cultural and, above all, cinema. Gustavo Ron Madrid opts for the first.His fable about love and all its stages (the first contact, seduction, delivery) manages to draw a permanent smile, but lacks strength to tear away us any other grimace. It is not surprising that recounts nor does, and that in the times, can be more than reason enough for your tape passing on tiptoe through the Billboard.The touch magical, supernatural, is not able to sustain the footage of this work for dreaming minds who feel fondness for the small details. And the Viewer to lose by other worlds instead of being attentive to the amorous entanglements between the characters of Veronica Sanchez, his first protagonist of weight, and Daniel Guzmán, in a more friendly tone and less barriobajero can fall in that? said with affection - than in previous works.Agoraphobia to love there is a step and who see the film will know why I say this. Not going here to uncover the few surprises that treasures this production filmed in Galicia - the periphery also exists, fortunately - where appears a Fernando Fernán-Gómez, who increasingly are lavished less. Ron relies on the complicit relationship established the veteran performer with the teenager Manuel Lozano, who was a child in the tongue of the butterflies. Another of the charms it Yes can reveal, resides in see in action a Phyllida Law, mother of Emma Thompson, in the epilogue to this story.Under the designs of an illustrious parallel with the name Amélie and multiple desires as to inculcate the love for the books and the desire for improvement. So are two stories intertwined, passionate stories each with drama and comedy in its fair measure and separated by comic parentheses provided by the character of Diana Palazón (Central Hospital), an actress who should have more opportunities in the cinema.</body>
</review>
