<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Lila dice" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without hand slap to?The camino de los ingleses? with which it shares many similarities but which leaves to the height of bitumen.</summary>
	<body>I decided to make this film criticism, because it is the best example I can give you to qualify, what I wanted to express when I spoke of "The way of the English".Well, Lila says is a 2004 film (released in 2005 I think) and that these days for those with TV cable, can enjoy. It is the second film of Ziad Doueiri.Se is a story of teenagers in a humble neighborhood of Marseille. Lila is a "Lolita" 16 years will be a boy named Chimo crazy that you'll end up being writer because she became the source of her inspirations: Musa.Esta his story is an adaptation for the film of the novel by the enigmatic French author Chimo.Un true delight for the senses. Well directed, correct and credible actors in their interpretations and most importantly, to represent the age interpret (are not 30 years making teenage guys). Great soundtrack, first flat primerisimos amazing, excellent script and two protagonists at the height of any Hollywood actor.Vahina Giocante masterfully plays Lila, the Muse of Chimo. This girl is a real bomb, similar to the Brook Shields beauty when he made "The Lake blue". A woman disconcerting, living, organic, credible, great (of oscar?).It is a very sexual tape, there are explicit sex everywhere, but what happens? It in a way that no attacks to the Viewer, with all the nonsense that they say during their development, at no time are profanity, pornographic but rather, erotic and sensual.This film is a slap in the face without hand "Camino de los ingleses" with which it shares many similarities but which leaves to the height of the bitumen.I invite you to reflect: compare to the former master? dancer Vahina giocante's vids with the ex - aide Maria Ruiz? Vahina if it is a muse to inspire even a frog, a beauty and an eroticism to go crazy.Compare the adaptation of both novels and as brought to the big screen.Compare the casting impeccable "Lila says" with the abrupt casting of "camino de los ingleses".And above all, treating sexual one and another movie.Do gentlemen, "Lila says"? do is a live sample of what it means to adapt a novel, well what is a good movie (better or worse directed but in any case best film), which is an inspiring love and fuck? what is a muse?To see if many learn the fuck up what is make decent movies and what are actors truth pussy! Enough of so much dandruff and throw away the budget already by itself insufficient Spanish film.</body>
</review>
