<review author="Rafa Martín" title="Candida" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fesser y Cía created a language of their own, a style that is simply unique in the world of cinema: a combination of visual extravagance which tells stories using a virtually unparalleled in the Assembly.</summary>
	<body>There is a class of films that produce me real fear. All films are trying to manipulate your emotions in a way or another, but there are some that do completely blatant way (rays, you can almost see the Director approaching with a knife): upload music, the characters cry, the boy embraces with the girl, everyone applauds bleep, spectator, you take the handkerchief and start to fill with snot, venga snot and boogers come. Included e.g. Love Actually, which she left crying, but for other reasons (basically, I felt as if he just take part in a traffic accident and I had escaped from the scene of the crime). Candida, and to start it no doubt to anyone, falls directly into this category. And I Kale movie the three minutes: I put the breastplate, I prepared to maintain an impenetrable face and even tried to force my dream mechanism, to see if it was for a couple of minutes that could be used to give me a shut-eye. I have to say that I have failed completely, my friends.For our readers abroad (any, any, I swear) that are unaware of the background of this story, saying that our protagonist, Cándida Villar, worked as a Lady of the cleaning of Guillermo and Javier Fesser, the first of which is one of the components of the radio comedians (among other things) known as foam Duo. Over time, this woman has become part of the staff of the programme making film criticism (which causes the descojone father in the public, mainly because it is unable to say a name only well and she alone is enough and enough to convert the plot of a film of Adam Sandler in a desparrame taken from the mind of David Lynch) once said: I don't care if you just return to cure genital herpes in Mozambique: has hardly been able to have worse than this lady. A drug addict son. Another son as one chota. A vástaga lost megachoni out there. He resides in a House of official protection and earn the living cleaning tour buses that teem by Madrid, discounting that cleaning of the floor of the Marquise Ms., and anything else that is out there. No matter the crooked put things, Candida always comes forward with a wisdom cachito, and another piece of tenderness of mother. It is a simple woman that works hard, who earn their bread by the sweat of their brow and who has sacrificed his entire life by his sons.Or: If you falls worse, congratulations, you're a son of a bitch.Enter wanted to embrace her.And Candida is the fundamental pillar on which structure this film, which is mostly a costumbrista painting by Madrid, which explains more or less how is the life of the good woman through isolated scenes and that gradually develops a story between the Lady and Paul, a broadcaster of television, alter ego of Fesserwhich which Uma Thurman in Beautiful Girls, will finish fixing his life and its problems of couple with his American girlfriend. Is clear that Fesser has much to tell, but neither he nor his brother had been before as concentrated on explaining a story, which greatly helps the film, most of the footage that keeps a good balance between comedy and drama, and never lose sight of the idea that is telling, that is the world of Candida, populated by which more eccentric characters (the neighbor)(, the Marquis, the goalkeeper, and the list continues until one million, more or less) and, unfortunately, more two-dimensional. The material, so good, so original, is marred occasionally by Fesser with completely unnecessary mechanisms such as this soundtrack everywhere, with cosas crammed with shoehorn (is a particular thing of mine: never put a song during the closing credits, made exception you're a Woody Allen or James Bond), because does not need it.However, what the film lost in audio wins it in video. This is the first film by Guillermo Fesser solo, but not need to be a genius to deduce that these two, as the Coens, working as one and I trill, forming the filmmaker visually more exciting in Spain (and I don't think there is many doubts on this point in question). Almodóvar gives a personal vision of the world, but Fesser y Cía created a language of their own, a style that is simply unique in the world of cinema: a combination of visual extravagance which tells stories using a virtually unparalleled in the Assembly and which are multiple tributes with wide-angle cañí Spain, the boom of the 1960s and lifelong neighborhood cinema. These guys backward-looking, but do so without anger, and when Candida is expressed in a moment in the film how nice it is Madrid, we cannot but agree. Because the film expresses alone.And given that Candida Candida plays, and that doesn't or Meryl Streep, well say that Ms. Villar nail the role itself. It wasn't very difficult at the end and all. The same desparpajo showing on the radio appears to the same extent in front of the camera. While I do not stop do not bloody grace the "candidismos", it is the way of being of this woman and their value system that me ends up winning. Failure of the movie is to be about to become a parody of chacha of cleansing, something that is about to fall in many moments, especially when the good woman confused words (and which leads to the laughter of the public, including some academic Emeritus sovereigns of the Spanish language) and Fesser is dedicated to exploit the phenomenon in every fucking line of dialogue to Candida. Works only once: at the time of the monologue (impressive: throughout the film pales in comparison) and is, in my opinion, one of the highlights of the Spanish film of this season and other many. Comes so natural and is so devastating, that Jorge Bosch, which throughout the film has been wandering with a rather poor role, descojona from within, gets to cry, becomes to laugh and finishes making the contraplanos of his life.Solving life to others.As for the rest of the actors, the truth is quite well, especially Raúl Peña (which most goes, on the other hand), in the role of son yonkarra. The case is. actually I imported an egg what should happen. What I care is how reacts Candida, the only personaje-personaje of the film, and a center of gravity in lathe which move minor roles. In any case, for me it is enough: I paid to see this good woman and the Lady meets far and the rest, well look, also. Then it all depends on how picky you are and as you have reacted to the flagrant manipulation (understood as "I'm going to grab by the neck until you cry") Fesser: If the film has not you come, the climax on the set of television you may seem completely ridiculous (if it has fact. get ready because you will cry egg and a half) and the epilogue in United States can be like the end of the Lord of the rings. In any case, repeat: let yourself go. It is a journey that is worth the trouble.</body>
</review>
