<review author="Rafa Martín" title="La alianza del mal" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I do not usually make firewood from the fallen tree (lie) and I don't like to go left (lie as a lousy bellaco) but this is too much. Jesus, what piece of shit movie.</summary>
	<body>The Geneva Convention has a new problem and is called The Covenant, is headed by Renny Harlin and hope they rented costumes anti-radiation in cinemas where release. I do not usually make firewood from the fallen tree (lie) and I don't like to go left (lie as a lousy bellaco) but this is too much. Yes, it is worse that it Alone in The Dark and Yes, Juan Manuel de Prada has another lover that bedtime. Jesus, what piece of shit movie.Perhaps it is not blamed for the director that bore the extraordinary imperial, wonderful (undisputed) maximum risk, which has counted with the budget of the part of the episode of charmed before advertising, but very badly must go you things to finish directing this pit of darkness. Disguised as a normal film, The Covenant follows the adventures of four young mages (and an egg: they are older than the initial lineup of Real Madrid, but colleagues caused a diametrical rules change so we spent the subject) who are facing a powerful malevolent force which threatens to take his powers and live like this forever. But it is unfair to thus define the plot of the film. Let's say that once explained the percale, for nothing, you again it to explain again (obviously the producers realize that the bulk of the film only covers 19 minutes and stretch). "Torture is extended to unimaginable extremes."Do you want thread of fishing? "As it takes."From the initial credit titles, where the band Tomandandy undertakes to crush us eardrums to get mashed and will continue over the footage, the first scene includes the four mamarrachos these dressed in black causing vomiting (literally) at a party of Institute (of those so cool, in the light of the fire) and making levitate a jeep to flee policethat or he bother to investigate as fuck the car chase is capable of jumping a ravine and end up falling from 30 meters behind his car patrol. Another sequence in which a car is reassembled from scratch after stamped on front against a truck hardly will thus be of concern in the Walker Texas Ranger. Anyone can point out inconsistencies and comings of pot in a movie, but The Covenant as the best truño displays with pride.The cast. Ay. This is the moment in which Harlin, breaking again with his line, it is believed Verhoeven. The four notes are outfits for Calvin Klein and, in addition, swimming champions. Unid points. Right: festival of abdominal, fights in the showers to coup towel, homoerotic, homocoche y. homomotocicleta unresolved, attraction perpetual state of fornication, girls in the film from time to time are dressed and carefully studied bodybuilders poses so that they appear spontaneous. To the Juani will seem fucking great. To my truth is that you'm me the same. He is the youngest of the problems of the film and is a damn joke.It is almost more painful to see how Harlin retains something of what it made him a director of class A in the action genre in Hollywood, as his sense of rhythm, while his newly found love of the music video is everywhere. The famed Slavic critic Rofl Merthinson stated in his "of the film, the praxis and stuff that exploit" that "If the public do not understand it, hipnotizalo", but this is concentrated Guantánamo. Please refer to the final match, where the good and the bad are thrown balls of transparent gelatin that exploit contact during 10 minutes Damn straight. There is only an audiovisual production worldwide employing this type of style. Ésta. the chavalería throwing rites.I rhubarb refer much more the rest of the plot, such as the mother of the protagonist, the ghost that appears and disappears, the historical background of the people etc, etc. If the writer of this, it is normal that I do so, too. Only one last thought to be done and refers to the horror genre, taking account of the succession in diarrhea of films that are making us go through scary movies. Why when you make a comedy of shit - see Spain - simply isn't funny and when you do a bad movie of terror touches the bottom of the barrel? Is this genus more difficult than it initially appears? Or is that we simply do not asustamos as before? And most importantly, after suffering from this scum of film: someone can provide me a sharp knife? Because my veins and death have an early appointment.</body>
</review>
