<review author="Jose Luis" title="Truman Capote" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Commissioning scene with a clinical accuracy that helps cause chills</summary>
	<body>The prestigious magazine Premiere of the United States, is by publishing the April issue, which will include a list with the 100 best performances in the history of cinema and specialists and critics conducted exhaustive research, decided to give him the number 35 post to Philip Seymour Hoffman, for his portrayal of Capote in the film of the same name. This list left out performances as Marlon Brando for the Godfather, Ingrid Bergman for Casablanca and Clark Gable for what the wind took, however Phil peaked at # 35, even over Anthony Hopkins for the silence of the lambs. Simple and cool appearance film is the work of this actor in Capote.Un of this size, but is only the necessary environment to narrate the obsession that slowly erodes the character, to take it to the limit, until that, both approaching the fire burned in the background.The action takes place in a small and quiet village of Kansas, where occurs the murder of an entire family, Truman Capote, author and journalist, read the news in a newspaper and immediately moved to the scene to make an article for the journal The New Yorker, little by little, will get to know its inhabitants, the people involved and witnesses, even to the murderers that starts a dangerous relationship of friendship.Truman never imagined that his stay would continue and that the article would become book, a book which cost him 5 years of work, a book that changed forever the way of telling stories and that today is a book bound for any library that you want to give to respect. So we disagree to biopic ordinary, not tells the life of Truman Capote, from his birth until his death, only tells this period of his life, in which this immersed in the creation of what would become his masterpiece, is the story of the creative process of his novel, in cold blood, a painful process that stretched for more than 5 years. And although several dialogues through give us a perspective of childhood and life of the eccentric writer, in reality the central theme remains her obsession and passion for the events and his book, passion that can be clearly behind the eyes of Hoffman, from the discovery of the facts, until suffering who lives to put an end to the book.Everything else that is to the rededor of the protagonist, seems only essential items so that Phil do his job, the Mise en scène with clinical accuracy helps to cause chills and follow almost the same Methodism to Capote scene by scene. Without doubt, a great job, that will be long remembered. Today I begin to read in cold blood by Truman Capote.</body>
</review>
