<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you uploaded have stairs to the Gallop with the hammering on the head of tanan, soundtrack tananan, will enjoy as marranos in a puddle. And if not, you will have a sports drama of those who makes the female sector odie the male sector. Stallone has certainly managed to return to excite me.</summary>
	<body>Look at that when I read that Stallone was going to make the sixth installment of the most famed and oscarizado title I started to tremble. After having enjoyed with the first, I saw with total amazement as he beat one of his creations, to do shit like that in which fights with Russian. Too patetisto for this actor. But well, as one is more innocent than a botijo, him I gave this opportunity of which expected with nostalgia that the course be straighten. And hey, that he straighten and long.The film is about a former heavyweight champion retired many years ago, who now runs an Italian restaurant. As all good champion, lives anchored in the past, recalling every moment and every person who listens to him, as it was his life when it was the largest. Although this does not hide if not quite lost life, with a dead of cancer woman and a son that not ve, and him living what was, what is not. And in these, an absurd idea emerges a glimmer of hope, a way to show himself that is still alive.Well, well, I have to admit I'm writing with the stiff penis as a mast of a sailing Brig, so it may be that it split the keyboard of a pollazo of a time to another (is that so much previous poetry could make you cambiaseis channel). The movie I loved, and I say that seriously. For starters, the pace is slow and weary, as the life of the protagonist, which turns off someone who was everything and life is consumed in the memory. Continuous memories of the past make that, the nostalgic, remember the original with the hairs on tip. And give a meaning to the film that without them is not well understand. Also has flaws and things that no one believes, but does and that nose care?In short, if you uploaded have stairs to the Gallop with the hammering on the head of tanan, soundtrack tananan, will enjoy as marranos in a puddle. And if not, you will have a sports drama of those who makes the female sector odie the male sector. Stallone has certainly managed to return to excite me.</body>
</review>
