<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La alianza del mal" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Peliculilla of action and half afraid, correct and good special effects which can be seen quite well. Too bad actors past age, that things could have been much better. Hey, and it is well small.</summary>
	<body>In my eternal fight against the trailers of the films, I must say that this called me attention to many things. To start one blowing him raises the skirt to a mocica that spends less on panties that I in quiff. Useasé, sex which always like. Then special effects cool car stamping against a truck. Okay, all right. So with these premises, I started to see it, come on, with a bad omen that things would be bad. And no, not what it seemed.The film's four kids under the age of dad (of those who have pipes eggs hairs but trying to convince us that are less) that descend from four of the five families of children of Ipswich. Apparently at the age of thirteen are powers of these malignant, but upon reaching the eighteen that becomes the repanocha and they are nearly invincible. In what they expect to arrive that happy moment, they begin to go unexplained things in the village, so suspect they themselves.In itself, what is the movie I entertained enough, passing a good time. It has enough special effects, without exceeding useless, with a script allowing to follow. The actors do not too bad, especially for what I expect of a simple viewing of the poster. In the plain negative, a few things. On the one hand that have already mentioned your age, given that these have seventeen years in each leg, and this kills me with potatoes. And on the other hand that have taken four effeminate cachitas that are far much of what we expect as the Alliance of evil. No, evil seems like more "first and hairy", right?In short, peliculilla of action and half afraid, correct and good special effects which can be seen quite well. Too bad actors past age, that things could have been much better. Hey, and it is well small.</body>
</review>
