<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Happy feet" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great tape animation with ecological message included and some impressive musical numbers. No doubt, we have the best film of animation of the year.</summary>
	<body>After seeing Al Gore defending the environment, one remains somewhat restless to know what is happening exactly in our world. I at least felt this feeling of concern, so I was like "amazed" before this smash we cause humans with Happy Feet, though in a more lively manner (sorry for double fun so little here, but is that not were I go nothing more). George Miller, director of several films failure (for me, at least), as the oil of life or Babe, a brave pig, invites us to this wonderful animated film with a moral message that is more than clear. This time they are not little pigs they appear penguins, while also leaving other animals of the glacial area such as Antarctica. One could say that Happy Feet is a mixture of the story of the ugly duckling and the film Free Willy that precisely displays topics as interesting as the rejection to be different and ecology. The film, in short, tells the story of a penguin who was born different, without knowing sing and who later reject it for this same problem. During the journey in search of something, better find other penguins that make you know that he is better than you think and it is worth follow and stop band to anyone that does not accept it as it is. The protagonist, rather than be able to sing her has to dance, which is not well seen in the world of penguins. So after rejection and the trip again in search of his beloved Gloria and seeking their happiness. From here it is when things start to get complicated and everything is changing until you reach a limit in which the protagonists see as they are human (for them, alien). Besides, the film features several tremendously entertaining musical numbers, of which one puts you goose bumps. Dances, most of them with tap dance, have a delicious pace and are not (most of them) heavy. For my the best of them is the final, although on playback (who has seen already I mean) is also excellent. So Happy Feet could be also called "ecological musical". But on the other hand, the film the animation of the film is also incredible, by what does that even you feel more comfortable seeing it (attention to the sequence where the ice is breaking and the pieces are chasing penguins). Although the script, that is to say, it is not no wonder, since half of the film presents a more or less significant drop that stops the incredible pace that had by then. Although then recovers it in a special way, with a magnificent dance as a whole (of all the penguins). So if we destacáramos something, it would be his incredible animation and not the script itself. In short, Happy Feet is a great tape of animation with ecological message included and some impressive musical numbers. No doubt, we have the best film of animation of the year.</body>
</review>
