<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="The Queen" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Delicious satire full of feelings but nothing tear (in reverse, totally perverse), with a performance that deserves more than an Oscar: of the more than Queen Helen Mirren. Essential.</summary>
	<body>Stephen Frears is a director that I admire. Either by their refined and at the same time critical talent or your exquisite tastes when it comes to choose and tell the stories. After giving us splendid films as dangerous liaisons, Irish coffee, or the latest hidden business, the director of English origin debuts this year The Queen. This intelligent story has the terrible political events that occurred after the death of Princess Diana, located in talks between Queen Elizabeth and Prime Minister Tony Blair, for carrying out a stability both political and social, that at that time the population was amazed in the absence of the Queen (he did not, nor gave any message until the efforts of Blair made her showing in public).The film is not counted or in documentary way or as a biography, but it is narrated, precisely, in a manner as if it were a normal story, film, where the facts go on and the characters are transforming. Although, as always, Frears addresses a drama post-Columbian of exquisite taste and introduces us to the feelings (if it is that you any) of the British Royal family. But what stands out mainly here is the performance of that Queen named Helen Mirren (COPPA Volpi for the best actress 2006 in Venice). Its prodigious depiction of Queen Elizabeth is moving, satirical, brilliant tremndamente and gives a very clear idea of how is in fact Queen Elizabeth: a cold and distant woman who can not show their feelings. In a key moment in the film, she tells Blair that that is how they taught him to be, so clearer still leaves us with the idea of how it really is the Queen of England. Michael Sheen (seen in Underworld and soon in blood diamond) correctly portraying Tony Blair, character which Frears takes to criticise their political interests. In my opinion, knowing that the director is not just a right-wing person, believe that this criticism to the Prime Minister, which is not precisely right-wing, is unrecognizable participation for the politician in the war of Iraq. So The Queen experienced personalities with social and political interests are not a sign of openness or good morals. On the other hand, say that the screenplay by Peter Morgan is a real Marvel structured as a screenplay and not a documentary or biography, although it is interspersed with real images that appeared on television during the events. This masterful proposed by the team of the film admire her for various reasons, but above all for the wisdom and courage to show one of the most powerful monarchies in Europe and one of the world's richest women. So in short, The Queen is a delicious full of feelings satire but nothing tear (in reverse, totally perverse), with a performance that deserves more than an Oscar: of the more than Queen Helen Mirren. Essential.</body>
</review>
