<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A masterpiece full of shocking sequences (I forgot to mention the explosion of the principle) and interpretations that rub or reach perfection. Alfonso, we thank you for giving us such wonderful.</summary>
	<body>There are times that a story can seem so real that it seems that you're experiencing the same moments that the protagonists. This is the case of children of men, a futuristic tape that shows how, in the year 2027, is born, after 18 years, the first child. It is clear that is a masterful film, full of absolutely stunning planos-secuencia (the picture is carried out, nothing more and nothing less than by Emanuel Lubezki), brilliant performances and a flawless script (based on the novel by P.D.James). Are you has of mention to Alfonso Cuarón for having given this cinematic gem.The argument base is simply brutal. Not only the base, not, but all together. The argument of children of men is, symbolically, a trip to hope. And it is that the film is told as a journey, so it makes, not only more beautiful, but also more interesting it. In reality, each one's life is a journey, and this I think is what you want us to count Cuarón. in this case, the journey begins with a series of actors really disconcerting: Clive Owen (the protagonist of the function, as well as show us that you know walk with sandals, showing its most dramatic and human facet), Julianne Moore (who did not get too)(, but you get completely into his character, thanks to his great performance), Michael Caine (what about this wonderful actor who here plays a hippie who will be a great help for the protagonist), Chiwetel Ejoifor, Pam Ferris (the evil Director of the school of Matilda) and the unknown but brilliant in his role, Clare-Hope Ashitey (his middle name is done on purpose?). With this cast, it is normal that realism is even greater, since actors give us the best of themselves.The film has many really memorable sequences. One of them, more than a sequence is a chapter, is that in which Owen, Ashitey and Ferris infiltrate in the field of refugee immigrants be able to access the boat that will take them to the human project. Another, no doubt, is the getaway car that does not boot. It is also necessary to mention such as dense dialogues between Owen Moore and Caine. And finally, the splendid end. Absolutely incredible.Cuarón speaks of humanity. Speaks of hope, of pain, of children, of pessimism, an apocalyptic future of a terrorized society, of political forces. This is one of those movies that have more or less everything. There are directors who know how to mix so many items at the same time (such as Cuarón), there are others that do not. Mexican director manages to create a totally overwhelming human speech. I would say that with few more, knows to show images of human philosophy. Children of men each actor plays, not only its role, but a symbolism. Note: Owen represents the company; The past Moore; Caine philosophy; and hope Ashitey.One of the best moments, as I have said before, the film is that in which Jasper (Caine) explains to Theo (Owen) the reason for the disappearance of children and the theory that the human project exists. The phrases that Jasper said have everything.In short, a masterpiece full of shocking sequences (I forgot to mention the explosion of the principle) and interpretations that rub or reach perfection. Alfonso, we thank you for giving us such wonderful.</body>
</review>
