<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Infiltrados" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A master piece (how van already?) that will certainly remain forever as a classic, and also the best film by Martin Scorsese (do I've been?).</summary>
	<body>When one is born to one thing, nothing can change you. Scorsese is back!, aviators, gangs and biopics. He has returned to what it gives better, mafia movies. And he is the director of one of ours was born to be director of film noir. His new work, the departed (The departed, or the dead, unpublished, but much more accurate title), it is an absolute example of film talent and Supreme intelligence. You will perhaps seem that I'm going through and that this, by many movie of Scorsese, no longer a tape of cops and gangsters. Because you are wrong: the departed exceeds the quality of many films of its genre. Why: Scorsese. The film could be termed as a return home. The truth is that I can not express all their virtues in a single sentence: his excellent script leaves you with your mouth open every minute that passes. The pace of the film is thrilling, because that keeps the viewer stuck in seat minute by minute (despite the film lasts two and a half hours!). Its cast is defined with one word: spectacular. And what can I say more? Ah, Yes!: Scorsese, are a true genius. Who would say that the departed is a remake? Because the truth is Yes, although more that a remake is an inspiration (based on the acclaimed trilogy hongkonesa Internal Affairs). I must admit that lately I like less remakes, but of course, there are exceptions, and the tape in question is one of them. Charge of the script is William Monahan, considerably unknown writer, and here, does a masterful job. The fact is that this inspiration has become a real paranoia scorseniana (or as it is called), and to end soon, say that it is a single piece, without a single bug that pretends to be, and get to be so, a work master. Another strong point of the film is its excellent cast. It shine three, or perhaps more, generations of actors. For a band, we have the great Leonardo DiCaprio, who plays his third collaboration with Scorsese after the normalillas Gangs of New York and the Aviator. The American actor, of, more or less, second generation confronts Matt Damon, who also played one of the best roles of his career, making evil mafia infiltrated the police, and finally, within the trio, protagonist, Jack Nicholson, rather than portraying someone in particular, plays himself (excellent as always, of course).  The rest of the cast is completed by Mark Wahlberg, the real discovery of the film, with a masterly played role; Martin Sheen, great actor, already veteran, which plays a role that I like very well; Alec Baldwin, an actor who never me has fallen too well, but here makes it Pearl; and finally, the only woman in the team, Vera Farmiga, a great actress that makes real "marbling" (in the other direction). And finally, say that with each actor you feel very, but very identified (look at the anguish of DiCaprio, the apparent naivety of Damon or frivolous and immoral personality of Nicholson). Scorsese has been surrounded by a few real stars.In short, a master piece (how many go, already, this month, right?) that no doubt will remain forever as a classic, and also the best film by Martin Scorsese (do I've been?).</body>
</review>
