<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film wonder can be, without doubt, or perhaps with Cuarón and Scorsese, one of the best films of the year. Do not hesitate to see it, maravillará them.</summary>
	<body>Just in the last year saw the first film of the, by then unknown, Mexican director Guillermo del Toro. Cronos was entitled, and was directed by the great actor Frederico Luppi. A film was beautiful, very poetic, and at the same time tragic and unpleasant. After several failures (all of them in Hollywood), the director signed his best film, El laberinto del Fauno, which describe her more or less as the previous.The tape blends perfectly the reality and fantasy. And is that it is situated in the Spanish war post, focusing on the life of Ofelia, a young girl whose mother is pregnant with Captain Vidal, his stepfather. When Carmen, the mother, being about to have the child, decides to go with her daughter to the village where her husband, so that your future child is born with it. Once there, in the middle of the guerrillas among the vestiges of Republican resistance and army captain, will create a nasty, cold and tense atmosphere for Ophelia. And one day, looking for the forest, discovers a labyrinth inhabited by a Faun who reveals a secret: she is actually a Princess, last of his lineage, which yours have long waiting. In order to return to the Magic Kingdom, the girl must face three tests will be gradually overcome. But the evidence will not be so easy for Ophelia, as it will not only have to use his intelligence (and the help of the book given to him by del fauno), but will also have to sacrifice their lives. Meanwhile, at the mill where Vidal has located its center of operations will occur parallel stories of Ophelia, as Mercedes, the housekeeper of the captain, that apparently meets everything that he sends.El laberinto del fauno is not (as you say) the Alice of Wonderland in Spanish, but a totally symbolic and poetic tale with real scenes of terror. What Guillermo del Toro wants to tell us, and here's the message of the film is as follows: reality is imposed before the fiction. It is a moral, if so you could say, terrible, but incredibly original if you know treat well. And here's the Bull is exceeded, in creativity. Each sequence has a meaning, real or imaginary, each has its beginning and its end, each scene shows his side more dark and bright at the same time. To represent this parallel (the fiction and reality), and placing us in the post war Spanish, excellent director of Photography Guillermo Navarro has opted to add dark shades and gray to the scenes where it appears the real world and the fact that the imaginary are really distressing and not very pleasant, leaving no band has added more picturesque in these colors. Attentive to the banquet scene, because there, all the colors are very own Mexicans (red, Orange, blue and yellow). And also look at the shades gives them night and day. In the first, are all more blue and orange, and in the second, green and grey. But first and foremost, it is a film overly (while not bad) dark. We, like all of the director. The film is sensitive and at the same time difficult, issues such as post war, death, the satisfaction of one's own, the imagination of a young girl and evil itself. And it is that few Directors are as William, and thus have their own style to have these issues. It is really difficult to play so many at the same time and that is you a tape like this, perfect, balanced, with sense. For their high quality, hope to win the Oscar to which chooses (best film estrangera). Altogether, the laberinto del fauno is unforgettable, either by his overflowing creativity and imagination by his talented and impeccable management. The incredible cast, does not include two or three, if not all. Both Sergi López (Vidal), the best role of her career, full of evil; Maribel Verdú, an actress that I never liked so far, shows, apart from having style acting, you do great (tuned to the forest scene); Doug Jones, playing one of the most difficult film roles masterfully, the Faun; Ariadna Gil, which we barely see it little (but more than Frederico Luppi, which appears exactly 5 seconds), but we enjoy her beautiful voice; Alex Angulo, that great actor that has a face of doctor; Roger Casamajor, as the brother of Mercedes (Verdú), in a wonderful role; and finally, the rookie (in starring roles) Ivana Baquero, a real prodigy girl that would give the same Goya. In short, as you can see, del Toro is has surrounded by the very best of the Spanish interpretation.Finally say that this wonderful film may be, without a doubt, or perhaps with Cuarón and Scorsese, one of the best films of the year. Do not hesitate to see it, maravillará them.</body>
</review>
