<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="World Trade Center" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>World Trade Center is a failed film that could have been a great representation of the courage and bravery that took several policemen.</summary>
	<body>You can perform a tear film, but however be minimally interesting, exciting face to the public or with pace. It appears that someone does not know to do. He is Oliver Stone, a director who has done a little of everything: from intersantísimos political and war films (Platoon, Nixon, JFK, Commander), films very, very controversial ex officio assassins (any given Sunday) until real shit (Alexander the great, born on the fourth of July). His last and expected work, so far, is nothing more and nothing less than a film dealing with a subject as controversial as September 11. But the trouble is that not treated it as Paul Greengrass in his wonderful United 93, not. He manipulates the feelings, if it reaches them playing, and turns what might have been "a story of courage and survival" in a seedy, corny, crappy with all topics of the American superproudcciones and a really pathetic end. And worst of all is that everything is based on real events, to the smallest detail, which is why Mr Stone can be embarrassed even more. World Trade Center, as well as called and I suppose you know, tells the story of two policemen who were trapped for hours (we also suffer and we slept with them) by pure luck, could be rescued and return with their families. Anyway, the topic was interesting, but I think it would have been more treat the 11-S in general, without focusing only on two lucky men. Well, first of all, this is my opinion, and I think that if the topic had treated well, it could have been just as interesting. The problem is that there has been as it should.Although everything has to say, and that is the first hour of footage incredibly master, which shows the ignorance of the people, the tranquility of the city prior to the attack (very well achieved with that shadow of a plane and an image of the towers from below) and at the same time nervousness created to crash an aircraft against the first tower. All this is perfect, also including the relaxed and normal lives of the two policemen protagonists, both with their wives and children happy (well, Cage isn't very well with his wife, something which is then arranged, how not). Now, once begin to collapse both towers, the film also collapses. I think that even when they prepare with the dresses with oxygen and lower the lift, the pace of the film begins already to wane. Both the script, the pace and up photography go after this collapse. Do perhaps Mr Stone not know a film to balance? Well apparently not, since that is a totally unbalanced film. It has a dash of more topical and without intensity. I dare say that even in the more dramatic scenes and more tragic not puts you goose bumps or you emotions (which it did happened with United 93). World Trade Center, in addition to being a long suckling pig, has several really pathetic failures. One of them is this mania that has the director of coloring and put (very common one in cheap telefilms) brightness in the flashbacks. Even in the homemade scenes, where women are all day moving restless from one side to another, contrasting and are coloured in a manner which seem recorded with a digital camera of high definition. Besides, who demons to makeup to Maria Bello? It seems more an exhausted mother of five, a wax Doll or a model. Another huge, incredibly pathetic failure is the appearance of Jesus Christ. Who, tell me, who demons come you to add a sequence very, very badly recorded a type dressed up as Jesus with a bottle of water the hand? By very symbolic that it is, is really unnecessary. When I saw her I thought that they were wrong tape or something similar. And you may not believe that then Mr Stone rectified, no, the image appears twice. On the other hand, the home scenes are nothing credible. Especially those of Maria Bello. How can so false as good actress you be? By God, who is does this woman hardly cried and consoled his son that her husband would return to take you to a game of baseball or American football? Well, perhaps it's true, surely it is, but do not think it appropriate to add it.Anyway, that World Trade Center is a failed movie that could have been a great representation of the courage and bravery that took several policemen. You do not sleep, you sleep not tells Michael Peña Nicolas Cage after several hours buried. I think this tells to the public, not to his partner.</body>
</review>
