<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Nueve vidas" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A masterly film which certainly will stay in my memory for many years, by its originality.</summary>
	<body>Did someone know that Gabriel García Márquez had a son? Because I do not. It's Rodrigo Garcia, director and writer of the very well received critically things that say just by looking at her and nine lives. The first the not got to see, although I spoke very well of it, and today, luckily, have seen the second, in my opinion, is one of the best films I've seen this year. Not only found me master for his script, but also for his peculiar style. By the director's own taste, each chapter is shot in a plano-secuencia, so it not only becomes more credible, but far more interesting and intriguing. Perhaps not all the stories are just as good, but what is clear is that with none of them lose interest. The second aspect after the hyphen would appoint would be spectacular cast where the majority are actresses. And is that each one of them (and them) gets both in her role that you sometimes really seems to be a home video (with very good quality, by the way). This cast is composed of Kathy Baker, Amy Brenneman, Elpidia Carrillo, Glenn Close, Stephen Dillane, Dakota Fanning, William Fichtner, Lisa Gay Hamilton, Holly Hunter, Jason Isaacs, Joe Mantegna, Molly Parker, Sissy Spacek, Robin Wright Penn. Impressed, huh?Each story is full of sensitivity, realism, drama and melancolismo. Not all, but many of them are interwoven with small characters. Well, one could decri what Rodrigo García wants is that you realize that behind every small lives of a character, by very secondary to it, there are a lot of problems, not only family, also personal, and in general, very complicated. He is not a sentimentaloide and tear film (wait for my criticism of Word Trade Center). No, this is a film lena's feelings, Yes, but real. I like both his rhythm as its intrigue. As I said before, each chapter is shot in an only plano-secuencia, which is why, as I have also mentioned, the interest and intrigue are more intense. Each of them is perfectly coordinated and structured. One can never tell what will happen within a minute (each chapter takes approximately 12 mintuos). In some of them, even the mystery cause real confusion (look carefully at last, played by splendid Glenn Close and Dakotta Fanning). Perhaps, in my opinion, the worst are the first and that of Kathy Baker and Joe Mantegna, by his lack of interest on the one hand and on the other hand, for not having a final as interesting as all the others. Although I'm not saying they are bad, simply, they are correct. Others, on the other hand, master. Under this heading, I would highlight the work of photography, which must have been incredibly difficult and laborious. For example, in the chapter on the daughter overwhelmed by his parents (a few superb Sissy Spacek and Ian McShane), photography is moved and the atmosphere very oppressive (tuned this corridor which is both repeated). One of them, also excellently coseguido level photographic is Holly Hunter. Really do not know how is them apañará the director to follow them without cutting the sequence and without that being the micros or anything. And the protagonists are to go up in a tiny elevator, where can barely fit more than five persons. In short, a masterly film which certainly will stay in my memory for many years, by its originality. Hopefully, Rodrigo García roll with more frecuéncia and touch other issues than women, not because they are not interesting, but because already it has deepened them so much that I doubt that he can tell us more than what has told us, or all. How difficult must be tell life learns in nine chapters, not?</body>
</review>
