<review author="Iñigo" title="No matarás" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What murder is more cruel? The individual or social?</summary>
	<body>Unpublished so far in Spain, "No Matarás" is one of the Summit of the Filmography of Kieslowski, both from a qualitative point of view and for being the film which raised the recognition of the director Polish, very limited until the explosion of his "Decalogue". On the occasion of the tenth anniversary of his death (Krzysztof Kieslowski died on 13 March 1996, at 54 years of age, because of multiple heart attacks, which already suffered from long ago), Wanda vision decided to pay homage to the genius through projection and revival, 10 of March, his visceral and sublime masterpiece. Kieslowski, rather than leave us a message ambiguous, as often do so regularly, here tells a crude and direct allegation against the murder. That Yes, contains numerous symbols and metaphorical moments that bind with the rest of the "Decalogue" and his filmography, which not everyone will succeed in capturing. And these intelligent winks are that bring the true magic and worth to the film. Flashes of true genius, knowledgeable about film based on a visual narrative language reaching a metaphysical level. As I said, Kieslowski here offers us his vision about the murder, rejecting it entirely. But not only speaks of the murder from the point of view of the individual, also speaks to us of the moral and physical murder of society and politics. For Kieslowski, life is something that no one has right to snatch. and when I said no one it was, of course, no one. No institution, no complex, any such. Here not only makes ridiculous policy Poland and his death sentence, also left in evidence to the society, to that world that has spawned violence and therefore only gets the same response. But that same society, we, we created the monster of aggressiveness, not known to solve a problem that escapes from the hands. And logically, the easiest way is to kill it. Why be upset? About always the case throughout history: those that have created the monster are unable to control it. To solve the problem, the best way is to put an end to it, strike it. When something disappears, logically, it already does not create problems. But that is not a morally acceptable position. If something you create conflict, what are we doing? We eliminate or put on our part that everything be fixed?"No Matarás" not it asks whether the accused is guilty or not, that in Kieslowski is something quite secondary. What really is questioned is whether someone has the right to decide on the fate of another someone. Why the figure of the "judge" appears frequently in films of Polish director. For Kieslowski, punishment must be carried out so that the accused aware and can be recovered, are you the chance of cure in a society which should be the true defendant. If we impose a punishment by way of revenge, the only thing we get is generate more hatred, throwing us against our main ideology, contradicting ourselves. As the Polish director: "never, since Cain, a punishment did improve anyone or dissuade him to commit a crime". It seems more difficult today, is to give aid to who really needs it. Therefore the simplest way, which suggests that our surroundings, our society, has cracks on all sides are used. Everything has become dangerously inhuman and automated. If the murder who commits Jacek is repulsive, it is also the murder being committed to executing the sentence of the offender (precisely, Kieslowski, to show the brutality, resorts to filming uncut and without spare on details of both crimes, which it is not for nothing usual therein.) (and it does as we reflect, that we realise that an act is so disgusting and dehumanised as the other). No one can decide on the life of anyone, whatever the situation, person or institution. Life is not something with which you can play two cards. As well, and each time is more, creating a virtually unrecoverable society, where the damage is not only made, but it has reached such a level that the murderers and criminals are very difficult to re-educate, due to a succession of laws that did not watch the person inside, you look only at the fact happened, unceremoniously. Many aseverarán that try to offer help sometimes is impossible, many people fails to choose their choices, which are not linked to personality problems, closer to an incorrigible psyche. and that might be an attempt to, occasionally, too naive. In current times, in part, yes it may be true. But the problem comes from much earlier. At any given time not been given the opportunity to fix it, they have not had neither support nor understanding. And gets to a point where by loneliness and lack of sincere help, arrive to lose his head in an uncontrollable manner. But is more than shown (in a very high percentage) this kind of performances (which, of course, become unpredictable once uncontrolled) have an emotional and purely personal basis. Therefore, if things are as they should be, and at the time, could avoid evil so accomplished and propagated as the aggressiveness or the (a good hours sleeves green), so criticized today, penalty of death. And that is what is questioned Piotr, newly licensed attorney who will take the case of Jacek. If, while he was in the cafeteria, in the moment in which Jacek is tied the rope to the hand, had tried to persuade not to do. What would have happened?The lives of the three characters crossing isn't free, that you can see its volitional decisions and chance are interwoven so coming that at the end they end up together. They are close, but they are not looking. they are simply one soul in the world, with no one who can listen to their prayers. Thus, the time in which Jacek is already absolutely uncontrolled comes. Even the character of Barcis (essential symbol throughout the "Decalogue", as it will be the old woman of the container in "The double life of Veronica" and "Three colors"), which crosses the road while working on a play and forced the taxi to stop, manages to stop with its supplicatory look (in an existential moment that close to perfection)(, and may feel in the meat of the Viewer to shake) to the already lost Jacek. He even wants to do so (as you can see, becomes it much worse than the victim at the time of committing brutal crime), but is devoted to a situation with no possible return. For this reason, from a start in the film, we see a Jacek walk alone, with a vacuum existential rather than evident in their walk and their actions, without knowing what to do with his life, and devoid of sense. We see a protagonist caught up by his past, who feel unhappy and guilty for the death of his sister. It has absolutely lost the sense of his life, which is why their subsequent reactions will be entirely illogical and dangerous. Only notes a little light in their existence, which is still able to smile (the only smile that we see Jacek's in the entirety of the footage is when he plays in the cafeteria with a few girls, in a scene full of emotion and sincerity): want to "return" to life to his beloved sister. But hatred towards his own person just destroying it all, and is forced to download it against someone. And for simple reasons of gaming (is not a choice at all) will be the taxi driver. Kieslowski, in this sense, not put on the side of evil. What it does is demonstrate that in our society (and increasingly), is not understanding the "villain" in turn. The simplest is put against him and get rid of him. Polish director we were invited to reflect on the why of such acts, to offer forgiveness, aid and re-education, in a world that has come to a point of absolute, but logical slippage by how events were happening in a society increasingly intolerant and dehumanized. As exquisite metaphor for this, we have the old woman of the pigeons, or your own driver. But most are those people who roam the world without looking to its around, without disturbing more than by his own ego. Thus, in the technical section of the film, we have several very significant details. It is not nothing free, isn't Gallery, it is no pretentiousness, but it requires the use of intelligence by the Viewer. For the majority of the footage, predominates a sepia tone light full of expressiveness, especially in the scenes of foreign (while it is not as sharp or as predominant as in "The double life of Veronica"), in which we can see close-ups of Jacek, trying to reach his soul, to understand the reasons for their actions, and can also glimpse a city, an environment completely rotten, obscured to the maximum of the picture. trying to reflect the more than obvious State of society and its people. One photography exceptional, on the other hand, it tries to focus on numerous objects filled with a very complex symbolic, since the "foreboding" cat of the beginning to the strings, eyes, gaps and silences. Therefore, Jacek, which has only had the love and understanding of two people in their lives, is lost and without direction in the middle of that nothing which is society. These two people would be the (now deceased) sister and lawyer Piotr (remember that, carcelera conversation, Jacek stated you he called him by his name, which really was interested in him), which from the outset wondered about the sense of morality in their work, about the meaning of life and its obligations as a human being. Many will tell you that the case was lost, that it was totally impossible to save him for any lawyer, that his destiny was written. But he knows that if that has become so it is due to a few errors that have not been resolved, human points out that not has attracted attention. A person (whatever that is), and, ultimately, always must be heard and cared for. And that is the greatest error of a policy and a society totally rotten, dehumanised and quite egomaniacal. Thus, Piotr cannot avoid being sunk. and even guilty. We will not see, but the life of Pyotr won't be the same at all. And Jacek, that after his performance will feel even more lost, what will be asked what he has done, how has reached this limit. And the answer is very clear. They have pushed you the circumstances, circumstances created by the same company, the sole culprit (if any). And that society, which has generated these assassins will be the same that want to solve your problem (remember that they have created) fast-track. Sometimes, we even see that Jacek or any other offender, really are not far so anyone else who walks around the world. By pure chance, come to the point of crime, but. and if Jacek had not drunk the day of the death of his sister? The taxi driver would have not died, he would continue with her normal life. and nothing would be the same. By a single decision (which sometimes lasts no more than a second) completely changes the lives of several people. And if the taxi driver had picked up the drunks rather than go in a bad way? I could not pick up Jacek. and the rest I think we would already. A small decision changes the lives of a complete environment. so do not think that anyone is different from anyone. There are occasions where there are to look at the circumstances, not to the facts. It's really incredible to how a volitional decision, a performance not always marked by chance, we can lead to the most serious of the underworld, to the continuing loss of freedom, even though we are not always aware of this. Freedom, once again, not only is called into question, for Kieslowski drawn by the society freedom is not more than a lie. And in the end, we will not find justification for our actions, as it happens to Jacek. We will suffer the intolerance of our environment, we will walk the streets alone, we drive the taxi without knowing where we go (the taxi driver is another in the world, with the same loss of love and understanding than the rest, and Jacek therefore acts in a way so despicable). In the end, we will become victims of our society. Surrounded by rot which, little by little, loses the sense of existence and that, without doubt, is becoming a problem without a solution. Do not look at our spirit is something that is killing us. Thus, there are no murders that can solve, everything is going to lead to a succession of acts without justification. because our life nor has it. The silence over the footage, the lack of communication that has come to suffer Jacek, everything is created in a way that is inviting us to reflect. Kieslowski, as I said, does not justify anything, evil or good, it is simply trying to delve into the human spirit, seek its meaning and make us understand that the values of life increasingly sink more, and that, despite a naivety and a desire for healing, everything is becoming a lot of shit. What society really deserves. What we have broken down, are not willing to fix it. And thus, the snake biting its tail over and over again. until that, finally, will not be tail biting. Kieslowski, thus may to seek something very difficult (to not impossible), but I think that search within ourselves, to understand and improve, is something to which everyone can get. Are we really ready? With the direction we are taking, I doubt it, and long. The death penalty, it is criticized when some also apply it (even if they are not aware of this), it is a creation of society itself, by its inability to cope with the deepening in them. Lack of understanding, lack of listening, the due (solidarity for the Gallery is not acceptable), are issues that, apparently, we are not prepared to deal with. Then, we suffer the consequences. And worst of all is that they believe that balking and amputating they manage to solve the wave of current rot. And laws are still their way. A path that, sooner or later end up being as impassable as a path of nails. Therefore I will try to conclude with a symbol that introduces Kieslowski along all the "Decalogue" and I said lightly. It is the Artur actor Barcis, which, like the old lady of the container, it seeks to establish linkages between the stories and Union among the most crucial moments of these. They are also a kind of person which seeks to represent reality, above all that of the Polish director. You could say that, Barcis, is as a kind of witness, as the conscience of the characters from his despair, and that, after having to take a decision on "Endless" made an appearance over and over again in each of the stories of the protagonists. "Endless" marked the first appearance of the actor, and most importantly, that it is shows in what situation was and that earned him a decision, always curtailing their moral freedom. A from there, the character of Barcis knows the consequences of actions, and is shown to those who go to another vital decision in its existence. Thus, always appears in the Summit moments and the most dangerous from the point of view of volitional, to show their knowledge in this respect. It is a kind of support subtle for them, but really hard to understand. Nobody realizes completely their aid and their presence, as much as observe you. Fail to understand his appearance, as it happens in real life sometimes. Also occurs, in my opinion, as a reflection of the own Kieslowski, as a means of Union that allows us to accept his position, his position in life as an observer of human contradictions. Polish director never said anything about it, but I think Barcis represented his own person. Little more to add. I will simply stop to praising the interpretation of Miroslaw Baka, totally accurate. All the gestures, silences, glances. perfect. Kieslowski and his visual narrative to a level that raya perfection, forcing involving the viewer in all and each one of the planes. The domain owned by Polish director in relation to the film treatment of objects, scenes and people is impressive. Sublime. Picture excellent, as well as loaded with emotion, impressive and melancholy music in charge of the Preisner Companion. a unforgettable, essential and timeless work that demonstrates what is the true cinema and left exposed to the rest of the Billboard, for many resources available. "Do not kill" is oriented towards the "5 Decalogue" Kieslowski created for Poland television in his day based on the ten commandments. As a necessary point of support and understanding of all of the message which Kieslowski was intended to show us, is extremely interesting and forced viewing of the entire series and his filmography. Then we will see the Union ties and direction changes based on personal and human experiences. "Short film or zabijaniu" shows his untouchable mastery when it comes to delve into the human spirit without assert, close circles or judge. The House of Kieslowski always was (and is) the best example of camera aseptic in search of concerns and questions, so that we seek with her answers, if it is that actually there are. It was, along with filmmakers as Bergman, one of the craftsmen who best understood the essence, humanity and spirituality of film as art and way of thought and expression. Kieslowski with his death left the cinema without the eye who best knew how to portray the human soul. And although many not realize it, the film has been very resentful with their loss. I doubt that any work that has touched the subject we are discussing here is has approached the slightest his genius, success and respect. Masterpiece. </body>
</review>
