<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="La joven del agua" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The water is a pure sample of visual poetry, extreme originality, of not tear sensitivity and, first and foremost, a big step to the Filmography of this so-called genius M. Night Shyamalan.</summary>
	<body>So far no director as Mr Shyamalan had managed to create so much intrigue in the premieres of his films. As you can see, I do not mean that his films have suspense and be entertaining (that also are), but to the public, by far than his fans expected impatient its next release. And why is it? As for the reason that his films, so hypnotic, poetic and symbolic, you submerge into another world, a world created by himself. M. Night Shyamalan is unique.In his last film, the girl of water, carried out through a story that they explained their daughters before going to sleep, the symbolism is the protagonist, or rather the gender. It could qualify this beautiful movie as a story for adults totally symbolic and poetic with the fantasy genre backdrop background (or perhaps not so Fund.). I know it may seem a paranoia, but the girl of water is a real paranoia. Or rather, her could define, focusing on the director, as the film more Shyamalan personnel, although that is not to say that it is perfect. And as sample that is its most ambitious proposal, the director has decided to do just a cameo appearance (which in my opinion was better) but it appears already as secondary (and of course indispensable) player in the plot. You know that I do not like too explain of what they try to film critic, but I think that so then you can better understand what you explain (if it is that you have not seen yet), I will tell you the brief overview: Cleveland Heep, a man locked up in itself, traumatized by a terrible past and that he does not know (or can not) see the world around youfound one fortuitous day a nymph in the pool of the apartments in which works as a maintenance man. The strange relationship that develops between them after their encounter will be nosy by monstrous beings pretenderan prevent the beautiful nymph called Story back to their world, the world blue. I believe that all the other details and moments of the film (which are numerous) are better to see them, in a film, which has more see to listen, it is essential to see it from start to finish without knowing any kind of trap, secret or little detail.This is a film with a multitude of characters (all of them bright and ironically described). All of them provide small amounts of importance to history, so it makes it more complex and entertaining. The two protagonists, Paul Giamatti and Bryce Dallas Howard, both the side have been excellent private elections. Think timely attention to Jeffrey Wright (as the addict to crosswords), Bob Balaban (in the role of an unsympathetic and eccentric film critic), Sarita Choudhury (as the sister of the Shyamalan actor), Bill Irwin (as Mr. Leeds, that man who takes life in apartments), Cindy Leung (as the Chinese daughter of the mother who knows the history of the blue world) and the set of friends that don't stop smoking, although prohibited in his small apartment. Girl with water is full of memorable scenes, and therefore I decided to describe some of them (briefly if you can), the most significant of the film. I will begin with the start (if someone does not want to know details about the film that do not read the next paragraph): the film opens with a beautiful and totally symbolic splendidly followed by drawings that tell the story of the people of the water with the humans, who after being with them, decided to secede and worry about themselves. This introduction is what makes you enter in the movie, so if you don't like or you think simple and pathetic, most worth you not see more piece of film, not worth it. For those who the opening, worthy of children's stories, has excited les (like me), look at the following sequences that I will mention (without disclosing part of the outcome, this time is not surprise). Although it is not too important to the plot, the first image of Paul Giamatti trying to kill a bug that was introduced in the apartment of some South American inhabitants who are shouting as desperate to the alleged asquerosidad of the animal is, apart from ironic, a great re-examine, symbol of the man before the apparent small animal. The second sequence to feature is the first dialogue between Story and Cleveland, paused and full sensitivity. When the protagonist is immersed in the pool, or rather, the hidden world of the by then unknown Story, is a scene that appears to terror and scares, but instead what he wants to transmit is said discovery, a step more in the history of Story. Another significant sequence is that of Paul Giamatti will trying to fight against the enemies of Story, at the same time tells you the steps to be followed so not attacked by evil beings (do not go into details). But the best for me is the Cleveland healing the wounds of Story nothing more than with the heart. And finally, the flat end, with that blurry Giamatti by water from the pool that has changed my life. These scenes would be so much beauty without the brilliant director of photography Christopher Doyle (usual collaborator of Wong Kar Wai). M Night Shyamalan has mixed and embedded all the pieces of this complicated puzzle with the intention of saving the beautiful Maja, to create what can be called a happy end that rewards all. As I said before, you don't have a fixed genus. In girl with the water you can find Paul Giamatti making the clown imitating a child for him to tell a story (which by the way, makes it very well) and the following scene and the sequence following a fearsome perro-lobo who wants to eat who crosses his path. To which I wish to refer is the great mix of genres, with the dominant drama, created by the Indian director.This proposed risky also enjoys an excellent soundtrack (attention to the main theme) composed by James Newton Howard (always present in the films of director), a working Assembly and impeccable editing, Visual effects extraordinary (although they are unimportant), a more elaborate script and a witty address.The water is a pure sample of visual poetry, extreme originality, of not tear sensitivity and, first and foremost, a big step to the Filmography of this so-called genius M. Night Shyamalan. It is not perfect, and that is why I admire her. The stories have never been perfect and less those who depart from one makeshift.</body>
</review>
