<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Alatriste has seemed a fairly slow and predictable film, but first and foremost, has to acknowledge that it is crafted production.</summary>
	<body>I have never attracted the blockbusters, and if I have to be more clear, the Spanish films in general even less (with exceptions, clear). And it is that this year we have received a Spanish blockbuster with the name of Alatriste. When I found out that you were going to shoot her, I never thought that a star of such caliber (and also American) as Viggo Mortensen could play this super. sorry, Spanish anithéroe. And Yes, the case was that the main character of the Lord of the rings was hired to give life to the character of Arturo Pérez Reverte.¿Y the director? Therefore nothing more and nothing less than Agustín Díaz Yanes, whose name it knew well few. Anyway, that Director without news of God not be him went nothing more than put together five books of Mr Reverte and convert them in one movie. The result has not been entirely disastrous, but could have been much better. No, do not think that it is badly made or none of it, what you will. If Visual effects and production are a jewel. What fails is the script. But well, I cannot argue either that it is a rubbish such as torrent or things like. It is correct. I had never read a book of Captain Alatriste. Well, I could say that he had not done because the adventures of swordsmen have never me too interested. And the fact is that the reason because I wanted to see the movie version was the following: the spectacular cast. And is who had no reason, that Viggo Mortensen he accompanied all Spanish actors: Eduardo Noriega, Blanca Portillo, Unax Uglade, Elena Anaya, Ariadna Gil, Juan Echanove, Javier Cámara, Eduard Fernández, Pilar López de Ayala and Pilar Bardem. Who does not like you see a film with that cast? Well to anyone. And the case is that I was very excited, and also if it was Reverte, I find a great writer. But, as it was also presumably, became production more expensive than has been done in Spain, and like it or not, it always hurts the quality of the film on the script. And as also is presumably, this happened, and what really startles in Alatriste is not the script (or less!) but the production design. Okay, we can say that also can evaluate a film by its effects and decorations, but for me, the most important thing is that it is well structured, and Alatriste is not. First of all, say that Diaz Yanes seems to take for granted your knowledge about the work and the time (well, this last also find logical). The truth is that I have to say, also, that the beginning is really good (which is very important in this type of movies). It all starts with a silent battle (at times) in a very disturbing atmosphere. Without knowing just the characters appear, by what can be seen, Diego Alatriste and Eduardo Noriega, along with others who nobody knows so far. Well, just say that the beginning is not to present the characters, pretty good. And so is the rest of the footage, we cannot say that it is too clear (set in liosa sequence of the ambush on the boat). It is too cut and barely gives you time to think about the stories of the characters, which are certainly not very well drawn, but excellently performed. The choice of Viggo Mortensen the meeting, into what is, quite right. His disconcerting voice, such as South American accent, makes her more interesting role, and is that Lord Aragorn also a great actor (as well has shown us in A history of violence). The rest of the cast, as I have said, do, and very well, what they have to. The only one which most you have had special mania, Eduardo Noriega, is precisely the interpreter makes it worse, or rather, more sobreactuadamente.Alatriste has seemed a fairly slow and predictable film, but first and foremost, has to acknowledge that it is crafted production. The picture is really good, it has to be said. But what I hope, is that the nomination for the Academy Award as best foreign non-English language film to return or Salvador. Anyway, that has not disappointed me, but isn't the very best this month, much less.</body>
</review>
