<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Anyway, a too zacchia, noisy and excessive special effects-laden adventure film in which there are not even intrigues.</summary>
	<body>The famous phrase "second parts were never good" the simple meeting. Yes, it is true that there are plenty of second parts que són infumables, but there are others who, on the basis of a first good delivery, follow the pace and quality of its predecessor. But as you adored, this is not the case of Caribbean Pirates: dead man's chest. Very simple is this phrase, in this case is true. If in the first part, the curse of the Black Pearl, the protagonists were amount of noise and Visual effects, at this resumed remain it. Not nothing has changed, just the story, although it is already much say. It is a film based on a script by the simplest and absurd (look at the scene of struggle formed by the trio of Depp-Bloom-Davenport, look like clowns in a PC game). Anyway, again I can say that this is a fun but totally empty tape (such as the recently criticized the shadow of suspicion). It is a film of summer.Part of a rather attractive idea (a debt of blood with a man Octopus), but Mr Verbinski has not taken her advantage well. The tape is extremely long, and finally as just, with an open end, it would have been more appropriate to that last much less. Although I'm not saying that this end is worse footage, not. You could say is the best of the movie with Johnny Depp. The default is the following question: what is a long movie to make then there is no sure end? Shall not speak of the argument, not by simple, but because I guess that with so much advertising you will know where the thing goes. I will only comment on the script seems untapped, although you may not believe that it is a great idea. It is only attractive.So yes I can highlight is the fun, but too expresiveness, much to do so on purpose, performance by Johnny Depp. It is a role, an untapped hair, but that is at least original. Today we will find few characters of blockbusters that mimic the style of a rock singer and in this case it is Keith Richards. I find it very risky. And there is at least a good evil (I mean his performance): Bill Nighy (Love Actually old rocker). It has a very difficult role. Has to admit that the villains of this trilogy of pirates have been very successful: in the first installment, together again to Depp, which stood out was the great Geoffrey Rush; in this second, Nighy plays a disgusting man Octopus; and in a not yet released third evil, nothing more and nothing less, than Chow Yun-Fat. The rest of the cast not include anyone more. Both the dull Orlando Bloom and the beautiful, but sometimes deadpan Keira Knightley don't give the size. Anyway, a too zacchia, noisy and excessive special effects-laden adventure film in which there are not even intrigues. Everyone knows what in that lucky chest, although it is at least not money (very common thing in adventures of pirates). The money you have spent on production.</body>
</review>
