<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Desayuno en Plutón" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The protagonist: a Cillian Murphy is Oscar. Who more than he could interpret this type of paper? No one.</summary>
	<body>There are films that for the reason that is, can treat many topics at the same time and not be liosas. Neil Jordan is capable of achieving this. His latest work, breakfast on Pluto, may begin with the story of a boy who has homosexual tendencies and after half an hour, can the issue of some IRA members seeking to put bombs in the city (although both stories are related, no doubt). Perhaps the way to explain to me seems a bit simple, but is what attracts me most of this film is its ability to develop so easily. Breakfast on Pluto is told as if it were a personal diary, with chapters numbered and quite short. But above all, it also seeks to be a film, and now as the beginning and the end, are not in a simple diary, but they are typical of a screenplay. It is not intended to be classical, rather it is intended to be more original. The film has a great starting point, and as I said above, knows develop excellently. Lacks it nothing, is totally round. It has moments of great dramatic intensity, which is why I can say that you it's a very depressing film. And is the story of a boy shemale without barely a hard in search of his biological parents and ANGER through the midst is not too pleasant. The protagonist: a Cillian Murphy is Oscar. Who more than he could interpret this type of paper? No one. Great cast, completely Irish, I would stress, apart from the already mentioned Murphy, Stephen Rea, playing a wizard that helps, like many other characters, the protagonist; Liam Neeson, who does not appear too, but when that comes out, he eats all those who are in front of him; Brendan Gleeson, who also appears little, but acts of wonder; and many others side that I do not know the name now, but certainly deserve to be mentioned. Me not stretch much more because I don't have time, so I will only comment on that you found me a wonderful film, where the technical aspects include photography, music (composed several songs of the 1960s) and the calculated mounting. Well, all in breakfast on Pluto worth.</body>
</review>
