<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Salvador" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>At the start of the film, after these opening titles with the beautiful song I if canto trist, of Lluis Llach, people are pulled tears with handkerchiefs (who had already prepared).</summary>
	<body>Who was Salvador Puig Antich? This question is not one that is formuláse too much for several years after his death. Today, in the 21st century, the rather unknown director Manuel Huerga (Antarctica) the question arises and carries out cinematically, putting the title of Salvador. For some time a Spanish filmmaker did not pose as to fund the Franco era, and I think very timely that today already talk of such a person as Puig Anitch. And this movie which makes it is an honour to him, a summary of his life perfectly narrated. Perhaps the best part is that unfolds in the jail, where the protagonist, masterfully played by Daniel Brühl (which give the Goya!), feel, obviously only and at times accompanied by that originally took more than evil guardian of the prison, played by a superb Leonardo Sbaraglia.La Salvador Puig Antich life begins with a hope that when detainee will fade, as anyone who's going to jail. But he, a man strong and decisively, not surrender unless you see that there is no possible solution, and that he hoped the death penalty. The film is divided into two distinct parts: the beginnings of Salvador as anarchist and his detention and prison for several years. It is a completely depressing, sad, sensitive film (not sentimental) and very pretty. The problem, for me, is that I experienced not the time nor all Franco what happened with Puig Antich, so that I have been a little more difficult to understand it. I think that I wait a few years to to see her again. But yes I have to admit that, despite all this, found me a film exceptional and very emotional. The interpretations other than those mentioned in Brühl and Sbaraglia, highlight of the beautiful Ingrid Rubio, Leonor Watling, Celso Bugallo (although barely appear less than two minutes and not talk), Bea Segura (one of the Sisters of Puig Antich) and Tristan Ulloa (that even though I fall not very well, I don't know why, it does not hurt).At the exit, after these opening titles with the beautiful song I if canto trist, of Lluis Llach, people is pulled tears with handkerchiefs (who had already prepared). It was really very nice.</body>
</review>
