<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="United 93" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film more impressive, realistic, human, touching, brave, tragic, intense and direct for years.</summary>
	<body>I would venture to say that United 93 is the film more impressive, realistic, human, touching, brave, tragic, intense and direct for years. With so many positive adjectives you can verify that the film of Paul Greengras is not missing anything, it's perfect. As we all know, United 93 has the real and tragic story of the abduction of the 93 on September 11 in the United States plane. But, along with other three flights, also abducted by Islamic terroritas, he was the only one not to reach its objective, and all thanks to the bravery and courage of its passengers. The film, narrated in real time, is divided into two intense parts. In the first fragment the events occur from the point of view of the towers of control, terrified see as their country is endangered: the World Trade Center and the Pentagon have been attacked by three aircraft and soon discover that the 93 also plane has been hijacked. The second shows the events in this aircraft which all know their destination. This courageous proposal, carried out by the already named Paul Greengras (English director of authentic quality entertainment such as Bloody sunday and the myth of Bourne), is not intended to have the events of patriotic and sentimental way as insurance will make Oliver Stone with the not yet released World Trade Center. What he wants is to show us the terrible move causing such abductions for the control centres and throughout the country and at the same time to immerse ourselves in a plane full of passengers who know the fate that awaits them, and which therefore will fight knowing that fate will be the same although his enemies die: death. Not only that, but that also wants to, in general, show us how the world is today: into chaos. You would stress primarily, along with the direction of the great Greengras, the cast of unknown actors. Some of them are relatives of the victims, others interpret themselves (as Patrick St. Esprit) and others that simply did not know them. Of all of them, would deploy Christian Clemenson (which in the last minutes of his life speaks with his wife and decides to find out that they have attacked more buildings with airplanes, create a plan to assassinate the terrorists), Ben Sliney (in the photo below, who plays himself), Trish Gates (the blonde stewardess), greenhorns Jackson (the passenger of the CAP who narrowly loses the flight) and several others of those who now I don't know the name. But in general is a casting of the rightness in which they all meet their duty: create realism. The film is how filmed an interview with the camera on his shoulders (which makes perfect sense because that gives it a touch of impressive realism), and therefore with a picture nothing convincing (although lately several directors her being used in his films, such as Fernando Meirelles, Michael Winterbottom and Michael Mann). Technical aspects, I should also highlight elaborate mount and the wonderful soundtrack of irregular John Powell. This is a hard and cruel movie. In many moments puts you goose bumps or you fall a tear. It's purely exciting. The interesting thing about it is that it isn't one of those stories based on real facts that you have everything happened perfectly. It is not, because it is not known exactly what happened on that plane. The relatives of the deceased passengers without air controllers, United 93 would not exist. It is a film totally necessary to know what is happening exactly here, in the world. Shows you the reactions of people to such facts, the nervousness both of which are in the Earth like that are in the air, and it shows you a sense of immediacy absolutely descorcentante. This is a masterful re-creation of a few facts that unfortunately have existed. We have the most touching and tragic film (based on a real event) of the last years or even decades. Before a masterpiece.</body>
</review>
