<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Scoop" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A notable comedy of entanglements (and laughter) that should be noted, in addition, one of the few comedies of genuine laughter in the Filmography of this excellent director, actor and screenwriter, Woody Allen.</summary>
	<body>Since Woody Allen began to opt for the simplest comedy with simple movies such as an end of made in Hollywood, everything else or middling Crooks, no one would have thought the director of crimes and misdemeanours returning to his most appreciated genre (with the exception of the first comedies), the drama. And so it was, he filmed a masterpiece called Match point, in London and with Scarlett Johansson. A year later, the director, remember, New York, has decided to return to the comedy, no doubt intelligent, but, instead of putting it on Manhattan as the rest of his films except the appointed, try again with London, and to follow his "Muse" routine, choose again to Scarlett Johansson. It's Scoop (here it is not translated, but we understand the Word as "scoop"), a comedy without pretensions and moral background (well, perhaps a little Yes.) which aims, creating laughter, no smiles. Perhaps you could tell that he speaks (or criticism), otherwise completely comical and without as much moral British society. And it's no fluke that the two únicsa films he has directed in the British capital are a critique of deep on their social classes. But we must also say, and the British upper class is, in general, totally classist and set, and encounter, successful, one way and another, what did Mr Allen. And nor do I want to be as pessimistic as the director does shows admiration, not by the class, but by the city itself, both in Match point and Scoop. Both films are totally different, so I do not think fair to compare them. I will only say that, as it is logical, the first is deeper and shows more feelings, as well as the second, it is simply a comedy, but intelligent. Yes, smart, and I would say that more than the previous, already mentioned at the beginning. Scoop is what it is, a comedy without pretensions, but nevertheless with a very cool script. It can be that the argument is not any wonder, but is not to be so. It is, without doubt, is a magnificent film, comic sense, because that will not let any scene without any gag. This you must thank Allen, that for years it not laughed so much with one of his films. A point that afavoreze a lot is the fact that he himself appears, each time that does it create laughter in the cinema. For me, Scoop is a mixture of the excellent murder mystery in Manhattan and Match Point, although rather less than these two. Well, rather than a mix, is as a portrait semi-calcado to the first, but in this case, the protagonist falls in love with the suspect.The actors are all splendid. Both Scarlett Johansson and Hugh Jackman play its role perfectly (she, a fearless rookie journalist, or rather, Woody Allen female and he a young actor who comes to the height of several collaborators of the director, Tony Roberts and Jeff Daniels). And then, there are two more veterans, the already mencionadísimo Allen and Ian McShane, a splendid actor, usually secondary, which here plays the deceased journalist giving you a tip-off to Johansson so that the plot begins to unfold. In short, a remarkable comedy of entanglements (and laughter) that should be noted, in addition, one of the few comedies of genuine laughter in the Filmography of this excellent director, actor and screenwriter, Woody Allen.</body>
</review>
