<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Superman returns" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A mediocre blockbuster which for me, has received too many good reviews for what it really is: an adventure without just personality (coming from such director) film seeking entertainment and little else.</summary>
	<body>I'm not very fan of superheroes, but I have to recognise that both Spider-Man and Superman are those that most attracted me, perhaps because they have more feelings than the others. Today I speak of the second, that small saw in TV series (and something of which one I liked him was how changed in the cabin). In 1978, Richard Donner made to fly for the first time to a man on the big screen with Superman, based on the comic book of Joe Shuster and Jerry Siegel. The result was pretty good, and I think that thanks to part of the originality, the actors: Christopher Reeve, Gene Hackman, Marlon Brando and Glenn Ford. Now, in 2006, we do not have this "repartazo", but yes to Bryan Singer (director of the magnificent usual suspects, although he fails to it or to the bottom of the shoes), which fails the same emotion, the other was a great innovation, but it gives a personal touch, and that note. But Superman Returns, thus is how this new version is called, also has its flaws, and believe that it is essential to discuss them: presents many topics of American films, such as the rescue of Lois and his son on the yacht or many dialogues that seems that you you know of memory. These aspects make much lower the quality of the film, especially because it is less credible. But I must also highlight some virtues that are not typical of this type of production, e.g. the way how account its plan Lex Luthor, several quite innovative camera movements and the spectacular main credit titles. Anyway, as you can see, the film is quite irregular. I alargaré not much, because half of what you could already explain it would (as the argument, for example, which is long, but known).One thing yes I will highlight are the special effects, which as usual in this kind of films, are spectacular, the scene of the rescue of the aircraft, both in the final outcome. Also it has of comenar to the scenes of action are rather limited, although they are brilliantly filmed and long-lasting; the music, which mainly highlights the theme that John Williams composed for the first film; and last but not least, the good, but a little contained performance of Kevin Spacey playing the villain and enemy of Superman, Lex Luthor. Other performances are, the truth very little credible, especially of Brandon Routh as mediocre Superman.Un blockbuster which for me, has received too many good reviews for what it really is: an adventure without just personality (coming from such director) film seeking entertainment and little else.</body>
</review>
