<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="La sombra de la sospecha" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A topical bad film, however, fulfilling its mission: entertain.</summary>
	<body>Summer movies tend to be, as you can see, palomiteros blockbusters, tapes of intrigue and action, sequels, more sequels and remakes. Of course, us we can always find a few exceptions, a film not necessarily commercial, rather independent, with a good and orignal script (such as the not yet released the girl of water). Since recently, with the intention to only entertain me and not worry large scripts or addresses impeccable, I went to see, I guess that by the attractive cast and the nothing orignal, but repeatedly entertained, argument (the attempted assassination of a President). It is of (do not think that her you already seen by the title, which must be the simplest and little original this year) the shadow of suspicion. Is starring an aged Michael Douglas (who bears a resemblance more than reasonable to Matías Prats, but without the segurata sunglasses), Kiefer Sutherland (which makes the same role as in the extraordinary television series 24), Eva Longoria (do not know how can have entered such production coming from the also excellent series desperate housewives) and Kim Basinger (that only who know say "going to kill")("Care, a weapon!" or similar crap). As you can see, the cast is nothing out of this world, but is quite right and above all, appealing to the public.The shadow of suspicion (The Sentinel is the original title, also is simple, but passable) tries to create a television environment (a chapter of the aforementioned series 24) in a film. The attempt, in my opinion, has not served to nothing, or rather, is much more less than the series of Jack Bauer. The film only would be it missing to transucurriera in real time so that he could call 24, the film. Ultimately, that is not orignal, but entertaining (which is what I was).The argument I can only say little, that little thing. I believe that with the phrase "the attempted assassination of the President impeded by a few federal agents and a conspiracy in the White House" can be summarized the shadow of suspicion. Ah!, and if you do not guess who is the traitor in the half hour of the film is that you have no experience (just kidding). I just want to say that it looks a lot.A topical bad film, however, fulfilling its mission: entertain (but not as much as 24, which a day longer I speak more carefully).</body>
</review>
