<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El señor de la guerra" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The three stars and not four I put them for a simple reason: the movie, by very good as it is, not liked as much as expected. Yes, good Yes, but a disappointing hair.</summary>
	<body>The issue of the arms trafficking in the U.S. has been treated many times útlimamente in the film. But what makes these films to not be repetitive and little original, I think that it is due to the directors. In the Lord of war, which is behind the cameras is not Michael Moore, but Andrew Niccol. The film reminds me, for the way in which tells the story of the protagonist, at the wonderful one of ours, although aunque ambas both are totally different issue dealing with. The Lord of war is a mixture of documentary, satire and drama of action featuring a cast which I must especially mention: Nicolas Cage (a great actor, but as Michael Douglas, has failed to choose many of their films), Jared Leto (young but always more than correct in all their supporting roles), Ian Holm (splendid and veteran actor)(, which will remember you for his appearance in the Lord of the rings Bilbo com), and Ethan Hawke (a young and charismatic actor who I have always loved). With respect to the history, you know that I almost never tell the sinospsis that I prefer, that if you can see the films, descubráis you all what you have to say. So would not add much else, except that found me really impressive, but perhaps you on some other touch "Hollywood". We could add other bugs as its excessive length, also. I believe that two hours are too many to count what you count Niccol. However, the film is good and is not only script slippages.Aspects such as music (which is based several fairly well-known songs), photography (which is not the most notable, but isn't bad) and the great initial credit titles (vigilant all the time to the bullet!) makes this striking film, with a terrific script, more attractive and personal.The three stars and not four I put them for a simple reason: the movie, by very good as it is, not liked as much as expected. Yes, good Yes, but a disappointing hair.</body>
</review>
