<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Sky Captain" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Exquisite ambience, combined with a moderate use of special effects and an exemplary translation of the comic to the screen, which makes you feel that you are seeing a comic book or reading a film. Pity that no history of for more.</summary>
	<body>One of the sub-genres of science fiction with greater profusion in recent times is the one that is dedicated to bringing to the screen the comic book heroes. In some cases, the result has been exceptional, as in Sin City, whose scenes seem to happen as bullets.Sky Captain and the world of tomorrow is set in a time close to the years of the second world war, and narrates the adventures of a young journalist and a famous pilot, the captain Sky, which faced hordes of flying robots and machines of all kinds that they loot the world and appropriate sources of energy of all countries.It should be noted that the atmosphere is very well made, with a set of filter colors and scenarios that seem to be halfway between the film and the role. Another strong point is the originality of the gadgets and the monstrous machines that appear throughout the entire film, which have been fully relocated from the cartoons to the screen, and get at all times give sense of sophistication, but at the same time tune with prevailing aesthetics in the film of the 1940s.Jude Law and Gwyneth Palthrow cover the file with solvency, and the rest of the cast on everything Giovanni Ribisi (many of you will recall the enormous work of this man in "Beyond the Fame"), are at one altitude of more than decent, including Angelina Jolie; Although the appearance of these last two is rather ephemeral. In technical terms, the director makes good use of special effects, which adds to its extent, which causes greater sense of credibility in many scenes, fleeing from the exaggeration that in many films, too, are those which dominate. In short, a good adaptation that fans to the genre not must lose.</body>
</review>
