<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Déjà Vu" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Leaves vu makes us Holy Communion with mill wheels, as I said my grandmother. Huge wheels, in this case. A huge mill, I'd say. Once swallowed the sweet, do not feel bad, in the background.</summary>
	<body>Now in action films beats the pulse of political cinema. In this Deja vu of Tony Scott there is a film of hondísima political concern which takes 11-s its material for reflection with popcorn and coca coca light. Does not create the gentle reader will swallow a farce of deep parliaments. Nothing of the sort. In a movie with the label Bruckheimer are interested in that the Viewer is two hours glued to the Chair, are interested in that the arguments are not excessively complicated and, finally, interested in that feeling ever, under any circumstances, is that the money has been squandered. The dance of genera that Scott tries to sneak us (thjriller, drama, romance, science fiction) not happy: shows an enormous effort check a competent, entertaining film, but it is damaged in the more rational level, which is the likelihood. In this sense, the film is a disaster. The tool of technology that makes it possible to observe the past is frankly absurd. Ignoring that functional resource, Deja vu is an appreciable film of enjoyable consumption which is left wanting at its final stretch, but hence (in excess) to the ramplonería argument when it comes to fix its fragile narrative concepts.The character of territorista (Caviezel) is completely wasted. The short strokes on his patriotism and his sense of duty towards a decidedly lost America could have given a huge game, taking into account the excellent actor who represented. Leaves vu makes us Holy Communion with mill wheels, as I said my grandmother. Huge wheels, in this case. A huge mill, I'd say. Once swallowed the sweet, do not feel bad, in the background. It has Scott forms and ways of director splendid (fire of revenge is a formidable film) and Denzel Washington is an actor of the first order. Then where is the error? They are the fifteen minutes, or were more than language metaphysical-paranormal that we slip of Rondon so we can understand what the time travel and the screenings of the past. In other films, even in other less successful than this, films are not concerned to explain both the magic of the deception. We simply cheat. Without both verb. Does anyone remember Frequency?</body>
</review>
