<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Dulce Emma, querida Bobbe" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Szabo cela lovingly Socialist culture, the legacy of the Russian school captured at levels fixed, short, the austerity of the props and, above all, true reconstitutivo affection by verbal on the iconic. Political cinema of much height.</summary>
	<body>From the outset, a warning. Sweet Emma, dear Bobe isn't film capitalized as it can be the grapes of wrath or psychosis or Casablanca or the tree of life. It is not a film that has marked a generation and then be marked to another. And what comes. Manifestly popular cinema is not which can hear at a table in a bar or in the Salon improvised on the tail of a film, but is film with uppercase and deserves the sentimentality of this vocational and passionate prose delivered for a while and the gentle reader foreign to the title can dive in film public or private archives to watch her. Repent not the slightest. Those who know (I saw in a pass from the glorious TVE 2 and now I have repescado her in digital format), as returns to its crude charm, but necessary. Splinters of the Socialist regime float over the pool and agujerean the raft in which trying to survive the teachers of a school. The line of flotacíón makes water and every future naúfrago crows knows to claim his portion of lifeboat. Emma, apart from the social revolution, concerned the sexual trade unionism and wanders the corridors of the public school of Budapest in which works lampando by brushing the Director: a cowardly, elusive, type stranded between marital fidelity and clandestine Vice Sin outside program. It is an easy woman, which aims to overcome a personal crisis surrounded by a crisis State, economic, political. in dreams, Emma falls as by a long embankment, naked, with the contracted face and mouth made a crooked, ugly gesture. Bobe is a Western, materialistic, spirit and lives his particular Odyssey of escalafonar and apply the carpe Latin diem to your book of savings with your vaginal solazo: becomes, bitch, and ends by throwing himself, in the end, from a third floor perhaps because it failed to respond to the strict observance of the classist regulation of entrenched communism of its Government. Szabo is a Hungarian director (Budapest, 1938) fully localize, but can recover the teen reads and write a film outside the narrative mechanism of European or American cinema that has tasted in its Westernization. There is no film correlation between this sweet emma, dear Bobe and his other films as the known appointment with Venus (Glenn Close) or Jan Hanussen (with his compatriot and friend Klaus Maria Brandauer, that we remember especially in out of Africa). Szabo cela lovingly Socialist culture, the legacy of the Russian school captured at levels fixed, short, the austerity of the props and, above all, true reconstitutivo affection by verbal on the iconic. An announcement of the time which premiered pointed out the idea that the film was the Thelma and Louis of the Eastern bloc. It is false. There is nothing of the sort. The Ridley Scott film moves to the public to identify gloriously with the women fled, seeking in particular escape an emotional hold his zarandeada life. The country in which they live goes well, reasonably well, clear. Hungary is not the United States of America. Sweet Emma, dear Bobe isn't a movie like that, feminist or slightly escorada a practitioner feminism: it is a sentimental Chronicle of the dsigregación of a way of life and how that fragmentation eventually destroy lots of lives that have failed (or not tried) to embrace the new militancy capitalist, modern, pop.The merit of Szabo (huge) is that it makes a film of domestic consumption that is clearly understood abroad: more in Europe than in the effervescent and watered-down Hollywood that does not see beyond their own garden. The Westernizers contours of the film (crowded tourists places, naked women for a film Arabist pass, the liberal and cosmopolitan talente of tolerant Bobe) articulate a window to look at to understand that the political reality of the countries of the East is not random work, but in this very complex plot also exercising its role values and behaviours of the West: the fair of the vanities that have become, for better, for worse, this side of the story. Twenty years later (or almost) the reading of the film is identical to early 1990s yawned when this awakening of the countries of the East to democracy and to the modern European life style, but now we know more and understand that the journey is worth.</body>
</review>
