<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="The holiday" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Clumsy, GLib, long, predictable, depressive, anything hilarious, monotonous, tiresome, long, cheesy, telar, cazurra, boba, deadpan, dull, long, mealy, boring, The holiday does not leave afloat either by the roster of actors.</summary>
	<body>The romantic comedy has given huge titles in the past (Philadelphia stories) or in the present (the wedding of my best friend) and is reventada of topics. Nancy Meyers is not Howard Hawks or Billy Wilder or George Cukor.Cameron Díaz, even monísima is not Katherine Hepburn. Jack Black is not Cary Grant.Y now the movie (today I jump to the Bullfighter the usual tone of my prose and descarnadamente go to the jugular of the matter so that the blood shoot soon, it spread down the carpet and, before the noise and the Vertigo of the tremebundo red, possible tail that will attend the function gives up and moves to another)(, growing her).Clumsy, GLib, long, predictable, depressive, anything hilarious, monotonous, tiresome, long, cheesy, telar, cazurra, boba, deadpan, dull, long, mealy, boring, The holiday does not leave afloat by the roster of actors with pull (Jude Law, Kate Winslet, Cameron Diaz, Jack Black) nor by the apparent management of its Director in the lides of the genus (already addressed with something better fortune when least expect you him or what women think). Read more: the emotional ravings of the girls and girls of the nuisance leave interest soon. There is a character of interest, well written, that immediately connects with the movie buff demanding that looks beyond an elegant production, that is. I refer to the character of Hong Kong the ineffable and already talludito Eli Wallach, which makes Councillor of the character of the Winslet as writer already retired of the Golden Hollywood.Finally, a lost time. I promise to compensate me with my sombremesa dvd and losing me two hours in Rio Bravo, John Ford. I love the role of Dean Martin drunkard. And even singing, I think. Ah, I said that it is very long?</body>
</review>
