<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El camino de los ingleses" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Worse, in my opinion, the movie is no longer your script or performances or slow or your address. Worst of all is its pretentiousness, its intention to go deep and artistic. I have come to ask me put negative score so that everything I say.</summary>
	<body>I was hoping with curiosity and a certain desire to the premiere of the new film by Antonio Banderas as director. Their debut, "Crazy in Alabama" I think it is a good movie, interesting and very well directed so that the intention of flags to tell us a story about his childhood Malaga did presage an emotional film.Isn't that wait a masterpiece but yes a good film. After the first, in general not very positive reviews, I slightly rebajé my expectations. But what I did not expect under any circumstances is a brick of this caliber, a suckling pig, a real horror like that myself. One could speak for hours of what bad is the film but I will try to be brief and concise, something that the film is not.First and foremost if someone commits the imprudence of going to the cinema to see it, it is better to be notified of that in the first 20 minutes absolutely nothing happens. Anything. Allegedly poetic images, one after the other and little else. But when they begin to move things, and the story starts, is even worse because every situation is more ridiculous than the last.The characters are very poorly defined, do not make any sense, and it is really difficult to feel minimally identified by that bunch of morons whose behavior is not at all justified or explained. That Yes, all the give of philosophers think that now it is fashionable.What to say needless that actors can do nothing with these characters so I stay with the doubt to know if they are good or not. What I do is clear is that diction remains one of the outstanding Spanish film accounts.The film is such silly plot that came to head "Mulholland Drive" but with the difference that, even when it makes no sense, the Lynch film has magnetism, atmosphere, hooked and not boring. Flags fails the same and I'm not even sure that has tried it. In fact I have not clear what has tried to.Worse, in my opinion, the movie is no longer your script or performances or slow or your address. Worst of all is its pretentiousness, its intention to go deep and artistic. I have come to ask me put negative score so that everything I say. But as the soundtrack is not bad I decided to do so.</body>
</review>
