<review author="Silvia" title="Azuloscurocasinegro" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The drama, the story behind an aura of optimism because, as reads the poster for the film: If you don't like the color of your life can be able to change it.</summary>
	<body>Blue are the costumes you saw George when he has to deal with a job interview. But he prefers the black suit which is always seen in a showcase everytime it goes through a store in your neighborhood. But what is relevant is not the suit itself if not representing because Azuloscurocasinegro is a story full of metaphors. Like with the costumes, Jorge aspires to work better than the goalkeeper.This is a metaphor for the struggle to improve in a more competitive society in which it is difficult to make progress.The dark blue (almost black) also which follows the lives of young people who appear in the story, some boys in the difficult process of building or rebuilding their own identity, both personal and professional. The situation is more worrying especially for George, who is forced to face the inability of moving from his father after a heart attack, while cares of their studies; too much responsibility for a young man who has just begun his career. However, Jorge shows the strength of moving forward without paying to see it all black.It is the story of personal battle for survival in a hostile and competitive world that creates frustrated individuals. The character of George represents the fight against the fate of each one, the desire to overcome and the desire to live a life that no one choose for him. George is not as working goalkeeper, legacy his father's trade, if not that he wants a "better" job, which is supposed provide "better" conditions of life. Fight with all your strength to get it because you don't want to live a life that has not elected. But the interesting thing is not will if you get it or not, if not the development of the film at the same time entailed the vital development of the protagonist. Personal growth which will accompany a brother spend their days in jail and a friend obsessed with spying on his neighbors through their binoculars. Paula, the bride's brother George, who was also in prison, will change without wanting to the life of the two brothers. As the story unfolds, the lives of all of them are weaving into a same struggle for the freedom of each one to choose their vital way.But although it's a theme of neighbourhood, that does not preclude that the Mise en scène and the Assembly are original and deeply care to detail. The lives of George and the presidiaria Paula are literally melting on the screen, using Visual and sound resources. But these stylistic resources aren't contrived, quite the contrary, the film follows an aura of truth, realism, so that anyone can be identified directly or indirectly with what happens to the protagonists. In addition to the success in the well cared aesthetics, what more the film captive is the emotional state in which immerses us. A sad mixture of tenderness and humor that leaves no cold nor to the indifferent. The deep drama qualifies with moments of humorous dye as the final scene between the son and the father at the door of the masseuse, probably with the intention to demystify the misfortunes and ease the suffering of the characters.Because the protagonists of this story hidden aspects of his life and they are deceiving themselves, hence the sweet and sour aftertaste that stays in the palate of the spectator once ends the film. However the drama, the story behind an aura of optimism because, as reads the poster for the film: If you don't like the color of your life can be able to change it. Because life is not black and white or of a single color, it is kaleidoscopic, full of nuances and the only way to survive is to try to see it from all angles, to be able to see the color that best defines us.</body>
</review>
