<review author="Silvia" title="15 días contigo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Shows the contradiction that prevails in the labour market based on the idea of how up to find work we lack money.</summary>
	<body>"There is no more unhappy person that can't see what has" Isabelita (Isabel Ampudia), a middle-aged woman who comes out of prison and is in the difficult position of having to find the life as you can think. Through the character of Isabelita, the director of 15 days with you reflects on the affluent life who enjoys the majority of society and how little we value what we have.Jesus Ponce filmmaker made his debut on the big screen with the address and the script for a movie that came out of a photo essay that the director made in 1992 to people who lived in the street. The idea was developed up to the current script, where Isabel and Rufus embody "to these beggars that we see every day in the street".The film teaches us to relativize the problems, that difficult our situation it is always there will be someone who is in worse circumstances. But the fundamental issue of 15 days with you is the reintegration of prisoners: these invisible people for society. The story shows how despises people who have not had the luck or the opportunity to integrate into society and become marginalized. Unfortunately, there are three common against persons such behaviors: indifference, fear (of the unknown) or contempt and abuse.It's time that we stopped the hypocrisy aside because: who not been changed pavement on the street once to see a person with aspect of drug addict? This film helps us put aside prejudices and bring us closer to those who for reasons several living on the margins of society, the outsiders. History discover us that they are people as others, with feelings and dreams, are not so different to us, "normal" people. Like everyone, they suffer from loneliness, have illusions, dreams (more modest? dream dining - of) the film shows the contradiction that prevails in the labour market based on the idea of how up to find work we lack money. Isabelita, after trying to find a job without success, decided to stay out of the system: lives in the street and manages as he can to survive: clean the crystals of the showcases for the will. A will that does not tend to be very generous in a matter of money. But Isabelita is not alone but has a partner that shares your life. Rufus (Sebastián Haro) is drug addict and earn some money to survive helping to park cars. This peculiar couple's life also has comic moments but of those that leave a bitter regustillo in the palate of the Viewer.It is tender and at the same time hard history of fifteen days with a couple of friends, Isabelita and Rufus. The story of their everyday experiences, problems and joys. "The bad out of prison is to see how everything changes and you stay behind." "And when you get back is forever", reflects Isabelita. But at the end of the story it is always a room for hope, so that softens bitterness and some dreams come true. They will be able to Isabelita and Rufus rebuild their lives?</body>
</review>
