<review author="Caty" title="Dick y Jane, ladrones de sonrisas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Through exaggeration does laugh at the same time functioning as a strong social commentary</summary>
	<body>New movie of the histrionic actor Jim Carrey, loved and hated in equal parts. "Dick and Jane thieves of laughter" is a remake of "steals well without looking at who," with Carrey and Tea Leoni in the roles originally played by George Segal and Jane Fonda in 1977. Executive of the powerful Globodyne, Dick Harper is promoted to the position of Vice President of communications and discovers that the company is bankrupt and that his boss, Jack McCallister (Alec Baldwin) escape with $ 400 million. Unemployed and with all its economy mortgaged, Dick and his wife Jane try to find several ways to maintain their standard of living, but end up in the conclusion that the only way is to resort to crime: so become ladrones.¿Absurdo? Clear that if, but this is exactly the objective of "Dick and Jane thieves of laughter", often using satire to comment on and criticize not only the consumerism of American society, but also the demagoguery of George W Bush-then display an image in which this arises by making a speech in which he says that the country is experiencing an era of prosperity - the film shows several executives struggling like animals for a jobwhich check for Earth words we see the President.It is necessary to understand, therefore, that "Dick and Jane thieves of laughter" is not intended to be a comedy of situations or tries to sound plausible, the blows given by the protagonists are totally absurd and would never occur in real life. It is therefore through exaggeration, where the movie makes laugh at the same time functioning as a strong social commentary. As we shown in many of his films of humor, Jim Carrey gives Dick Harper his usual energy, using all its elasticity facial and body to compose the character. As well as with Robin Williams or Mike Myers, Carrey is an actor that needs a director with firm hand to prevent going more beyond, something that the filmmaker Dean Parisot makes only partially: there are some moments in the tape in which Carrey is visibly in an uncontrolled improvisation, what is even if it is more humorous.On the other hand, Tea Leoni creates an important counterpoint to the histrionics of Carrey, making Jane a woman more contained but by no means less "funny". I have to say that I found that comically fit very well these two actors, and that it would not be strange to see them acting again (the scene in which Jane, in the absence of money, goes to a laboratory to sell as a Guinea pig to him they injected a kind of botox-like substance is just great). Completing the cast, we have to Alec Baldwin and Richard Jenkins, although we have to say that the weight of everything falls in Carrey and Leoni.Divertida and with a social message, "Dick and Jane thieves of laughter" is a rare example in Hollywood: a comedy that, unpretentious, has something important to say.</body>
</review>
