<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La alianza del mal" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This Alliance of evil is a Harry Potter last lap: a hodgepodge of topics caught with the fingertips and mixed in a blender of last generation to deliver to the teen audience.</summary>
	<body>This Alliance of evil is a Harry Potter last lap: a hodgepodge of topics caught with the fingertips and mixed in a blender of last generation to deliver teen public a film of powerful attractive visual, but hollow inside, hampered by an argument already seen on many occasions and sentenced to the pass by digital chains or the shelf more golosa film club neighborhood.Say that the case entertains i.e. already plenty, and there who take the time in the armchair of the film and leave proud of its low level of demand because, written brutally, what we have is a carambola carefully planned, properly shot and generous budget of pieces of a puzzle that never comes to assemble at all. They are four kids already talluditos, although mess us the idea that have less than 18 years, who have some powers that reduce them as they use them, who are also addictive and used to lift the skirt a blonde chocolate that is does not have any panties. It is as if Lucius Malfoy, the blonde very bad of the Harry Potter series, had won an award of bad milk extra and got in another book, alien to the children's innocent mind swings, fell into the account that it is God, but not religion or metaphysics, to the donkey, with a plus of spells, spiders, witches and bostonianas mansions of you not menees.They are not superheroes, but paint as if they were. Girls coming out are not meat porn soft, but there are scenes more moved to the encendimiento and lubrication of the pubescent mass that look. (Tomandandy, the architect of the crappy) music is loud, accidental and sparsely dramatic. My friend j., always so attentive to detail, led me to the idea of that, sometimes, the film reminded him, by parties, the coyote bar and, in others, lost boys. The mescolanza explodes into many frames, screeching.Directed by Renny Harlin (theirs are Deep blue or, Cliffhanger lethal memory, all decent titles) solves nothing: it embadurna all ex officio, trafficking in lifting a mediocre script pulling bad or bad approaching deplorable and so insubstantial mimbres may not build a cathedral of taste.</body>
</review>
