<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Babel" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Alejandro González Iñárritu has worn once again with this stunning universal drama that will not leave indifferent any (I hope that ye may be many) to see. It is not perfect, but however thats what makes it be more intimate.</summary>
	<body>There are people that is repetitive and pedantic, charisma and nothing creative. The prodigious tandem formed by Alejandro González Iñárritu and Guillermo Arriaga might say that it fails none of these adjectives, i.e. just the opposite: times repeat the structure of his films (and three with the same go), will never prove to be tired. The trick? Here there is no trick. One is born as it arises, and this pair of geniuses are born as they were born. After loves dogs (which I have pending see immediately) and 21 grams (that dramón destroys the day to anyone and yet is formidable), Iñárritu and Arriaga have decided to finish the trilogy of the (in) communication with Babel. As well as the first stood at Mexico, the director's native country, the second was American ground and stood in a city in the country. The last step not an only ground, but pisa different and scattered around the world (Morocco, Mexico, Japan and United States). So we could call to Babel as a universal film at the same time, obviously speaking of isolation and despair, although in a somewhat moderate way - latter-, to be Iñárritu, clear. I will explain. 21 Grams drama that was presented was a caliber, for me, surpassing the hardness. It was an incredibly dramatic film. But in Babel, perhaps what has taken more care has been transmission through aesthetics and not the extreme dramatization. And that for my has been a relief. Not because the other was bad, I already commented before or much less, but I think that so many things had both left the viewer with a depression of horse. So let's talk about aesthetics. As in all author film, Babel presents a dazzling, atrapadora, aesthetic varied (never better said) and overwhelming (in many cases). But as in all film of author, the plot of the film, or rather, the history is reflected by its aesthetics. Therefore, the tape of Iñárritu is a story (or rather several or a fragmented) with an aesthetic impregnated with it really disconcerting. I believe that this conseguidísima aesthetics is due to the frequent change of situations, countries and cultures. For example: the director has chosen a type specific and different from millimeters to shoot each country. What I do not know is how many millimeters has shot each, up there fail. But what this makes clear is that this perfectionist filmmaker, part of storytelling we creepily located in different worlds and cultures, wheel each one of them with a particular aesthetic. So in short, say that Babel presents several different aesthetics who narrowly that look like, qualify for the film of extremely detailed.The history of the Tower of Babel told the story of a group of men who wanted to build a tower that exceeded the limit of the sky, the power of God. For this reason, it punished them changing the language to each one so that they could not be understood and, therefore, they could not build the tower. Alejandro González Iñárritu and Guillermo Arriaga have used this idea to create the basis of its history, so deduced before seeing, could promise much. I see her and dazzles me, but I do not know why, get me the feeling that this isolation posed not reflected in some respects (or more, well, not her I have found). Well, these "some" are reduced to one, then the only story that has no relationship to the incommunicado detention (for my) is of Moroccan children. Though perhaps I that do not see, but since then I see this terrible media relations like Brad Pitt and Cate Blanchett, of the Japanese girl with almost everyone (it is precisely sordomuda, which further complicates things) and the more than obvious isolation between the Americans and Mexicans (véa is sublime onstage of the border). So the only bug that I see Babel is this lack of isolation that promised so much advertising for the film and that however, in one of the Central stories, not be presence. In any case, this is a film of complex analización, so if this small detail not clear to me, it is because of so complex that is, I have not captured or simply isn't.As the previous two films of the trilogy, Babel is a puzzle of stories that intersect each other. Although the focal point of all the stories here is this metaphor of the Tower of Babel, Iñárritu has not hesitated to structure the film in a manner similar to the others: messy and entrecruzada. However, as with the violence and drama, the filmmaker has moderated and has chosen to structure their film in an orderly and siutable. I think this option is completely in favour, either by own understanding (21 grams should see it at least twice to capture it from beginning to end) or simply to moderate and focus more on the history and not on him frantic movement of sequences. We, Babel, really a film that is understood and heard as understood and hear life itself. Babel is without a doubt, the closest thing to the confusions and problems facing us today in our lives. As always, Alexander has been surrounded by a brilliant cast with actors belonging to his native country. What more clashes here is the emergence of the, already not so star Brad Pitt, which undoubtedly makes a formidable role full of tension and suffering. Cate Blanchett, who plays his wife, in the few moments that appears normal speaking (before it receives the shot) is also great, although I must admit that then does very well sufferer mother - not for bleeding - for their children who are at the other end of the planet. Gael García Bernal (who had already worked with the director on loves dogs) it makes an unforgettable interpretation with an ending that one since you can imagine. But that for my stressed above all is Adriana Barraza (who also appeared in the first film of the director), portraying the nanny of the children of Pitt and Blanchett who commits a huge imprudence which will have to save it on your own. Certainly makes a magnificent role which I hope gets Golden Globe. Rinku Kikuchi (Japanese actress who plays the young sordomuda) also makes excellent work, even if you have a role for me, too unsympathetic (my hobbies, or at least I think). The rest of the cast is equally excellent, even if you have actors who are not practically known (highlighting, for example, Koji Yakusho, Japanese actor with quite a reputation in your country). Within the technical aspects, the beautiful picture of the usual collaborator of director Rodrigo Prieto and breathtaking music highlight of the also associate Gustavo Santaolalla, presenting a series of really precious items.In short: Babel is an essential film (probably one of the best of the year) where circumstances produced are the result of pure chance. It has a few performances that exceed the normal and an unbeatable aesthetic. Alejandro González Iñárritu has worn once again with this stunning universal drama that will not leave indifferent any (I hope that ye may be many) to see. It is not perfect, but however thats what makes it be more intimate.</body>
</review>
