<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Luces al atardecer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It's an intimate film, full of emotions contained in stories not told in the solitude of a cold, almost eternal night, in which the light is an object of unattainable desire.</summary>
	<body>In the current film seems already only matter that movies do much box office and reap substantial benefits, and whether to reach so prized goal we must strangle the originality, creativity, and ultimately, what has made the film an art. But with the existence of several film awards, and the prestige that dan (or in theory they should be), the leaders of the film industry are the excuse to continue betting, minimally, for the quality. All sectors of the film we obsess to know what film will win such or which award, the human being takes competitiveness in the blood. Why surprised that someone that a filmmaker as Aki Kaurismäki reject once again go to the Oscars (for his opposition to American policy) to be his film lights in the evening selected to compete for the statuette.Lights of the sunset, Kaurismäki offers an intense portrait of the loneliness of the human soul through the character of Koistinen (Janne Hyytiäinen), a poor man who earn the living as security guard, with which the fate he has prepared a bad play. It is the story of a loser, but not a loser sordid as the film we are accustomed, but a romantic loser, that always keeps a ray of hope for more shaking it receives from life. Kaurismäki shows with Finnish Cadence to a Koistinen fits the beatings with resignation and stoicism, which therefore becomes a character loved by the Viewer. It's an intimate film, full of emotions contained in stories not told in the solitude of a cold, almost eternal night, in which the light is an object of unattainable desire. All this is based on wonderful performances of its cast, which highlights a Janne Hyytiäinen that supports the entire weight of the tape, and like his character, makes it quiet way, with great restraint.Lights at dusk is a film to a minority audience, but those viewers who dare to see the new work of Aki Kaurismäki will find a kind of cinema that is not common nowadays, and will be pleasantly surprised of the room.</body>
</review>
