<review author="Caruco" title="Babel" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Only elitists and hollow images, untapped ideas and approaches to the navel. Do do do do more than? enraptured?, Iñárritu and Arriaga leave us? embabelados?.</summary>
	<body>If it is already difficult to reach an agreement between a couple, among a community of neighbors living under the same roof, or among the Group of co-workers sharing objectives; and in addition to speaking the same language, imagine what can happen on an international scale, in a "Babel" which is a mosaic of cultures, languages, interests and ways of acting. As film is the Magnum Opus of the Mexican Alejandro González Iñárritu, endowed with the ambition necessary to develop a project that leave footprints, supported in his usual screenwriter Guillermo Arriaga, an artist of the stories entrecruzadas, circulars and fragmented in terms of structure and space, physical and temporal. And together have given birth films like the magnificent "loves dogs", or the irregular "21 grams".In "Babel," from a banal fact, two Moroccan brothers that test the new rifle from his father, get tangled in children piques and end up shooting at a bus and injuring an American tourist. This will trigger an international incident, never narrated in the foreground, but citing diplomatic barriers and the spectre of Islamic terrorism. But above all will have consequences in characters and so apparently far away countries like Japan or the border territory between Mexico and California.El modern chaos.With regard to "Babel," they hear and read much the word "globalization". As well as what emerges from the film and the statements of the director about his intention of making a film about "the physical and language barriers" and ending up not in these pitfalls but also in "what unites us: love and pain". What is true, because in the end abound the inserts of joining hands and hugs.In addition, it must add other important issues, such as unpredictable of chance and fate, feelings of guilt, and a look at human stupidity. So Iñárritu stands, with this and their two previous titles, a chronicler of the "pain" and "human", more fortunate beings or not, with desire for transcendence."But despite having a very interesting material and ideas, what more remains in evidence is the pretentiousness, so empty and relamido that they break down this huge (artifice) tower that is"Babel,"and all the best intentions of Iñárritu and Arriaga.""Babel," we can get to reflect on many things, but more by his bombast or his careful photography, for the sincerity of his images and characters, which seem to operate more than by the blows of fate, a coup d ' état of script.Portraying the pain.And to make the message more clear, each of the varied characters players will have their moment, his great "pose" (carefully studied), pain and isolation in the form of a map or a scene Summit to look demonstrating that they are lost in these islets of global isolation than a J.J. Abrams Castaway looking for answers or foreign aid.There are many of these moments, but to highlight: Amelia (Adriana Barraza, and the best cast), an illegal nanny lost in the middle of the desert with a, so striking as grotesque, dressed in red wedding; Yasujiro (Koji Yakusho, the second best of the cast); a teenage sordomuda traumatized by the suicide of his mother, the inability to communicate with his father and obcecada with losing his virginity, alone and lost in a sea of people and noise of uan disco (not for her, as it undertakes to make us notice intermittent sound cuts); Chieko (Rinko Kikuchi, best male cast), supporting desolate in the elevator; or Richard (a Brad Pitt that no clashes, nor with the gray hair and wrinkles added), demonstrating their suffering that it should embrace his heartfelt wife (Cate Blanchett, shining even in minimal interventions) or grab the phone up the photogenic achieve more appropriate. Little life beyond. Only elitists and hollow images, untapped ideas and approaches to the navel. Rather than "enraptured" Iñárritu and Arriaga leave us "embabelados".</body>
</review>
