<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La casa de tus sueños" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The House of your dreams is a film so ruinous and shameful as the House of the title.</summary>
	<body>We are a few hours of finishing one year and begin a new one, and it is inevitable that people currently do a certain balance of the year to be. This year has been good, not to say excellent, for cinema that we have seen in our country, both national and foreign. If you have to put a but is the shortage of comedies of height, with the almost annual exception of Woody Allen. In this regard, little or nothing can be expected from Hollywood, in 2006 Spanish film has focused more on dramas, so the door has been open pair in pair to European comedies. This is therefore a genre almost extinction, in modern cinema, a good comedy is more rare to find a four-leaf clover on the roof of any skyscraper. The House of your dreams has been the last in a long list of French comedies released in our country this year, which include this great fiasco of Francis Veber called the game the idiots, and that more than acceptable tender and romantic entitled story you are very handsome. One of the most socorridos topics relating to the comedies is that it is harder to make you laugh that cry, and hardened by the experience one has to surrender to the evidence: it is true, it is easier to make desperate mourn and bitterly, especially if tapes are seen as the home of your dreams. There are comedies that not only is that they do not have the slightest grace, or dabble, but serve as a cruel martyrdom for those most in need of distraction and laughter. Dany Boon, a popular comedian in the neighbouring country, made his debut in the direction with the adaptation of a play itself, which chronicles the misadventures of a poor type to buy a country house. Not have passed many minutes so that the Viewer is account of the shortage of originality and mediocrity of the proposal. However, appears a faint ray of hope called Daniel Prèvost; with each appearance his character the film seems to go back slightly, but more by the skill of Prèvost and memories of true inspector of finance and its a "Bully" wine drinks which for the screenplay of Boon. And then comes the comic nucleus of the story, the reforms of the casa de campo. Suffice it to say that dialogues and situations of any episode of that series of Vicente Escrivá seem to extruding film the Marx Brothers in comparison with similar succession of desprópositos. If of alone weren't enough the calamities that offers the film, the inexperience of Dany Boon in the direction causes a total lack of pace, not to mention its interpretation, flat, the protagonist. The House of your dreams is a film so ruinous and shameful as the House of the title, and from here we strongly recommend that all those unhappy that sudan blood to pay a mortgage to refrain from seeing the film, because it will provoke a furious anger in them, and leave the rooms with the bloodshot eyes blood and a big thirst for revenge.</body>
</review>
