<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Babel" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Babel reaches very high levels in what regards to the cinematographic art. It is not only a masterpiece, not only has already become a modern classic, but is it film, truth, film with a capital.</summary>
	<body>There are some films that create great expectations since before even that will begin shooting, and in most cases to multiply the information, those expectations are declining. However, some movies not only manage to keep those expectations, they get progressively increase. This is the case of Babel, one of the most anticipated of the year by the excellent feelings left in Cannes, by its Director Alejandro González Iñárritu, and its extraordinary cast.Alejandro González Iñárritu is one of the most personal filmmakers that have emerged in recent years, and proof of this is that its passage to Hollywood after Amores Perros not le has been "corrupted", but has made him grow even more. A series of events will join a group of people who live and suffer in various parts of the world: in the mountains of the Atlas, Morocco, Japan, California and Mexico. It is a story which talks through different cultures and different languages, of the inability of current human beings to communicate with their peers, and also of the loneliness and isolation that this brings. We take this opportunity to protest at the decision of IPU Spain double Babel, it is a betrayal of the spirit of the film, even more so when much of it must be subtitled. If before we were talking about the growth of González Iñárritu, is not less of Guillermo Arriaga, Babel with signing one of the best scripts that have been written in the last decades, and which undoubtedly will go down in the history of cinema. Alejandro González Iñárritu directed accurately surgeon this jewel of script, and with his very personal narration, and a sense of impeccable film rhythm, get to do something that is within the reach of very few: a film that oozes truth from all its pores, with nothing artificial or forced. Babel is those tapes that capture the full attention of the Viewer, that leave you stuck to the seat, and when they conclude, missing several minutes so it can react and assimilate what he has seen. They also deserve mention the wonderful music of Gustavo Santaolalla, and the excellent photography Rodrigo Prieto. The interpretations are, as a whole, extraordinary, and even unfair to nominate a few above the others, not to do so also it would. Adriana Barraza, Rinko Kikuchi, Brad Pitt and Cate Blanchett are simply grandiose work, making the difficult easy, and contributing significantly to that sense of reality which transmits the set.Babel reaches very high levels in what regards to the cinematographic art. It is not only a masterpiece, not only has already become a modern classic, but is it film, truth, film with a capital. And before this, the only thing we can do is take away the hat, and applaud one of the greatest geniuses of the cinema of the 21st century as Alejandro González Iñárritu, and enjoy with his new creation.</body>
</review>
