<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Babel" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is without doubt, the worst movie of the director, who has failed to improve his masterpiece loves dogs, 2000.</summary>
	<body>On Friday, when I went to the cinema to see the expected premiere of the latest work of admired director Alejandro González Iñárritu, Babel, I estrañó see a group of teenage girls who not above 15 years of age. They are very mature or have come here by two of the players, Brad Pitt and Gael García Bernal - said to my himself. The issue is that, at the end of the film, the poor ended up crying as a few muffins, too much pain for a few teenagers - I thought. But the truth is that the loud sound was heard throughout the film, from some another kleenex fiddling with some restless naricilla inside. And it is not for less because, if we were to find a common denominator to the development of the three stories that make up the global narrative, this would be a pain.Precisely the suffering will be the engine that will move our protagonists, either in search of salvation, as a prelude to self-destruction. The pain means not of race, sex, age or social status and will get us the best or the worst.It is without doubt, the worst movie of the director (that has failed to improve his masterpiece loves dogs, 2000). The feeling I took is the work could have been much more than itself, but this argument should have worked more and not reach exhaustion (the history of the Japanese girl is tedious to induce indifference). Some scenes do not make no sense and have been directly introduced to force wedge, possibly on a whim of the director (that someone explain to me the meaning of the image of the Muslim girl masturbating, especially when a minute earlier was discussing with his brother).Instead, the film also features elements in their favor: a great work of completely unknown on the big screen actors (Adriana Barraza, Boubker Ait El Caid and Said Tarchani (the kids had never worked as actors;) the difficulty of linking in the script so different scenarios as the skyscrapers of Japan, the border between Mexico and United States and Morocco desert and, especially), the intention with which was born the film to talk of solitary confinement in which we live (remembering the chaos that originated Jehovah in the Tower of Babel). Only one Council: If you are one of those who have the easy tear, don't forget to take the handkerchief.</body>
</review>
