<review author="Dario Lavia" title="Doctor X" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the first terrifying films in technicolor (if not the first) was reported missing and developed a reputation for "lost masterpiece" for years.</summary>
	<body>One of the first terrifying films in technicolor (if not the first) was reported missing and developed a reputation for "lost masterpiece" for years. Reicén when a copy appeared in white and black could enhance better film, which certainly was that established the status of "Queen of el Grito" of Fay Wray (whose first onstage enters the library of his father, Dr. Xavier and paste flower of cry for no reason, just because "are you afraid"). In 1973, when a copy appeared in color, found the known (black-and-white) copy was filmed apart from the copy in color (which was aimed at the time at larger circuits). The police are baffled by a new crime of the "full moon killer", and Dr. Xavier (Lionel Atwill, one of the great classic horror "plugged") is called to perform the autopsy. The inspector in charge (usually cash Robert Warwick) explains to the doctor suspects that a member of its Academy of medical research is responsible for the crimes, so Xavier requested 48 hours to carry out its own investigation, so as to avoid a negative publicity that could harm his good name. In the midst of this we have a witty journalist (Lee Tracy) which seeks to get fresh information for his newspaper. Xavier takes the decision to leave his mansion in Blackstone Shoals, on Long Island, with his daughter, his retainers and the four suspected doctors, one allegedly free of any suspicion (Preston Foster) manco; other Germanic and given to poetry (Arthur Edmund Carewe); a third party with a possible history of cannibalism (John Wray); and one crippled (Harry Beresford). There he prepared a series of experiments that will reveal the identity of the murderer (who also undergoes the own Xavier). Announced at time of its premiere as a "film that will provide scares and laughs", the scares are well grounded in climates that director Michael Curtiz achieved through the use of bichromate color, especially during the experiment of Dr. Xavier and the final appearance of the "Monster". The laughter, which supposedly would have to be provided by the occurrences of the journalist and his romantic interlude with the beautiful daughter of the doctor, aren't as effective, perhaps by the forced chemistry between both characters, although certainly Tracy isn't anything wrong in his grimacing. Without having the insistent appearance in camera of the journalist, the film has its subtle profile of black humor, provided essentially by Atwill and their doctors (more delusional than the other one). The true burden is not humor but the fact that history is poorly told, with cracks in logic and lack of synchronization between the characters. In the next horror film of Curtiz, mystery of the Wax Museum (1933), the comic role of Tracy went to Glenda Farrell, whose mischievous journalist at least enjoyed best dialogues.Note: This review is on the copy in color.</body>
</review>
