<review author="Javier" title="Cargo" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There is no where to take her</summary>
	<body>Yesterday, while returning from my breakfast of pseudo official, a snowing stopped me on the street asking me if I wanted to go to the movies free. Obviously said yes, and there we were last night surrounded by people whose average age could fully overcome the sixty years, seeing charge, a strange film (strange by the incomprehensible in its cast, type European co-productions in which there is an actor in each country, for notice who has contributed money and how much money has brought) directed by Clive Gordon (author of documentaries that becomes the long and that has not begun to a very good start) (his career) and written by Paul Laverty, long-time collaborator of Ken Loach in the writing of some of their films (sixteen happy or Carla song) and I guess already had wanted to get rid of both social and committed cinema and go directly to the entertainment pure and simple.The film tells the story of a man (Daniel Brhül) who must escape from an African country where have stolen you all the documentation and where can't get out (why is there? how is it possible to escape so easily the police? who is so stupid to steal a bracelet in an African country?). Therefore sneaks into a gigantic ship of smugglers bound for Marseille, where the person with a group of sailors (avoid jokes, please) whose fans throw overboard all free riders who are on the boat during the journey (but incompresiblemente, to him they adopt and protect: will be that you just throw if you stowaway and black) not be where to start for gutting the film, because there is really no where take it. For starters, the characters are reliable far impossible: sailors (not is if eight or ten, I lost the account) are gross to but not power, and does not add absolutely nothing when they open their mouths to Growl. Say two words without releasing a taco and shout, and the writer puts in his mouth dialogues like these: Captain: "Id to register the cellar and found him!"Sailor 1: "It, that it is not any living bastard" sailor 2: "(a) that hijoputa" sailor ·: "Come on, we will find that bastard" character of the captain, played by Peter Mullan (go disservice that has made him the screenwriter of Ken Loach in recommend it), is of those who speak with metaphors all the time, and has an oscurísimo past that must have been horrible to do the things it does. This (the mystery of something that happened in the past) is what supposedly makes move history; but I can say that no, which is precisely what her sinking. During one hour and a half trying to know what happened on the boat for. Discover at the end that nothing happened. Characters throw people overboard to not pay the fine which imposed it in the port if discover. Do not look for more.Luis Tosar, contribution more visible Spanish acts with the autopilot required in this type of movies. It seems that went there and he was asked to act. Above, if they ask to go made a pig and bearded to the Fray Leopoldo, then the in their sauce. For more inri, bends if same, although well, not it note too, because more talk seems that everytime he opens his mouth he Snarls.The only that is saved is Daniel Brühl, which gets put face of scared during the footage, not sure if by history or see what were perpretando them they surrounding him. In addition there are failures of photography, obvious blurs, inconsistencies in the story, things happen that Yes, and a final scene type "Piety", which has no waste (by sonrojante).Photography is the only thing that seems designed and worked on a tape in which was very easy to get the feeling of claustrophobia that ahogara to the viewer and you would identify with the protagonist (a boat in the middle of the sea full of ins and outs, corridors and rooms), but it seems that only the director of photography was raised this possibility, and the screenwriter and the director are determined to destroy the feelings it provokes.And all this for a film which shows, in its promotional poster, the phrase "Magnificently filmed." "excellent interpretations" (Geoff Gilmore, director of the Sundance Film Festival) and "Inquietante." "rough and feverish as a heartbeat" (La Razón). If so is the level of quality, I do not want to even imagine what is to come if this infumable tape is successful. Let us hope that not.</body>
</review>
