<review author="Dario Lavia" title="The return of Doctor X" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A horror, the film Bogart gestated in a time Warner was, if we are allowed to the expression, a "machine for sausages".</summary>
	<body>It seems simple today disqualify films such as the return of Doctor X by narrative poverty and his refusal to produce bemusement at the public. But we must bear in mind that the film was concocted at a time Warner was, if we are allowed to the expression, a "machine for sausages". Usually producers sought to satisfy the public generating films of social theme, westerns, adventure, the always police and, eventually, some terrifying film. So enjoyed a roster of players under contract on which seemed a kind of lottery raffle above who you played which character. That seems to be the only explanation to understand to Humphrey Bogart in a horror film. Warner appealed to old success of the House, DOCTOR X (El Doctor X-1932) that marked the first alignment between the "mouthed" Fay Wray and Lionel Atwill. For 1939, with the resurgence of the genre (consolidated from several interesting Universal films), Warner had no intention of staying outside, and this is how we have a "return" on this ténebre Dr. X, that while it is not a proper sequel to the 1932 film, pivotea in several matching points, namely:-synthetic blood: remember that in the 1932 filma mad scientist used "synthetic flesh" - the role of a journalist: Lee Tracy of 1932 (too witty and funny) succeeded by Wayne Morris of the film occupies us, less interested in becoming the funny that in investigating the case - of course, the presence of a "Doctor X", in this case Bogart, that carries the same name as the character of Lionel Atwill (although without kinship) A stage actress (Lya Lys) is "killed" and a reporter (Wayne Morris) gives the scoop to his newspaper. However, the next day she appears with life to deny it. The strange fact arouses their curiosity, and together with a young doctor, friend (Dennis Morgan), gets to investigate. The chance to be one of those involved the renowned Dr. Flegg (John Beal) whose Assistant is the strange and cold Quesne (Bogart), who is none other than the fearsome Dr. JFK, that needs frequent doses of certain types of blood. Bogart newly makes his appearance in the 22 minute of the film and is director Sherman wanted to equip its presence with ominous climates, because of the speed with which seems to have been filmed, never achieve. In fact, the final 4 minutes are a prodigy in concise narrative and more than an outcome seems a summary of the outcome (which obviously takes expected suspense). Its similarity to the outcome of the subsequent if die before of Awakening (1952), can still be checked by Carlos H. Christensen.</body>
</review>
