<review author="Dario Lavia" title="Mad love" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film opts in an outcome with forced logic, despite the incredible attempt of Lorre and always correct Frances Drake give credibility to the action. This ballast obviously fails to overshadow previous accomplishments.</summary>
	<body>A brilliant surgeon, Dr. Gogol (Peter Lorre), is enfermamente in love with an actress (Frances Drake) who is the star of the theatre of Horror Parisian (whose Grand guignol also pervades the entire film). The actress rejects the romantic suggestion of the doctor, but when her husband, a virtuoso pianist named Orlac (Colin Clive) suffers a terrible rail accident, he pleads to save the hands of the rugged husband. To achieve this, Gogol decides to transplant the healthy hands of a recently executed serial killer (Edward Brophy), while hiding the details of the operation, even to the patient. The result is beneficial, and not only Orlac has hands but can also return to dream of playing the piano. However, soon there are more tragedies, as Gogol tries to sow into Orlac ideas sickly on their hands, it becomes crazy and release him the road to the woman he loves. So when the stepfather of Orlac (Ian Wolfe) is stabbed, the former pianist is blamed and arrested.The film picks up in its subject matter the interesting world of Grand Guignol, and adapts it to your needs. Based on a novel by Maurice Renard, which had already been adapted for the screen as ORLACS HANDE (the hands of Orlac-1924) with Conrad Veidt in the lead role here Orlac passes to a secondary plane (to Clive also looks it great), and is the Gogol of Peter Lorre (anthological) which takes a key preponderance. Traditional rule of horror at that time, including a character half comedian to lighten tensions, we have Ted Healy (here without their Stooges), as an American journalist that investigates the case, although fortunately the camera not stops long in their occurrences. The emergence of Gogol disguised as the executed murderer (for traumar Orlac) is more gloomy that you can imagine and is perhaps a valid precedent for subsequent surgical film by David Cronenberg. After this "pre-climax", the film opts in an outcome with forced logic, despite the incredible attempt of Lorre and always correct Frances Drake give credibility to the action. This ballast obviously fails to overshadow previous accomplishments.</body>
</review>
