<review author="Vsancha" title="Brick" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Brick is one of the most original products, bold and fresh from last year, everything failed Palm giving us with his Black Dahlia, has given it us Rian Johnson in Brick, a dark, clever, twisted, bizarre and hypnotic film.</summary>
	<body>Not lying if I said that one of the major problems, not to say the elder, of the current Hollywood industry, is the dearth of ideas original and daring. The most interesting products we get mostly through the small screen, TV is becoming a constant source of ideas to the world of cinema. All years leaving a pair or three of a series of high quality. One of the most interesting series of recent years is Veronica Mars, once I already read that writing on it. A series who got very well move the spirit that enjoyed the first seasons of Buffy the Vampire Slayer, adding touches of the best film noir, what has come to be called the teen-noir. And there is, in part, the success of Veronica Mars to learn together so brilliantly, two worlds, in completely different appearance such as the classic film noir and the movies and series on adolescents, adding the factor of serial television and the offer us every week a piece of that mystery. This year we have left behind, it brought us many disappointments, but also some surprises, films that a priori expected little or nothing, or that we even desconocíamos its existence, one of those gratas, wonderful surprise is "Brick", the movie of rookie and promising filmmaker Rian Johnson, the closest thing that can find Veronica Mars film, but in contrast to this, "Brick" away much more than the teen and gets to film noir, something that initially can remove you realism, but "Brick" makes a fun with a few touches of humor really made whole and occasionally product. All topics on film noir and each of his characters, the tormented detective, the femme fatale, confident partner, "mafioso", we are in "Brick" the bully? but this time it's simple adolescents. Brick not only demystifies the genre as their characters, if not also in their locations, here there is no dark alley of large cities like Chicago or Los Angeles, here we are in a small village in Southern California, and the action is set in long corridors of Institute, large open spaces, fields of football, long roads, etc? The atmosphere recalls occasionally to the movies of the Coen brothers and David Lynch (for larger example the House of The Pin) and it is that it resembles the sordidness of "TP: fire walk with me" and in general the visual elegance of David Lynch and his film. Brick is one of the most original products, bold and fresh from last year, everything failed Palm giving us with his Black Dahlia, has given it us Rian Johnson in Brick, a dark, clever, twisted, bizarre and hypnotic film. A film shot with a huge sense of elegance and the narrative pulse, with brilliant scenes as the fight of the protagonist with the leader of the football team or the chase through the corridors of the Institute. Two small samples of the virtues of Brick and what a future can offer us Rian Johnson.</body>
</review>
