<review author="Silvia" title="El intruso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Psychological thriller that tells the story of how a simple life, quiet and happy, skewed after an incident.</summary>
	<body>The intruder (Enduring Love) is the latest film by Roger Mitchell, an adaptation of the best-selling "Enduring love" from Ian McEwan, who has become a British thriller paused, but without falling into boredom. Many may be familiar name of the director by the famous "Notting Hill" and that is why many may back down to go see this movie thinking that you it's a new romantic comedy. Nothing further from the truth. It is a psychological thriller that tells the story of how a simple, quiet and happy, life is impaired following an incident and the obsessive insistence of a character played brilliantly by Rhys Ifans (known for his role of roommate of Hugh Grant in Notting Hill) the story begins in a manner more innocent. Joe (a superb Daniel Craig, the new James Bond) has something to tell Claire (Samantha Morton), his partner. So it has chosen a beautiful sunny day picnic in the field. But apparently harmless balloon will leave a terrible impression on the memory of both, but it will be more intense in the Joe. That day apparently unimportant will mark the existence of all the characters in the film.From that day, Joe can not think that he could have prevented what happened on day of the incident with the globe, so that feeling of guilt ends up becoming an obsession. One day he receives a call from Jed Parry (Rhys Ifans), one of the people who were there that day, expressing their need to see him. Jed insists that they have shared a transcendental moment and therefore something unites them since the day of the incident with the balloon. The film is the impact of the casual events of our lives and the way in which these strange events can hopelessly desquebrajar lives. As reflected a critic of the Chicago Sun-Times about the film, the way to raise the conflict is interesting: "most of the films focus on what is happening." "Few films are called into question what is happening, and let alone deal with the fact that we can decide, most of the times, about what is happening and what to do about".The film benefits from a script in which the important things are not the facts that are happening but fears, obsessions and desires of the protagonists. This is a great challenge cinematically speaking, that the feelings seem easier to explain with words (as in the novels) that only with images. Although the best and the worst (because it may be repetitive) is the continuous reflection raised characters on the single fact (but essential) that leads the narration. A fact that each of them arises and interprets differently. But a masterful home (with the bright scene of the globe) able to engage the viewer in the story after few seconds followed by a development which at times can seem slow. While it is true that the film boasts quite a few scenes suggestive and intriguing thanks to which is is holding narration. Example of this is the scene of the birthday where about the words to know the innermost thoughts of each.Finally, the story wondered if love really exists, if it is forever. The character of Joe has a nihilist's life and love vision as he believes that love is an illusion and life makes no sense (apart from the biological) Although we endeavor to give it. In the film refers to different types of love but in the end it reaches the same conclusion: love exists by itself and must not find any rational explanation.</body>
</review>
