<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="La central" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mathematics do not fail, and in the cinematographic field tell us that when joined many absurdities in a same film, the result can only be a hodgepodge of huge caliber, as it turns out this monstrosity.</summary>
	<body>The truth is not expected much from this film. He supposed that it would be typical of desinhibidos teenagers who spend time making apology of drugs, alcohol and the chabacanería; one thing similar to 13 Friday, but the Spanish and more modern. But I was wrong.Not even in the worst scenario could be me of course the magnitude of the crappy that I was going to find lighting certainly in the light of any State subsidy such that Governments attach to certain artists as payment for services rendered (see never Mais, No to war, etc.).A movie as the Central will roll, produce and release in Spain is an indecency, the least. In addition to an absurd script that relies on all existing topics and far exceeds the tolerable limits, the characters are heinous subjects that give a picture of the deplorable and vomit youth, until the point that greater arouses sympathy is the killer that is passing a knife slowly to the gang of Brats who make up the castwhich is to be welcomed. Constant obviously and retahílas no sense are the basis of the screenplay, seasoned with a bit of tomato sauce and a lot of nonsense.The interpretation is more artificial, without giving any do actors? at no time sense of credibility, while the soundtrack is non-existent. Perhaps the only thing that can save a little, and only in certain moments is the picture, but that being very generous.This monstrosity, as it is only natural, spent with more penalty glory by theaters. But the simple fact that has been planned already is of itself irritating. And is that this film there is no where on take it, because everything in it is disastrous: from the script to the characterization of the characters, the purported shocks or constant hysteria of the rabble that appears on screen. But above all, that claim to give a touch of cheap Americanism (children of dad with huge mansion, which they drink beer, smoke marijuana without stop and rest corners) make the Central infumable rubbish which is only capable of awakening contempt and cause torpor in the courageous who manages to reach the final.</body>
</review>
