<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When the talents of three geniuses such as Eastwood, Spielberg and Haggis come together, the result cannot be but a masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>World War II has been and is one of the large veins for the American film. Before even of after the war, but with victory secured Europe, Hollywood machinery began to make the first films, propaganda, on the war. Once past the euphoria by the positive outcome, the films became less panfleteros and more suited to reality. The battle of Iwo Jima was the beginning of the end of the war in the Pacific, to be the first Japanese territory invaded by the Americans. It was one of the most bloody war moments, as in little more than one month the Americans suffered almost 26,000 casualties, of which nearly 7,000 dead, while almost all of the 20,000 Japanese soldiers of the garrison of Iwo Jima were killed.The film tells the story of the three survivors who raised the flag on Mount Suribachi, immortalized by Joe Rosenthal instantly. That picture makes heroes John Bradley (Ryan Philippe), Rene Gagnon (Jesse Bradford) and Ira Hayes (Adam Beach), and they are embarked on a tour to dupe the country in hopes of victory, and to upload the sale of war bonds. Clint Eastwood from a fabulous script by William Broyles, Jr. and Paul Haggis is immersed fully in the history to make it own to offer the viewer a film that will leave you shocked and stunned. Eastwood tells the war in all its harshness, showing an almost indescribable horror, and at the same time, uncertainty and fear of the soldiers. War scenes remind saving soldier Ryan, and rightly so, that own Steven Spielberg is a producer of the film. But flags of our fathers is not only war and battle, its hardness is also found in how politicians manipulate three survivors, and without any qualms, put them in a race to sell more, to become icons of heroism. Clint Eastwood demonstrates once again that dominates the art and magic of cinema like few others, that pace that prints is the perfect history. Not to mention her beautiful score, hopefully that recognized this time in the form of nomination for an Oscar. All the technical work is impressive, highlighting photography Tom Stern, and the Assembly of Joel Cox. The icing to the cake put him interpretations, excellent, especially those of Ryan Philippe and Adam Beach.Cuando gather the talents of three geniuses such as Eastwood, Spielberg and Haggis, the result may not be but a masterpiece. And flags of our fathers. Now you only need to wait a few months to see the second movie of the project, the Japanese vision of the battle, letters from Iwo Jima.</body>
</review>
