<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El ilusionista" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film of Neil Burger is a quality entertainment, with outstanding performance and a correct script (with a final twist too sharp).</summary>
	<body>Last year I discovered in this excellent comedy-drama called sideways to a sublime actor Paul Giamatti (secondary par excellence of the past years). Since his triumph with this independent experience, Giamatti has led his career as a way to respond. The last time that we saw his interpretation has been in "The illusionist", a film that without it would be practically nothing. As well stated in the title, the film revolves around a magician (a kind of wizard that creates illusions and performed by a correct Edward Norton) in Vienna at the beginning of the 1900s. After one of his works to the Crown Prince Leopold (a charismatic Rufus Sewell), the thing starts to get complicated, especially because of the appearance of the fiancée of the latter, Sophie (Super Jessica Biel), a childhood friend of Eisenheim the illusionist and the inspector of police (an excellent Giamatti) Uhl. Mystery, magic, romance and plot twists could be (or are) the main genres of the film by Neil Burger. The film has a formidable beginning, absolutely coerente eventually, entretenidísimo and with the start of a flash-back which continues almost finish the film. Well, the script presents some fall considerably mild pace that makes losing interest to the story and the characters (pretty well drawn, yes). The rest of the film is simply entertaining, to reach that end too evident surprise but, on the other hand, not too misleading (being a film nowadays). "The illusionist" is a story that attracts (the Magi, like it or not, always captivate the public), because lately we are seeing an excessive appearance in the film ("Scoop", the not yet released "the final trick: the prestige").Interpretations of the film, as I have said, are in general more than correct, highlighting the huge Paul Giamatti and Jessica Biel in a brief role, but intense. Although Edward Norton, the great King of the movie, does a correct interpretation, not giving much of it.Within the technical aspects, "The illusionist" presents a photograph beautiful with a dark touch too dark. For me, it is tired to be seeing during the film a touch of contrast black around the image, as if it were a dream (or illusion).. Mounting is really good, with a few cuts and transitions (circular) really imnotizantes.In short, the film of Neil Burger is a quality entertainment, with outstanding performance and a correct script (with a final twist too sharp).</body>
</review>
