<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Babel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The final message of Babel, is a call to the compression. The importance of paying attention to what others have to say. A highly recommended film and a fantastic farewell for 2006.</summary>
	<body>Alejandro González Iñárritu (Mexico 1963) after indisputable as "Amores Perros" or "21 grams" successes, brings us a fábulosa and unpredictable, Babel. The name of the film is derived from the Hebrew verb balál, "confused". And precisely on the confusion, on the words and the important thing is to listen to them, is about what this magnificent film.Alexander, returns to surprise us and fall in love with your genuine personal touch. This man not wheel, this man makes authentic verse visual with the camera, although the result of this tape as well as well as those mentioned above, not have been possible without the narrative magic of Guillermo Arriaga (Mexico 1958) writer of the three titles.Having chosen Babel as a name, is a colossal success, for those who do not know the history, the Tower of Babel prentedía be a construction of type ziggurat, will reach heaven, mentioned in the Bible in Genesis Chapter 11. According to, Dios Yahweh descended to see the city and the tower that the men were lifting and said: "Behold all form one people and all speak the same language, this being the principle of their companies." Nothing precludes them that they carried out what they intend. «As well, let us go down and there same confuse their language so may not understand each other '.Something similar is occurring in this film, people with parallel stories that are United in a point whose butterfly effect influences as a Domino in all of them.Outstanding players not only in its interpretation, but in his characterization, Brad Pit with those wrinkles of father and husband, tired or the real Adriana Barraza (Amores Perros) as a nanny. The truth is that you it can not put no but (although Gael García, interpreted likewise).This director like me, because it is faithful to the actors who have helped him get the triumph. Hovers them again and this time accompanied by names stellar as Brad Pitt and Cate Blanchet (beautiful).Perhaps someone rate the movie as slow pace, but it is not, we must think that this story with a faster pace would be hasty.As a novelty, Alexander us discover a new Muse for Hollywood "Rinko Kikuchi (Japan 1981)" to which we have previously seen in "69", the rest of his filmography is from Japanese, but has enough films in his credit and announcement that will give much to talk about in the Hollywood universe. For the confused, this is the actress who plays the teenage sordomuda Japonesa.El final message of Babel is an appeal to the compression. The importance of paying attention to what others have to say. To make a better world through words, our words and the words of each other in perfect harmony.A highly recommended film and a fantastic farewell for 2006.</body>
</review>
