<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Zathura" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Allsburg knows the small gap between the game's fiction</summary>
	<body>Chris van Allsburg already created another story from a game titled Jumanji, very similar to this. Also is the creator of Polar express, that I do not I liked nothing. Jon Favreau is the director of Elf. And the screenwriter David Koepp is the most solvent stocks. He worked in Jurassic Park and in several of De Palma as Snake Eyes, caught up by his past or mission Imposible.Dos children from 6 to 10 years stay alone at home, under the tutelage of a teenage sister. The smallest is an age-old game of Tin that works with a wrench to give rope and two spacecraft that compete to reach the goal. When you start the game its home is transferred to outer space. They don't want to keep playing because the evidence of the boxes put at risk their lives. But they have to move, they want the game to end. What most strikes me from this film is as confirmed by each of the rules that Huizinga found to define a game. But as each one of these rules is equally applicable to the game and fiction. The film starts with the daily life of the two brothers. The largest despises the small and beats all. The small hides in the dumbwaiter when he feels bad. When they begin the game the two are transferred to another space. It is playful space the viewer knows to perfection. Knows what is, knows that the two children are in danger. Those who do not know how to play, nor what the rules are children. This is the strong point of the film. The viewer anticipates things and wants to still the lucky ship, children are entertained in children's quarrels.The older sister is passed half criogenizada film and the other half sleeping. I wonder he paints. On the other hand the astronaut gives them the best lesson of history. Van Allsburg knows the small gap between the game of fiction. The game contains in itself, the fiction teaches us to know us.</body>
</review>
