<review author="Caruco" title="Luces al atardecer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Rarely a makeshift vase with Rose had been so melancholy or the smoke of a cigarette so eloquently: minimum resources, maximum expressiveness.</summary>
	<body>The best photography, is to close the year 2006, of the new film by the Finnish sinpar Aki Kaurismäki. It is both technically and for its content. By its chromaticism of saturated colors, fascinating!, in a design that combines hypnotic way; and by its decor, attentive both to what is happening in the frame as to what is outside, and always at the service of its history.When night comes, Helsinki lights begin to illuminate, and in the urban space, cold, almost desert, also begins to take its first steps the persevering main character, Koistinen (Janne Hyytïainen), a watchman of security which, day to day, also must drag behind him with three of their curses: his solitude, the impossible dreams and the fact that seems to attract only the contempt or indifference of all who surround him.Ice cream outside, burning inside.Koistinen is a loser with a capital, a bug that is rare in the eyes of others without any reason. One of his superiors, even though that has been years in the service, is still unable to remember his name, the ringleader of the seguratas group is mania, and Koistinen is the kind capable of reaching a bar to flirt and achieve, in record time, a blonde to separate him or that, to cornering, give with a smack in the face to open the door of the services.It is impressive the amount of close-ups of characters who look to him with disdain, as well as the number of hits this resigned autobiographical must fit with stoic rigidity, but that he will be leaving proof of honesty and idealism of his spirit.And more amazing is still asistitir to this recital of absolutely hieratic, impassive performances. The actors are as deadpan statuary. They can feel fear, hatred, anger or love, without his face inmute in the slightest. When they speak, sparing in words, is to go straight to the grain will contrast the Nordic with, for example, the Latins, as given the excesses! Do Kaurismäki? forever?.Do do do do images cobrán life to the sound of the voice of Carlos Gardel and "Return" and will be closed to the beat of another tango, "El día que me quieras", having gone to pure cinema is melodrama, comedy and? noir?, with a? femme fatale? blonde, Mirja (Maria Järvenhelmi), the mistress of a gangster; and another brunette, Aila (Maria Heiskanen), shaped from selling sausages and perhaps the only light of hope.Do with the? plus? added that it possesses extraordinary moments. Plenty to discover each one, but it is impossible to not highlight two scenes? off field?, the from the beating received by trying to help a dog; and the ellipsis that is generated to be an empty armchair, when the explosive Mirja gets up to go to the sexual call of his Machiavellian lover. To me like her would place "A man without a past", after the great or very good "lives of bohemia" and "The girl in the factory of matches"; but the same level of "Passing clouds". With all share that attraction to beings who live with their pain and quiet solitude. And a mise en scene that leaves us speechless. Rarely a makeshift vase with Rose had been so melancholy or the smoke of a cigarette so eloquently: minimum resources, maximum expressiveness. And your footage even reaches the hour and a quarter.</body>
</review>
