<review author="Berto" title="Candida" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie for a laugh us and as not to cast any it tears, this woman's life has not been a bed of roses, but it is worth going to see.</summary>
	<body>The history of Candida could be any woman wrestler that life has given countless clubs and dislikes, who has been compelled to move forward by his sons, a struggle for survival.The film tells the life of Candida and their children, a mug, a misguided daughter, a drug addict and a schizophrenic, four jewels will, but she always gives the face by them and tries to help them until the end. This film reflects the life of a slum of Madrid and of the typical building "officially protected" as the protagonist tells us, we must highlight the performance of Candida, for my splendid, while almost no it can read or write, showing, as he has done throughout his life, that, with effort, everything is possible. The cast is headed by the protagonist Candida Villar which embodies if same, for my does a great job and also had to make a big effort to learn scripts. Then this Raúl Peña which gives life to the Candida, Javi, drug addict son whose goal in life is to be a singer, but the drug is always in the middle. This series as A step forward or SMS, actor on the small screen dares in this film with a difficult to interpret as the politoxicomano role.Another of the protagonists is George Bosh, giving life, in a way different to the reality, to William Fresser. Paul, Jorge Bosh, it is a news presenter who has the good fortune to find in his life with Candida, which makes him see the small things in life. Finally I must mention the characters where Candida will clean, the owners of these homes; to the marquises, the doorman of the building or the writer, giving the film more touches of humor. To highlight the soundtrack, because both choose to start and finish a song performed by David Broza and the great Jorge Drexler on the little things, those that Candida is only to see the people.Only say that it is a film for a laugh us and as not to cast any it tears, that this woman's life has not been a bed of roses, but it deserves going to see her.</body>
</review>
