<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El pisito" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The pisito tells a true story of a man who consented to marry the old that realquilaba the fourth in order to inherit the floor and so the dream Golden (institutional) marry his girlfriend of a lifetime. Cinematography adult, free of clichés.</summary>
	<body>The dreadful darkness of the Spain of the Chilblains and coffee with hunger Azcona and Ferreri reflected in the pisito appears in the light of the now a costumbrista, picturesque portrait, a variegated novelón of the life of our ancestors has no validity in these new times, but currently us denies as he wants and the Rotary information agencies vomit titualres that could be attributed, without any effort, to the Spain of the post-war.What makes Azcona as nobody has done in the Spanish film is writing with the nasty in the tip of the pen or the keys of the Underwood heavy then. Azcona moves away from the topical landscaping of exaltation of military and patriotic it was boring and cinema drowned to make destornillantes, lyrical and beautiful arguments in his stark vision of poverty of man and popular consent of a moral and economic hardship that rambling that Valle-Inclán, a few years earlier, baptized as Esperpento.La the pisitio dissent comes here: open channel (with vitriol, fine viciously occasionally) monotone contemplation to the Spanish of a foot was its national navel. Everything will crumble with the classical prose of the sainete and between joke and joke a bloody puyazo to the censor, i.e., to the consciousness of a country coming out as it could in a war and was left to cajole by a flamenco show rich and lively, anthological manifestation of our homeland culture strain Azcona and simpar icon of everything that we thought beyond the Pyrenees. Berlanga, Bardem, Neville (in their own way) and Ferreri formed a film adult, free of clichés and fully exportable in the manner of Italian neorealism was three quarters of the same but with a Pleiad nourished of dissidents of the regime of artists concerned about the policy and that they saw in the cinema (we say in art) ideal for venting a little vehicle and, of road, give food for thought (that said my grandmother) to any citizen accomplice in history.The pisito tells a true story of a man who consented to marry the old that realquilaba the fourth in order to inherit the floor and so the dream Golden (institutional) marry his girlfriend of a lifetime. Mode 13, Rue of barnacle, exemplary comic in all aspects, Ferreri opens your camera to many characters: not allowed to carry by the dramatic skills of Rodolfo, novio-esposo - widower added formidably interprets a never well weighted José Luis López Vázquez. What makes Ferreri is giving us a huge additional information at every level: isn't one thing but they are several and they all have readings which affect the main, to put it in some way. Ferreri flees the close-ups and work wonders when, mudamente almost, plant camera in the center of the narrative action and leaves the characters go trampling, occupying the space, creating a rich choral representation which then has been triumphantly copied by other directors to demonstrate, as Ferreri, the thick interweaving of several frames that are juxtaposed without objectto create the unique plot that we believe to be seeing.I am now thinking of Woody Allen, but that is going very by the branches.Azcona, who then made (there goes) El cochecito, the executioner, Plácido, cousin Angélica, the national shotgun, the girl of your dreams, Belle Epoque, the tongue of the butterflies and Ay, Carmela, who remember, some I've forgotten, is the master of the estrangement: his characters populate the lines of his works and there is no sign which can be understood as author's mark: Azcona is limited to plant his universe of middle class, their neighbors staircases, and accelerate, as if it were a wrist watch, the ancient mechanisms of the comedy of kid humor, that is true, perhaps the most serious.The idiosyncrasies of the Spanish people of the time (already seen with a remoteness) is not in the translation of some social references: Ferreri and Azcona go further and burrow in where it hurts most biempensante class and detentadora of power. Do hilarity of the death, of marriage. Evidenced with genius live in Spain between the year 40 and 70, then halt the fall, was a heroism which does not paliaban the divas of the copla and rural stories botijo and boyfriend who speaks with his girlfriend through a fence. Poverty RIDs ethics. The need for housing, never before so manifest in the film, conducive to morality ally with interest. Of as a result of this marriage was born the ingenuity, the trap, the funny picture of ugliness.</body>
</review>
