<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="María Antonieta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sofia Coppola portrays the 18th century society and the life of Marie Antoinette from a different point of view. And it does so with subtlety.</summary>
	<body>If there is someone in the world of cinema that we can say that he descended from a family with tradition, this is Sophia Coppola. Daughter of the Union between Eleanor Coppola and famed director Francis Ford Coppola, Sofia is the clearest demonstration that can be a great figure daughter and have a talent, the less, similar to that which comes from. It is true that the identity of his parents and his family (the infamous Nicolas Cage is his cousin) may have paved you the way, but there is no doubt that this girl has an innate talent for the interpretation and, above all, for the address. Sofia Coppola, who like curious started film being the baby that appears in the Godfather (directed by his father in 1972), shows labour to work that deserves a place among the great, and is increasingly closer make Francis Ford is known for being the father of Sofia Coppola, and not Sophia the daughter of Francis. Obviously, the film tells the story of Marie Antoinette, who with only fourteen years was betrothed to the future King Louis XVI, in a marriage that would be carried out when she was nineteen years. This film aims to show the most human part of a woman that the story has been portrayed as a quasi mythical being, and do it with an own sensitivity of female, but at the same time without losing the perspective of an undeniable historical reality. Its performers reach a great level, aided no doubt by the excellent leadership that exploits to the maximum the great script of the own Coppola. Ultimately, an innovative vision of an historical epoch that is sure will not leave indifferent to almost no one, and will wake up the reactions, favorable or contrary of the majority of fans to the cinema or the modern history of our continent.</body>
</review>
