<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Eastwood is halfway between the masterpiece that has tried to shoot and the message</summary>
	<body>There is something in the films Eastwood to me resulta.pesado. Has happened to me with the last three: 'Mystic River' is a good movie, but I think that it is overrated; 'Million Dollar Baby' has begun to realize that smell of torpor and pretension: a duo something strange, but it has been confirmed in 'Flags of our fathers': a film made to conscience, knowing that it would be seen with magnifying glass, that would be with the complicity of much of the criticism and the public. and that has resulted a more complex film than it might seem, but also easier at the same time. And something heavy, Yes.No, I do not think that it is a contradiction: Eastwood is a large in this film. And 'Flags of our fathers' is a good movie. But their cassettes are always double-edged: the sins of the past, the importance of the future, euthanasia, and now manipulation. The American filmmaker does not stop criticizing absolutely the essential aspect of the film, perhaps for fear of indirect censorship of American society. I still do not know. But everything leads me to believe that Eastwood is halfway between the masterpiece that has tried to shoot and the message.Flags of our fathers is typical and atypical elements. Knowing that it was a battle of World War II, no one could expect less than an impressive landing on the island of Iwo Jima. Masterful, almost to the height of the Normandy in 'Saving private Ryan'. However, it is disadvantaged by the continuous flashbacks, that make the pace of the film can be somewhat irregular. The idea itself is understood, but perhaps they should not be so long or so apart.But since that I have brought to light the greatest war film of the last decade, there is something that do should be noted Eastwood: the story is more interesting than Spielberg (producer also in 'Flags of our fathers'). And what about the cast? Ryan Philippe plays, like the rest. There is no performance greatly highlighted, although to be honest, the tape is not made for the showcasing of its actors.Once again, Eastwood will take the cat to the water. Although well could have been reduced its footage, that rather than extensive becomes weary, 'Flags of our fathers' is a film that will not hardly, like. And this is already quite say.</body>
</review>
