<review author="José A. Peig" title="Babel" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>That anyone thinks that there are cinematic genius behind the crushing apparatus of images and sounds. We are once again faced with a deceptive film, uséase, films that look very good movies but which are nothing more than correct mediocrity.</summary>
	<body>"How much pain, how much misunderstanding and passivity how much there is in this global village". Thus, speaking above, can be summarized the nature, the theme and the intention of Alejandro González Iñarritu and writers in his eagerness to create a very raw drama film, with a visual Bill which refers to the documentary style and that at this point has already been exploited on several occasions and in various genres.To begin with, if you want to make a film sobre "Oh my God, how bad is the world" isn't very constructive to restrict to a realism-style camera in hand to be directly inspired by the immediate reality of the documentary. If what is give a sense of realism in order to accentuate the dramatic potential of the narrated events, well it is as dramatic and effective gadget towards, at least, a decent show. But not to lose sight of your claims of film artist faced to the very heart of our current collective tragedy: that we are part of a whole interrelated, but more isolated and destructive than ever because of the absence of a global consciousness that manage (manage is not the exact word, but we are going so understanding.) and hold this network of responsibilities between all and for all.What we are trying to say is that, undoubtedly, "Babel" is a very well-intentioned film, which puts us in the face of a collective reality raw and devastating, but is not sufficient in relation to the proposed artwork. We are talking about little imagination conceptual, structural and visual envelope behind the film story. In the visual, so we have already said, pure documentary style so the viewer can have "sense of reality", which is inherent in the story actually unnecessarily. Nor is it to spare, but that no one creates there film genius behind the crushing apparatus of images and sounds. We are once again faced with a deceptive film, uséase, films that look very good movies but which are nothing more than correct mediocrity. In the case of "Babel," it is an interesting mediocrity, admit it. Go ahead of all that a "us" we liked the movie, but in "Images and words" touched us the ordeal of being objective, so, to the cloth.The superficiality and the plain of "Babel" are obvious instantly, with a look that integrates all seen in almost three hours: a Japanese who has a daughter sordomuda (poor passes very badly, this very single, society is very superfluous, etc etc etc.) which has sold a gun to a Moroccan Hunter which in turn sells it to another villager who leaves her provided to their children which, stick a shot by accident (?), an American tourist who has two children at home that they will spend straws because they take them holiday and amid the traffic of illegal immigrants are involved in dangerous tribulations. And that is the movie.Then, in regard to structure, nor is it too strong. Good organization of the sequences, but many of them do not end to anything truly substantial. See, see how the story of the Mexican lost in the desert and the type that is the flight ends leaving two children homeless. That it was not missing anything else?. Maybe, but it remains topical and insubstantial. The resolution of situations in a great movie (with a good dash of base) are never left halfway or finish as predictable way. Another thing is how the story of the japonesita and dad, ends that final hug Yes opens a subtle channel of suggestions, and is of the few moments in which one has the feeling of watching film. And the resolution of the story of the couple of Americans in Marruecos.prrrrrrrrfffffffffff. Yes, worth, the final hue of Brad Pit makes sense, but for that they don't need 145 minutes, that already I am nine in TVE news.Well, from that thread of connection between stories, an idea clear, Mannerist, topical will deploy. Full of feeling and pain by how are things, but his ability to dissect the complex and powerful reality facing the, it is null. And it aims to, there is the problem. If you want to express how bad that goes the world, just a single story that represents the universal problems. Mr González Iñarritu, to build a history of histories, a mystical vision of the global problem, is deflected onto one greater claim. This claim requires more than a succession of passages in which the Viewer cannot otherwise go jumping from one to another with the unique stunt that "there is a link between all of them".That something else had to leave the conceptual and visual creativity of the filmmaker, is not our task to find it, but will that, intuitively, any serious analyst discover that this film is hollow from the moment in which we deal with your "base text" and its substantive issues. The "superficial text", no doubt, has an overwhelming performance, rhythm not lapses ever and, at times, reach a subtle look of the intricate relationships between minds, cultures and spaces to the length and breadth of this unfortunate human globe. But only at times.From there, the only thing we have is an extensive video about people of diverse latitudes and cultures to which they happen a number of things. To end the slide show, the Viewer is left with the idea: "how screwed are and how bad we are". But, I repeat, that are now the news. What it was was put that same idea under a film treatment arising in a personal vision (genuine in art), which occurs, but at a minimum, a mere coral structure in which the facts are as simple as minimum progression (the narrated events respond to a sequence that could be summarized in a paragraph or a ten minute television documentary). I.e. Iñarritu tells me nothing that I do not know in advance, and even shows a capacity for approach me the problem from a unique perspective. And that — offer a unique perspective - is the creativity. And the film should be an act of creation, not a claim to say this or that thing about obvious issues and we know every day.Synthesizing, Babel is a significant, correct and well-intentioned production for free sentimental expression of their authors, but film, which reportedly cinema, there is very very little the justito.</body>
</review>
