<review author="El mágico" title="Firewall" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Discreet thriller that promises a lot of boot and will languish</summary>
	<body>And one day returned Harrison Ford, which is not little. He returned to the film of suspense, which historically is that has produced more regular dividends throughout his extensive career. "Firewall" is a discreet thriller that promises a lot of boot and will languish as it progresses the tape, wasting many tips of a script that promised much and only manages to sustain the tension toward the final moments of the film. Little known here, "Firewall" is directed by Richard Loncraine ("My house in Umbria", very interesting - can be seen on HBO every both — "Wimbledon" - here released in DVD and other small TV in the U.S. jobs, so far don't know whether this man will take off or dark side of the industry) and has in its cast as respectable as Paul Bettany people (here for the first time as a villain seriously)Virginia Madsen and Robert Patrick (speaking returns!). The plot of Firewall is quite predictable. Jack Stanfield (Ford, good father and honest man, in its classical position already bored) is in charge of computer security of a prestigious Bank that is about to create a fusion with another company to increase its assets. Jack has a perfect family, and will be the target of a group of extortionists with skilled computer skills who will take his family hostage pressing him to commit a crime on a large scale. To my item in your home found me quite interesting, look at the world of computer security from the inside is very didactic and access a bit the back of all this great business, and their vulnerabilities. That point is strange, because the script by Joe Forte promises much and resolves certain issues complicated (in the end, for example, the Tracker GPS which has the family dog), relatively easy dodging turns and simplifying all the time, I guess that to get the viewer average who doesn't know fund the technical language of the speaker. "Firewall" is a predictable thriller that will only meet your expectations if you're a fan of Harrison Ford or you are interested in having a superficial and film idea of how the safety devices in the banking system. Very little to justify the price of a ticket. It remains to be seen whether Ford finally dares to bring the chest of memories to his Indiana, in the light of his last performances, as you should be writing himself the script for the quarter...</body>
</review>
