<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Candida" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Candida has a natural talent and charisma wishing many stars endiosadas and drunk of a glory for himself more media than film. And Guillermo Fesser has been able to exploit that quality. Go to if did it.</summary>
	<body>Almost ten years ago now, I had the opportunity to meet personally to the components of the duo rubber foam, on the occasion of the presentation of a book on internet for clumsy when this network was incipient in Spain. Since childhood he had followed them and I had always liked his humor of cut surreal, full of wit and sarcasm, and so different from the my nearest usually by my status as proud Cadiz that exercises such.El Milagro de P. Tinto seemed like a huge breath of fresh air, by their diverse characters, bizarre scenarios and revolutionary approach. This combination of factors will confer a very special nature. The case of Candida is different. Here, Candida is the Sun around which revolves the entire film. This good woman, whose character has her own real name, dreams about having a small house in America, and thanks to their efforts of Celestite, manages to reach him. Wit based on the simplicity of the dialogues, bright at the same time that intelligible for everyone is the main feature of this film. Observe the way of function of this lady is prevalent in interest on any other aspect of the film. Single achieved what many big stars fail, she is fill the screen and make the rest of the cast and the purely cinematic issues languidezcan. And is that although it may seem exaggerated, Fesser defined perfectly to this woman, without academic training, when he said that having access to appropriate studies, surely today I would be sitting on a bench of Congress maybe isn't a masterpiece, but the pleasure of seeing a simple and endearing lady as Candida, offset by more than the almost five dollars that today I have stuck by the entrance.</body>
</review>
