<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="María Antonieta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Marie Antoinette is a blur in the hitherto flawless race of Sofia Coppola, blur that we all hope that he recovers, it is one of the most promising of his generation filmmakers.</summary>
	<body>There are many people who believe that if you have a good last name he can succeed in life, and somehow is true, since there are surnames which open doors with ease. However, it can also be a very heavy burden if the person in question has talent, and wants to demonstrate that it has more to offer the world than its name. This has happened to Sofia Coppola, daughter of major Francis Ford Coppola all of his works are examined with a magnifying glass, and not be few who try to search similarities to his father's films. After his remarkable debut with the Virgin suicides and its later Lost jewel in Translation, showed that his talent was innate and won the right to let people think about her as "the daughter of".For his third feature film, Sofia Coppola takes film once more the life of Marie Antoinette (Kirsten Dunst), the last Queen of France, executed on the guillotine during the revolution. It is not a current portrait that shows the character from another angle, from the inside of their palatial and festive world. Trying to humanize and justify a character demonising historically by its excesses and scandals is actually very risky, and unfortunately the film deteriorates markedly. Marie Antoinette is the story of a capricious, inconstant, insecure and unconscious young woman, whom the Director to justify showing the suffering of his early life at the Court of Versailles. Surprisingly, his trajector, Sofia Coppola to make a story so pink and somewhat caramel like this. Although it sounds opportunistic, one must admit that to portray a historical character as important as Marie Antoinette, must be widely show the reality in which they lived (and not only with a map of Kirsten Dunst in the balcony of Versailles showing his solitude, or other leaning against an enraged crowd) and its socio-historical context. A point in favor of the tape is being filmed in the same palaces of Versailles, although it must be admitted that Sofia Coppola does not possess the visual power master Visconti had similar questions. The pace of the film is quite slow, and becomes especially heavy in the sequences in which scarce dialogues. Kirsten Dunst, by their stop, fulfills the role of teen Queen who never left the age of Turkey.Marie Antoinette is a blur in the hitherto flawless race of Sofia Coppola, blur that we all hope that he recovers, it is one of the most promising of his generation filmmakers.</body>
</review>
