<review author="Ana" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The irony is the weapon of the losers and this group of losers this very well armed.</summary>
	<body>The irony is the weapon of the losers and this group of losers this very well armed. Little Miss Sunshine is endearing as Happiness [Solonz] is happy. The plot of this film is very simple, a road movie. The characters travel by road to Redondo Beach, California to encourage Olive participate in a beauty contest for girls. But that is not what it is. It's the characters who are all complex and more real than rare. Although they are quite rare and fall a little wrong. Above all the frustrated optimist [Greg Kinnear].Although fall ill it is much better to shame. And do laugh more, as the academic gay expert in Proust [Steve Carell] that fails the success as suicide. And of course the grandfather who sniffed heroin and loves pornography. He says above all obscenities, but also tells her granddaughter of seven years: "I'm madly in love with you, and it is not by your intelligence or by your personality;" "it is because you are beautiful inside and out."It is brave to make a movie with characters that I am not exactly good and they have few noble qualities. It's refreshing in a world in which we all be ever more equal and politically correct. A world that seems increasingly a beauty contest after another. Where have we forgotten to ask what is really beautiful, instead of leaving us to feed plastic aesthetics of advertising. This film is a call to say fuck? em and return to see the world through our own eyes.And there they go, in a yellow VW van that may seem a bit unreal, as if only they had chosen to be rare, but after meeting the Hoovers I think that this is the car they have, the other is a miata. They are not randomly selected geeks details, they arrive to talk about real life.In the end the strangest thing is what is real. Both girls involved in the beauty contest as their mothers are not actresses but beauty contests participants appearing in the film of her own volition. By which you might say that is a horror film, for me it is a comedy-drama (which is how conceived it the screenwriter) but also could say that it is a drama that makes people laugh (which is more the idea of managers).</body>
</review>
