<review author="Puspus" title="El perfume" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The true joy of the film lies in enjoying the Tykwer estilazo behind the camera. Do do these finest plans, this superb recreation of the time, these images that almost up? smell?...</summary>
	<body>Years ago I knew nothing about one of my directors fetish, German Tom Tykwer. For too long this gentleman, responsible of "Run, Lola, run" and the fascinating "the Princess and the Warrior", presented his films at various European festivals without any national distributor dared to a acquire their rights and release them in Spain. They should be too busy funding masterpieces such as "Since that dawns fancy" or "GAL". The case is that this drought is over (and I predict that you forever) with "El Perfume", brilliant adaptation of the best-seller of Patrick Süskind and definitive consecration of Tykwer as "European reference author". "The Perfume" tells the fascinating story of Jean Baptiste Grenouille, a man of exceptional smell and obsessive goals in the middle of the 18th century France. How were its squalid origins and how, thanks to his nose, he was escaping progressively, while never being a dangerous misfit, a poignant mutant to the eternal quest for affection. Unknown Ben Whishaw embodies this character with unnerving conviction. The entire film is based on his narrow shoulders and uncle supports the weight without the least hint of exhaustion. Almost the same as the great Dustin Hoffman, which endorses the perfumer Baldini and dispatched the order with a naturalness that acompleja. However, for me, the true joy of the film lies in enjoying the Tykwer estilazo behind the camera. These finest plans, this superb recreation of the time, these images that almost to "smell". To me this guy I love. What can I do. By that even forgive him that controversial end, much derided by all, where some levels fall unambiguously into the most absolute of the ridiculous. The film is a sad and beautiful tale. A story about loneliness, rejection, and unrequited love. A tale that must end as such. I understand it as well. Although it is true its farcical tone disconnect of the seriousness of the whole.</body>
</review>
