<review author="Rafa Marin" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite some puzzling initial point and some blow with the flash forwards and flashbacks that are something boring, the film is gaining strength and has a masterful last third.</summary>
	<body>Him does not fail the pulse to the old Clint, but perhaps we are spoiled and we ask that each film is overcome himself. After a brilliant acting career where he was happily accused of reactionary and quasi-fascist, and a directorial career which already promised interesting works in his first chills at night, the old and wise Eastwood is unanimously accepted as the last great classic live enjoying, despite its already advanced age, the privilege to continue leading and directing very well. However, in this film have won him the hand three factors: first, the aesthetics of the war, how the war was filmed and how color war, which has an inescapable debt, as I imagine her will in the future all war films, with the marvelous opening sequence of saving private Ryan by Steven Spielbergproducer of this flags of our fathers, and, it seems, the director who was going to bring it to fruition in the first instance. The second factor is that the structure narrative, jumps in time and space, the desire to do almost documentary film (and there is no more to see actual photographs of the capture of Iwo Jima and the amazing resemblance of actors with the soldiers of truth that interpret, and MIME of the Mise en scène, from the color of the Earth to the details of bandages)(, misconception, even dogs) almost could have given more court and best narrative expressiveness in a television miniseries, as we saw, and we saw very well, in Band of Brothers. The third factor is that, like good film of war, the characters are confused, tries all stained and dirty and injured, all almost adolescent and the script to make a tribute to the six soldiers who raised the historical flag, twice, and only you can do it with three of them, the survivors, at the end only show some interest in the figure of the Indian soldier Ira Hayesthat had already been the subject of a biopic starring Tony Curtis, the sixth hero, none other than in 1961. That the performance of any of the three central characters is outstanding remains enough merits to the film. However, despite some puzzling initial point and some blow with the flash forwards and flashbacks that are something boring, the film is gaining strength and has a masterful last third. Eastwood spared no scenes of hardness, but not on the battlefield (do will be we all too accustomed to the gore?), but in scenes of everyday life: the family of the true soldier hoisted the flag and is ignored in perpetuity in the photo and the tributes; the encounter with another mother and crying of the Indian in her arms; latent racism (at that time the Indians even had the right to vote) and the alcohol as a remedy; and, above all, once finished the war, return to the mediocrity of life for some characters that never were heroes and have to suffer in meat ignorance and alienation. As already without forgiveness, neither the press nor the politicians go too well standing in the eyes of Eastwood. As part of a diptych which will be complemented in a few months with letters from Iwo Jima, shot in Japanese and from Japanese side, is curious here barely see the enemy, always hidden in bunkers, committed suicide in the caves or attacking at night. Perhaps you have to wait to see how the old Clint rounds out his vision of this fierce battle of history, and his version of the other no-héroes, but human beings at the end and all, who fought for the flags of other parents.</body>
</review>
