<review author="Juan Nadie" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This has not made that start, because soon we will have on our screens the other part of the story. The battle of Iwo Jima from the Japanese side. For the moment, all cry and are looking for our Iggy.</summary>
	<body>If there was a key moment in the history of Iwo Jima according to the civilian population that was in which an AP reporter took an image that he sailed around the world and, seen thousands of miles away, it was a powerful blow to the Japanese army in World War II. It was February 1944 and several American soldiers were sent to the top of Mount Suribachi, at the Centre of the island of Iwo Jima Pacific, to hoist the flag of stars and the bars. A milestone it that would trigger the euphoria after five days of arduous battle. Moments later, another group of soldiers is sent with the purpose of replacing the original flag for a spare. It is then, in which iza spare is in which Joe Rosenthal take the significant snapshot. United States needs heroes, need to know that their men are fighting for something and that image of the flag is for them a triumph over the enemy. The battle lasted one month, but that no longer mattered. The marketing was done and soldiers surviving protagonists in the picture are sent returned home to the United States. They are heroes and as such they should behave. They will help the Government to raise funds for the rest of colleagues who have stayed on the battlefield and to ensure that the army not missing neither ammunition nor resources. They have become the best claim to box. But they aren't just a product. They are men. A doctor (John 'Doc' Bradley - Ryan Phillippe), a Messenger (Rene Gagnon - Jesse Bradford) and a (Ira Hayes - Adam Beach) Indian who drag war traumas that do not leave them at any time. They are alive. Yes. But they are also victims of human barbarity. The war being persecuted. Each with a personal story. And all of them are master Clint Eastwood has decided to capture with your camera in a masterpiece.The hardest man in Hollywood who was once again demonstrates his talent behind the camera and builds a great film built on a very solid script and a tremendously successful casting. Ryan Phillippe is perhaps the main protagonist. His son will, on the death of the father, decide to investigate what happened and how marked the placement of that flag and the war to his father and his battalion companions. The image is only the present to tell the life of the protagonists, their feelings, sufferings, paths crossed and tragic end, already the most forgotten. Phillippe, the doctor who the cries of the fight and the inability to save all his companions you pursued throughout his life, gives the character the fragility and vitality necessary. Bradford, known face, portraying a young soldier with aspirations and a girlfriend addicted to fame. Adam Beach, the Indian who already starred opposite Nicolas Cage Wildtalkers, returns to appeal to his indigenous face as a symbol of identity. But only as characterization, since that is the hardest character in all and, therefore, one of the most complicated to interpret. Especially if we take into account that it must address much of the film with more alcohol that blood in the veins. They also deserve a special mention Barry Pepper (Mike Strank in the film) and James Bell, actor who rose to fame for his role as Billy Eliot and here gives life to the inseparable companion of Doc, Iggy. In addition to actions already mentioned, we must unite a great cast of side which Eastwood is able to get the best. Only have to look at the performance of Paul Walker (the undercover police to any gas). More meritorious is everything if one takes into account that, despite being a war film, it has not been necessary to Prime with bloody scenes. Although, as a good war film, one has.All this with a refined technique of flashbacks. The son of Doc is the photo and cuts in newspaper the news in a box. Then decides to start researching this chapter that his father never told her to write her. For this talk with veterans of war that tell you their vision of the protagonists. At the same time, Eastwood introduces flashbacks within flashbacks to capture the story in first person. An ingenious way to introduce all the visions resulted in flags of our fathers. Not only the technique is perfect, but that the music that accompanies it all (written by the director himself), levels of the faces and the most insignificant details rounded whole. This has not made that start, because soon we will have on our screens the other part of the story. The battle of Iwo Jima from the Japanese side. For the moment, all cry and are looking for our Iggy.</body>
</review>
