<review author="Dino" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is not worth much, but at least not ashamed as the poker of absurdities that Stallone launched after the overwhelming success of the original.</summary>
	<body>The film is home to the legends. The celluloid are born, grow, multiply with unnecessary sequels and you prequels, and if one day they die, is that they never deserved similar consideration. We see characters with which we would like to have a drink, to which we would like to get to know, and that they probably felt a special affection. For a generation, Rocky Balboa is a legend. Belatedly, for me also. And Yes, influences my particular passion for boxing and the film subgenre that has created this sport. I am of thrill me with Paul Newman in "Marked by hatred", by Robert de Niro in "Wild Bull", and even Russell Crowe in "Cinderella Man". "Nod for Robert Ryan in" The Set-Up ", of the master Robert Wise.""Rocky" (1976) us (I) touched as the typical story of a normal type of the heap by pulling little thing. It was a character who was offered a fistful of dollars so a boxing champion won three times and engordara his pride. It cost spun four consecutive sentences. He was shy, but with a clever point, more for his innocence than anything else. But above all, it rose to a ring knowing that it was going to take a beating. Gave him equal. Because in that wonderful film of John g. Avildsen, Rocky taught us that many times not importantly win in this life, but keep you standing and endure the stakes when it hits hard, let him know that you are not afraid and that shall pass over yours earlier that throw the towel. "The victory is not a title, but an emotional state.""Rocky Balboa" is a shadow of that wonder of 1976. 30 Years have passed. And the film has the same pattern that the four continuations who tried to exploit the story of unhappy that conquest glory without success. They were garbage, designed to make money with a myth, mistakenly thinking that they though the legend. Da nausea remind Rocky incorporated in the trousers with the colors of USA sticking with that meaner Russian Ivan Drago. Now, there is an old, decadent, type who lives tell war stories in his restaurant, widower, and just needs to feel alive again. The film is not worth much, but at least not ashamed as the poker of absurdities that Stallone launched after the overwhelming success of the original.This does not make you cry. Just takes you to remember when Rocky listened, in the last moments of the first film, and with the unmistakable melody of Bill Conti's background, the "ring announcer" by Victor gave Apollo Creed, but his sole concern was to embrace with the fragile Adrian, that presence lurks "Rocky Balboa" and is not anywhere. Stallone pays homage to himself, or perhaps it simply seeks to that, keep alive a legend not seeing its present, but giving reasons to recall the past. You can look for transport then the emotions his film not already raised. However, it remains within decent formally. That is the spirit of Rocky, the "Italian Colt", though it may not of his films. Long live the legend, champion.</body>
</review>
