<review author="José A. Peig" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It has everything to be misunderstood and also has everything to be a great movie. It has its flaws and may not be a round work. Above all, a classic delicacy, an honest and beautiful film.</summary>
	<body>Go film friend Clint Eastwood, one of the few and best classical announcers we are, heir of John Ford and rich baggage accumulated over decades of cinematic craftsmanship has gone. Just like Spielberg but, if anything, more brainy and forceful in addressing the major issues or North American genera. Spielberg is a master of the show in the different areas, either in a war melodrama (soldier Ryan) in a fantastic fable ("E.T"). Eastwood, moreover, is a much more mature intellectual.Go film, he said, because it tells a story which, I am afraid, bored and leave indifferent to most of the public. We are faced with a personal whim of the author, a film that have existed almost nobody would lay in lack. We are before the typical film that makes a filmmaker who already nothing cares, except his identity as the author who is involved in the history and society of his time and his ability to express whatever he pleases.The story is not original, the style is unmistakable. I.e., although it treads ground hipermegatrillado, Eastwood makes this sensitive and evocative tribute to the "Heroes" of the second World War (in reality, human beings of the myths of the war victims) one of his most personal films, endorses this story based on an exquisite taste for narrating and make us reflect on issues concerning the feeling and the collective symbols of an eraof which it becomes the identity and current pride of American society. On the one hand, in the other channel returns to delve into the horror of the war, and here the novelty comes from the hand of a montage that takes us to a journey in circle from the most elementary facts until a final moral quite predictable, but by no means stops working. Veamos.no is a war film, is an intimate look that emphasizes the collective pain of the men and women who participated in the war and suffered its consequences directly or indirectly. And above all it emphasizes the importance of the patriotic symbols of collective representations that are the fruit of a hope or a need to justify as a hegemonic nation.But do not fall into the same error: "Flags of our fathers" is not a film patriotic or nativist. If someone doubt you, consult the dictionary to see what meaning has the word "pamphlet". We have already said that symbols and patriotic imagery are the true protagonists of the last film of Eastwood, but are not used as an instrument of propaganda, but that serve as key pieces to develop a very concrete idea, idea that comes with a considerable burden sharp and provocative.The film does not walk with contemplations and shows us the need for myths and heroes in war times. The need to identify with a flag, with an army representative and defender of the ideals system of life, to reaffirm with a uniform and democracy acts by a group of boys who, much to his regret, makes them prisoners of this network of myths and symbols. Victims, nothing less, the screeching, despair, manipulation and the hypocrisy of society which lost to his friends on the battlefield, what really mattered to them. It is particularly dramatic for the Indian character, for who his involuntary heroic corset will be the total loss of identity and meaning to their lives, grabbing ultimately to the proclamation of the truth, the true heroes that nobody has known know or never. (This is an issue, by the way, very typical of John Ford). You have to see how he ends his errabunda crusade along highways and deserts.I.e., Eastwood speaks of symbols and beliefs of the motherland, but tried and tested under a strong critical look and bitter, as wanting to rid of this collective drunkenness that he was part from its position of industrial Narrator. The film, therefore, is sincere and deeply crepuscular and elegiac, combat myths and the ghosts that poisoned the minds of the citizens helpless before the harshness of events, which always seeks a way of escape to the myth. And let us not forget that when the myths go as timely and local to the universal, has been a first step towards fascist totalitarianism. And ojito to the three central characters, that each of them is representing three different prisms through which is is weaving the criticism and bitter look: all three are victims of an incipient fascism, they themselves are the excuse from which manufacture the large lies that form a poisonous myth for minds. Falsehoods (heroes of the fatherland, forgers and protectors of the democracies) which in the future may be used to idealize and justify the wars and invasions.Eastwood - As Spielberg in "Saving private Ryan", that discussed another day - the poison that can convert these falsehoods, but humanity hidden and violated after the uniform and undergo under the propaganda apparatus is not interested. And expresses it in a direct, simple and beautiful at the past levels of the film: a group of boys, stripped of their armor of war - abandoned in the sand of the beach of Iwo Jima - who, for a few moments, are preparing to enjoy the game, splash in the water, the laughter shared with colleagues and amigos.lo a lot toin spite of everything, remains of humanity. And that is the moral; the truth over lies, the person real and vulnerable over the armor and idealized hero, the intimate and sincere identity above all the flags and the homelands. Some unwary are already saying is a film nativist and simplistic, but is a lesson of humanity in which the issues and the patriotic iconography is the initial excuse, the starting point of a race to the discovery of truth, at the same time that are putting in evidence the burdens that hinder the best of life and of the human being.On this last, should emphasize the magnificent structure, quite unique in addition. It is not a linear narrative, but circular. Already been said; Eastwood proposes a journey of discovery, and this route extends in a narrative that is including new information and expand the full spectrum of narrated experience. I.e., are several concentric circles that extend the perspective as it is advancing the story: from the beginning to the purest style of the war classic film, then shades are introduced as we discover the circumstances, feelings and thoughts of the characters (a smaller circle item is a larger, one covering more information, and thus the story is revealing) until the final resolution, the largest circle that integrates and includes all previous development, in a magnificent setting of the meaning and the final message.In conclusion, a film that has everything to be misunderstood and also has everything to be a great movie. It has its flaws and may not be a round work: excessive length and very well defined characters but do not have the depth and freshness that would have been able to have. Above all, a classic delicacy, an honest and beautiful film that leaves after if a great thematic complexity subjected to an exhibition so fluid that the confused them will be too simple.</body>
</review>
