<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Hard candy" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This artifact of macabre entertainment not disappoint anyone with a Meridian interest by see where will new intellectual cinema, author</summary>
	<body>Films on pedophiles not abound: is a matter of thorny treatment that often little interest among the public. The merit of Hard candy is take an argument about moral anomaly that repugnant to who has well dressed the roof with traces of highly successful thriller halfway between the thesis of the cinema of trials and the Freudian drama.Throughout the film rests on two actors and barely out of the living room of a House does that everything is valued more strongly because has (also) the character amateur (in the sense of first-time) director David Slade, who comes from the video and leaves his clipero label in many plans and references to pop icons to the mtv (Goldfrapp). The film has an unpleasant time: solve it requires a point of effort, but that value plus then brings a reward, albeit in its resolution, in my opinion, imperfect, but acceptable. It was difficult to complete with verve, successfully, an argument so excellently done.Raw milk in abundance (the scene of the destesticulización, said crudely), is based on the story of a hard candy (Internet is named girls made pass for females to hold chats with adults), a cultured and malevolent, gut absolutely Machiavellian extremes to its particular vendetta against the slob photographer who seeks and which remains. A murder of a girl as a backdrop and a nutritional dose of dialogs to clarify / darken the reasons of amorality of paedophilia cover footage without the friendly viewer aware at any time that is attending a thriller as a cathedral, oddly at times a film of trials (the girl Hayley is the Prosecutor and the photographer Jeff is the pathetic accused) or a theatre play hardcore and edgy.Allowed to lead by byways then somewhat weak in credibility with the story of a bride who the photographer was, but anyway, isn't thing (of course) of uncovering the Pandora of this artifact of macabre entertainment that does not disappoint anyone with a Meridian interest by see where will new intellectual cinema, copyright (we can call it that).</body>
</review>
