<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Cinderella Man" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Manichean tape and thousand times viewed</summary>
	<body>Cinderella Man is like eating a Whopper with cheese. One knows exactly what is going to eat. Who know the bread, the meat, and all the prefabricated ingredients. You know what is going to know every bite.We find ourselves with a film that respects step by step and academicism the a, b, c of Hollywood cinema. There is one moment that actually surprised or escape parameters merely standard. A bad, very bad, a good very good that will represent and will carry the alleged fighting spirit required to embody again an inexhaustible wrestler to achieve the American dream.The ingredients are not included nor mixed with the intention of innovate nor please directly to the public tanning or demanding, but to cover the expectations desired by those who ultimately sharing the Oscars. Thus repeats the formula of "Seabiscuit" (repeating and copying so its virtues and defects), but this time without horse race and the scene of the great American economic depression. Boxing as the main theme to the "Rocky" and "One Million Dollar Baby", where returns to join the director and protagonist of "A beautiful mind". It is not that I do not like the Whopper with cheese, to the you upside down, but it is that I I eat them with such gusto with both boredom and the pleasure lasts only vaguely until the fourth bite. Russel Crowe acts very well, without leaving not what we are accustomed, which is already fairly. Very remarkable scene in which, descending to hell, has to go begging to the Federation that, in better times, had been part being a renowned Boxer.Though Russel Crowe not I can remove the head a film former that I recommend and where this really incredible, "Break Stomper" (1992). Renée Zellweger, therefore, finally, his face always with that so retorcidito lip. She does more or less what we are accustomed, even though it is not of my devotion and I believe that the couple does not work at all.I liked much Paul Giamatti, who outboard his histrionic supporting role.The setting, on the other hand, this very successful, as you might expect from a million dollar production of the Universal. Although one does not end to believe quite some dramatic excesses and we are faced with situations and dialogues dulzones and wrapped on clichés of those that only Americans are allowed to make over and over again. Ron Howard, who is usually empachar in his films with dulce de leche with sugar added and cream extra, here performs a right direction and get one film more than correct about courage and overcoming, with some moments of great cinema. The boxing scenes are really exciting, even already always knowing what will be the result. You know, a little and you have fun playing only join the Monopoli.</body>
</review>
