<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Babel" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For who see without any kind of prejudice, it will be a wonder. But I'm staying with the feeling that this time has not been so great with Amores Perros and 21 grams.</summary>
	<body>There are films that, even knowing that they are good, do not end you convince. Do not know sometimes why, others are so achacas to other externos.y factors others by expectations. With Babel has happened to me this same: many sense of expectancy that has not been accomplished. This is in the three films of the great tandem Iñárritu and Arriaga, the worst. However, the film is good, and for who see without any kind of prejudice, it will be a wonder.The end of this particular and peculiar vital connections trilogy focuses on the same: linkages between such different lives. Four stories intertwined in the most simple way (at least taking into account what has accustomed us this Mexican Duo), addressing topics as profound as cultural diversity and human language. I say simple because I know that it could get you more out of everything: four stories separately gave to much more, the relationship between them unconvincing and it seems that finally they are incomplete.I must repeat that Babel is a good movie. But room for improvement. He has stellar moments, thanks in part to the script, the direction, and the great division which has the tape: shootout between the police and the Moroccan family; a good Pitt helping a desaprovechada Blanchett to urinate; Rinko Kikuchi (a revelation) naked before the police and a splendid Adriana Barraza trying to save the children of Pitt on the night of the Mexican desert.And although I know very well that is much better than the average films in 2006, can not so much appreciate its merit. I'm staying with the feeling that this time has not been so great with Amores Perros and 21 grams. And it is a pity, because the duo will not work together more.</body>
</review>
