<review author="José A. Peig" title="Mulholland drive" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lynch builds its oneiric universe not capricious manner, but very playful, perhaps too much and often gives the impression of being a creation improvised intuitive impulses, which not always acertarán to give a consistent meaning to the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>To tackle well the value of cinema in its multiple manifestations must take into account that it offers rates and very diverse styles, degrees, areas, to try to define it accurately, in which the type or level of demands presented a huge variety. This so pedantic way to kick off the commentary is an attempt to be more just to qualify a film as "Mulholland drive", because, in one direction or another, it is very easy to fall into the superficiality and hasty conclusion. There are therefore areas: there is a film made to entertain, a film to tell to the conventional mode, a symbolic film, metaphorical movies, movies of social criticism or exposure of thesis and/or ideas of anthropological content, etc, etc, etc, etc. David Lynch likes to do a bit of everything, mezcladito and scrambled so that it is not palatable to all the stomachs. But in this notebook are not valued or are judged the tastes and the stomachs, but raw art, to understand us, much to our regret the same art is subject to rules of industry. First and foremost, "Mulholland drive" is intuitive film which refers and affect your intuitive ability of the Viewer. It is a type of film in which which looks at the screen has an active role in the construction of the meaning, causes and effects of the narrated history, because its creator leaves a margin of undefined and ambiguity that the viewer imagine the rest. This is achieved through the use of intentional loose and with a sense of narrative based on the symbolic, and the symbol is always a representation of another thing to the same symbol. All this implies that, in many cases, it requires the viewer more than what can cover, because not all have the same intuitive sensitivity or the same cultural formation. But, again, the film critic is not judging the tastes and sensibilities, but to analyze and verify Lynch to build a symbolic structure vertebrado in a specific narrative, with the consequent artistic value. And the Parrot must be to filmmakers as Lynch, who like a lot of smart people go. Here, the critic has to be increadibly cunning. First of all, descabecemos topics and errors. There is the quite widespread belief that drew Lynch as a filmmaker "incomprehensible", "complex", "tight", "unclassifiable", adding to the Repertoire expressions of the type of "nor he himself knows what will be his films", "does not tell a story, but improvises without ton or they are" and the like. But all this is an error and, in relation to the film before us, when one says that is complicated or complex or even its same creator understood, all that is showing is that he has not understood and, above all, that it has not been able to enter in the ambiguous game in which only exists a weapon with which to succeed: the creative intuition, in parallel with the process of creating its author. In an attempt to synthesize the idea, say that Lynch is very simple and concrete in the history tells us, but very twisted in the way to deal with it, extend it, extend it beyond the immediate. Replace "twisted" with creative, intuitive, poetic, symbolic, psychoanalytic or artistic. Lynch tells us a very specific and simple story in its most obvious and visible aspects, but avoids the conventional narrative structure to give free rein to their creativity and ability to suggest things without saying them explicitly. And in art it is not essential that the poet understands each of his poems. Therefore, to say that the film is not good because the author does not understand such or which aspect shows mental narrowness and the flat encephalogram that some have posted on the brains. Both "Mulholland drive" as "Blue Velvet" tell a story very easy and simple. The way of narrating - through use of symbols and a mise en scene which refers to the dream world - is giving them a strange singularity that breaks the schemes of many viewers. Let's see. The story: "Mulholland drive" tells the story of a young aspiring actress who becomes involved in a dark fabric around an amnesiac girl's dark past and a band of mafiosi involved in the film industry. From a fairly simple premise, Lynch made up a story that includes a lesbian love story, a sour and sarcastic look at senior executives and promoters of the industry of hollywood and a hidden subplot which holds in the presence of esoteric elements: a mysterious blue key which opens a blue box, a being of terrifying aspect hidden in a dirty corneran elderly couple and the enigmatic "cowboy". At a given moment - after a visit to the theatre where we look at the performance of "la llorona" - the "cowboy" (character of symbolic character who, apparently, knows and holds all the enigmas of the plot) enters the room where the body of Diana is and tells him that "it is time to wake up". Awakening from the dream. Diane is the counterpart of Betty and Betty is the dream that compensates the frustration of a bitter reality that will take Diane to suicide. We must focus on the roles and dramatic place of the characters suffer a reverse translation from the moment that Diane is awoken by the cowboy. Am not going to elaborate because it is not necessary (and the attentive Viewer will see it easily) but for example see as the film director in the world of Betty was victim of disloyalty and humiliation in the world of Diane (again, the counterpart of Betty) that same character is who it is birlando the bride to her. Camila captures all the attention, success, and fame in the world of Betty (under the name of Rita) it was a you disoriented and victim of a conspiracy for another Camila. I.e., there is a central character who is Betty/Diane (Naomi Watts), on which are built two universes of facts and opposite meanings, but complement, the universe that happens prior to the awakening of Diane is, say so, a "revenge" to everything us shown from that point onwards footage. As we see, what makes Lynch is to narrate a reverse structure, making it difficult how easy. If the film began with the death of Diane after hiring the services of a bully to avenge his beloved Camila, would be much more easy guess that the narrative below is a reflection of frustrated hopes and dreams. But if Diane dies at the end, who dreams in reality?. And hence this key, and it is a constant of the cinema of David Lynch. Everything we see in the film is part of a dream with two different levels. A circular dream that extends according to the data provided in the visual representation, most intuition of the spectator who enters a maze game, either for losing in the enigma or to try to give a more or less logical way to seemingly unrelated aspects. Where it begins and ends the film really?. Betty is a dream of Diane or is Diane Betty nightmarish?. Blue key and the box symbolize the door between the two levels or worlds. Be terrifying aspect seems to hold the magic that makes possible the translation. The cowboy is the gaze cold and distant from the diosecillo which directs and is aware of everything that is happening. In the dream world, "Mulholland drive" is an intentional chaos that does not need a logic to justify himself as film creation. Therefore not worth saying that it is a failed film because it has too many loose ends and not explained aspects. Summing up: history of lesbian love, plot of suspense with mobsters and people of the cinema as an excuse to develop a sour view of high society Hollywood and symbolic elements that provide the backbone as a whole towards oneiric treatment, in such a way that everything is subject to this fascination by the disturbing and "vaporous" nature of dreams. Now however, this mixture does packing?. Is it lawful to mix made real and subject to the logic of the State of vigil within elements of the way in which does it?. For example, the death of Diane (one of the last and most disturbing sequences of the film): the "real" fact is the suicide with firearm, which appears next to an onírico-simbólico element; the elderly couple. If we look at the laws implied in the very nature of the film, it is lawful because in the first scenes that same elderly couple already played a symbolic but in a reverse role. There is a coherent continuum, in which each piece plays its role. With these examples, I do notice as Lynch builds its oneiric universe not capricious manner, but very playful, perhaps too much and often gives the impression of being a creation improvised intuitive impulses, which not always acertarán to give a consistent meaning to the Viewer. But the same Viewer is who must do the rest of the work, requiring the movie, which raises it to category of artwork if we attend their exclusive nature arising from a mind of singular creativity. As the work of art lies in short, in the infinity of its meaning, as it extends to the infinite intuition of the Viewer. The complicated nature of "Mulholland drive" is not history that counts, but the structure and the elements used to tell, which leads to a mixture explosive though not as excessive as it seems (without ceasing to be so), and from the more industrial than merely artistic Prism (i.e., the Prism subjected to rules and conventions according to a model commercial and also aesthetic), "Mulholland drive" presents some problems that prevent it a perfect film. As for the characters, as we have already said, much of them have a symbolic role (two elders, the hidden man in the corner, the cowboy) and all the remaining weight rests with the two female profiles, both managed quite fluently and occasionally have charged a penetrating sensual scenes. Formally, and ending, the film succeeds in an exalted degree. Since the use of color, the interiors luxury in contrast to the harshness of an old motel room, the interior of a theater, the light that accompanies the world exciting Betty as opposed to Diane, world's darker tones this millimeter calculated for optimal visual representation in each of the States or within levels. In other passages, reaches an atmosphere of dreamlike through small oscillations circular in the close-ups and flat sequence showing a face, a street or the interiors of a room, creating the feeling of sleep which covers all the content and style of this unique masterpiece that can do not like everyone, but what this without saying is its originality and the fact of being the expression of a single filmmaker. </body>
</review>
