<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Candida" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pay homage to a person who has lived through things that nobody should live is no guarantee of a good product. Films must be much more work, spinning a plot of movie, not documentary, make the characters seem real (though they are, not what resembling), etc.</summary>
	<body>There are movies that you want to see to be able to criticize them, not to implement them to give birth, if not quite the opposite. I usually hear in the afternoons to foam, when I return from work, and had long hearing as they praised his own film. They carried the original soundtrack, he spoke the same Candida, and everything seemed great. Thus it was eager to reach the time to put it through the roof and talk of a delicious comedy vital and energetic. Not be why still biting in the same always, anyway.The film is about a Candida called Lady living happy despite his miserable life. A drug addict son, one schizophrenic and one that leaves little but not to leave, better is the sweetener of life of eternal cleansing. The plot runs linearly on an extracted from his life time, that has been this as it could have been another.Look, if I have to be honest, the film seemed to me shit. And I say this with all my heart pain, given that this woman I love and me tenders in equal parts. But the film made about it is not worth a pepper. To begin with, it is not a film, it is a simple course of events, to each one more sad, but without a logical beginning and an incredible end (which gives me just to be real, the reality surpasses fiction and I think). It is a drama, but a drama very fat, told from the filter feeders that I like so little when it comes to filmmaking. And the jokes are not such, honestly I felt the grace was laughing of bad talking this poor woman, who seemed very cruel thing. That is not humor, and people laughed at that, not situations. Saving the time that will recover the television, the rest is not funny, if not very sad.In short, pay homage to a person who has lived through things that nobody should live is no guarantee of a good product. Films must be much more work, spinning a plot of movie, not documentary, make the characters seem real (though they are, not what resembling), etc.</body>
</review>
