<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El próximo Oriente" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Delicious comedy that will make you laugh, suffer, mourn, excite you and give free rein to your emotions without any problem. Shows us that they aren't needed large deployments of media, nor actors of renown for making great films. We love it.</summary>
	<body>The Billboard is like a box of chocolates, always you you eat first those who do not bring wrapper and are more attractive, for at the end, when only remain those of rectangular and bland wrapper you have no other who taste them. The film this is the same, I have not seen any promotion of it, passing on tiptoe to egregious truño of attractive appearance, but since then that batters them with virulence. My recommendation, veanlá, film or video store, but veanlá, in company or alone, but do me case and vedla, insurance that you like.The film is about a type is called Caín who lives in a downtown neighborhood in a big city, which has seen its population has gone from being an aging colony Spanish to a Symphony of immigrants from various countries with their cultures and traditions. Cain is fat, good-natured, something alelado, butcher and a perfect loser. On the contrary, he has a brother named Abel which is just the opposite, a winner of the living married with two daughters, that in a slip leaves Muslim a girl pregnant and women who loved Caín. For more mess, this is neighbor of Cain. Total rejects that as Abel, this is suicide, moment in which her family discovers that she is pregnant. Cain, to safeguard his brother, decides to tell everyone that he is the father and assume with everything.Look, I'm not film wise, nor practically have no idea of it, but only is if it ends a movie and we got up dancing to the sound of the soundtrack, laughing and jumping, meaning that the film has delighted us (or that we we smoked a SPLIFF giant, which is not the case). It has the freshness of the films of Spanish comedy, but which were before, without great pretensions than show us a little story, insignificant to the evolution of humanity, but us cala in the depths of the heart. I do not think that the director intends to show a picture of immigration in Spain far, simply tells a modern story, and currently there are immigrants living among us. And more and more, so you can count stories such as these, in which cultures mingle and ways of seeing the world with the greatest possible purity.In short, delicious comedy that will make you laugh, suffer, mourn, excite you and give free rein to your emotions without any problem. Shows us that they aren't needed large deployments of media, nor actors of renown for making great films. We love it.</body>
</review>
