<review author="Ana" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the end who knows be too trick and without enough reverence by the magic. But experience swings and no longer a recommended show.</summary>
	<body>It is difficult to not go to a movie by Christofer Nolan with huge expectations, but it is unfair. This film this well built and works but it is not Memento. It is as if you know her best trick, very difficult to leave impressed. But it's fun to see someone play with the line of the narrative with the talent he has. It is a satisfying experience although I can not be sure if it is consistent.My favorite scene of The Prestige is better to know nothing about this film before the start, but is very important to pay attention. It is a fluid, but complex structure as it should be a trick. It seems easy but at the same time you don't understand how it works. When you discover the secret you realize how easy that is and then you can not see it without giving you, the magic is lost. Here what interests are the tricks.The novel which is based the script must also be a complex structure, it shows scenes in each of the three protagonists reads the diary of his rival, something which is difficult to translate to film work but insurance was a quick trick in literature.Michael Caine reminds us that it is important to pay attention when you start the movie. His performance is so good that he steals all the attention of every scene in which he participates. The emergence of David Bowie as most scientist is also a great pleasure.The problem is that at times the film gets a little repetitive. It gives many laps on the same idea. And it seems to not be relied upon for having made it clear his message so at the end it becomes a little talkative. But it's fun and you catch in their game. In the end who knows be too trick and without enough reverence by the magic. But experience swings and no longer a recommended show.</body>
</review>
