<review author="Rafa Martín" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For a few glorious five minutes, Rocky Balboa has the best boxing scenes seen in years. You don't say much, given that the genre is not abundant.</summary>
	<body>There are times in which Rocky Balboa reminds me that old gets to look at works and explain to the foreman that the building is going to fall because the cement not curdled and as it collapses the very bastard with thirteen families inside which will load the OWL is him. You look to the poor Lord with affection and sympathy, but generally speaking, we usually spend their views by the lining of the balls. Rocky Balboa isn't the resurrection of Stallone (born in 1946), and even less when he returns to a saga which began personally more than thirty years (30, thirty seven Olympics). But it is a film that not offended anyone, performed correctísimamente, with a good script and, above all, a splendid photography and is a return to realistic in the first film and much of the second tone (up to Adrian wakes up from his coma, in Rocky II, and the first thing that tells her husband is it aniquile to Apollo Creed)(, from there, the Rocky series becomes Portaventura).Adrian has not been able to cheat death again. Us has died of cancer and Rocky Balboa still in his little world and living of the past, as Walter Sobchak. The clientele goes to his restaurant to hear their war stories, his brother-in-law Paulie continues to work on the same meat factory, his son has gone to the dark side and become stock exchange broker (could have been journalist, almost worse) and tries to rebuild his life with the girl who sent him to hell in the first installment, Marienow divorced and with another kid to slopes. Do this that comes the leap of faith: a computer program determines that, in the old days, it would have been capable of ending the unbeaten champion of world heavyweight, Mason?The Line? Dixon. Pifostio media that generates forces the Italian Colt to return to the ring and hence we have again. "Gonna Fly Now, staircases, sweat shirt and grey pants included.""I have 60, but to see who gets the vein as I."The first three quarters of an hour of the film are a pain in the right direction. Rocky talks with Marie. Rocky talk to Paulie. Rocky speaks to his son. His son speaks to his father. Rocky speaks to the son of Marie. Buy a new dog. And come to remember Mickey (the old deaf which trained him until that pushed you Mr. T and died in the third - Port Aventura, remember-), and the ice rink, the gym and the old bar, and that monumental ass. However, as all these scenes are very well shot, and it seems that they exude genuine emotions, the public who really knows that Rocky was always a saga about a poor sack of hosts who refused to fall when they said it, with its two balls, feel a lagrimita of nostalgia. There are really good moments, as everything about Adrian and Paulie, as well as talks with Marie (very good, Geraldine Hughes) and other completely unnecessary and that it could have cut, with the danger of turning the film into a medium (all the stuff of the son, played by the baleful Milo Ventimiglia, who does not know of the reality that surrounds him and if not there is the ultrasobrevalorada Heroes to prove it).What works in this part is the classical sense of Stallone and magnificent photography of j. Clark Mathis, which much resembles what was Robert Richardson in Casino, with colors everywhere and light sources from don't know where, they threaten to cause blindness to the actors. Sly has been in this business of film more of what I've been in this world and fuck that if it shows, because even the most boring dialogue is treated with sufficient care and MIME that we draw the attention. In addition to time when Rocky chistecitos are always ("I feel like a kangaroo, with all these things in your Pocket"), bad pure which are hilarious. Everything is treated with much care and that is not bad, but if you alargas too, it will be unbearable. And it is just at that moment that Stallone decided to launch the train with the structure that all devotees know: training, musical, after Assembly and hosts. Highlight above all the presence of Tony Burton, in the role of Duke, coach of the deceased Apollo Creed which is casca best monologue from the film ("? gonna you give the old trauma by forceful blow of a lifetime") and see Stallone, as Donkey Kong throwing barrels to gain strength, which is the only thing he has left the such Dixon is a miracle of genetics and hits you four hosts before your body receives the first.And for a few glorious five minutes, Rocky Balboa has the best boxing scenes seen in years. Not IE much, given that gender is not abundant, but those first five minutes, with a television planning (including pay-per-view logo) worth all of Ali. Stallone is still Boxer like me player of curling, but Antonio Tarver is a bad beast and although sings when hides the fist to not to let the rest of his life, Stallone incapacitated?Magic Man? know move (mainly because it has been the world's Lightweight Champion). Then director Stallone her shit completely, start to do strange things with the camera (black and white, slow enables camera, degraded, mounting to the Michael Bay). "For someone who has tried to maintain a calm tone and with his feet on the ground throughout the film, is a contradiction.""Potoma!"And you know what? To the peo. Better stay with the end where win or lose, everyone applauds Rocky saga comes to a happy conclusion, without "nothing in the basement", as it said Stallone, and with the feeling that we got rid of a real disaster, the heart and the efforts that had been in the filming. Rocky Balboa is the very best that has been done in years and leads to the desire to go back to the Viewer from ventitantos, who grew up with the best of the eighties action cinema, and now cannot but weep to see the show that give this bunch of cocoons made through action heroes. I those climbed them into the ring, so them fostiara Tito Rocky (and if it fails, I always have the option of jumping I? and my friend Fergie, the chainsaw).</body>
</review>
