<review author="Caruco" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It may the interpretations section be more bland than the desirable, or your pace and brilliance is irregular, especially in its final stretch, but Eastwood still very in shape.</summary>
	<body>A feat of Clint Eastwood. 76 years and even giving much war with "Flags of our fathers", an example of his wisdom, good taste and classicism directing. Providing us entertainment and cinema at the same time. As we have never seen before in his films, it combines the most intimate sequences with big action. Necessary to show the double conflict, or the two fronts open during World War II: one on the first line of combat, with thousands of young people dying; and the other in the cities themselves and people of the nation, besieged and resisting against the enemy (if, for example, France), or away from the firing of bombs and machine guns (the case of the United States.)(UU.), but with the pressing need to raise huge amounts of money that pay all war material.The film opens with the scene of a soldier only, disoriented and frightened in the middle of a desert terrain of battle, hearing the cries of relief and combat hisses.Without heroes or villains.The episode is the nightmare of one older man who still wakes up suddenly with the nightmares of the past, isolated and helpless by the trauma of such experience.The first images and dialogues are what will be the look of the film. Shortly thereafter, an ' off' voice specific this vision: "There are many morons who believe that they know what is war, especially those who have not been in one." Well clearly things like: good and bad, heroes and villains. "That there, but most of the time are not who we believe."Shows the heroism of American forces during the invasion of the island of Iwo Jima in 1944, volcanic island and strategic point. And some villains who must defeat, of course, for the sake of humanity: the Japanese. Images of guns and fuses Japanese emerging almost from scratch, from the forts and tunnels, as if they were a ghostly enemy, a threat which lurks the protagonists in a worthy of the fantasy genre scenes are splendid.But in reality there is no heroes or villains. Combatants Yankees recognize that, as much to speak of patriotism, freedom and other things, their struggle is for survival or companionship. There villains, because many are seen with a certain respect. To complete this vision soon will have "Letters from Iwo Jima", the same but from the Japanese perspective, and that of the losers.In the form.Then there is the other front, that of politicians and military waging the Mission of selling millions of war with which to finance bonds. Here intervenes all the media circus and politician extolling before public opinion to three of the six survivors who raised an American flag in the Suribachi.La mount need icons and heroes made three young idols. But also were heroes who doubted their status, who believed betray the true heroes, usurping them honors his companions dead on the battlefield. And heroes with expiration date, they would very soon be a gift no one. And not even the architects of handling and selling your image might be considered as villains. Collect many dollars every day was essential. The baggage, weapons or fuel, does not appear from nowhere.Eastwood manages to largely collect and convey the issues and proposed nuances, with an extraordinary photography, muted colors, frames of a pictorial plasticity and a production design that puts us squarely in the era and the time.Also makes us step back, and look for reflection, with a structure of the story progresses and regresses in the facts, which even does not allow us to easily identify others side, heroes and martyrs anonymous, launched into a fatuous destination, and only remembered by the sobbing of mothers.It may the interpretations section be more bland than the desirable, or your pace and brilliance is irregular, especially in its final stretch, but Eastwood is still (very) in the form.</body>
</review>
