<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Eragon" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>On the other hand it has the virtue of not being excessively long, barely lasting one hour and three quarters, or pretentious so as entertainment for a later silly could be worth. View group and with willingness to laugh of it, for sure to improve.</summary>
	<body>Queire worldwide take advantage of the success and the desire of fantasy film by Christmas, created by "The Lord of the rings" saga. That is why the past Christmas Mariah "The Chronicles of Narnia", which threatens to turn into a quite long serial, and this Christmas we have received this "Eragón" of which we have the consolation that there are only three novels. "There go getting used, that it will not be the last film in the same style we get.""Eragon" represents the debut in the direction of Stefen December, former Visual effects supervisor. And tenor as seen it seems clear that his adventure has been, when less, little fortunate. The address is very flat, lacks life, personality and because of him, the film lacks the claw and the force should be.It is not that the script was wonderful, because it is ultimately a remix of elements of "The Lord of the rings" and "Star Wars", but with a powerful direction would have been otherwise. At least, maybe not he had crappy what looks, terrible detail in a film that is sold as a Christmas blockbuster full of special effects and heiress of milestones such as those already mentioned.Fortunately Jeremy Irons through there and offers us some time in charismatic, average gas performance because her character does not give much, but higher than his teammates. Djimon Hounsou and John Malkovich spend out there but little seen, while Robert Carlyle sees more but the truth is that it is a tad embarrassing.What is a total disaster is the choice of Edward Speleers as main actor. The kid is a bully, it cannot be denied, but acting is not theirs. It is difficult to understand that a woman as the played by Sienna Guillory might be interested by such little thing (for some reason from the first moment he sees, look you as if it were to brush there same). The main actor Dragon acts better than him is so bad.On the other hand it has the virtue of not being excessively long, barely lasting one hour and three quarters, or pretentious so as entertainment for a later silly could be worth. View group and with willingness to laugh of it, for sure to improve.</body>
</review>
