<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Gisaku" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It would be a prodigy but it just hampered by being a brochure to disseminate the Spain today</summary>
	<body>Entertaining product aimed at children, in the case of national consumer and profane aliens in Spanish culture.True to its objectives as a publicity pamphlet of this our Spain, this title from the creators of P3k: Pinocchio 3000 and El Cid the legend was born as contribution of animation industry patria to the Universal Exposition of Aichi nipponese 2005.Los had stay delighted about the adventures of a samurai in State of hibernation for nearly four centuries, lost in time and alien to the changes. Yohei, which is the name the disciplined supporter of the good arts, wakes up in the Seville of the 21st century and you can imagine the shock that suffers to see how the Expo in 1992 marked a turning point in the Andalusian capital. A somewhat forced plot leads to a peculiar group commanded by this character, which in turn pays homage to the manga, travel through the Iberian Peninsula and disembark in the Balearic Islands. This trip includes stops not only tourism, but also moral, to promote the principles of brotherhood and respect for the environment and advocating the eternal struggle between good and evil: enough to see the first actions of the quixotic samurai, which led him to stand in front of an enraged Dragon is not anything other than the AVE train to reach the station of Santa Justa. This curious example of animation to the Japanese, with a rather slow pace and many special effects, would by itself only a prodigy in Spanish animation, although just filling by continuous references "brochure" in an attempt to spread the Spain today. And while "the eighth industrial country in the world no longer believes in legends", its new inhabitants - we refer to the more young people - they should contemplate this educational film which exalts, nothing subtly, the excellence of Mediterranean cuisine, the wine culture and technological progress through their unique characters.</body>
</review>
