<review author="Plissken" title="Candida" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It ñoña, disjointed and boring, but it is worth seeing in action to the Candida.</summary>
	<body>The universe of Javier and Guillermo Fesser is the most atypical of our filmography. From 'That ritmillo' or 'The secdleto of the tdompleta' until 'El milagro de p. Tinto' have been able to build a kind of giant comic book where the man of the canister, the bungling, the Martians and the Narrator type NO-DO have an own entity, and the tontorrón and naïve humor disguises of surrealism and is highly effective. All this is to say that, Yes, I love the Fesser film work until 'p. Tinto' However, when they go out of their territory, the results considerably lower. 'Adventure of Mortadelo and Filemón', despite its brilliant appearance, went from being a collection of vignettes that reached to stun the painted. And 'Candida' repeated the same mistakes, more added one: the address is borne by Guillermo Fesser, who is clearly the least gifted of the two brothers to get behind the camera. The truth, pass the hipervitaminado pace and shantytowns of one to the parsimony and lack of Audacity to the other would already be enough to think this movie. But, unfortunately, there is more.The argument of 'Candida' could be as simple as "Forward things that happen to a lady that has to get his family to base of mopping floors". Because, simply, the narrative as such does not exist. Javier Fesser adapting the book by the endearing home employee catch-up, with a plot excuse I guess is based on the relationship between Candida and Guillermo Fesser (in the film become a stressed and antipatiquísimo anchor A3TV, poorly portrayed by Jorge Bosch), but ends up being more incredible that the saga of the p. Tinto. It features characters to then forget them, after releasing a couple of jokes about them. It unnecessarily lengthens the resolution of the plot, up to scratch in the fussiness. Try us to sell the story of redemption and never goes beyond the story of a few snobs with a bad conscience. I have not read the book, but really the life of Candida not does for more?The chapter of interpretations, better not speak. One assumes the amateurism of the protagonist (even so, which is more airy leaves) and several side, but really what Jorge Bosch has no name. To Raúl Peña (former UPA Dance) gives credibility to his junkie with four tricks everyone can apply to that type of character, we are or not actors. But it is what the that Bosch is painful, Furthermore he being the character with which the average viewer should identify.And having said all that, it could say that it is one of the worst movies that I have missed in the face in a long time. As you see, it is not the case. Simply because Candida, that character that rescued his gray anonymity Gomaespuma, rises above everything bad that has its "biopic" and get what they could not get or Viggo Mortensen in "Alatriste", for example: forget everything bad and laugh not she, but their peculiar vision of life. And that you do not leave the room with sense of manifest fraud. And forgive all the blunders at least for nearly two hours, to its around. Candida (and with it, all the Cándidas in the world have been) deserved tribute, certainly, but much better than this one.It ñoña, disjointed and boring, but it is worth seeing in action to the Candida. 5.</body>
</review>
