<review author="Natalia Eseverri" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You would recommend it without doubt to have the opportunity of seeing something different in war movies and also with an interesting message. It has become one of my films of the year and I hope more...</summary>
	<body>Watching movies like this, you really give account of why Clint Eastwood beats the battle directors as Martin Scorsese at the ceremony of the Oscar.No only because it manages to make a wonderful film in which both the script and the history, quality exceeds and even get to the work of the actors, very well done that issee overflowed by the plot and the mastery with which this film is directed. But because in addition, Clint Eastwood dares to deepen with something very difficult which is essential in life and American history as it is the pride and to criticize the search for heroes in something so cruel as it is the war.From the beginning, the intention of the film is shown through the testimonies of persons who took part in that famous photo of the lifting of the American flag at the battle of Iwo Jima, that for me is novel, that in most of the films release us a bland moral at the end is almost of joke and that in the majority of those times could have been saved. Then we can see details that we remember much the principle of saving private Ryan and being Mr Spielberg, one of the producers, I am not surprised that any advice or suggestion has shown in the film. But as things notable, especially stress the two main that I recommend this film: A magnificent address by Mr Eastwood, not only by its planes from camera, to which more risky. But to come accompanied by an extraordinary photography and a way of approaching a war film in a very different way to them that they were observing usually that is an original vision welcome. Increasingly, Mr Clint Eastwood demonstrates me its versatility when it comes to address issues of diverse nature and which is becoming, but it is already, in one of my favorite directors.And above all a script, which confirms that the relationship Paul Haggis - Clint Eastwood, is more productive and surprising. Through many flash-backs, us are telling the history of such frivolity, without losing even a second the pace of the plot and without losing the thread of what is happening to the Viewer. This, coupled with magnificent dialogue that manage to make you move from laughter to tears of one scene to another, succeed in getting the message of the film directly and without hesitation with scenes superflúas that lead nowhere.If I have to add some sticks, would be a poor music accompanying sometimes not to what is happening in some scenes and a somewhat poor use of the computer in some scenes of the battle which is quite noticeable that the scenes are not real.And already Finally, I her I would recommend without doubt to have the opportunity of seeing something different in war movies and also with an interesting message. It has become one of my films of the year and I hope you have more.</body>
</review>
