<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="The holiday" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An entertaining comedy romantic to have a good time without complications nor requirements but fully respectful of the intelligence of the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>Every year premiered a film for Christmas which aims to drag to the cinemas to all those who are not watching action movies, adventure, flying dragons or cartoons.If the year passed the winner between this type of tapes was "The jewel of the family", this year it has the turn to "The Holiday", the new film by Director Nancy Meyers, signatory of "what think women?" and "When least so expect you".The official synopsis (summary) is as follows: A little before Christmas, Amanda (Cameron Diaz) and Iris (Kate Winslet) decide that they need to get away as much as possible their respective boyfriends (Rufus Sewell and Edward Burns) so they agree to exchange their homes for two weeks. Shortly after install at home of Amanda in California, Iris lock friendship with Arthur (Eli Wallach), a famous writer of the golden age of Hollywood, and thousands (Jack Black), a composer. Meanwhile, in England, Amanda known Graham (Jude Law), the brother of Iris?We must not forget that we we have a film whose only mission is to entertain. There is no pretentiousness here. It is a conventional romantic comedy. But well done.In that regard, the script follows typical patterns of the romantic comedy with the particularity of being telling two stories in parallel. It can blame you being a bit more length (while watching the film one not noticing), not having better drawn the character of Jack Black and not have dared to Jude Law's character was a crápula with all of the law, which have to take out the manga quite implausible.No one can escape nor that much of the appeal lies in the protagonists. In this case I would say that they meet all perfectly although, as I insinué before, soon you can do Jack Black with a character so lacking in content. I especially like Kate Winslet and Eli Wallach, two big players of very different and distant generations, whose relationship is the most beautiful of all of the film.In summary, an entertaining comedy romantic to have a good time without complications nor requirements but fully respectful of the intelligence of the Viewer.</body>
</review>
