<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Ratónpolis" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pleasant viewing animated film but that will not go down in history or too long will remain in our memory.</summary>
	<body>"British" (Flushed Away) is an Aardman production directed by David Bowers and Sam Fell. Tells the story of Roddy (Hugh Jackman in the original version), a high-society rat, after falling to the sewers from the bathroom of your House, multiple adventures will live and discover a very different life than that known.Aardman is a name associated so far, with the cinema of animation with plasticine. It is the creative factory feature "Evasion on the farm" and the drama "Wallace and Gromit: the curse of the vegetables" as well as short films of these last characters or the "Creature Comforts" television series.For this reason, his leap to the 3D computer animated feature film, was expected with curiosity and enthusiasm by fans. The result, without being disappointing, do not think it meets too such illusions.Starting with defects will say that, although in the character design is has been trying to keep the visual style of the company, on the pass to the 3D part of the essence is lost. The usual generic transgression is not here present and lack something of the freshness and originality.In other words, "British" is more conventional than its predecessors and seems born with the will, on the other hand respectable, sweeping to victory at the box office. That Yes, without renouncing to quality criteria and a few touches of humor quite British and they provide some of the best moments of the film.These defects are offset, for me, for a couple of fairly important virtues. The first of these is the accelerated pace of the film, I would almost say that too high if we put picky, that they make a really entertaining although somewhat experience hasty.Add, moreover, a funny script although not anything innovative and we get a nice viewing animated film but that will not go down in history or you'll be too long in our memory. As it stands the courtyard that leaves at a level something higher than average but far from the brilliance which the cinema of animation can be reached.</body>
</review>
