<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Ratónpolis" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Targeting an audience often animated film. Action and humor in a recording original and surprising, that shows animated cinema can make blockbusters as effective as beings of flesh and bone. And surely more cheap.</summary>
	<body>Clay animation has always been something magical and amazing. It can be supermala as argument, but just thinking that someone has created these wonders with the same which tí you only served to make "churros" superlargos staining the table to your mother, already put the hairs as hooks. As this film is in reverse, with animation, made drawings of plasticine. Curioso.la film is a pet mouse who lives with a rich girl. For reasons unknown, they leave and stays him as King of the House at the worst possible moment. A rat strain by the drains and is installed in the House. Surprisingly, this win and expels our "fine" friend to the world of British, where will fight to return to the comfort of your home.The thing to be honest, has not been bad. My average pumpkin says that it is hell and snoring in the third frame, everything is said. But to me I have not found so loose. Is true that the story is very mozalbetes, but has funny giños to the elderly, such as the continuous references to James Bond (so fashionable now) or the subtle inclusion of Desafio Total (Prize for who to see). The argument is not much worse than any action of real actors, with their introduction, his knot and its outcome, but instead of explosions and challenges to physics, we have shots and ingenuity to solve problems. Deserves special mention animation, given that they have achieved that the drawings seem clay dolls, was it necessary? Man, not what, but original if that is.In short, focused on an audience often animated film. Action and humor in a recording original and surprising, that shows animated cinema can make blockbusters as effective as beings of flesh and bone. And surely more cheap.</body>
</review>
