<review author="Elena Suárez" title="María Antonieta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What cut you your head! -I thought yesterday while leaving the cinema after seeing the last work of Sofia Coppola - and I was not referring precisely to the already decapitated Marie Antoinette but to the author of such nonsense.</summary>
	<body>What cut you your head! -I thought yesterday while leaving the cinema after seeing the last work of Sofia Coppola - and I was not referring precisely to the already decapitated Marie Antoinette but to the author of such nonsense.The film begins with an interesting historical accuracy (which shows us that in that sense, yes have done the homework), but the narrative development concentrates too much on some aspects which may be boring to the Viewer (half of the narrative is dedicated to explain the noted fact consummated that not their sexual intercourse until after several years of marriage). On the other hand, the Director has stated in more than one interview that the intention was to show us that the sovereign was not an idiot but a smart woman who retained their human side, but in the movie the only thing we see is a niñata that is exclusively dedicated to take cakes at all hours and drink champagne together with friends of the Court. (I obviaré the comment of the human facet of Marie Antoinette and her husband that I do not think that the Coppola knows what is starving).The main problem of the film is that he has considered the design and image to the detriment of the argument, that is why I had the feeling of watching a video clip instead of a feature film: the scenes of Marie Antoinette and her friends in a palatial retreat reminiscent of a famous advertising campaign in which asked us what smelled the clouds brought me.As for the soundtrack, the great controversy, I have to say that not it seemed neither strident nor in bad taste. Few songs pop that appear and frankly, they do not desentonaban in the environment, in fact, I would not surprised the couple of fashion, Almodovar and "Pe", appeared in the midst of so much move, that Yes, Parisian scene.As a final auction, in a world so cool grow is not synonymous with aging, in fact both Marie Antoinette and Louis look exactly the same when they marry (she fifteen and sixteen) that when fleeing from Versailles (thirty-five and thirty-six, respectively).</body>
</review>
