<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El ilusionista" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Personally I liked. In large part, I guess, because I try to go to the prejudice-free movies, immersing me in the movie and enjoy the story without trying to anticipate the same, without searching five feet to the cat.</summary>
	<body>"Film with trick". At this point in the season, when according to the advertising has already been viewed by I do not know how many millions of viewers, I do not believe that pass anything because we talk about movie with trick. However, the fact that before release are references in all the reviews to his relationship with "The coup" and other films for the style, condition viewing.Personally I liked. In large part, I guess, because I try to go to the prejudice-free movies, immersing me in the movie and enjoy the story without trying to anticipate the same, without seeking five feet to the cat, leaving me entice by director and screenwriter. If the movie is good, we will enjoy with surprises and the twists of the script, with the evolution of the events and characters, etc. If not, we effectively anticiparemos what will happen. and we aburriremos mortally.In this case, even knowing that it was a movie of tricks with magic and illusionism. I enjoyed the surprising end. I liked the way of telling the story and I identified with that tortured in love with illusionist that her magic fails to provide what they most need, want and yearns for: the true love of his life. Since those roles in "The fight club" and "American History X", Edward Norton seems to me one of the actors with the greatest power of seduction of the moment. With his face of good, but mischievous child; of healthy tortured muchachote; hard sportsman with artistic concerns and much inner world; in "The illusionist" is sensational. As colossal are secondary, that detective with pretensions and, above all, that Prince conspirator, illustrated and sadistic. Perhaps it would have made him need to another edge to the latter, but to be an unusual 90-minute film, is much what it tells us.And Vienna, one of the most seductive capitals of Europe was booming in times that runs one movie more interesting and that has been a bestial box-office success. without the usual attributes for this: either sex or violence. Now premiered another magical film, from the hand of the team revived the moribund Batman? what has merit and is welcome - Christopher Nolan and Christian Bale. Although you will have difficulty to put so many spectators in the Pocket as "The illusionist", this challenge of the film magicians is the most interesting and stimulating.We look forward to the screens.</body>
</review>
