<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Last trick (the Prestige) is, broadly, a more than acceptable film of intrigue, despite its excessive length not bored to anyone, but it will be remembered as one minor by Christopher Nolan work.</summary>
	<body>Christopher Nolan is an atypical cinematographer for the times, in which people try to not get out of the way we have marked, and do what is expected of us. This rule applies to many filmmakers, distinguished by voluntarily in any genre in particular, which isn't necessarily a bad thing. But there are a few with each new job trying to do something different to the above, and there are those who in addition to try, succeed. Christopher Nolan belongs to this last group.But it must also be said that the ability of Hollywood producing projects with a similar at the same time theme is amazing, and what better example than two feature films on magicians as the magician and the Final trick (the Prestige). Alfred Borden (Christian Bale) and Robert Angier (Hugh Jackman) are two magicians that since young people have competed among themselves. A tragic fact definitely face them, and neither of them can rest until you find the final trick that impose. Taking the novel by Christopher Priest, Nolan performs an intense portrait of human obsession and the destruction that entails. The British filmmaker takes the story, with its particular narrative transforms it, makes it yours, and as if it were a conjurer, gives the back completely in the third Act, the prestige. The Final trick (the Prestige) has a great start, but towards the middle of the tape, it declines slightly, and fails to go back at any time. It is also true that some things seem forced, that there are several blurred characters (especially that of Scarlett Johansson) who seem to be merely decorative elements. Perhaps the worst flaw in the film is predictable that comes back in the second half, as the big final surprises are easily guessed by smart viewers. For its part, the interpretations are good, although excels Hugh Jackman, who performs his best work (with the Scoop) to date.Last trick (the Prestige) is, broadly, a more than acceptable film of intrigue, despite its excessive length not bored to anyone, but it will be remembered as one minor by Christopher Nolan work.</body>
</review>
