<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Mujeres en el parque" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Women in the Park is a good film that dissects a few characters to display them as they are to the public. However, it is half way of the excellent film that could have been, which is always a real shame.</summary>
	<body>Every year, during the months of January and February, the charts of the Spanish cinemas are filled with a huge amount of titles from Hollywood, most of them with aspirations to the Oscars, or at least theoretically made to suck up to them. For this reason, it is not surprising that barely has premieres of Spanish films during the first months of each year, because they expect warmed until it reaches March and with it the Festival of Málaga. But there is always some courageous trying to cope with the American avalanche, and Felipe Vega is one of them.Daniel (Adolfo Fernández), music teacher and pianist, and Ana (Blanca Apilánez), gallerist, in crisis of couple after more than twenty years of life in common. Daniel has gone to live alone and wants to divorce. Anne refuses to accept the reality. Distress affects his daughter Monica (Barbara Lennie), which, after finishing his studies of journalism, is particularly sensitive to not find work. Felipe Vega is a very personal and equipped with a high sensitivity, filmmaker as it already demonstrated in his previous work, this great little story which was summer clouds. With women in the Park, Vega and Manuel Hidalgo (his usual co-screenwriter) go a step further and make a portrait of the separation on crises that can affect a person and how they affect inevitably in others. It is simply a portrait of the human soul, a dark and at times turbulent part. The main virtue of the film is the sense of reality that transmits, with nearby, and real characters that any viewer can recognize easily. Vega does not judge his characters but yes examines them with magnifying glass, analyzing them until exhaustion, to display, as we said before, a facet of the human soul without ornaments and flourishes. Regardless of original score, the music of Chopin serves as necessary vehicle to talk by the characters, say what they silent, in short, to transmit all kinds of feelings to the Viewer. However, the tape has some defects, like the ups and downs of the script, which causes history to decay and lose intensity in some moments. Does this not help precisely the style of narration of Vega, leisurely and calm, to slow down in excess. It is a story based on his characters, the work of the actors is essential. And all respond giving the best, works excellent, full of naturalness and realism, and contributing to the feeling of truth that conveys the film. Especially noted the Madrid young Bárbara Lennie, with a clean performance and great emotional containment.Women in the Park is a good film that dissects a few characters to display them as they are to the public. However, it is half way of the excellent film that could have been, which is always a real shame.</body>
</review>
