<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Mujeres en el parque" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Clean, sincere over not being able to film. Vega film going to horse between the everyday and how wonderful and their characters are not given your personal halo: let them fly free; He shoots them with enormous asepsis, leaving them succeed and be wrong.</summary>
	<body>All emotions are predictable. All hopes. And fears. The contradictions encourage an inaccurate, imperfect world, accomplice of all barbaric and all the prodigies who have executed in its fragile resistance to the giro, but the world keeps turning and the rhetoric of the giro (of complicity in good and bad, of this abstract concept of Pantheism inclusive) is useful to give some light to this simple exercise in film very semanticforged around the morality of necessarily unstable characters, stranded in the communication, made to say and listen to, but do not say or not listen: maybe a sign of these times.Felipe Vega and screenwriter Manuel Hidalgo offer a clean, sincere over not being able to film, a universe of couples who never fall into conflict beaten by the plentiful supply of that film of personal relationships, couples to the Woody Allen, who delivered and are rejected, that they burrow until you find the key that redeems them from its existential boredom. Vega film (remember the wonderful summer clouds) going to horse between the everyday and how wonderful and their characters are not given your personal halo: let them fly free; He shoots them with enormous asepsis, leaving them succeed and be wrong. The small raised generational drama does not give a solution to the problems: it exposes without frivolity, it brings closer them to the sensitivity of who, stunned, notes how everything is articulated under the cold layer of solitary confinement, which sometimes comes dressed as arrogance or hypocrisy or weakness.Actress Blanca Apilánez is immense. Too bad the end, something ridiculous, away the last of the pure excellence impression. Nor collaborates certain formal eviction in scenes that we understand key (the scene of the bar with customers that have just been going).</body>
</review>
