<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Volver" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Delicious piece of real life, portrait with envy, quarrels and resentments to the surface</summary>
	<body>Not disappointed Almodóvar with this exercise of cinema in its purest form, a costumbrista, vibrant and concise story, in which exudes humor, and that he speaks of the death.Let the high bar, recovering a tone that pervaded characteristic of its first stage titles, leaving visible the it autocita to what have I done to deserve this?, in particular to the mother who comes to resolve issues pending, and the acid humor of darkness.Levels of Almodóvar, studied to the millimetre, are usually living paintings. Rarely a level concentrated so much as the first, with all the women of the people in the cemetery, adecentando the tombs of face to the day of the dead. The costumes of the sisters protagonists anticipate the bright and colorful accent that will dominate all the footage, full always eternal symbols in his filmography (maternity hospitals, neighbouring, etc.) and any new, as the table stretcher.It gives us a chorus formed by six strong characters. Through them he draws women recalls his childhood in La Mancha, but far from proposing a reflection, it assimilates them and recasts, entering a round, surprising story by their portentous twists. We understand this point as opposite to the dalliances they did err in La mala educación.It shows their feminine in all its intensity characters although somewhat idealized, hence superb interpretations of Penelope Cruz. His role-playing exercises spine although she puts much of his party, leaving behind their best work so far, of No move. Aware that the Spanish housewives have some fringe or pejorative connotation, Almodóvar has become an Italian casalinga Cruz, a housewife with character and glamour, a mixture between the racial beauty of Sophia Loren and the athletic bearing of Silvana Mangano.La accompany his travels of the people to the city - and vice versa - one close and distant at the same timeDo, Lola Dueñas, Chus Lampreave, exploited to the maximum and a very correct Yohana Cobo which is not amohína to both together wonder? its presence in surreal situations serves as anchor on the more earthly side of Almodóvar. We continue to hear Blanca Portillo, "this film animal", is the great discovery of Almodóvar to the big screen. The truth is that their contribution to the career of the actress is similar to that in his day made to Leonor Watling talk to her (and Alejandro Amenábar to Dueñas on sea) inside. And is not nothing to shore up, with much skill, return to the celluloid of an actress that was already big in television and film (remember the dog in the Manger and the color of the clouds) and, above all, huge theater.The manchego with everyday but carried to its extreme histrionic and very funny situations is reunited. Account to do this with one of his muses, which made its first six films. The grateful and fruitful work of Carmen Maura gives a dimension, leaving anecdote (or surrealist dream) as you look at it an interpretation that in the hands of another actress had been somewhat risky.Under a first appearance of fable, return is a delicious piece of real life, a portrait with envy, quarrels between sisters, resentments to the surface of skin, mourning, phones, shoes and rebequitas, many rebequitas. A nod to the more traditional Spain, the neighborhood and the people that most of us have grown.</body>
</review>
