<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Luces al atardecer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Filmed with the hieratic austerity Spartan typical of Kaurismäki, those look torva faces, those few dialogues, that pale microcosm of a Helsinki permanently in shadows, not he defrauded his followers, and leaves some pearls of desolate beauty.</summary>
	<body>Anyone who has seen a Finnish Aki Kaurismäki film knows what kind of movies does: a sad and desolate universe, a urban wasteland full of hieratic faces, one tragedy after another, entirely a valley of tears to the edge of the Arctic Circle, as if figuratively six months night lasted forever in that inhospitable (do as regards climate: in social welfare gives soups with honda to the rest of the world?) land. "Lights in the evening" not worthy at all of that feeling that conveys all the films of Kaurismäki, with "The girl of the factory of matches" (see criticism in CRITICALIA) as película-insignia his filmography and their intentions thematic and aesthetic; We are, therefore, face a depressing story, which should go "because" Prozac. The protagonist happen all conceivable misfortunes, and that not to give account of the cure to his solitude is so close: vigilant sworn (come on, "segurata", as it is colloquially in Spain) despised by his fellow is unexpectedly courted by a girl that he seeks a ruin on the orders of his boss, a capomafia without appearance no italic, but with the same unscrupulous (i.e.)(none?) their Sicilian colleagues. In the meantime, our unhappy poor will not have their eyes: love, so close, so silent? Filmed with the hieratic austerity Spartan typical of Kaurismäki, with those faces of baleful gaze, those few dialogues, that pale microcosm of a Helsinki permanently in shadows, not disappointed his followers, and leaves some pearls of bleak beauty: the exceptional scene in which the silent lover of the protagonist (who has not yet knows that love) learns that his beloved segurata comes with another: the lights of his small kiosk selling sausages will be shutting down, one after another, to darken the cubicle completely, as the own mood of selling hot dogs, to hear the sad news of the loss of his beloved. This is not a movie just to pass the time: need stomach (not by that has harsh scenes, but by its lack of seasoning, spice to her make more tasty) and much spirit movie buff. But it is also true, however, it is unusual film, which should be protected if it were in danger. Clear that, fortunately, Kaurismaki keeps making cinema regularly; It is good that has spend less on budget that Chiquito in anxiolytics?</body>
</review>
