<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Babel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Well directed, well performed and it is sufficiently entertaining, but is far from being the masterpiece many trumpets. One thing are the intentions or the message, and quite another the artistic result.</summary>
	<body>"Heralded as the end of the trilogy of the tandem formed by Guillermo Arriaga and Alejandro González Iñárritu guionista-director pain, at last I could see what will be, in all probability, one of the most nominated films at the oscars this year.""Babel," tells us several interwoven stories which have an unfortunate accident as epicenter: some children in Morocco shoot and injure an American tourist (Cate Blanchett), who is travelling with her husband (Brad Pitt).I will say it bluntly: the film I like but I was disappointed. After all the positive reviews that had heard about her, praising her as great narrative exercise, poetry in images or great script expected me more. I'm glad that screenwriter and director have decided not to do more joint work because I believe that it is time that both fly separately before the start to be too repetitivosMe like the way of directing Iñárritu, and I agree that creates images of great beauty, also supported in a magnificent photography and a good soundtrack. He knows to create emotional and dramatic tension with very few elements in a scene; something essential in a good director.The actors are all superb, especially inspired Adriana Barraza in his role as caretaker of the sons of the American couple and Rinko Kikuchi as sordomuda. It is a pity that Spain the film is issued folded because it is not only sense the title, message, and many scenes but that, Furthermore, we lose a very important part of these interpretations. I believe that Franco is dead long enough so we'd us one of their first "cultural" laws without too many regrets, no?Turning to the issue before us, in my opinion the main problem is the script. It seems a good idea, that of the apparently non-event event, in a kind of butterfly effect, giving rise to all the events of the film, but I think that there are things that are too caught by the hairs.And I do not mean, only, that there are elements difficult to believe, that it is also a handicap in a film that is not sold as a fable (something which very well made "Crash", for example) but as a "realistic" and in-depth portrait about the problem of solitary confinement and lack of understanding. I mean that, in fact, the history of the Japanese has no a clear relationship with the central story but, in return, it may be the most harrowing of all and that most engages the Viewer. The director himself should be aware of this when booking the wonderful flat end of the function.It also seems that Gael Garcia Bernal's character doesn't make much sense and almost all of their actions seem inexplicable. I fear that both the character and their strange decisions are not anything other than a resource writer helpings to complicate the situation.In the field of the anecdotal comment that some problem must have Arriaga with masturbation because both his script for "The 3 burials of Melquiades Estrada" as in this case, the masturbation precedes the tragedy. There is some psychologist in the room?Ultimately, the film is well directed, well performed and it is sufficiently entertaining, but is far from being the masterpiece many trumpets. One thing are the intentions or the message, and quite another the artistic result.</body>
</review>
