<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When a movie makes you forget you're in a movie theater and almost gives you the feeling that you who are fleeing for his life, is that this movie is good, separate controversies.</summary>
	<body>It seems that all film touched by the hand of the actor before and now director Mel Gibson comes with controversy. It was the case with the controversial "the passion of Christ" and now returns to our screens with Apocalypto, which some try to brand racist.The main issue is that the film is, above all, a story of action and, in any case, I think you try to submit an essay on the causes of the decline of the great Mayan Empire (and not the desapación of civilization maya as I read in some articles). As well, however, the data showing the narrative are not false, namely; the Mayans practiced human sacrifices (extirpations and beheadings) and even the autosacrificios (drilling of some parts of the body to bleed as well). Thus, believed to feed the gods, something which was necessary for the man alimentase, in turn, of the products created by the gods. It is also true that in the last period of the Empire the population was divided into independent provinces and, therefore, with various political, administrative and military bodies. What follows the struggles between various provinces was something feasible. Nor is is very clueless when it tells us that had excasez of natural resources and the population was becoming ill (is one of the theories more accepted by anthropologists to explain the decline of this great Empire). what no speak of progress demonstrated the Mayans in subjects such as mathematics or astronomy? Therefore not because it would not bring anything to the story, it was simply not necessary. I say that this is a movie and not a documentary of the Nathional Geographic. What displays a bloody picture of the Mayans? Therefore neither more nor less bloody than most of the civilizations in the 15th century. Do you, think perhaps, that all Spaniards were dedicated to colonize Islands and kill natives? Do as Spanish I shocked me everytime I see a film about Hernán Cortés? (and more when the British massacred even more but nothing is said).That said, that he thought it necessary, Apocalypto (Greek meaning "I revealed") is a great action movie, that Yes, with a high content of violence (not in vain, speaks to us of the kidnapping of a village, his subsequent torture and humiliation and, above all, the courage of a man to save his family from death). Just as in the passion of Christ dialogues are produciran in the native language according to the historical and geographical situation, in this case, the Yucatec maya; However, the image will charge much more emphatically that the word latter being used with discretion but with intensity.Are careful in detail the scenery as well as physical adaptation of the actors within the geographical environment (in fact, many of them are natives of Mexico); If to this we add that the faces of the actors are not widely known, the great integration of elements make us feel history with more realism.In summary, when a movie makes you forget that you are in a movie theater and almost gives you the feeling that you who are fleeing for his life, it is that this movie is good, separate controversies.</body>
</review>
