<review author="Bloody Will" title="Candida" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fesser, has a very special mood, and channeled it in an extraordinary way through all the characters in the film, creating that world where the protagonist dealt much tenderness and affection.</summary>
	<body>Me is very difficult to be able to classify this film, because undoubtedly plays a few genres: drama, comedy, social commentary. The undoubted is that "Candida" is presented as a certainly endearing character, and counts for a lot know that here the protagonist does not interpret, is unchanged, and its history is very in keeping with its time of release. Speaks of lost people and an angel guardian which does not have to wear pigtails or pronounced cleavage.For those we have followed the duo Gomaespuma for quite a few years now this film we are familiar. Family by the type of humor that uses, how to hold the dialogues, the apparently incoherent phrases, and at the same time to be seen on screen to this lady that has been delighting us with their impossible criticism. Quite rightly, those who come to see the film without passing through the filter prior is find something misplaced at the beginning and perhaps fail to understand fully the protagonist, but this does not mean that towards the 5 minute already keep us eating out of his hand.Candida, as in reality, facing the hardness of his family life through the kindness and without obstacles. Junkie (Raul Peña) has a son and another crazy auction (Victor Sevilla), works for a Countess of the three to the room that racanea you up the Loofah, and begins to ensure the master Pablo, a presenter of TV with chaotic personal life. The objective of Candida will be the same for all: make life pleasant as possible at the expense of their kidneys.The director of "Candida", Guillermo Fesser, 50% of Gomaespuma and brother of "Mortadelo and Filemón" - Javier Fesser, has a very special humor and channeled it in an extraordinary way through all the characters in the film, creating that world where the protagonist dealt much tenderness and affection. Like his brother, low Fesser histrionico and not so colorful a stepping stone towards situations more real and harsh as the drug addiction of the youngest son, the irresponsibility of a daughter something lightweight helmets, a neighbor who receives sticks every day and Marathon days of an Assistant which conforms only with his tele.Best thing is that at the end erizaron me hairs and the knot of the throat was I not going. The worst must also mention it, and is the film towards the second half loses the direction altogether. Perhaps lengthen too much the relationship between Candida and the master Pablo makes you lose at the end the axis on which rested the movie at the beginning. A final very conformist and very white, perhaps too much for so much shame that the protagonist brings.Indeed, something that characterizes the Fesser brothers is the music chosen for his films. Once more, songs in 100 increase the intentions of the director and give a warmth to the film that is very difficult to achieve with hits of the 90. The version of Julio Iglesias Gwendoline Pitingo is impressive.Nevertheless, "Candida" I meant the same shock that was "Babel," and by God not me crucifiqueis because I am not comparing them. I am referring to a lagrimitas is never wrong, and a history of ordinary people in the neighborhood of 500 metres beyond is as a stew that you take two weeks after eating spaghetti: a warm for the head.</body>
</review>
