<review author="Yul B." title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In conclusion, a Council: enjoy this film with an open willingness to ignore his trick, because surely you sorprenderéis.</summary>
	<body>There is never a magician without trick. Do do do the deception caused by the magic in the mind and in the vision of the viewer need always a small? trap?, a? trick? to achieve the intended effect of fascination and enthusiasm.This trick, which is vital for a magician, it also needs a film to create the same effect. How many times we have spoken of foreseeable that has been a film and the disappointment that have led us to witness something already known. I.e. using a simile fitting for the occasion, was missing what we call? the magic of cinema?. This expected film of which I speak also has trick, not only in its title. As in any show of any magician, the success of the function relies on the ability of the artist to make inexplicable anything that actually has rational explanation; and willingness of the public to be fooled.The beauty with which I went to the cinema not realized the deception of the film until its final outcome. However, I've seen the trick 10 minutes to start the film, although confirmation that what I thought was happened last an hour. You you imaginaréis then where has been my fascination and enthusiasm for this magic number.(Sin_embargo,_apropiándo_me_de_las_palabras_deel_personaje_interpretado_por_Michael_Caine,_diré_que_todo_gran_truco_de_magia_consiste_en_tres_actos:_1) the presentation, the magician showing something that seems ordinary, but, of course,? It is not. (2) the performance, in which the magician makes the ordinary is transformed into something special; (and 3) prestige, the part with the unexpected twists, where you see something shocking that you had never seen before.Although for my prestige of the movie has become the first Act, the presentation and the action that makes Chris Nolan and company I have loved.The strong point is the rivalry of the two protagonists Magi, Robert Angier (Hugh Jackman) and Alfred Borden (Christian Bale), friends that respect each other until that fateful event makes them enemies encarnicados. From that moment begins a ruthless confrontation between the two for finishing each other with their careers, most obsessive by Angier, trying to do so discover the secret of the successful number of Borden of the people carrier.I was pleasantly surprised by the way in which Nolan tells the story. It is a little conventional, and in my opinion very sensible way of telling a plot requiring handed games to make it unpredictable: argument is clearly structured in the same three acts to which referred above, with a messy Assembly but with order (can apparently contradictory but when you see the movie understand it) and with continuous recurrence to the flashbacks. Something fresh and different from what is already known.Perhaps in the first minutes of the film, this approach can be confusing, but spent a little more than one quarter of an hour of footage one is perfectly situated on the thread of the story and understand the way in which it is mounted. This technique used by Nolan certainly creates an expectation to know what part of the plot will be below, which makes it more attractive.It has Visual and technically no buts. A good Victorian atmosphere, with a time in continuous changes London, situated perfectly the feelings of obsession, destruction and betrayal that frequent the film. It can be that the film also fails in the depth of the relationships of the characters with the actors, and some that another slip of script; But what really matters here is the terrifying? you to you? Jackman and Bale, collected with great skill (actors has enough blame for this), with which this detail becomes expendable.The film stars bring the magic. Jackman visibly transmits the unhealthy obsession of his character and is nice to see that unadorned werewolves is also an actor with stage presence. That Yes, until that deal again with his role as Wolverine will have the opportunity to further test their artistic skills. Sorry to not be more explicit because if I go in detail I leave a spoiler as a large House.Bale as much the same. Nor can I dwell much to speak of its interpretation, for reasons that will also understand when you see the film, but would only say that his career is reaching a very high peak due to its excellent qualities as an actor.Do as regards the? side? recognizable, Michael Caine, in his paper Cutter, ingeniero-representante Angier, acolyte is at its usual level. It always fills the screen, and never disappointed (at least to me).About Scarlett Johansson, you dashed those who go to the cinema only for her a disappointment because it has a character of little benefit as Mademoiselle. Olivia, an Assistant of Angier; a pair of demure exhibitions of pectoral merchandise and curves, and two or three scenes of some importance, settled with a good performance, is the only thing you will find.David Bowie as Nikola Tesla, passable. Andy Serkis as Alley of the lot.In conclusion, a Council: enjoy this film with an open willingness to ignore his trick, because surely you sorprenderéis.</body>
</review>
