<review author="Yul B." title="Arthur y los Minimoys" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you are going with your children to the cinema to see?Arthur and the Invisibles? You pasaréis a fun afternoon. That Yes, enjoy it with the spirit and the eyes of a child.</summary>
	<body>Said me a bird out there on this blog not critical films of animation with the appropriate point of view: that of a child.I even read a comment on one of our entries in which a reader predicts almost rightly we have no churumbeles (some Yes) for the way in which we writing about the news in question.It may be true; do first, something obvious: the drafters of this blog are no longer children, although I particularly have something of? kid-adult?; and, secondly, because it is such the avalanche suffered in the last years of animated films exclusively adult court, or theme interspersed between talludita and child, or only intended for children, already one loses perspective.So moved by the healthy slap me I decided to go see?Arthur and the Invisibles? with the intention of objectively be a toddler and put me in a situation. Pail large popcorn, a couple of chocolates, a bag of gums, and a bottle of water (cola soft drinks give me gas; what I am going to do, I can not deceive me both).The truth is that the film mixes real images and CGI, found me entertaining, ideal so her you can see with your children (who have them). The argument makes things much easier: just when his grandmother (Mia Farrow) is about to lose the House in which he lives, Arthur (Freddie Highmore), a 10-year-old boy, recalls that his grandfather he had spoken of a large hidden treasure in the land of the Minimoys, a universe of small fantastic beings that live in harmony with naturea world so distant and nevertheless so near and invisible to the human eye.Determined to save his grandmother, Arthur will get the key to enter therein and there will know the Princess Selenia and her brother Betameche. Together they will look for the hidden treasure and must face the evil M, in a fast-paced adventure.I love the aesthetics of video game that has this film. Luc Besson and his team have succeeded in creating a lively world very close to your destination, with a hotel look audience for the film. All CGI characters are designed in detail, but without being hyperrealistic, giving them a personality to each one of them easily recognizable. The Princess Selenia is a beauty.Do I could not help but remember of?The tiny? in many of the scenes taking place in the fascinating world of the Minimoys, which has been a virtue because for me the memories of this TV series are absolutely welcome.Perhaps the decision of not joining in the same scene real footage with CGI disconcerting even to the smallest Viewer, that the change of several planes of other animation with flesh bone, without apparent continuity, actors disturbs a bit. Except some that another story slip, the script is at good level, maintaining an adventurous tension directed clearly to not rest nor the most clueless child.As for the main actors, I just have exceptional words about Freddie Highmore. It is a machine of actor, hopefully keep this magic that transmits when it passes through adolescence and reach maturity, because if so we are before a crack in the history of the cinema; as Mia Farrow, sorry to say that it is expendable, because any other actress of his same fifth could have done this role.As I can not avoid having the age I am, flaws that I see as an adult of this film are as follows: the plot is so fast, that it not delves into the characters, not of flesh and blood, or animated, so there are times that the storyline is lost. Footage from the film, an hour and a low average, may be one of the reasons for this defect.On the other hand, although the film is aimed at children between 4 and 13 years, there are certain times with a sexual component uncomfortable and not very suitable for a child audience (though today children is very short).Do with explained, can say without risk to make mistakes that if are going to the movies with your children to see?Arthur and the Invisibles? You pasaréis a fun afternoon. That Yes, enjoy it with the spirit and the eyes of a child.</body>
</review>
