<review author="Bloody Will" title="Babel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you were to define a Word to?Babel? I would say: emotional. It is magnificent, and as such, it is one of the best products made this year. Please see and is advised, especially, feel.</summary>
	<body>If I had to define a word "Babel" would say: emotional. It is a film of feelings, human relations, human miseries and tragedies, the end and Cape. After spending the last few weeks watching movies you empty and with crude content, "Babel" has been around a film break. Respite for knowing that still makes film telling important stories.I침arritu, which already showed part of him in "Amores Perros" and "21 grams" has come with "Babel" to articulate a film with a priori disjointed vidas cruzadas. To catch you after the first frame you're understanding that Morocco, Mexico and Japan are not as far as you think. Perhaps remember something a "Crash", because the drama surrounds the life of each one of the characters that make up the film, but not you confund치is, "Babel" do not have histories of racism and prejudice, in "Babel" tell stories of humans arrived to limit, the frustration, the irresponsabbilidad and the sadness.Susan (Cate Blanchett) and Richard (Brad Pitt) travel by Morocco, however we fail ever to know why are there, and what has led them to that point on the planet. However that is not the important thing, but that their relationship, of will on their fragile, be tested after a dramatic accident, in which a native family in the country will be involved. Japan, Chieko, a deaf girl, becomes their worst moments: it is still Virgin, desperately searching for romance, and you must deal with her mother's fatal death, which affects her and his father in different versions. Finally, in San Diego, two children are in the care of a Mexican maid, which, in view of the long permanence of their parents outside, shall decide to take children to the wedding of his son in Mexico with a fitting end of stroke.I would like to extend over the synopsis, but it would be to reveal you aspects of the film that I prefer to be in surprise, as I happened to me at the beginning of the film. No doubt, all the characters take wrong decisions and fatal in the majority of cases, but are not decisions that not irme none of us. Without doubt, the story of the caretaker Mexican and American children makes me goose bumps, that I think how easy it is to trust someone that can mess up to the bottom. The story in Morocco shows the simplicity of a fortuitous setback and the sadness of not knowing whether who surrounds us is in free fall full passed me on Japan.Much to my regret, and after several disagreements with Brad Pitt I must admit is that it leaves in the hands of I침arritu. Get to maintain dramatic tension, as it must be, during his segment and its final collapse is much far from those ridiculously low tears of "Legends of passion". I would not surprise me that you entered into the Academy tickets for the next Oscars. His best counterpoint is Cate Blanchett, of which I can say that rarely disappoints me. Rinko Kikuchi, who plays the Japanese deaf girl performs the saddest performance that I have seen in recent years, and speak of emotional grief. This girl is Miss dust and trnasmite without saying a single word.Nothing matters to in "Babel" is change of the Moroccan into English, then to the Spanish and then to the Japanese. I침arritu makes these languages to flow as one only teach us that language is phonetically distinct words, that the human soul has the same soft you are where you are. It is magnificent, and as such, it is one of the best products made this year. Please see and is advised, especially, feel.</body>
</review>
