<review author="Bloody Will" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is designed to become a classic, while I doubt if this will be the part of the duo Iwo Jima it is most remarkable memory.</summary>
	<body>Increasingly more and more we expect from Mr. Clint Eastwood. Who we were going to say that that dirty Harry would become everything a landmark film in the 21st century. Pointing ways, back in 92 with the multioscarizada "Without pardon", Eastwood has managed to give his career a crescendo effect, with peak in "Million Dollar Baby", and culminating in the ambitious project of Iwo Jima to date: "Flags of our fathers", which lands first, and the next "Letters from Iwo Jima" which will come later.After brush these records go to the point: "Flags" is designed to become a classic, while I doubt if this will be the part of the duo Iwo Jima it is most remarkable memory. From the first frame up the last Eastwood looks the most moving war film of recent years, and this not be war, but by having the most petty of the Yankees feeling to battle the 2nd World War: the need for heroes at all costs. As a result, a patriotic film, with a portion of the history of America that is not is if everyone will be interested.Really, when I began to see the film didn't know exactly what I would be the director, if be scenes of fighting cruel style of "Saving private Ryan", or the scars of war in unfortunate beings as "The Hunter". Both schemes are interwoven in "Flags", and I have to say that it does in a masterful way. Flashbacks, a story-teller, phony interviews, all which allow Eastwood to move of forward towards back and vice versa, to finally complete the story in a way perfect. "Flags of our fathers" tells the story of the six men who, on the Hill of Iwo Jima, in the heat of the 2nd World War, placed the American being immortalized flag of for life. Conviritiéndose photography in an icon of war, 4 of them will return to the United States for a promotional tour in search of funding for the war. The memories of fallen comrades, and the difficulty of erecting in "famous" for nothing will change the course of their lives.I must confess that I was surprised pleasantly to find me in the middle of the plot with a so fierce critique of American society that raises to the heavens to people that really does nothing. It does not mean that the six men who flew the flag were on vacation, but that really was placed in battle, nor were killed while put, or anything like risk, something that, disregarding completely the American history, made me special grace.Thus, my favorite scenes are the three soldiers doing everything a "tour" show to get people to buy war bonds. The relationship so cold that it unites them, despite having shared dead in combat, and John Slattery, the figure of the "manager", ruthless, selfish and all an execrable individual, gives a dimension to the film that makes the soldiers little known, without to lose at the same time the most emotional of his weakness, side very difficult to accomplish when it is assumed that there must be more violence of medio.¿Todo is so good?, then not. Although together the entire fabric is perfectly embedded, interpretations fail to the quality of the script. On the basis that, from the beginning, I find it hard to distinguish Hank of Harlon, Doc and no-be-who-more with both hull up to eyebrows, Ryan Phillipe is too stiff, Paul Walker we hardly distinguished, Jamie Bell has little screen time and who has more dramatic weight in the film, the Indian Adam Beach, no outboard precisely. On the other hand the footage again, is excessive for what counts. They are 2 hours and 15 minutes, and vale that "Pirates 2 &Prime; lasts longer, but who said that" Pirates 2 &Prime; was short. "" As always, it's best to launch a film with intentions of Oscar with a worthy of Oscar footage. However at times the action relantiza unnecessarily.Those who go looking for a war without mercy movie are going to leave the room very disappointed. Perhaps there lie its failure at the box office. The public believed that he saw viscera and blood, and Eastwood in fact shows much more heart.What does I'm sure is, which a precedent like this, "Letters form Iwo Jima" it will be excellent, because Eastwood turn away from so much flag and patriotic sentiment to focus on the Japanese vision of the conflict, and that, in the hands of this director is something I don't want to lose me.</body>
</review>
