<review author="Bloody Will" title="María Antonieta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Two hours of beautiful images without any content. Without plot, without script, without words. A true relax my muscles with basically soporíferos results.</summary>
	<body>To it give back me my money. Just attend the screening of a new film experiment which did not know, is draw your attention premiering a film called "Marie Antoinette" (here "Marie Antoinette.") ("Queen teenager"), and directed by Sofia Coppola, but indeed colleagues, when you're sitting in front of the screen, you plug dormidina through a script, which swear is conformed by three folios. where is the Coppola for "Lost in Translation"?, well here is, but radicalizada to 100%. I do not lie it when I say unto the voice of Kirsten Dunst is not heard until well after 25 minutes. Nor I'm lying it when I say that they have to spend another 20 that are completed 3 consecutive sentences. Sofia Coppola has tried to tell the story of a teenage girl, Princess and later Queen, which is supposed is not very different from the others: light-hearted, partying and, with possible, a spender of the chalice. However, with all these elements, the story is slowly, without emotion and boring in most of its footage.The film tells the story of how Marie Antoinette spent her years in the Palace of Versailles, focusing on something so stupid how the attitude of Louis XVI by not touching her hair. The French revolution is played last, and such important events as the execution of the King, the Queen's own or an aspect truculenta tran how that of the best friend of Mary head was impaled and exposed to the own Queen must be of little significance for the Director. On the contrary, Coppola is dedicated to shaping a flat encephalogram and stupid Queen. Possibly, and in order to put something of cane to the issue Sofia Coppola has decided to decorate the whole with music by New Order, leaving this Union the most significant scene of the film, in which Mary and his court were desmadran in the halls of Versailles as if it were a rave. Even so, if I have to throw me hour and a half to see it, to put me in the trailer and we are already. Are they needed two hours in total to tell the binge spirit of the protagonist? , liked the clothes, drink, play and sex, yet the way to tell is the most pretentious thing I've seen in a long time. Looking for some history of the Queen of France I find "look how passes the aunt in his palace".If there is one thing which can not condemn the Director is that detail missing. The image and the atmosphere of the film is fine, reminding me quite aesthetic that had several scenes of "Lost in Translation", because Coppola is recreated over and over again in stop people and how it moves everything to his around, but once again, the plot breaks it all. The lack of sexual interest of Mary's husband takes more time than necessary and after a while, all this so beautiful versaillesque aesthetic to the principle becomes redundant and tiresome.If we need to think of the interpretations of the film, here goes: Kirsten Dunst gives the same depth to his character than to an ashtray. I do not know if the own Coppola is responsible for that not be deepen more the historical character, but so much disregard and pasotismo through the interior of the character is not credible if we take into account that Marie Antoinette is not passed to the history by vanal. Jason Scwartzman, the husband of Mary, passing by. Said to him: "get a suit of era and pusillanimous beam". It borda it in both tasks, and the chemistry between the two characters is that has to be: zero. The only one that deserves my attention is Asia Argento, and yet his interpretation is flat.In conclusion, "Marie Antoinette." "Teenage Queen" has meant for me nearly two hours of beautiful images without any content. Without plot, without script, without words. A true relax my muscles with basically soporíferos results. If you pass the constant action, this is your movie. For me it is a joke. Didn't the abucheada Coppola in Cannes.?</body>
</review>
