<review author="Marta" title="Paradise now" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without being a masterpiece, it seems interesting enough to be recommended</summary>
	<body>On Friday I saw, at long last, Paradise Now, a film which, without being a masterpiece, seems interesting enough to deserve to be recommended. Had already long been hearing about it, and a nomination for an Oscar seems a good argument in favour (in the category of foreign film, because the other does not use anything as a reference point Academy). The truth is that, except a couple of things, I quite liked. The story is of two Palestinian youths who are chosen to carry out a suicide attack. Point. Not tell more. The case is that we always hear of these things in the news and I think that we fail to make the idea that what lies behind these acts are people, people like any of us, with their fears, their concerns and their dreams. Paradise Now get that we get to see the characters as real people, that doubt and which reflects; and, although we do not agree with them, we can understand the whys. It is so difficult to see that what lies behind the international news is not a species of "indefinite mass". The film achieved that we realize that, in reality, are not so different that all suffered and we all want (and one of the protagonists uses exactly the same toothbrush I!). Unfortunately, I had to see it folded, and resulted from the strange thing to listen to Palestinians with the same voice than American actors. Against arguably could dig a little deeper in other characters that offer different views of the same conflict, and the pace a bit wrong. At a crucial moment, the film begins to be something slow and boring, when precisely it should convey the most intense emotions. Anyway, appreciated the opportunity to see something like that, that touches a sensitive subject with sensitivity and you get to see it in a different way. A scene to remember: one of the two protagonists are recording one of those protest videos of the attacks suicide, and remember to tell his mother where he has to buy the water filter. Sweet, absurd and tragic at the same time. Go to see it. It is worth the trouble.</body>
</review>
