<review author="Kahzrrak" title="Eragon" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>And now comes the required question: and if someone tells me that he has not read the book nor wants to do this?, because in that case the film you'll love, because as the basis of the script is good, for those who do not know all that missing, going you to like.</summary>
	<body>And, as it could not be otherwise, here came I talking about this palícula. Now recall that I spoke at the time of this book (and, if not, look in Yo Geek in April 2006) and put it through the roof: in fact the book was pretty good (nothing like the Lord of the rings, but books like that there is only one). Perhaps that is why the film has seemed so mediocre. We return again to an important issue: who can think sum up such book in one hour and forty minutes?. History in armchair loses a lot strength: let you explain a lot of things. Poorly represented characters (what Paolini village lost in the horns the úrgalos? from the Elf when appears half in love with Eragon?. and goes on and on), not to mention the "peazo" throne that has Galbatorix.Tampoco explains where Durza does, the name of the Dragon is prefixed by Eragon, not be invented it (in fact, in the book is given some importance to the name)(, as that was the name of a very famous Dragon in the history of Paolini), not to mention that Saphira constantly leads the opposite to Eragon (and of course, is not "what you say blonde," as they say in the film). Let's talk about something else: to anyone who has not read the book know where does the power of magic?: I won't say here if someone even has intention of reading the book, which is one of the things that make the book to have consistency and, in fact it will be important in the second part(: anyway, if unto someone was curious, to ask me in the section "comments" and will reply you). In short, that the script has been quite bungler.And now comes the required question: and if someone tells me that he has not read the book nor wants to do this?, because in that case the film you'll love, because as the basis of the script is good, for those who do not know all that missing, going you to like.Another point: talk about the place where the vardenos are hidden: we must recognize that the mental image writer (Christopher Paolini) left in my mind of such a place, not correspond at all to the scenario in which the battle of the end of the film then unfolds! (I know, the vardenos lived in a kind of 'hollow mountain', not in a kind of Valley with a shabby wooden Middle bridge).In summary: If you've not read the book, probably the movie you like. If you've already read the book, probably the film also you like, but will be quite disappointed in comparison to how one makes you vibrate.</body>
</review>
