<review author="Kahzrrak" title="La alianza del mal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You can wait to hang out with her, but since then I have known before, would have not gone to see her movies or joke.</summary>
	<body>Good afternoon, dear readers. Here comes again your dear colleague and neighbor. i.e., I. Today we come to talk about cinema. The truth is that I'm a little late but, with my apologies, not I have written earlier by that "labour issues". Let's talk about a partnership that, unfortunately, and much to my regret, seems to me that won't be as famous as some had hoped.We are talking about a story primarily of science fiction, at least to my mind, that (as someone told me there): but wasn't terror?. because the truth is that it tries to, but of fear gives more but little, except for a couple of sustillos of low level (course, from that I saw on a large surface, the film "Outbreak" classified as terror, I believe anything). The truth is that I went to the cinema with intention to watch another movie, but when I saw that the investigation was not, however, had just planted on Billboard "Alliance of evil", said: because this I had also wanted to see her, as announced on TV were a couple of scenes that were very good. As well: the truth is that the effects are not bad, although it is not that they are wonderful, but the script is disastrous. I don't know how you can lose in nothing an idea that, although repeated, could give so much of themselves for a few geeks like us. He is a series of families, the "sons of Ipswich", generation after generation ranging through is "powers" of parents to children. These families are United not only by friendship, but also by such secret, because in modern times they were persecuted and killed for witchcraft. Some supposed powers of this depth and a typical cast of teenagers (supposedly teenagers, because I doubt that anyone has less years than I) guaperas, even if they are already very seen, they could have given more than Yes, of course with little more than an hour and a half of duration, all good intentions would be nothing (do anything any producer and/or director thought that a good movie that isn't child can develop in such a short time?).By the way, because I have a joint with my colleagues page, take this opportunity to complain: who would think that making the film six euros is a good idea? really will think that economics is to risk again to go see a film of which I doubt any? From now on, and with prices that are being theaters (and make clear that I know in Madrid and Catalonia it will be still more expensive, which seems even more chilling) gives me the feeling that more than one we will rethink very much if we are going to return to go to the movies (and they will be able to tell me now that the number of clients has not lowered?)(, because that what I do not think), except to see authentic peliculones (i.e. one of thousand.).Putting already here my complaint, step to summarize the issue: the synopsis I her I said and, although found me little, the truth is that not I tell you more without risk of spoiling you the movie (logically, a movie of an hour and a half, slightly more must have). In short, you can expect to hang out with her, but since then I have known before, not would have gone to see her movies or joke.</body>
</review>
