<review author="Plissken" title="Mujeres en el parque" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Women in the Park I thought it was boring, neglected and, what is worse, seems to be made only for its director and his screenwriter.</summary>
	<body>Show me. How to write this without that one of the creators of the film take it badly. Bah, I can not. 'Women in the Park' I thought it was boring, neglected and, what is worse, seems to be made only for its director and his screenwriter.Official Synopsis: "Daniel, music teacher and pianist and Ana, gallerist, in crisis of couple after more than twenty years of life in common." Daniel has gone to live alone and wants to divorce. Anne refuses to accept the reality.Distress affects his daughter Monica, which, after finishing the career of journalism, is particularly sensitive to not find work, task which is dedicated along with her boyfriend, David.La music seems to be the only activity that focuses and sosiega Daniel, a man uncomfortable I get same and others, and a relationship that is far from perfect with Clara", a married woman that arouses the curiosity of Monica. A night, Monica lives an incomprehensible and embarrassing episode in which becomes involved along with Daniel and Ana Clara."My Synopsis: "Daniel and Ana are in the process of separation, and do not communicate too well." Monica, her daughter, cannot find work, and also communicates well. When you try to rebuild his relationship with his father, he meets Clara, her lover to not communicate well neither she, nor her father. The one that seems not experience communication problems is David, Monica's boyfriend. A pity that is surrounded by so much incommunicado. They all walk through Retiro "Felipe Vega, director, and Manuel Hidalgo, screenwriter, they claim to have focused on the characters when creating 'Women in the Park', and ensure that themselves characters are that, with total freedom, shape history." The first thing I think so, because it is true that the main characters are absolutely consistent with its nature, from beginning to end: come on, progression, the minimum. Daniel (Adolfo Fernández), Anne (Blanca Apilánez) and Clara (Emma Vilarasau) make up a triangle monochord, inexplicably lacking in tension. Monica (Barbara Lennie) should be the reagent to finally jump Sparks, but stays too long in the position of simple observer. David (Alberto Ferreiro) is a mere accessory to reveal Monica copy the conduct of his father. The other side, better not speak, because they are simple Springs script so that the characters can tell you about themselves. In summary: Vega and Hidalgo don't tell a story, they show the miseries of characters close to them, perhaps, but vastly alien to me, for example.At the technical level is also reflected the priority of director and screenwriter: most of the film's sequences are static dialogues between two characters, most of them seated and determined to master/level/contraplano. The other half of sequences are walking in the Park of the Retiro and surroundings, illustrating, I suppose, the closure of these characters. Man, not say I that make travelling circulars, but if the narrative of alone it was already non-existent rhythm deteriorates to the fainting. Or the cabezada.Not everything is negative. The interpretations are adjusted, but the characters are so content that the actors sometimes rub the hieratismo. They are generally correct, highlighting Bárbara Lennie in the positive part and a kid very hostiable making student of the Professor of music at the negative side.But worst of all is not statism and sobriety (poverty) or visual, or the feeling of me are counting something that me doesn't interest me. The worst thing is that the last twenty minutes are dedicated to trying to give an explanation to the dysfunctional of all these relationships, with a twist worthy of a soap opera and totally out of place. Go fabric, so sobriety and then come me with them.In short, I bored me and much, and still not know who expect those responsible for the film than his public. 4, For the performances.</body>
</review>
