<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Caja Kovak" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Kovak box is a film of remarkable intrigue, that fulfills its function perfectly, keep intigrado to the public until the last moment.</summary>
	<body>The thriller, intrigue and mystery films have not been historically very cultivated in the film Spanish, while in recent years is trying to remedy that. And most of these works have nothing to envy to major foreign productions, since they are very on top in terms of intelligence and originality. Spanish film is gradually losing their complexes with other film, and has demonstrated the capacity to address all kinds of genres and succeed in the challenge. Now, are the spectators who must forget prejudices against different Spanish films, and with examples such as La Caja Kovak, the company should not be very complicated.Daniel Monzón directed his third feature film, after a fairy tale, the heart of the Warrior and a wacky comedy, El Robo Más Grande never cash. Filmmaker proposes a thriller with La Caja Kovak psicólogico which does not take the Viewer by silly, which, although at first glance it seems an obvious achievement is commendable today. The opening credits sequence is a good sample of what you can expect from the film. David Norton (Timothy Hutton), a renowned science fiction writer travels to Mallorca to give a lecture, but in the course of your stay, will suffer a terrible loss. With the help of Silvia (Lucía Jiménez), a young and energetic girl, David will try to discover the strange events taking place in the island, and which person in charge seems to be an old man called Kovak (David Kelly). Daniel Monzón immerses the viewer in a disturbing and labyrinthine story, and not loose until that appear uncredited. The Kovak box is a film of intrigue and mystery made with the same spirit of the great classics of the genre, and is honest with himself, and that it offers what it promises, without any trap. Little by little, the tape will increasing intensity, and at the same time, the atmosphere that creates monsoon becomes more harrowing, catching the viewer completely, leaving him breathless and at the total mercy of the vagaries of the plot. In no time monsoon uses easy, free truculence, scares or the guts. Special mention merecn the last thirty minutes of La Caja Kovak and his intense climax. Technically, the film is outstanding, as well as the interpretative work of Timothy Hutton, Lucía Jiménez and David Kelly, which embroider their roles under the careful direction of the Majorcan.The Kovak box is a film of remarkable intrigue, that fulfills its function perfectly, keep intigrado to the public until the last moment, and it's an excellent example of good artistic health affecting the Spanish film.</body>
</review>
