<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="María Antonieta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Marie Antoinette is quite improved, both in the aspect of the strength of the script, sometimes apparent lack of feelings behind the cameras. Nevertheless, it has an admirable production design and style with an exquisite taste.</summary>
	<body>After seeing the great Lost in translation, one could have very high hopes with the new draft of the daughter of Francis, Sofia Coppola. At least, I had them. As it turns out that his new project for her, the closure of the trilogy of the misunderstanding, is based not in the story of a young sisters and two individuals lost in Tokyo, but in the life of Marie Antoinette, which at the time was Queen France. This astonishing decision, according to her, is based on the portrait of a young misunderstood at the Court with a style of the Director. For me, is based on the portrait of a being misunderstood in a court that did not understand anyone and in excess of pastels, lace and flowers. But above all, Marie Antoinette presents a delicate scene (virtually perfect), some formidable performances, a beautiful photograph and music chosen with exquisite taste.The script might present a rhythm excessively slow and repetitive, but I will say what else can tell of the life of a teenager living on cakes and lace. So what is made to miss are deeper relations between the Court, political debates (appear, but very superficial)? In my opinion, I think that Coppola could have gotten a lot more advantage, not the girl, but all her surrounding, but not him he belonged. Okay, is entertaining and cool record, cakes, (tuned to the All Stars!) shoes and lace, but think that the Director of Lost in translation could have filled this void that is both noticeable in history. While it is true that the script is not bad, nor much less. I am thinking it may be a bit empty, but poorly structured is not. Despite its slow pace and some that another downturn is a totally innovative and captivating film. But this, I think that he owes more to his style which not in the script.Austrian cakes, flowers, dresses and rock and roll.Some criticize the style of Coppola saying that it is empty, posh and immoderate hijísima. But let's see! In his films, for me, what most influences is the style. So you enter or not enter. I went in Lost in translation, and I was amazed. His second feature was in the 21st century, i.e. that it was not a film of time. Marie Antoinette, obviously, yes it is. And one may wonder: how will its modernísmo reflected style in a film of time?. Very simple. The issue is to have good taste to add modern music in scenes of time and make you believe that society has not changed much. And for my succeeds. Moreover, can the film style is what attracts me most. Perhaps occasionally exceed (especially with show shoes and dresses) but is that really what this set of "animal" of the Court lived. Although I have to say that the best part is the music. Songs of New Order, The Cure and Gang of Four, and all of them are exceptional (highlighting Celebration of the first group). Although also introduces music of the 18th century, suppose that you to not load too staff. Best scene with modern music is undoubtedly that of the Ballo in Maschera, with a song by Siouxsie &amp; the Banshees, totally incréible.He has accused Sofia Coppola do not portray the people (who at that time was playing poverty). I think that the retarta bit, like the Court and the political events, but also think the key scene of the film is that that Marie Antoinette takes his defeat over showing to the people, who intends to kill her. It is a superbly shot scene and that counts more than it seems, like the delicate and arriesgadísimo level of change of box (who has seen already will know what I mean). So, ultimately, I have to say that the film fails when it exceeds and on the other hand, when it summarizes an important event in a short sequence, is when it is most incredible.Another absolutely remarkable point is the sublime interpretation of Kirsten Dunst. His role, despite contain totally empty feelings, is portrayed with expertise and common sense. Certainly, the performance of this girl deserves some prize, although I doubt they give. Also appearances of Jason Swartzman and Judy Davis are wonderful (what aging is!), in a totally different but unique roles.In conclusion, it could be argued that Marie Antoinette is quite improved, both in the aspect of the strength of the script, sometimes apparent lack of feelings behind the cameras. Nevertheless, it has an admirable production design and style with an exquisite taste.</body>
</review>
