<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Mujeres en el parque" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The truth is that I love the films about intimate relationships between people, but if one is not going to be able to do a good job it is better to resort to other great classics.</summary>
	<body>I don't know if the fact of being a strange and lonely person has made me worship films that talk about the social relations; the comings and goings of a group of something silly beings and, above all, very selfish, usually known by the name of human. However, I must also acknowledge that when a feature of these features does not meet a minimum of expectations, the result is more negative than with other kinds of less pretentious genres.Something like I thought when I saw women in the Park, the last work of Felipe Vega. A supposed drama which chronicles the emotional crisis of a couple and the impact that leads to this problem on the closest environment: his daughter. The intention of the director has been the Add reality on the subject and in some respects has done (some other dialogue, the interpretation of Bárbara Lennie, urbanized images of Madrid) but the main problem lies in the lack of depth and search, above all, because we are talking about feelings.As auction, to try to get out of step, the ending suspiciously revolves and gives the feeling that this trick is an attempt to cover the lack of creative research, but all you get is increasing disbelief to a story which is very real. Nor very clear the existence of certain characters and its importance in the development of the story (the heavy student overflows Monica with questions and when it starts to show its interior disappears - and it is a shame because it is one of the more interesting character - or friend with aspirations to violator of Ana).The truth is that I love the films about intimate relationships between people but if one is not going to be able to do a good job is better to rely on other great classics that still worst bring you more profit at the box office (musical with people that we can sing, comedies with scurfy humor, with many nude films and short argument)(, suffered widows penniless dramas that go to market with a suit of Gucci and bun from hairdresser, etc.).</body>
</review>
