<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Prestige is a film that entertains, and since it is designed as such, I think that it does not deserve more trial than intended. Meets and, note, its objective.</summary>
	<body>If we make a comparison between the film and the magic, we could get many parecidos.y of course, differences. 'The Prestige' is film with magic, and trick. A good story, which never leaves aside the characters and giving you everything what is intended to: Entertainment.The problem is that it seems that from the outset, they are telling us that we we have this trick. A trick, everything must be said, that seems rather a succession of ellos.pero that is relatively easy to realize in the course of the film. And if not? Better, you will most enjoy the tape.Two London magicians of the 19th century, following the tragic death of the wife of one of them, begin a struggle to put an end to the career (and life) of the other. Perhaps simple argument for some, but with the presentation Nolan made the film, and thanks to its protagonists (great deal), makes the film more than interesting, to the point of being highly recommended, that Yes, to a mere enjoyment of the 'magical' film.A remarkable aspect of this last film of Director Christopher Nolan is its continued interest because the Viewer is attentive to the screen. As a magic trick, Yes. And although at the beginning the pace may be somewhat slow, and in fact, it is possible that you on some footage, the expectation increases thanks to a few good shots of effect by the director, the script, the excellent ambiance and the quality of the performances: Hugh Jackman and Christian Bale are the height, as well as Michael Caine (as always)though but it is true that the role of Scarlett Johansson is not as important as for his showcasing (or precisely it was only to show it off?).The Prestige is a film that entertains, and since it is designed as such, I think that it does not deserve more trial than intended. Meets and, note, its objective.</body>
</review>
