<review author="Rafa Marin" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We have the first great film of the year. A serious and rigorous adaptation that does not have any qualms about simplify the history of the novel, cutting it in the precise and stripping of secondary sub-plots.</summary>
	<body>Good movies of good books, can be although it surprised us. And it can be to remain faithful to the spirit and the characters and betraying the letter whatever is missing so the film product, which will never remove the book from where it starts, can understand itself and is, in its own structure, a work that hold single. It is what they have done Christopher Nolan and his brother Jonathan with the work of his namesake Christopher Priest: a serious and rigorous adaptation that does not have any qualms about simplify the history of the novel, cutting it in the precise and stripping it of secondary sub-plots to focus simply on the history of shared obsession with two magicians and their continuous feints in search of a revenge has no meaning beyond the pursuit of confrontation by the prestige. Raised almost like a play in their lack of scenic air, almost always in closed enclaves which refer to the scenarios or the scenes where the two magicians (or their engineers or scientists) are its representations and their training, prestige (absurdly pretitulada in Spain "The final trick", I imagine that because the same the name of the movie recalls a sunken ship that conveniently then did not want to agree to no one) is a scenic duel between Hugh Jackman and Christian Bale, converted each in reflection of the other, with juicy game narrative, in mirrors of themselves. Helps rather than a giant of the interpretative as Michael Caine provided the necessary serenity and appreciated that, stripped of subterfuges narrative history, the presence of three women on stage (including the beautiful Scarlett Johansson) is adequately high. Without renouncing the narrative technique of desbarajados flashbacks so good result gave in Memento and Batman Begins, here the feints in the feints allow perfectly the game of newspapers and discoveries, structural hocus passes that can confuse who is not in the garlic of the narration from the beginning. Because, as they warn the images and the voice of Michael Caine, everything is in sight and the narrative of the film already shows, almost at the beginning, between the Canaries, is the great mystery of the trick of the Transportado man. The graduation of the history improves the climax of the book, and focuses to perfection in the appearance of Nikola Tesla, perhaps too soberly interpreted by a severe David Bowie, or perhaps I expect to see something closer to Ziggy Stardust. Although it hints in any line of dialogue, it would have been interesting to see some of the compulsive food obsessions of the own Tesla in the lunch scene. With planes that sometime referred to Coppola's Dracula (arrival at Colorado powerfully reminds the arrival of Jonathan Harker to Transylvania, and in some walk in London one almost can see close to anda Mina Murray in the body of Wynona Rider), the dramatic tension builds up in an intense narrative, almost to against the grain in the film today. Perhaps somewhat loses the reference quantum tongue-in-cheek to the cat of Tesla and his science ahead of time, so the viewer will no doubt believe that we are seeing a new magic trick. Deliberately confined to an apparent secondary role (perhaps in the book her character has more force), Christian Bale gives much of the footage and the performance to a magnificent Hugh Jackman, who is not only able to briefly play a dual role, but that changing her pose and imagine that slightly his physique, gives the impression of being another person indeed: we will have to wait for the DVD to hear him declaim to Henry IV in his constant drunkenness. Only must be set carefully to realize that we are before the first great film of the year.</body>
</review>
