<review author="José A. Peig" title="Salvar al soldado Ryan" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a great movie by Spielberg, it is a superfluous product, but it is a great visual spectacle and entertainment consumption easy mode adventure film with a speech followed American institutional dogmas.</summary>
	<body>Third raid of Steven Spielberg in the second world war, popularly acclaimed in the past eight years since its premiere as one of his masterpieces and one of the best war films of all time, which is a mistake, start there. "Saving private Ryan", not only it is not a masterpiece but that I could say that it is one of the films most insubstantial, overblown and failures of the Filmography of the "King midas" of Hollywood. A filmography, incidentally step, so amazing and prodigious as irregular.However, are talking about one of the best narrators of the last forty years, a filmmaker already in their own right, as part of the basic iconography of the seventh art. Therefore soldier Ryan, being a product that does not reach the height of their claims, neither is it a brilliant, full film great moments that look the mastery of a visual and scenographic orchestration of the anthology. Anthology is the initial sequence of twenty minutes in length, by the creation of a climax of reality naked and torn, the "hiperrealism" that Spielberg inaugurated a style imitated in recent productions: "Flags of our fathers" or "Children of men". Never filmed the harshness of the battlefield of the way in which did Spielberg, and the fact that certain constituent sequences of a foundational style - in the framework of the cinema of masses - been imitation reason make them a small contemporary classic.Spielberg is a master when it comes to give show, we have no doubt, and the soldier Ryan is, above all, a show developed in a context of war film. The problem is that it is intended to be a discursive reflection on the war and on human ethics dilemmas and the military code of conduct. And, in the words of the own Spielberg, also wants to be an anti-war film, which is already hilarious. You have already hinted you at in the previous comment: Spielberg is not an intellectual, is not trained to deal with ideological problems of a certain complexity. Spielberg is a kid with a great visual imagination and moves very well in the field of entertainment, of drawing the strong emotional profiles and feelings of helplessness in areas like the fable ("AI"), science fiction ("encounters in the third stage") or the more Classicist melodrama ("the color purple"), to give examples.But certainly lacks sufficient maturity intellectual to know what is an anti-war film. The antibelicismo, in film, involves a cold and distant look to show us the nonsense and absurdity of war, emptying the space and the visual content of symbols, justifications and collective representations about the contest. And what makes Spielberg is just the opposite; you want to show the horror of the war, but not eyebrow in trying to convince us that everything has a justification, that there is a reward and a merit. Thus, input, "Saving private Ryan" shows the incoherence and superficiality of a child facing a speech before which does not have sufficient resources.The theme and history, look at the simplicity: we must save a soldier because sends it the Chief of the General staff (for the glory of patriotic heroes and their respective mamaítas) and you are responsible mission to another group of soldiers who spend the entire film wondering if it is worth sacrificing their lives for the life of a single soldier. Or what is the same, but changing the human reference framework, the question of whether is ethical and morally legitimate to kill one hundred men knowing that you are saving the lives of others many, either 200 or the computation of any Western defence civilization of which, a guess, the war was fought. Spielberg is positioned without blushing, manipulating the Viewer without any hint of subtlety; the conclusion is that any war or act of death is justifiable if done on behalf of certain institutional values and, above all, on behalf of the collective or individual humanity. In the individual case of the soldier Ryan, the sacrifice of John Miller (Tom Hanks) is a reason for Ryan justified the deaths of his companions with that of "tell me that I've been a good person". Spielberg used almost three hours to speak to us about these simplicities.Deserves the case highlight the bland and excessive footage, are nearly three hours for a very static development and too repetitive structure. This temporary space is completely untapped as its characters just evolve. See his central character, simply place a space journey, but his demeanor, his gestures and decisions - loaded with different nuances, as we shall see - are the same at the end than at the beginning. The side do not go to a filling, on the other hand, quite effective. This responds to the true nature of the film; an excuse for filming many scenes of action and that worldwide applaud the excellent virtues of Spielberg in the operation of the camera, angulation, the pace, the Mise en scène.In script, too often falls into a drama helpings and uncouth: as in the scene of the soldier who wants to take and protect the girl: "it reminds me of my niece".The speech is well-meaning, justified the war but expected that the war has served to a worthy end: because those men sacrificed their lives for our welfare and in defence of our style of life and enlightened values, at least, be good people. In the end.The speech is so pamphleteering, obvious and simplistic, ends up damaging the impeccable visual and technical Bill.However, we have a spectacular and bright, product with superb, but irregular moments as a whole. Best of the function, is undoubtedly his character protagonist, John Miller, a profile with a bitter and contradictory gesture at his disposal of military commander and human being protective and responsible for the security of their boys. During the film he is torn between the duty under the military code and feelings towards his pupils. There is a superb scene - probably the best, authentic luxury interpretive - reflecting the dimensionality of the character: after the death of one of his boys, immediate cause of their unnecessary commitment to cover ground according to a purely military target, we see Miller in solitude trying to suppress tears, struggling with himself with the human part of the military subject to a code of ethics. In this regard, Miller represents the complexity of a tormented character who plays two irreconcilable bands. It is John Miller, in short, the human profile that gives personality and versatility film to the film, the only one that truly takes back us to that classic taste of John Ford.En synthesis, saving private Ryan is not a great movie by Spielberg, it is a superfluous product, but yes it is a great visual spectacle and entertainment consumption easy mode adventure film with a speech followed American institutional dogmas.Don't enter to assess whether such institutional dogmas are good or evil, useful or ineffective, legitimate or illegitimate, fair or unfair (that is not our goal). What we are concerned and occupies is that Spielberg is limited to "copy" and incorporate them in a plain speech, with which many moviegoers will say - good reasons - that this film is an act of propaganda in 163 minutes.In the language of the film, the opening narration and the image that closes play a decisive role. Well, here begins with a map of the flag of the United States of America and ends with a map of the same flag. Hold it by where you can.</body>
</review>
