<review author="Caruco" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do do do the? Italian Colt VI?, stands in one of the products most? trash? of the Billboard. Pure Z series that can raise their sympathies.</summary>
	<body>Drooping eyes, sad, crooked mouth and aspect, despite the years and blows, yet strong and good-natured. Stallone returns to unearth the trunk of memories to the most famous boxer of film fiction. And rather than dedicate a mausoleum, his character is still alive and eager to fight, so dedicated a monument, if same, facts and beloved people of the past. Fans of the saga "Rocky" is it will pass well.In his retirement, double the world heavyweight champion already not dedicated to distribute smacks in the ring, but yes to divide tips among friends, acquaintances and everyone who is cruze good in their way, although not come and beside the point. Also to tell their war stories of the past again and again to unknown fans or customers of his restaurant, if purposely coming because it is included in the menu of your "do Adrian? s".And has its charms a film during most of its footage is filmed in a realistic and street way go destelleando veneer of all the fantastic up to move into the mainstream in the most incredible ground during its final stretch. When the legendary Rocky Balboa, of nearly 60 years, enfunde the trousers and gloves again to endure not only the type in the quadrilateral sinó also to give cane to a more young and undefeated rival, a machine to distribute vain leñazos and unpopular called Mason "The Line, Dixon, portrayed by Antonio Tarver (real and current Middleweight Champion)", and had not yet given with the toebox of the shoe.Never feel that it has been completed.For Rocky, combat will help to leave behind vacuum by not able to return to demonstrate what one really was and is, and a son tontorrón and acomplejado by the long shadow of his father.Rocky never throws the towel. Do its formal daring reaches dip of the black and white,? close-ups? and? zooms? fast; broken images, vintage style or making television, emulating a broadcast on television. Do do do do for that, and for the whole, "Rocky Balboa", the? Italian Colt VI?, stands in one of the products most? trash? of the Billboard. Pure Z series that can raise their sympathies and which, in its decadent vision of the show, even comes as ring to the finger take to Las vegas as the setting for the final confrontation.The steps of the Philadelphia Museum of art, immortalized in the first Rocky, are the subject of a special tribute; and also famous music Bill Conti, and the "Gonna fly now", become more slow and melancholic, to explode in its euphoria before the arrival of the final fight inmininente.But I'll stick with that old and abandoned dog hosts the protagonist, played by Baskis, the same can Stallone property; and with those close-ups of an aging Rocky, Cap ready and perhaps defeated by the years and memories. And little else.</body>
</review>
