<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Babel" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that leaves no one indifferent and that view once and announced the divorce between Arriaga and Iñarritu, leaves us with the question of which will continue to both parties of an extraordinary pairing that, with this route?Does babel?, as well as with?Love dogs? and? 21 grams? It has set the bar very high.</summary>
	<body>The flapping of a butterfly in Hong Kong can unleash a storm in New York. This is the poetic definition of chaos theory, also known as butterfly effect. And "Babel", an original ideal of González Iñarritu and Guillero Arriaga, part of a premise as simple as worrying: a grateful Hunter gives his gun to his mountain guide. and this simple gesture will affect and trastornará the lives of four families forever.Chester Himes, for its part, in the introduction to his wonderful "A blind man with a pistol" departed from an anecdote that told you a friend, Phil Lomax. According to his friend, "a blind man had been shot with a pistol against a man who had slapped him on the subway and had killed an innocent spectator reading his newspaper on the other side of the ride quiet." And I thought: damn is, just as the news of today, the riots in the ghettos, the war in Viet Nam, masochistic acts in the Middle East. "Then I thought of one of the leaders of strident voice that incite our vulnerable brothers of soul and harass them to make killing, and finally thought that all disorganized violence is like a blind man with a pistol".Breton, father of surrealism, argued that the surreal act par excellence would be to take to the streets armed with a gun and firing indiscriminately into the crowd. Can the boot in "Babel" be an example of globalized surrealism in which we are plunged into this boot of the 21st century?Photographs of tourists in the Atlas Moroccan, watching the landscape from the Windows of a bus, as the astronauts watch outer space, as if they were in a Zoo, but upside down, tucked inside his cage of glass to protect themselves from a hostile environment; they are a perfect example of that surrealism which flows in a bullet missed, absurd, impossible and meaningless that triggers an unpredictable sequence of events linked together by chance, fate and a chaotic to precise sequence of cause-effect as unlikely as some.Paul Bowles was carried the deep South of Morocco the characters of "Protective heaven" to address his existential vacuum with vacuum of a wilderness and border space in which begins black, poor, unknown Africa and hopeless. Arriaga and Iñarritu do the same with those parents who seek solitude in the crowd to overcome by the loss of a child. "And this effort almost cost them life, to them and, paradoxically, their other two children, living comfortably in the modern and prosperous San Diego.""Babel" is a border film that speaks of silence, solitary confinement, the clash of cultures, globalization, the contradiction and dissatisfaction. It is an undogmatic, without good and bad film. It is a film that drinks of surrealism, Existentialism and the aforementioned chaos theory. Have we evolved really? Towards where? Sense for our life?The Japanese part of the story is thematically more fix far-fetched, but it is very illustrative in this regard. If the open spaces of the Atlas can be arid and oppressive, nothing more distressing than the deep and unfathomable loneliness that you may feel in a room, at a restaurant in a plaza or a disco, spaces all brimming with people.As all movies episodes, and this is, as much as the three stories are linked, there are fragments achieved more than others. Personally, perhaps because I identify with the landscape, aesthetically I like the Moroccan side of the story, humanly, excites me that most nanny character which, among all and almost without that she can do anything, they complicate you and fuck the existence. However, the Japanese history ends making somewhat tired.The character of the girl sordomuda and his deep grief are so long. Curiously, however, it is the part that better connects with the previous work of the Mexican, one of the eleven stories of the film shorts that many directors around the world filmed on the attacks of the 11-S, where skyscrapers, artificial silence and leap into the void acquire all ownership.We have a great ultracontemporánea film that, even though not perfect, is told with the premiosidad history requires putting feelings into a foreground. A film that leaves no one indifferent and that view once and announced the divorce between Arriaga and Iñarritu, leaves us with the question of the way to follow the two parts of a binomial extraordinary that, with this "Babel", as with "love dogs" and "21 grams" has put the bar very high, putting in images that tempus fugit which accompanies the human being since man is man.</body>
</review>
