<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Long film about the goings of wizards, it would be surprising if simply incredibly had translated the original title. Even so, the final product is of very high quality, despite the slippages in the pace at which we amuerman.</summary>
	<body>Hi, for some time that I it was not anodadado to the title of a film. It is this called in English "The prestige", whose translation may be "The prestige". Okay, so it is already is to say what is already sold pescao. Because they have had to change the name to fuck us the surprise ending. It reminds me the movie the fear that "The son of the Rosamary" should have called and it was called "The seed of the devil", when it could well have been "the Mary Rose is the has the devil follao". Seeing is believing.The film's two apprentices of Mage which are separated by things that happen. Well, for things that happen and that one makes something that other sit as a kick in the testicles themselves. Total, they are mounted on their own, but as they are the best two of London (and in Europe and in the whole world) devoted part of its efforts to bitching to another. Indeed, nothing more to start it seems that one kills the other drowning him, that I had forgotten. Heh, heh.I have to admit that, for a change, not I learned too well. The use of the flashback kills me completely, and spends half movie changing its aspect to bitching to another, because I do not hear. But as my medium Zucchini if he finds me guide with wisdom. The first thing is to comment that the movie is long, and is long. Also as you know that at the end there is a tremendous Fireworks (which does not lock) because you you spend the time thinking about what it will be. The atmosphere is more than correct, and the plot is very successful. I was pleasantly surprised by the inclusion of Nikola Tesla, and know that the magicians of the time were engineers who rode them all the sheds.In short, long film about the goings of wizards, it would be surprising if simply incredibly had translated the original title. Even so, the final product is of very high quality, despite the slippages in the pace at which we amuerman.</body>
</review>
