<review author="Silvia Giner" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Two artists, two magicians, confronted with a unique ending, to be the best. But there are battles in which there are no winners or losers, but the destruction that leaves his step combat in which all lose and gain something.</summary>
	<body>The Prestige (I refuse to call it the "the trick ending" is absurdísimo) is a film that shows how you can transform us obsession to the point of becoming people that we never believed to reach to become.Two artists, two magicians, confronted with a unique ending, to be the best. But there are battles in which there are no winners or losers, but the destruction that leaves his step combat in which all lose and gain something.This to see Batman (Christian Bale) and Wolverine (Hugh Jackman) converted to magicians is cane. I personally have a great weakness for Christian (for my taste more credible and better interpreted the story of batman), his performance as Borden is magnificent, slightly touching psychopathy. Looks sharp with the steel of the best swords, are you stuck in the pupils and do not let you see nothing more than it's not that karma that follows it in every scene. On this occasion not can Flay anyone, as I have already said that the actors are tremendous, tremendous is always the voluptuous and sexy Scarlett (learn Pataki), which is correct in all of his intentions.Although at one point the birds scene, can begin to reveal us which is the double face of the matter, could even have gone unnoticed, but is too emphasized the theme of doubles "that trick is only possible with a double" which be become already predictable, which just does not like me at all, another example are phrases like "Nobody cares of the box" I think that they are not necessarythat as I always reach a point in which insults the intelligence of the Viewer.To more than one they look like á a peliculón, I'm going to make a good movie that recommend seeing. As anecdote during the first minutes of the film can count on the presence of Piper warmer (Violet in Coyote Ugly) that after clunkers as George and the Dragon will start to emerge in upcoming projects for 2007 and 2008.</body>
</review>
