<review author="José A. Peig" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film of Díaz Yanes unconvincing because never get to find herself, tells stories and tells the story of a villain-hero, but he fails the basic idea to clearly define all the development and the human sense of adventure.</summary>
	<body>If, when talking of "code Da Vinci" it seemed to us that subjecting the film to the book - and therefore not differentiate and not understand that cinema and literature use different stylistic resources - was the worst of mistakes and, accordingly, the result was a gravel, here we have an attempt to put five books into a whole film % forty minutes. and do time in the history of the Spanish cinema. A chestnut, come on, it has everything to be. But what about Alatriste?. Because I, honestly, do not perceive any clarity of ideas in that sense by their perpetrators.If you want to make a great film it is essential to have very clear the idea, the concept and style. And "Alatriste" stays at half way up several things, without creating the essence and the meaning absolute in any of them. It is an adventure film?. Something that wants to be, but develop own adventure (entertainment without ups and downs, the show, the Odyssey of the hero which lies at the epicenter of all frames and byways that wrap) the climate and the tone is incompatible with that pace so slow, with harangues that don't come to mind and hamper the action (probably in the original book of Pérez Reverte made his role)(, but here are a drag) and, above all, with the absence of an effective structure to develop and explain emotional ties, reasons, causes and effects of the events, actions or thoughts of the different characters and different situations that confront us, all too often, unless we know why or without having the viewer a reason to be interested by the Fortune or the misfortunes of some and others. "I.e., narration is quite disjointed, though perhaps not as well as it seems, case that we sort the film under another different"adventure film"concept.""Alatriste" also can be understood as a mosaic of an era or a whimsical documentary historia-ficción in which the main character serves as a thread for the argument and excuse to develop a rich scenery and the range of devoid of own essence profiles that appear on the screen for the sole purpose of giving game. Ultimately, the film works a little better if I consider a "mosaic of time", not so much if it is an adventure film. (However, the Duelists, it has something of the two things and solves much better, by the way). But even so, I repeat, Díaz Yanes film unconvincing because never get to find herself, tells stories and tells the story of a villain-hero, but he fails the basic idea to clearly define all development and sense human adventure (soon talk of "The captain Blood", to explain in more detail what I mean by that). If add you the tedium produced by the slow pace, by unnecessary long flat, scenes that pass slowly but that do not contribute anything to the story, and the bad use of the ellipsis to the absence of a properly articulated the development content (I thought the ellipsis was a method to save surplus parts that the viewer can assume)(, not to break the structure and the narrative fluidity), could reach a conclusion: is a very bad movie. However, saved from burning by a brilliant use of technical resources and a laudable discretion to the director: say Yanes camera not risk not one inch more than the conventional, but retains dignity in almost all of the footage, well directed scenes of battles (and with this the only thing I'm saying is that you do not worse than Peter Jackson)(for example, which it doesn't have much merit, said it in passing) and know create a certain atmosphere with a proper staging. Photography, art direction, costumes, the successful soundtrack, the sporadic moments of emotional tension, etc, end up restore dignity to a film that being quite loose, insubstantial and empty, does not become so disastrous, as it has been written in recent weeks.What I have no doubt is that "Alatriste" end up being an inconsequential product in the Spanish area and, even more, in the international; a purely anecdotal, interesting product as a representation of our "golden age" and to see family admiring worthy representations of famous historical personalities such as Quevedo, the count Duke of Olivares or King Philip. But for that I think it would have been better to make a series of television thirty chapters.</body>
</review>
