<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="María Antonieta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tristísima loneliness of the Queen becomes Crassus experiment result eccentric. The vicissitudes of the argument, in short, nor convince: lost in the sewing of the costumes in the brightness of the lamps.</summary>
	<body>What speaks in Marie Antoinette is the glorious preamble of the French Revolution, a milestone in the history of mankind, episode where the reason debate his bitter fight against his monsters, but language by Soffia Coppola traviste Convention, they trivialize and stands as a vulgar fireworks show that, in other hands petardería, it had been a symphony with an orchestral mass overwhelming, sublime, with its artifice, coherent, lyric. There is nothing that in this exercise of the daughter of the master marketing Francis Ford. Marie Antoinette is not, however, a bad film. Alone in the dark, I had unbearable sin or capricho de see makes a few nights, it is big sumo. The pseudobiográfico film of this girl turned into Queen from their Waltz Austria until the burning Paris of ideas sacrifice psychological depth of characters, by strength, rich, for the sake of provoking (and succeeds) with doses mayestáticas glamour, as if everything out, deviniese a long (two hours) video to MTV as that great of Queen called It's a hard life.Kirsten Dunst, infante, the Queen is willful, delicately chic, abandoned as a Chair refined in a classroom presentation, never better written, happily unstable in their world of protocols, wigs and costumes of 50 kilos, efficient under his hairstyle of printing.The character, lowered to banal adorno, attends to a coming and going of time tables, seasoned by a unusual wire music, provocative and enjoyable, but clearly inappropriate.Is not, under any circumstances, an update a day (necessary) the gender even though we have placed so many hopes in the confidence that Soffia Coppola, view Lost in translation, was going to make a film of greater nombradía, limited to build a unbearable by baroque painting of time, without background in the latest commercial cinema, made with Audacity, but wrongheaded, subordinating it all to the sound of sequinsto the appalling Palace that we see a thousand times, shot in disconcerting and beautiful angles. Tristísima loneliness of the Queen, his escoramiento to a modern profile of fémina submitted by strict conventions of society, is in Crassus experiment result eccentric. The vicissitudes of the argument, in short, nor convince: lost in the sewing of the costumes in the brightness of the lamps.</body>
</review>
