<review author="Caruco" title="La Caja Kovak" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Does Alfred Hitchcock entering in?The twilight?. Thus could be defined the new proposal of the film excrítico Daniel Monzón.</summary>
	<body>Alfred Hitchcock entering "The twilight zone" (The twilight zone). The new proposal for the excrítico of film Daniel Monzón putting in serious distress and treats a novelist science fiction, David Norton (Timothy Hutton), could be defined as well while it rests in Mallorca.Un fatal fan, a fateful melody, suicide inexpicable of the people around him and a labyrinthine conspiracy orchestrated by the own monsoon and screenwriter Javier Guerricaechevarría, who takes borrowed from Alex Iglesia.Apasionado and simpatiquísimo in personDaniel Monzón, as director, had left me open-mouthed, by bad that was!, with "The heart of the Warrior". On the other hand, his previous title, cleptómana comedy "The biggest robbery never told" possessed a ritmazo, execution and brilliant performances.A model of comedy, if not outside who, for reasons of work, were also exactly 25 minutes, the last of the film, which I saw. You have to see what you earn some movies with a short montage!.A box of surprises.So imagínenese my willingness to confront me with this new proposal and all its length of almost 2 hours. But here, hete we encounter before a film so careful as elegant invoice, a pace paused but not weary and with a less predictable script of what one might assume.And this despite the fact that not all the shackles of los cabos always loose are credible in this puzzle game, who knows even resolve the sequences of increased tension, and in the interior of the coves of the Drac with a dignísima correction (this handkerchief entangled in the motor of a boat!).I think that this invention starring Lucia Jimenez and Timothy Hutton, you like more to that Rod Serling to Hitchcock. Worst thing is that despite ingenious of some of his ideas, it is the feeling of a forgettable product. But it is in film, or recovering it in DVD, would not escape this opportunity to check that the filmmakers here also know good storytelling flavored mystery.</body>
</review>
