<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La vida en juego" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Prison sports film of overcoming, in which a retired player takes some offal of society to become people's benefit. Would happen further penalty glory of not is because it is a true story, as well as having a sober development although long.</summary>
	<body>There are films that have an added value which makes that they go a little level. In this case, that added value that we find ourselves is that it is based on real events. Moreover, at the end of the film, when leaving the letters and people rises and can't you see the cast, leaving "real" scenes from the life of boys that are reflected in the tape. It is very interesting to think that the scenes, which in many cases are "absurd", is not so much and have really happened.The film is a worker of a reformatory in the us. Apparently 75% of those who pass by this country's prison system before turning 18, to become senior citizens return to the same, and the percentage of dead is also violently chilling. Total, he decides that this has to change, and that the problem facing these guys can solve with the discipline of a team sport. So it joins kids with very different characteristics, and in cases of rival gangs, to form a football team.Look at that when I saw the theme I supposed to be a very big roll. When my Middle Chinese melon slept in the first talk that gives them, I thought to myself "this is good". And is that they spend the entire film with speeches Braveheart roll, but with less clothing. History, however, is told in depth, but with many sporting moments. The characters are quite believable, although situations facing us are very far here in Europe. But hey, if it is a true story, it will be that they are true.In short, prison sports film of overcoming, in which a retired player takes some offal of society to become people's benefit. Would happen further penalty glory of not is because it is a true story, as well as having a sober development although long.</body>
</review>
