<review author="José A. Peig" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Want to recognize or not, in the human aspect, in the real heart of the story, the film is too crude and mechanical. When it comes to the end, simply, one hears the predictable screeching of the machinery and is discovered is not such a good film as it seemed, while being a great narrative with many virtues.</summary>
	<body>Confirming to Christopher Nolan as one of the most interesting and talented current cinema filmmakers, The Prestige addresses the world of spectacle and issues such as fame, competitiveness between brothers of vocation and the precio-sacrificio achieving certain goals of originality and their consequent astonishment reflected in the faces of the audience. The magician and his magic understood as art; show unusual facts but explain the secret in order to keep the sense of mystery and wonder. According to the final slogan reads, it is preferable to ignore the secret.The greatest merit of the film lies in its classic scent, a sense of suspense in the line of Edgar Allan Poe, has a tenebrist touch that, at times, is quite disturbing. Such darkness, loaded with a certain romanticism, are a clear effect aesthetics used by Nolan in the Mise en scène, photography, the right soundtrack and a visual style midway between the sober and the Baroque. Creating, therefore a great atmosphere of romantic aromas, tells a dark history, and is approaching the various items with a runaway obsessive pulse. It is inevitable to remember "The Duelists" of Ridley Scoot, both productions share themes and forms, and one could say that "The Prestige" is a transposition of the same story at a time and different social framework. The obsessive obstinacy is the main theme of the work, an obsession which covers the entire area of the kind of world freak that wizards are weaving the secrets and the rules of the game. The truth is that Nolan, through its visual language and their striking sense of mounting and the rhythm, takes a poetic turn: we can define the film as a sinister, playful and poignant poem about magic and its exceptional effects on both the viewer and the wizards own minds. Accordingly, the film is beautifully poetic. But above all, "The Prestige" is a brilliant entertainment, which, broadly speaking, able to maintain the viewer glued to the seat waiting for resolution, although it has enough surplus parts and interest lapses at times. On the other hand, it also has a glaring problem; history, in itself, is not original, and not surprised. The end is rather disappointing by predictable and devoid of imagination both in how to solve it in the plot element that explains the entire network of puzzles which have been exposing over 140 minutes.You don't have too much sense configure narration in order to surprise the viewer with a final outbreak (the true final trick) of sorpresas.siendo that the surprise - for a minimally attentive Viewer - is not such, seen the Duster from the first hour of footage. The film therefore, failed in its ultimate purpose. There is no trick because there is no originality. This is a motto which is part of the explicit text of the film but that, without however, the own Nolan - perhaps because it is inspired by a rather mediocre book, perhaps because its excesses in the use of temporary jumps end up hurting the history - is not capable of carrying out the effect of wonder. His traps are you noticed too to menudoResumiendo, which makes it interesting to this movie is the way of structuring the narration (which gives rise to a fun game of clues and suggestions), the absorbent mise en scène and the strength of its classicism, but history deflated in its final part, precisely when it should enlarge and put that final heading of great films. On the one hand, it is a narrative joy. On the other hand, leaves us with a taste halfway. The treatment of the characters, while it boasts magnificent male interpretations, is too abrupt. And you want to recognize or not, in the human aspect, in the real heart of the story, the film is too crude and mechanical. When it comes to the end, simply, one hears the predictable screeching of the machinery and is discovered is not such a good film as it seemed, while being a great narrative with many virtues.</body>
</review>
