<review author="Taliesin" title="Babel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Babel its three protagonists are worlds hostile, alone and frustrated by not to break the cultural, social and physical barriers which prevent them from communicating with each other.</summary>
	<body>Babel is the third in a trilogy that began with Amores Perros year 2000 and continued with 21 grams in 2003. Three films, separated three years together, telling three stories each. In all of them a chance, an accident, makes that the lives of its protagonists, which otherwise would have traveled separately intersect. It is the parable of the chaos Butterfly made reality: a Japanese Hunter gives a rifle to a Moroccan Guide and, years later, this rifle will trigger a series of events that end up affecting people in various parts of the world.In Babel, Iñárritu, its director, returns to use the Assembly to give force to the magnificent script Guillermo Arriaga. The three stories are pieces, in a disorderly manner in time, although at no time the viewer lose sight of what is happening. However, does not occur in Babel as in 21 grams, where the Assembly was above a script that told how classic would have not been so interesting. Babel its three protagonists are worlds hostile, alone and frustrated by not to break the cultural, social and physical barriers which prevent them from communicating with each other. In these situations a look or a hug say more than words and they check that, below what there is in sight, we are all equal.Babel is a film built with silences, so the interpretation of the actors is fundamental to give credibility to the story. And the truth is that there is no objection. Both Brad Pitt, as Mexican Adriana Barraza and Rinko Kikuchi Japanese have gotten into the skin of their respective characters and the viewer enters history fully. The film features several moments of great strength, and despite having dyes of tragedy, finally leaves a sour taste. The work of localization is very remarkable and scenarios in Morocco, Mexico and Japan are shocking.In summary, Babel is a perfect snap for this trilogy that started three years ago, with Alejandro González Iñárritu directing and Guillermo Arriaga as screenwriter, although following very closely throughout the creative process. Indeed, it seems that from now on will work separately, and many are those who think that together total more than by separate. But that will tell the future. For the moment, today we can enjoy this interesting film.</body>
</review>
