<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Sospecha" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the less fortunate of Hitchcock, which does save the mediocrity of the genius of Cary Grant and Joan Fontaine charming.</summary>
	<body>It has always been said that there were two Hitchcocks: the first, his stage British, before crossing the pond; and the second, which for years obviously worked on then glittering Mecca of celluloid.Known by his predilection for certain actresses that reached obsessing, is certainly his mastery in the recreation of environments and suspense-laden environments what led him to going down in history with the category of myth.Suspicion is not precisely one of their more fortunate titles. Having that having seen a colored version (seemed at times scenes from a video game), has not helped, but the copy that has fallen into my hands had this built-in "gift", and as much as I rummaged in the options of the DVD, there was no way to remove the dye.Basically, it is a film that has two distinct parts. The first is more comedy anything else, that simply shows the friendly face of a vividor, a viva la vida of those remaining at the expense of giving saber and others, using a good last name and presence more than correct. Later, begins to glimpse another different person behind under the guise of frivolity, and that generates mistrust in his own wife, to the point of making her fear for his life. Without being, as I said before, one of their more fortunate works, highlights the magnificent interpretation of the always fabulous Cary Grant and the tremendously emotional Joan Fontaine, specialist in giving his characters of enormous emotional and expressive intensity. Joan received an Academy Award for his work on suspicion in 1941, defeating her sister curiously also well-known actress Olivia de Havilland, who chose the award for her performance in "if not amaneciera". This led to a feud between the two which lasted many years. Joan Fontaine, who currently lives completely withdrawn from public life (has more than 90 years) is one of my favorite actresses, and in my opinion has always enjoyed recognition much less than it deserves. Although this is another percale arena.Returning to the film, drew attention to the somewhat strange combination of more or less solemn scenes with others of a lighter nature, or the incursion of certain jokes not entirely fortunate at inopportune moments. Also it collides a bit alternating between dialogues vibrant, fast, and full of energy with each other excessively muffled.Producer beat Hitchcock a particular ending I not desvelaré for those who have not seen the film, which was far from which the director wished to give to the film, as confessed the director himself years later another genius from the screen, Truffaut.Reitero is not their more fortunate titles, but still worth seeing it, and simply view on screen its protagonists is a delight for the Viewer.</body>
</review>
