<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Karate Kid" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential film about overcoming, respect for elders, tenacity, and other values quite forgotten by society. It may seem a little pastelón, but at the time it certainly marked a generation.</summary>
	<body>There are many people who say that television is a shit and they never give interesting programmes. I do not think so, but if it is true that the amount of ads is that I think much before I venture to see a movie on TV. There are good programs and often can see films already print of all the sites. And one of these was Karate Kid, at Christmas I took to the small, which in what he was to his roll, I I saw for the umpteenth time Larusso and Miyagi giving wax and polishing wax. That if the final scene saw her gaining knowledge to defend in the nursery.The film is a teenage boy who moves to a new town with her mother. Total, in his eagerness to make friends is approaching the girl more beautiful of the area. Of course, this already is being courted by the cool more cool of the locality, which coincidentally is a bloody teenager karateka, so her tanned back. In these, when it is about to collapse the poor Daniel, discovers that the waiter of the tasks where lives (has no less than 60 years) knows something of karate, by what begins teachings, without much faith. what I'm going to tell you a movie they have spare a few thousand times? So many things. To start regardless of the quality of the same, created a very interesting trend and many other titles have followed. The films of the Court "new kid gets to bad girl, did you this and the new has to fight against all to achieve the girl and save his own skin". On the other hand, this film caused a great impact on our young lives, who did not say pulil cela, cela dal? Do or who has not repeated until nausea the gesture of the garza with mixed results? Many things pra are one movie.In short, essential film about overcoming, respect for elders, tenacity, and other values quite forgotten by society. It may seem a little pastelón, but at the time it certainly marked a generation.Moments to remember: when Miyagi tells Daniel San, with a huge row of cars, the concept "give wax - polishing wax".When leaving the House floor nickel, explains that he has served all."Miyagi leathers them the lomo at the Cobras.""Knee" tells the bad teacher.Healing which makes Miyagi Daniel.La kick from the crane in the final scene.</body>
</review>
