<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Braveheart" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of my five favorite films. Since then, he has the floor more times habré able to shout when I get excited I "Libeeeertaaaad". We may take our lives, but can not steal you our freedom!</summary>
	<body>First of all, congratulate the new year we have just released to all my readers. I hope this year be at the same level as last year, or that at least I continue liking thing to read. Well, it is that we were seeing the television programming, with several films interesting when my medium Zucchini has commented that he had not seen Braveheart. After three downloads to half an hour of breathing and the heart I have regained the sense. What my medium Zucchini has not seen one of my favorite movies? Fast doctor, an ultra-thin cylinder via dvd and three hours of sondadas needs.The film is about William Wallace, a Mr Scottish living during the English invasion of a stack of years ago. Total, than the live happy as a child when life gives him a blow on the nose and becomes adult in a matter of six frames. The boy recovers, but as life is very bitch, and the King of England again, they begin to happen little things that make the piece of Scottish this mount one of shit the dog lame, until finally yell "Libeeeeeeeeertad" and make me jump from the sofa to search around the kitchen knives and release I alone Scotland. I'm not saying more.Puff, hairs and hooks are me. I am going to confess something, only think about the film cloudy me sight, I drop the distemper and an emotion runs through my body. The film has everything what I can expect from this biographical - war - historical genre or as desired name. It's very exciting, with moments that put the skin of chicken, as the first rebellion or the final emotional incredibly. Other very dramatic moments of betrayal and broken love. And moments of action that current media is not reached or imagine something like this. Good, and not to mention the use of photography or soundtrack. No, I have no words to describe a film as well.To sum up, one of my five favorite films. Since then, he has the floor more times habré able to shout when I get excited I "Libeeeeeeeeertaaaaaaaaaaad". We may take our lives, but can not steal you our freedom!Besitos.P.D: See that Mel Gibson I don't like anything, but since then I am thrilled at this papelón.Pd2: I heard one day the scene in which more naked ass out of the history of the cinema, which has not be if is it true.P.D.3: Tears as balan Canyon ply my face while I write these lines.Moments to remember: when it enters the village riding his horse to surrender and starts the alone rebellion.Two vengeance of two husbands.The mostramiento of the buttocks (also called bald) that make them to the English.The meeting, in the center of the battle of the Irish with the Scots.When the father of the carrot throws his lover by the window.Treachery on the battlefield of the nobles.The scene of the battle against heavy cavalry, when Wallace says "Quietos, quieeetos, quieeeeeeeeetos" rather than the scene itself, by the picture at that time.Treason in the castle of the nobles.The first speech by Wallace, referred to the enemies "[...]" "they will be willing to change a lifetime for this day, by a chance, only an opportunity to come back here and tell our enemy we can kill, but never will remove us our freedom!"Of course, with hair like hooks and the penis as a mast of a sailing Brig, when cuando está is suffering torture and everyone he shouts "clemency" and him, with the last breath left chest shouts "Libeeeeeertaaaaaaad" thus killing the son of a bitch of the King.The final speech of Bruce "in the year of the Lord of 1314, Patriots Scottish, starving and outnumbered, attacked the fields of Bannockburn." They fought like Warrior poets. They fought as Scots. "And they earned their freedom." Pufff, tremendous.</body>
</review>
