<review author="José A. Peig" title="Braveheart" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Gibson is not a filmmaker or staff or great, but relied on a solid script, with a structure effective and honest, and a direction between sober and correct, sets up a historical drama in which - to practical purposes - not enough or missing pieces.</summary>
	<body>Mel Gibson signed in this strong historical biopic with messianic airs, which is probably his best film (that either IE both considering the mediocrity of the rest of his work) and - as in the Kevin Costner with his "dancing with Wolves" - came to recover the flavour of epic film deployed with all kinds of media and with an elegiac tone quite suited for his story about the Scottish liberator for the general public, while is true that cannot be said that "Braveheart" is a complex movie. The case is that, if we look at the whole of the final result, nor that complexity was a prerequisite to be the great film that is.The idea on which is based the whole of the story is a heroic profile that brings together the physical force with the strategy and intelligence in the battle, adding the faith in ideals brought to its maximum consequences, which creates a rebellion perpetrated even by those who originally moved by self-interest and unafraid to run the most vile of betrayals. That messianic air has established the value of William Wallace in the last moments of his life: the Resolutive cry of freedom (including the position of the crucified), at this point in the footage and in the context of a situation in which everything has already become against their chances after a long and intense trajectory of exploitsvictories and bitter betrayal, contains a deep emotional significance of liberation in the intimate space of the hero and momentum and faith in the great ideals for beings of their immediate environment. Wallace, with its huge and powerful obstinacy, defeating pain and fear, leaves a seed of hope.Gibson is not a filmmaker or staff or great, but relied on a solid script, with a structure effective and honest, and a direction between sober and correct, sets up a historical drama in which - to practical purposes - not enough or missing pieces. Characters live, react, are wrong, feel desire of freedom, falter in their faith, fall in the weakness of the betrayal, repent, reflect, lose or win according to the impressions and/or facts arising out of each act or Word of Wallace. This cause of a script perfectly structured, is always in the Centre from which the plot is structured. A plot not complex, but not mechanical. There is always a margin for reflection between the facts of some subtlety in the decisions of Wallace and those who form its environment, whether they are friends or enemies. Therefore, without being a round work, the narration has life, human spirit and a lyrical sense of the epic, which is result not so much of a good preparation and a good script. When you have a good story to tell, if it you add the careful structure of the script, almost everything else has been done.Is not a round film: can be detected a deal too stereotypical to characterize the profiles of different warring groups; Revolutionary slaves are gross, dirty and brave and the dominant English are given an effeminate air, which is somewhat simplistic and vulgar. And in another order of things, Gibson combines his meticulous style visual, very laudable in many sequences of battles, with plans crappy-salchicheros of TV: happy close-up (or also flat media) slowed in scenes of dramatic emphasis. Such plans and slowed sequences are easy recourse of the filmmaker who does not know to emphasize the dramatic far beyond the mere sensationalism. Gibson is not Orson Welles and his own narration puts in evidence when it requires greater depth. The fact is that us is narrating a story sustained in an argument of masterpiece: the final cry of freedom, even with its powerful dramatic significance and symbolism of the cross position, would have a greater expressivity visual (and, consequently, value and film depth) if Gibson had placed the camera in a position in which the human and spiritual profile of William Wallace dying charge a more subtle meaning than what is derived from a simple game of close-up and slowed sequences. What type of angle, perspective or position of the camera be ideal for that purpose? I neither know nor I is responsible for, that is a job and a challenge for the visual imagination of a film director. What I do know is that the mode used by Gibson is irrelevant and little expressive in its form, while the Fund itself is great dramatic force and thereby the viewer can well guess the tragedy of the represented.To the end and all, not just film is narrated, but, above all, intelligence, insight or the creativity of an artist who plays with his instrument, camera and its huge resources as window open to a world of representations, in this case, the representation of someone who put an ideal world the immediate consequences of the reality. And that demands and requires something more.</body>
</review>
