<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great film that does but note that Eastwood is at its best as director.</summary>
	<body>Already disregarded a priori, due to its title, by many to be not taken the trouble to see it or find out, it has come to our country "Flags of our fathers" Clint Eastwood.Como as it is known, is the first part of a diptych, complete with "Letters from Iwo Jima" and aims to tell the story of the battle of Iwo Jima from American and Japanese point of view.In fact, the battle and everything that surrounds to the placement of the protagonist of the famous photo of Joe Ronsenthal flag are not, you would expect coming from Eastwood, but a pretext to tell us otherwise.Tells us the screenplay by William Broyles, Jr. and Paul Haggis, based on the book by James Bradley and Ron Powers, is a story about how Governments built false heroes and how you use them for their own purposes. And as such, could not be clearer: the Governments care them a pepper people or even much less the truth.But it is also a story about another kind of heroism: that of loyalty to your peers that you can do to give your life for them, not for your country. Showing the other side of the coin, the human side, Eastwood composed an ode to the fellowship.Recurrre so, moving voluntarily and clearly model "Saving private Ryan" with which some her compare mistakenly, to nothing confusing time jumps that allow us not tire us never, nor of the United States or of the field of battle scenes. Thanks to this structure, the film starts quickly, which would have been impossible had they been told in a linear fashion.Because, I repeat, the war is not more than an excuse for what Eastwood we want to count. "Flags of our fathers" much closer is thematically "The man who shot Liberty Valance" that of "Saving private Ryan". In fact, references to John Ford (director of the aforementioned masterpiece) come to be evident in a scene with a rocking chair, metaphor fordiana of family unity, in the foreground for a few seconds. Needless to say, that the direction of Eastwood is so elegant as always.Posts to seek the tickling to the film we can argue that, while all stakeholders met to perfection, there is no any wonderful performance that stands out above the others. But the truth is that there are two explanations to this: the first is that we are in a choral film where would not have much sense that some highlight on others and the second is that I had the misfortune to see the dubbed film (if we are that fold better in the world I don't want to imagine how will be the worst).The way of introducing the character of James Bradley, son of John "doc" Bradley (Ryan Phillippe), protagonist of a scene is also a bit strange a tad forced that it seems to be there with the purpose of making us cry (and indeed did with me).But leaving aside these small defectillos, it's a great film that does but note that Eastwood is at its best as director.</body>
</review>
