<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The smart will solve the game of deception earlier than others, but the feeling of all at the end of the long function believe that it is tantamount to having completed a complex sudoku.</summary>
	<body>In recent years, few Directors have pointed out so many ways shortly after to walk his career as Christopher Nolan. I do not know I can think of a more resounding cover letter as having directed and written Memento, a tape original, brain and with a power of seduction that, shortly after release (year 2000), became a cult movie instantly. It is logical that the offers more attractive and wealthy llovieran you just after this phenomenal success. His next album, another thriller with characters in distressing situations, already featured actors such as outstanding as to Al Pacino. Insomnia is an interesting film, but low brilliance. This film was followed his debut in a blockbuster with Batman Begins. Nolan again demonstrated its ability to make art with almost everything it touches, it has or not billions after Yes. For all cash had deposited many expectations in the final trick (The Prestige), and for this reason, some we've stayed with honey on the lips this time.The film is limited to offer the typical Russian dolls game in which the spectator is surmising what lies at the end of every plot turn. The smart will solve the game of deception earlier than others, but the feeling of all at the end of the long function believe that it is tantamount to having completed a complex sudoku. It finishes even hook the story of friendship turned hatred between two of the best magicians of his time. And despite the fact that all its artistic elements (interpretations, locker rooms or picture) rallen a height more than estimable, one is left with the feeling of having attended one it tape excessively cold and only concerned about carefully hide all their plot recesses.It is curious that this tape has coincided with another of similar context as the magician and that, in both cases, the magic has been absent rather. It seems that, after both surfeit of tricks, in none of the two works we have achieved see the desired prestige all great magician must provide at the end of his performance.</body>
</review>
