<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La lista de Schindler" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential drama that unleashes the most basic feelings in the Viewer. Nothing to write will get any reader capable of approaching the emotion that evokes. To view once and not martirizar more.</summary>
	<body>I hardly comment on this film, for starters, not be well what to say by way of introduction. That already I know you know that I am easy to tear, so no is if the anecdote that I am going to tell you will illustrate or not, but I tell. The last time I dared to see entire this movie still lived with my mother. Was I sitting on the couch with his eyes swollen and reddened and I approached my mother told me "why you like suffering?". It is one of those phrases that you remain in the memory recorded forever. Not be if was why, but her I have been able to return to see anymore.The film tells the life of Oskar Schindler, a businessman without scruples, who sees a reef in the invasion that makes Germany of Poland at the beginning of World War II. As it has contacts at a high level, it manages to a factory in the newly invaded Krakow. Once there, after having "hired" a game of worker Jews, begins to realize the atrocities that are committed and decided to devote their efforts to save the greatest number of prisoners possible.As said before, no is good to say, given that this film surpasses me in all areas. Like all has their opponents seeking his major point of support in the lack of veracity. Well, I do like the film is based on real events or not. No matter, I believe that it is above the facts. Emotions and feelings that get that they arise in the Viewer, in this case I can not describe with words. That feeling of extreme distress, this suffering by people of fiction based on real people, that joy by small accomplishments, that emotion, that indignation by the events, this compendium of feelings few films manage to transmit them.In short, essential drama that unleashes the most basic feelings in the Viewer. Nothing to write will get any reader capable of approaching the emotion that evokes. To view once and not martirizar more.I have no words.Besitos.P.D: Fuck that llorera has given me so suddenly.Pd2: Urban legend, which not is if it is true, that it was recorded entirely (except for the red coat) in black and white due to the excessive cost which had record it in color.Moments to remember (or not): ** the scene of showers, when you don't know if it will leave water or gas.* Cuado Oskar picks up a child to explain that you need to Polish the bullets by dentro.* at the end of the film, the final Fireworks where the Jews give the farewell and he thrilled, wondered that to how many people could have been saved with that car, or with that joya.* the kiss scene the girl Jewish. ** the time that the Jewish architect says that they are building the building poorly and Commander la mata, to then say to his subordinates do what she had dicho.* the tape transport of corpses. ** even within the previous, has its own impact, the girl in the red coatwhich only comes out twice but you recording to fire in the retina.* the "snow" on Krakovia.* the "game" of the Commander of shooting with the rifle telescopic. ** the time they discover that trains men and women have separado.* the last sequence, in which survivors and children of survivors place stones on the grave of Oskar.</body>
</review>
