<review author="Plissken" title="Más extraño que la ficción" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The good part of ' Stranger than fiction' is that can be seen perfectly, without offending or bore anyone. The bad part is the simplicity of its main plot and excessive calm with which unfolds all around Harold Crick.</summary>
	<body>Curious this Marc Forster. In just five years has signed four very different movies as ' Monsters ball' (dense racial drama), 'Finding Neverland' (sweetened biopic), 'Stay' (conventional thriller) and his latest release, ' Stranger than fiction' (tragicomedy absurd-romanticona). And three of them their protagonists (Halle Berry, Johnny Depp and Will Ferrell) in latter have sounded strong as candidate to the oscar (Berry took him). Without doubt, a guy with a talent for the direction of actors, eye for the choice of projects and versatility to adapt to any company.With ' Stranger than fiction', Forster explores familiar ground for all of us thanks to Charlie Kaufman: eccentric characters, absurd situations and reflections on life, destiny and envelope the craft of writing, in particular on the relationship between character and creator, demiurge and creature. Does a character escape the control of his literary father, or each and every one of their actions are given by the imprint it awarded? Or seen from the other side, once it has been created to "someone", what right does the writer to decide for him?Harold Crick is a grey, lonely, without goals in life. One day, a voiceover begins to narrate his every day. It is the beginning of a search, the search for the ultimate purpose of the existence of Crick. Yes, the truth is that synopsis is not worth a damn, but it is that really the main plot can be summarized in that, and for revelations already this trailer (if not have seen you do not, shoots two thirds of film). The originality of the script from Zach Helm is that while we are witnessing the absurd miniepopeya of Harold Crick (effective and sober Will Ferrell), also attended the miseries of the creative process with the parallel story of Kay Eiffel (excellent Emma Thompson), blocked writer. Stories complement each other to create a kind of friendly variant of 'The Truman show', which starts with decision relying on the work of Ferrell and it deflated somewhat to spend the surprise effect, after passing by nice roads in excess (for my taste, eye).The good part of ' Stranger than fiction' is that can be seen perfectly, without offending or bore anyone. Good performances (the main add a fun Dustin Hoffman, Maggie Gyllenhaal a sparkling, something a sosaina Queen Latifah and a past of laps (what rare) Tom Hulce), interesting visual aspect (in charge of his man of trust, Roberto Schaefer), and a curious use of music (from The Clash to Vangelis passing by Maxïmo Park) make up an attractive mix.The bad part is the simplicity of its main plot and excessive calm with which unfolds all around Crick, except fun specific moments. It is missing a greater dramatic tension to help bring the history of the manidas four corners of romántico-fantástica comedy. Perhaps more black humor would have been good.'Stranger than fiction', another enjoyable film by Marc Forster, but nothing you're going to remember here at year's end. a 6'5.</body>
</review>
