<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Atrapa el fuego" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bitter story, based on a real event, which makes us understand that silence in the face of injustice can be just as bad as herself.</summary>
	<body>Based on real events which occurred in 1980, when South Africa desangraba dominated by the white minority and full Apartheid, catches fire tells the story of a white man that the inevitability of fate makes discover that look another way when you have the injustice before you become silent accomplice and potential future victim. It is a concept which defines perfectly the maximum that is popularly attributed to Bertolt Brecht, but belongs to a priest victim of the nazis called Martín Nimoeller, and which reads as follows: "first they came for the Jews, and I said nothing because I was not a Jew." Then they came for the Communists and I said nothing because I was not a Communist. Then they came for the trade unionists and I said nothing because I was not a trade unionist. "Then they came for me, but by then, already was nobody saying anything".The film tries to transmit the heart-rending cry of a people that suffered indignity and humiliation during decades of subjugation. And it does so with a bit of demagogic populism, license taken certainly to try to increase tax revenue at the box office. Being a completely lawful measure, it is also true that you subtract something of solemnity to the story, even though the end product is quite interesting and it is not dared predict potential eligibility for the Golden statuette. Very good, as usual, the interpretation of Tim Robbins, one of those billionaires on the left that they photograph with Fidel Castro but they repudiate a handshake of people as Ruiz Gallardón (hand which by the way has not signed any death penalty) and usually work and become involved in projects of this type, combining politics and cinema quality. And on the way, everything is said, pocketing some millions of dollars from your current account.</body>
</review>
