<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El ejército de las tinieblas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You have to see the army of darkness because it is dignified, fun, solid and noble if you know to contextualize the film in a necessarily paracinematográfico order, mestizo, outside standards.</summary>
	<body>Founded on the prolific series B or Z of Italian gore and humorous sci-fi Martian of the early 1950s in the United States, the army of darkness exercises of hinge between the visual aversion of the first (entrails, blood, mutilation) and domestic, tacky and cheap romanticism of the second (with its narrative imagination, with its neighborhood morning film marketing).Raimi obvious seriousness which then exhibited in Spider-man (1, 2 and 3, now assume) or Darkman, to take two examples pleasant for this chronicler, to give us a ration of terror to the monthly Python with gags worthy of a good Mel Brooks. And get out this collage of elements Crystal decent ends plagiarizing himself (ole) and doing fine chacota of his infernal possession (highly recommended if you want to see quality disgusting horror film) or the aforementioned Darkman is evasion, comic rupture and, above all, do not forget, box, ring, ring.Bruce Campbell is the actor fetish of Raimi and squeezes it wonderfully in this film. Well stuck in the role of Ash (ASH), the journey of the time ends in the middle ages and should assume a role heroic, prophetic, which redeem the inhabitants of the Castle and, at the time, to himself. There is no deep psychology of characters or paper-thin paths of the morals of the time. There are no characters. There is no time.Steal the Necronomicon, the book of evil attributed by Lovecraft to an apocryphal Arabic got Faust, above the resistance to an army of skeletons: for that matter. Skeletons? Yes, jaws, coccyx, shoulder blades, femurs dancing as in the Thriller by Michael Jackson in a great tribute to the classic Haskin, Jason and the ARgonautas.Yo I enjoyed it very much in this magnificent scene that already worth seeing the film, but there are more: there is a playful tribute to the cinema medievalist of Cape, sword and torreón, injecting modernity: pouring a point of modest bombast that warnsespecially in the first twenty or thirty minutes. Then the film decays, but that already knew.Merit is the two seemingly disparate, non juntables genera mescolanza: era film (the medieval, of course) and cuasigore terror without that any loss of substance.You have to see the army of darkness because it is dignified, easily arrumbable to the receiver of the moments lost in a room, in this case an ear Chair of House, but fun, solid and noble if you know to contextualize the film in a necessarily paracinematográfico, mestizo, order out of standards.</body>
</review>
