<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Bobby" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nominated for two as best film and best original song Golden Globes, finally there was none; something that even I can not ented, above all, in the first case that was Babel which won the award for best dramatic film.</summary>
	<body>Surely everyone could talk fluently about the figure of John Fitzgerald Kennedy, however, it is possible that we had more doubts if we were to do the same with his younger brother: Robert Francis Fitzgerald Kennedy.No worry, if them has been curious to learn more about this historical figure, can count on the invaluable help of twenty-two fictional characters that we presenterán Bobby in a subtle and intelligent way. Not us they become bored with a biography full of data and hieroglyphics; their own lives, their ideas and feelings IFF environment the message that the aspiring President released to the American public.This is, without a doubt, the greatest success of the film: reach the depths of an individual, what really is his being, his ideas and feelings but, in addition, this transmitted through the intimate stories of a group of people that match for various reasons in the Ambassador hotel. And do not believe that they are distant stories: love, infidelity, youth, old age, aspirations, disappointments; the good and bad of life with a common goal: have moments of happiness.Spectacular cast into perspective and acting was not disappointed anyone, all and I repeat, all, are exquisite. That certainly helps them a solid script which has been seasoned with witty dialogues that will make us enjoy 120 minutes in which we can observe the political changes that occurred in American Society of the 1960s. All this will be done in a way that is agile, leaving behind unnecessary, friends barroquismos always lack of creativity. Maybe - and this is a very personal note which does not reach the category of criticism - I had shortened the final speech of Robert Kennedy and, thus, would have been a more concise result.Nominated for two as best film and best original song Golden Globes, finally there was none; something that still can not ented, above all, in the first case that was Babel which won the award for best film drama, this last being a clear example of how to tell a story about feelings of how chaotic and Kafkaesque, something of which, fortunately, flees Bobby.</body>
</review>
