<review author="Silvia" title="Hard candy" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film manages to catch the attention of the Viewer without having to resort to special effects, or changes of scenarios and with very few characters.</summary>
	<body>Desquiciante. Hard Candy is a psychological thriller that tells the story of a revenge. Cruel revenge of a teenager a photographer which considers guilty of sexual harassment. The film speaks about the danger of the network for many children who are subjected to harassment of paedophiles or paedophile. But in this case, the bully who will become prey to his "victim".Hayley and Jeff are known through a chat. Jeff has 30 years and Hayley is only a girl, but that does not preclude that they are to get to know. The title of the tape, Hard Candy (hard candy) is a colloquial term in Internet for underage girls. The meeting at home of photographer mark a turning point in the film after which becomes every a thriller full of psychological sadism whose environment is stifling above all thanks to the brilliant performances of Patrick Wilson and Ellen Page. The sarcastic dialogues? sometimes monologues-which keeps the protagonist with the photographer acting as an engine of the action of the story. It is surprising how the film comes to provoke disgust, malaise, discomfort, perhaps even nausea and all this without that there is not a single plane explicit nor unpleasant. The images suggest more than show, play with the spectator, awaken the panic and terror so it never looks.It's the first film as director David Slade, who has a remarkable experience in the world of advertising and video clips. And that advertising style is noticeable especially in aesthetic approach of the film (very sharp images, close-ups, etc.) The contrast of red colours (of the costumes for the girl) is frequent and the chromatic game between the Red Wall and the blood. In addition, the girl is dressed in a red outfit which hood, but in this case the tale is reversed and Riding Hood which snack to the Wolf. The film manages to catch the attention of the Viewer without having to resort to special effects, or changes of scenarios (practically the entirety of the history unfolds on the floor of the photographer) and with very few characters (most of the footage occupied the couple protagonist). To hook the viewer its greatest asset is the dialogue between the two characters, conversations that keep in suspense to anyone who is following the story.The home perhaps is something forced because the characters are given to know superficially and thriller arises somewhat sharply. But then the pace develops radically more slowly? than not tedious - but managing to keep the viewer in tension in the majority of the footage. A story that plays with the psyche of the Viewer, to make it go really wrong but without seeing a drop of blood more than any scratch. Another point in its favour is that it points to any of the two characters as good or bad. At times we do not know who is more terrifying for us: the teenager with dyes psychopaths or the photographer that entertains photographing naked girls. The film is limited to show us both to make the viewer who judge.The end is somewhat confusing as the justification for acts of the protagonists are not entirely clear. There is a lack of really understandable reasons does not show the protagonists, as Hayley seems to act simply for spite, without that we come to understand their real motivations. While they glimpse some justifications of their ways, it is also true that motives are not entirely credible. But although the story has some shortcomings in terms of likelihood (mature talks of the girl child are more characteristic of a university than a college student), the truth is that this lack of reality does not prevent that the Viewer is immersed in the distressing atmosphere and reach introduced himself in history.</body>
</review>
