<review author="Yojimbo" title="Volver" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Almodovar returns to talk about women and turns them into the absolute protagonists of his story</summary>
	<body>Good thing about artists is that they may provoke loves, hatreds but almost always curious. There are who hates Almodóvar. And who revered. There are those who try to see his films without influence by the stir he created as a character (I might add, is a lousy). And without bias (although see the criminal trailer is a shock) I went to see his latest film. Do talk to her felt me absolutely wonderful and I did not see the bad education because no one had spoken to me well it, wanted to satisfy my curiosity with its Volver.Que stating that the best return is its title: returns to his earth, returns to his subjects always, demonstrates once again that you have music taste, returns to his actresses fetish? and the verb conjugará in future time that he will return to the Academy, will return to win Goyas, will return to earn international reputation?The film is unclassifiable, as you said my companion of HL (although the score do not share at all) I am familiar with the "manchego" world that portrays, why I see that one of the movie's weakest points is shuffle onto a glamorous Penelope Cruz the weight of the protagonist. We will, that equal parts is out of place and elsewhere get thrill. In fact, and that specialists may tell you me, cross is lit differently. Come on, as they did with the divas of Hollywood. Does anyone know the details of the contract of Pe as an actress? I remember perfectly when commented me the long-winded and complex which was the contract and conditions of Salma Hayek to put it in the great life of Antonio Cuadri.El most attractive aspect of the film is the "fantastic". The always fantastic Carmen Maura. Reconcile a story with that element (not specific more because I believe that it would be a spoiler) it's great and gives the film a without weight, little seen in our cinema. The actresses are very well directed. Lola Dueñas does a good job, as well as Blanca Portillo and Chus Lampreave (known to little and which should have been more comic).Almodovar returns to talk about women and turns them into the absolute protagonists of his story; do not hesitate to return to its "man bastard who only lives to torment" constants. The music by Alberto Iglesias see misguided, but it works well at times. Alcaine photography is notable and the Assembly of very successful Salcedo.A movie interesting, quite uneven in its pace and pretensions, but of the most original and personal Spanish current film.Without going any further, I think that the best analysis of the film (very detailed and spoilers) is Mambotaxi, fervent admirer of don Pedro.</body>
</review>
