<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="La lista de Schindler" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The horror some of so clearly that you can smell, feel, gum and breath almost in 180 minutes of footage, in a clear manner, that takes you to the cries of the casting to the chagrin of sigh and that does not leave you with a clear conscience.</summary>
	<body>I have to admit and say almost with true embarrassment, which did not remember if he had seen this movie and that everytime someone spoke to me of the masterpiece of Spielberg I shrink from shoulders and rascaba me the head thoughtful I do not remember if I have seen was that repeated over and over again, so as it is to remedy things and have to see the films that are not known, today that had more than enough (at the end of three hours that lasts the same I had seen almost in 5) and, of course, because logically I was pleasantly satisfied. The horror of something so clearly that you can smell, feel, gum and breath almost in 180 minutes of footage in a clear way which takes you in sigh to tears, of the casting to the chagrin and does not leave you with a clear conscience, is true that movies about the Holocaust has been made hundreds and but it's something quite "chewing" is (made in 1993) let in way exemplary role of Oskar Schindlera businessman German who decides to grab the bull by the horns and treat the Jews as they are, human beings and not as "animals" (as they dealt with the nazis). Me is difficult to talk about, almost with tears in his eyes and skin chicken, after as it has made me this film, coldly of which has been transmitted to me (go two days I've been!)(WOW!) but no doubt there are many scenes in which Spielberg knows to convey "something" that goes to the heart of the viewer screen and stays there, sitting, quiet and clear manner during the time of projection, the faces, gestures, hope passenger. Excellent interpretations of Liam Neeson, Ben Kingsley, Ralph Fiennes, in addition to all those actors (unnamed) that make a great role (asi, in all caps) that you're left with the mouth open and the meat of chicken throughout the film. Note also the soundtrack by John Williams, transmitting excellently all moments of the film. It is the typical film that when it ends "let sediment", we as my father said, "that something is and that's what matters" I know that it might be the last people on the face of the Earth that had not seen this movie, so sobran recommendations.</body>
</review>
