<review author="Manel Juanico" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The development is too confusing, the screenwriter, hoping to solve everything in the end, confuses the viewer through tricks, bad tricks I would say.</summary>
	<body>The feeling that with which I was at the end of this film is strange. On the one hand he liked, it has very interesting things, address is very good, Christopher Nolan is a great director, despite having led one of the worst movies I've seen in my life, Insomnia. As usual in the current film see the problem of always, the script, that lame too. The development is too confusing, the screenwriter, hoping to solve everything in the end, confuses the viewer through tricks, bad tricks I would say. This confusion is present throughout the film and many now quite uncomfortable because you think that not you you are learning from the film. To be the story told through flashbacks, the confusion is even greater, especially for people who are not accustomed to watch movies party in pieces and displayed after the form in which the writer wants to. I personally felt during many moments of totally lost footage, and the truth, I do not think that a film as it is is well liar to the viewer in this way.In the actions they would like to express my dissatisfaction with Christian Bale, making one of the worst roles of his career, completely out of place, false and lacking in expression, for more INRI dubber of this actor is bad really. As for the rest nothing to highlight correct, Michael Caine does well but personally I do not like that actor. David Bowie little acts but do well although it would like to have seen in original version to see it otherwise.Another thing that I did not like anything is the setting, the recreation of the era, until it wasn't a good bit of the film didn't know if they were in the 1960s, in the early 20th century or in the middle of the 19, therefore more confusion for the Viewer. The dressing rooms not help a lot, pretty bad in this aspect also.There are many things that had been changed from this film, if development not liked, the end has seemed hasty and foolish, and especially the last two seconds could being saved, painful truth. In short, a movie of science fiction which should be taken as such. Surely one of the problems might not expect you watch science fiction movies, I expected something different, I do not know, in my opinion could have been a great movie but he has been frustrated by, or a bad script, or be based on a novel not just work carried to the cinema. During the projection was spinning at the head about how I had developed the film and seemed much better that that in the end they carried out, clear that that is already very personal, but it had that feeling all the time, as thinking that they were wrong by doing so.There is a part that found me totally ridiculous, there is a moment in that, to do a trick, the actor interprets Hugh Jackman looking for a double. Curiously in a short time are in a tavern to a guy that is nailed him, so nailed him portraying if same, a chorrada without any sense. To find a double you can take months, make hundreds of auditions, is not in one day, and less so nailed one to you who you really. IMHO could have taken another actor, someone with a mild resemblance and then cut the same hair, dress him like, or fudge it, whatever before catch the same actor.Disappointing only halfway, at least it is entertaining and has some hits. With a second viewing you can earn. or losing absolutely everything. not be if risk I...</body>
</review>
