<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Evil bong" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Infamous monstrosity created by and for impenitent porreros. I suppose that to what makes grace must be very smoked, but I have to admit that you there were a couple of moments that made me laugh. Also leave women in leather dancing sexy dances.</summary>
	<body>The brain of a viewer of film must be reset, as well as computers from time to time. We got accustomed to a level of quality, that everything seems to be bad. Why there are people who, moved by the loving kindness towards his fellow men, record these things for the good of humanity. Thus, those who see it, restart critical vision and appreciate more what we usually see. Already happened with "As smoke is going" and I has become to go with this.The film is an apartment shared by four diverse characters, three of them linked by marijuana. With the money that gives the non-smoker only, one of the inhabitants of the floor buys a second-hand (calls Bong) water pipe, according to High Times Magazine is cursed and its previous owner died. Obnubilado by the beauty of the pipe, they place in the classroom after smoking it. The next day, after a delusional erotic festive sequence, one of the companions appears dead on the couch.My medium Zucchini slept in the titles of the beginning, just to see that marijuana plants out. Well, more specifically when I recognized you that it was Mr Chong (of as smoke goes). Well, the film falls or quality to call as well. The script is tremendous, showing us how a killer bong wants to dominate the world letting their smoke. All this allows us to end a patriotic talk that parodies big titles that I can blend them in criticism of this monstrosity. The actors are obviously more bad than dog meat. Special mention should be made to the special effects, which takes us back to older films of series B, was where the imagination it supplying everything.In short, engendro infamous created by and for impenitent porreros. I suppose that to what makes grace must be very smoked, but I have to admit that you there were a couple of moments that made me laugh. Also leave women in leather dancing sexy dances.</body>
</review>
