<review author="Noa" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Children of men is the perfect excuse to love the film. It works as a puzzle, nobody stands out more than necessary, the star is the film as a whole.</summary>
	<body>"Some of the anticipated dangers that have been excluded from the list of accidents in the arguments that seem too unlikely to cause a terminal disaster at the global level are: solar flares, supernovae, explosions or mergers of black holes, explosions x-ray range, implosions of the center of the Galaxy, supervolcanes, loss of biodiversity, pollution, gradual loss of human fertility accumulation"", and several religious views on the final day." (Nick Bostrom, director of the Institute for the future of the humanity of Oxford University).Alfonso Cuarón is a quite peculiar, able to deal with all kinds of films, such as the "Harry Potter and the prisoner of Azkaban" entertaining, to give a new revision to the works of Charles Dickens in "Great hopes" or do his most personal work to date, the road-movie "Y tu mamá also". I guess no one argued for "Children of the men", beyond of several advances that aroused our curiosity.In my case, upon seeing her relatively late on its premiere, it was willing to meet with something pretty good, but everything that presupposed falls short. It is (and greatly sorry for Marty and yours) the best of the year (in the absence of seeing "Babel" and "Flags of our fathers" and some that another release, which like this remain so will not have numbers to rate my assessment).The story is sensational and terrifying: 18 years ago that the company is doomed to extinction, for unknown reasons (or lack it does know them) mankind has lost the ability to procreate. With such history, we would already have enough for an interesting film, but Cuaron includes other evils global as a direct consequence to that problem and also derived from ours, now, 2007 newly released: immigration, poverty, terrorism, military control, the war and the hopelessness facing an uncertain future. And Cuaron discusses everything from a Prism pessimistic and spectacular, full of verismo. Involves us in history, we participate in the movie, sorry. The narrative is beautiful. It is also able to embed camera in the most shocking scenes of the film, giving legs to run between chaos and death, and making us all actors of barbarism.And to bring forward this jewel of the Sci-Fi plant on the charismatic (and other things) Clive Owen, to make it he who guide us on the path to Tomorrow, giving it life as a great current hero. And also gives a small role to Michael Caine, leaving us more endearing and comic of the film sequences. Julianne Moore is different, the time is so well shot no matter at all to not enjoy it the rest of the film. Each secondary (Chiwetel Ejiofor, Claire-Hope Ashitey,.) works as a puzzle, nobody stands out more than necessary, the star is the film as a whole.Children of men is the perfect excuse to love the film.</body>
</review>
