<review author="Hartigan" title="Apocalypto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It promised to be the storm of the Apocalypse, and in the end, Apocalypto Mel Gibson has seen the storm clouds hide the lightning. Or to put it in a way less great, as the multicultural and well-intentioned controversy surrounding has exaggerated expectations can comply with Apocalypto.</summary>
	<body>It promised to be the storm of the Apocalypse, and in the end, Apocalypto Mel Gibson has seen the storm clouds hide the lightning. Or to put it in a way less great, as the multicultural and well-intentioned controversy surrounding has exaggerated expectations can comply with Apocalypto. There is reason for racism in Apocalypto? Yes, if you want to find. On the other hand is an ethnic Ode to the indigenous preservation? You want to be him, but fails without albeit. Is it violent? Of course. When struggles with maces of stone is natural that jump brains. But it is not much less in comparison to other products reveling in the guts and that nobody thinks to ban. Finally: Is a great movie Apocalypto? The nickname is the protagonist could be applied to the set of the film: Casi.Garra Jaguar (the fantastic rookie Rudy Youngblood) is a young Hunter who lives with his family and his tribe in the jungle. In a hunting party found a community of refugees displaced from their lands by Mayan warriors. Shortly after the own Jaguar claw village is attacked. This gets put away his family from the massacre by hiding them in a chasm, but is captured and taken to be sacrificed in the capital. By the way it will be witnessed the degradation of the Maya civilization with sinister omens of destruction. A series of circumstances will lead his flight, and the ruthless and vindictive persecution of the warriors who captured him.Actually the premise is not overly complex. Why surprised its duration, two hours for a "film of persecution" (such and how her defined own Gibson) of which hunting only occupies the second. The first is a long presentation of the idyllic life of the jungle community, among costumbrismo and garrulas jokes; then, it is a detailed presentation of the affecting both the degenerate and the spectacular Mayan civilization. When it comes to action, both stuffed him catches the Viewer. And the pace of the game ends up not being as hectic as we would expect: "Hunter hunted" manages to bring them to their ground while their opponents are falling one by one so not especially surprising. Some even by chance, so are not talking about exactly Depredador.En what really dazzles Apocalypto is in the visual aspect. The Mayan warriors tattooed and covered in human jaws are much more frightening than the Uruk-Hai of Peter Jackson. However, such intensity just highlighting clearly that the film has little to offer beyond the obvious. And out the whiff of Manichaeism. The Mayans are cruel, sadistic, brutal and superstitious. Their leaders manipulate them without dissimulation. The only redeeming quality that seem to show that of the paternal love, is based in terms of violence and only serves to justify the persecution as something personal. They represent civilization and are bad, some exaggerated even for an action film. Gibson has no need to be neutral, but onion in the negative to disfiguring it. What it bother to give them names, if only we will know them by the IMDB?Mel Gibson is a guy with serious obsessions. The martyrdom and the horror of war seem to be predominant, seen what expresses in his films and in other more dubious circumstances. You feel that you need to communicate a message and finds difficult it to leave him: some scenes are directly modelled Braveheart and the passion. And as I often say about him, not known to be subtle: believes that it has to present things in black and white, and just working on his own ambiguity. East the case of Apocalypto and its unfortunate conclusion, which leaves in the air the intention of Gibson. Those white men who appear armed crosses and armor mean Salvation or a new era of horror in which executioners are now the victims? What was presented with simplicity just leaving the confused Viewer. And even will have moved it as well as expected.</body>
</review>
