<review author="Bloody Will" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apocalypto is one of the best films that has left the 2.006, and if you forget the mood of argue with its director, you are going to enjoy as it deserves.</summary>
	<body>Tremendous controversy I have with myself for this movie, so it would not surprise me that this time the suits were very unevenly distributed.I have not seen "The passion of the Christ", and believe that I will never do it. It is not for religious reasons, is that simply I it upset at the time that Gibson become phenomenon of marketing a film that nothing should have blockbuster. Even so, does not interest me his view of Christ's death and I have both right to avoid it as that refuses to see "Los Lizenz" of Pajares-Esteso. Why get "Virgin" to "Apocalypto", by how much this technique of "tell what gives me the win and as the win gives me" Gibson have met her in a film that seems to me perfect in cinematography but that touches the co ** by their constant improprieties.If you've been in Mexico you know that the most essential travel tour is the city of Chichen Itza, and that on their journey by bus will try a very nice guide to explain you in time record the history of the Mayan civilization. Mel Gibson has done the same thing that made my guide, but added violence, savagery, anguish and all cabreante end. Even so, there a minute of the film that makes me take off the eyes of the fantastic story the director tells me through the misfortunes of its protagonist, Jaguar, and that lasts 2 hours and 10, to me I spent flying.The argument I will tell you in a very simple way: Jaguar Paw. This is our hero and his life, and I do not advance absolutely anything of the argument because I have proven that the less you know more surprising is each lance of the film. That Yes, through the eyes of Jaguar are going to see a very small piece of a civilization and a culture, but also a massacre, a slavery and a way of life that (now comes the mess), Mel Gibson has shown in his peculiar style, and perhaps not the most correct.For this reason, we divide the concept of the film between film and historical correction. In the film, I have no buts no: solid script by its four flanks, continuous action without filling scenes, unknown actors that you submerge fully in a culture that looks more alive than ever, stunning natural scenery, impeccable costume recreations and last 40 minutes, which I will call "after the Jaguar" that I add to my favorites of for life. There are four key scenes on which rests the rest of the footage (village, crossing, city and escape) and they are so necessary that we cannot think that history be extended absurdly. All this is architect certainly Mel Gibson as director of film is demonstrating his technique goes upward? now, as historian, has won a sure beating.Here we go with the historical correction. I have no doubt at all that Gibson has not documented, moreover, it seems to me that it has soaked until exhaustion; However, this is as newspapers today: each tells the same story from the point of view that fits him best. Gibson blatantly seeks Kinky-violent factor than it is telling. Were the Mayans as Mr. Gibson has?; It is true that they made sacrifices, but the director not staged "a" sacrifice but a real orgy of cries, prayers, blood and mutilation, there is nothing. Although on the other hand, our hero is also Maya, and still our hero; Therefore, it is not the typical story of good and bad within a racial group?.That Gibson has gone through the Bullfighter the contributions made by the Mayans to their future, sure it is. Gibson portrays this culture as if they were the cannibals of "The hills have eyes", also; but keep in mind that Mel Gibson not owes nothing to this people, and has had his film as he feels. Let us remember that in "Mission Impossible II" we placed at the fallero next to a passage of Holy week. I know that it is not the same, but so can we explain that an American director does not have to be faithful to the maximum with a few ancestors who ultimately does not care nothing.Attention to the scene of the film gloriously. Source of anger for our Mexican friends. We can comment in the post and not so still deflate to anyone who wants to go to the cinema to see it. If I have to get me wet, me mojo: "Apocalypto" is one of the best films that has left the 2.006, and if you forget the mood of argue with its director, you are going to enjoy as it deserves.</body>
</review>
