<review author="Kiko de España" title="María Antonieta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good. He said that you history or better said, the story is unimportant. This will of parties, champagne, strawberries, dogs and excesses in general, not forget that it begins with a punk theme. Epopca.</summary>
	<body>Marie Antoinette is a movie by Sofia Coppola. The Virgin suicides and Lost in translation were movies of Sofia Coppola.¿No said you nothing? Not you they liked? It then passes the French Queen, because it is more of the same.When do you Ding, (to my did me, especially the second), you will spend it great watching the show of "girl do woman?" which marks the pair Coppola/Dunst at the expense of the historical personaje.¿Recordais Clueless (out of wave)? Because Marie Antoinette are you feel much: it is the story of a rich and capricious girl to which all give a shit and thinks only of hairdressers and shoemakers. And well endowed Swedish soldiers, heroes of war to be.At historic level the film NO APORTA absolutely nothing, but is that the story is unimportant in the film. And I thank you, despite the two hours because, do you imagine a Marie Antoinette of, for example, Anthony Minghella, with its 214 minutes?Good. He said that you history or better said, the story is unimportant. This will of parties, champagne, strawberries, dogs and excesses in general, not forget that it begins with a punk theme (by the way, I love its beginning and its end) and with a map of the Dunst you entering a desire to get off the seat and skip the screen...Shows that the movie does not go anything which will take an hour and peak in show as it bored the Queen and then in a seen and unseen events precipitate using an ellipsis as heavy, especially that of the birth of their offspring.The case is that I I I passed big during the greater part of the footage because I like as tells me things this woman specialist in placing the camera next to the vetanilla of all car or wagon, either in Japan or at Versailles, or because it uses music in an exemplary fashion and leaving a few all-star lying on the floor, the Parrot. I'm not going to deny that the burst of Marie Antoinette. "Marie Antoinette farmer" is about to throw rushing everything, but it is then it recovers. And I love the end. UPS, that it had already said.</body>
</review>
