<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Bobby" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Well built characters, a solid script full of intensity and some fabulous performances make Bobby's one of the films any restless Viewer should not be missed.</summary>
	<body>Reach the Spanish screens Bobby, film sneaks by surprise in Golden Globe nominations, and that United States has raised many blisters in the more conservative sectors of society. With the recent, controversial and very unfortunate statements of true patriotic politician on the Union of actors and their right to demonstrate, is easier to imagine the kind of reactions that will be elicited Bobby in United States. Although the title seems to announce it, it is not a biopic of Robert F. Kennedy, nor of a chronicle of his assassination and subsequent investigation, as JFK by Oliver Stone. The tape continues to 22 different characters, which all have in common is their presence at the hotel the day was murdered Robert Kenndy.Se is obviously a very political story, with a clear ideology, in which Emilio Estévez employs these fictional characters to draw an x-ray very accurate of American society, the problems and ailments suffered in 1969. Bobby uses all these elements not to have the status of United States forty years ago, but to denounce the current situation of the country. Don't have a grand vision to detect that almost forty years later, these social and economic problems have not diminished, they have increased. The country returns to live an unpopular war that leaves as balance thousands of deaths, while social inequalities are increasing, as well as unemployment and poverty. Estévez made that complaint through the spirit of a great statesman, as already it was his brother (coincidentally, also killed), or Marthin Luther King, Robert Kenndy represented the hope for a better world, leaving aside frivolous and absurd wars, and concerned about the welfare of the people. Well built characters, a solid script full of intensity and some fabulous performances make Bobby's one of the films any restless Viewer should not be missed. And if not, as the final scene of the film shows there is.</body>
</review>
