<review author="José A. Peig" title="Apocalypto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apocalypto offers us not only awhile of great show but also of good cinema. Leaving aside to?Do Braveheart?, is the best Mel Gibson movie to date.</summary>
	<body>We started with a plane in travelling to us closer to wild nature of the physical world in which runs the story. Hunting and trapping of the wild boar that ends in bloody death in the trap of Aboriginal comes to inform us what is to come. The plan that closes the narrative shows a family of survivors that they delve deep in the jungle. Apocalypto is a film about survival and violence in a half wild and on the fears and hopes of an individual and an Aboriginal community. The presence of the Maya plays no essential role. That here there is a story that could have happened in different times and places.Therefore, what is interesting and what deserves to be highlighted is the physical and geographical environment that Mel Gibson used to develop a history of action, which, to her we sort under the label of "action film" always works very well. And it works thanks to the brioso and often stunning pulse camera and barbed levels which, in this case, for the pure and simple, violent action take a great effect for a memorable show. The pace also is more than correct and we have a filming have little or nothing to envy to the most consolidated authors on the subject. Gibson, what question should be, is it happened big filming this story that encandilará to a large segment of the public.In its initial stretch, the story has all the earmarks of being an adventure film, without more, with the eternal theme of revenge giving wings to a very topical argument: invasión-agresión - abduction-escape-revenge-new beginning. If it were an other unpretentious adventure film, as required wouldn't the originality in the history, but that how history is expressed in images. Many accuse Gibson give treatment stereotyped groups faced. But, I insist and no mistake, Apocalypto it is (?) an adventure film, it is not a "historical review of the Mayans" or nonsense like that you can listen to or read these days in different media. It is a film - starting, we make that assumption - about "good against evil" and in such a case, it is fair to characterize the characters agree with Manichean, dualistic representation. The human emotional relationship is compressed in a few essential ideas: the love of family, fundamentally. Clear, put the adventure in an Aboriginal context with its corresponding tribal regime - organized by kinship - does not gives rise to make too many stunts.We are attentive, however, Apocalypto has more than one level of understanding. We have already said that if we stay in that order of things which is pure entertainment with style and strength, little would accuse him of. But it would be naive to deny claims go beyond that. "Apocalypto" embeds a discourse on survival, dominance and power between civilizations, and conflicts between different collective human onscreen: guerreros-sacerdotes power of influence in the Mayan culture, a minority group represented in the subject Aboriginal tribe which rises in protagonist of the final moral (a new beginning) and the European conquerors who come to the shore of the new world with his menacing shipsarmor, and religious symbols. "Higher" civilizations subject and enslave the "lower". This speech has no depth or originality, is reduced to a mere scheme. It matters little that either, at the thematic level, it aims to provide otherwise.But the content of the film is not limited to the human level: the fauna is integrated into that chain of struggling to survive. What we have said at the beginning: the initial level (which suddenly appears a boar emerged from the undergrowth of the forest) opens the circle which closes with the flat end (a family of Aboriginal people entering the same thickness). Thus, what we have is an adventure that unfolds in struggles for survival or dominate either in a natural or cultural sense. It would seem that the whole of humanity, stripped of the modern tricks and inserted in a dangerous wild world, is represented in the movie using a structure and an organization of topics quite coherent and cohesive in some of them, not on the entire spectrum of styles and subjects, as we'll explain immediately. With this, we conclude that Apocalypto offers us a great show, but also good movies not only while. Leaving aside to "Braveheart" (much higher than the rest), Mel Gibson's best movie to date.However, its flaws are the same as the usual in the Filmography of Australian filmmaker; The capricious use of disruptive and plot elements. The case of the eclipse that saves the life of the hero in extremis creates a confusion of genres and consistency in style: do stand before a realistic film (subjected to the laws of reality) or before a fantastic fable?. Know that an eclipse never develops the form shown in the film and is a scene which seems taken from a comic book or an animated film. In this scene, key in the argumentative aspect, Gibson is not respected either himself or his work by capriciously breaking the logical coherence of the represented world. Uses a plot excuse inspired by the prophecy promulgated by a young Aboriginal girl to drive the plot where you but to violate the laws of the represented world. In this mixture of elements (realistic elements with fantasy elements) there is a confusion not justified.Gives the impression that the writer makes things "because it", with what the plot structure deteriorates considerably. Cannot be introduced variables in history without creating a few channels (implicit or explicit laws) so that these variables not deforming the contents, tones and the style. It is not more than a whim dramatic, like many other scenes of dream-like nature that catch-up, are filling the screen as a cheap trick to impress impressionable viewers but tools for critical judgment.</body>
</review>
