<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Más extraño que la ficción" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is intended to be a comedy of height as a drama about human feelings, although the resulting product is closer to pure and simple pathos that to something else.</summary>
	<body>All the arts have been always interrelated, have always drunk each other for mutual benefit. Since it appeared the seventh art, it has maintained a close relationship with literature, not only by the number of novels or plays brought to the big screen, but also for the good of many writers, creators of real gems, desiring to be considered as formalized most of being recognized as pure writers.Charlie Kaufman is, and that there is no who can discuss it, one of the best writers of screenplays in the global film scene. His imagination have come true masterpieces, and waiting for his directorial debut, here comes more stranger than fiction. That despite not included your name anywhere, the original idea of the movie is yours, idea developed by Zach Helm. Harold Crick (Will Ferrell) is a nondescript man, which takes a gray existence, until one day begins to hear a voice that narrates his life. Was it Karen Eiffel (Emma Thompson), an author who is writing his next novel, which plans to kill Harold Crick? Thus begins the new tape of Marc Forster, aires and very literary aspirations, which has not necessarily a defect, as many believe. Since then, developing the idea initial, which could have resulted a brilliant history, was an arduous task, and unfortunately the novel Zach Helm is not the height. Signing a script bombastic, with aspirations of small great author, full of inconsistencies and plot decisions looming everywhere. Desdibujados, lost and stereotyped until the end, the characters are more flat than a whistle encephalogram. It is intended to be a comedy of height as a drama about human feelings, although the resulting product is closer to pure and simple pathos that to something else. The plot suffers several mysterious and unexplained mutations, because it begins as a comedy to then move on to the tragedy, to finally become a stodgy cake. If that little was the ordeal, the weight of the tape lies with Will Ferrel, an actor full of nuances, specifically two: of the personified hieratismo can become the best approximation of the evil doll. Emma Thompson and Dustin Hoffman met in their roles without disheveled, while Maggie Gyllenhaal, only positive point of the film, is a good interpretation, eating at every level to Ferrell. more stranger that fiction is, without doubt, a film of great contrasts, which will not leave indifferent anybody – or you love or you are, there is no middle ground. And if still doubted by which option we opted, we do deeply by the second.</body>
</review>
