<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Fuego en el cuerpo" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is an excellent black movie that joins the sex - and its classical aura of fatalism and reverses - as Apostolic engine of the whole narrative fabric.</summary>
	<body>Unfortunately, body heat is not an erotic film flavored with a history of black series, and first advertised in a display information interested speculation: is an excellent black movie that joins the sex - and its classical aura of fatalism and reverses - as Apostolic throughout the narrative warp engine. The tragedy arrope the end of footage is not surprising: like, is mark of genre, which adds nothing new. Kasdan, very intelligent director and fine stylist of the advertising market, takes the sketches that crave you, the clichés, the common places of the accessible inventory, here and there and filmed with desparpajo, with absolute knowledge of the medium of film a personal, beautiful work.While the Turner never was my prayer book santa, here seduce, as the concise and sensible character of William Hurt in the role of lawyer in collusion with sin (the meat of the femme fatal so beloved in the film noir) to finish perpretando predictable crime.One reminds Jack Nicholson cake flour in the postman always flame twice of Bob Rafelson or the first version of Garnett Garfield or the Don Johnson lips fiery hole to find a background, but is Hurt by my way, who takes the cake, perhaps because he who most reliably represents the role of sex and does not fall, as Johnson, as the same Nicholson, save acting distances in the gestures of the first free and this raucous and pathetic divismo of the second. Ed Harris, who plays a similar role in China Moon and meets no more recently springs.In the feminine side, Jessica Lange, Lana Turner, Virginia Madsen, Madeleine Stowe, Veronica Lake, naming women then and now. Kathleen Turner has it infinitely easier than them: should be for tolerance of these frivolous times that the film not only does not cover their intimacies (genitalia) but that airea them: with full knowledge of what this exhibition will bring box office. We are all voyeurs good when we need to. And that body heat, as I say, not abused the erotic helpings, but who prefers loitering the murky world of feelings, of morals, contributing to the genus traps a rather than never stopped study allowances and repentances of crime.When other sisters movies arañan superficially, without further, here we have colourful film folk atmosphere (South night sweat, the spilled tópido as gasoline on a bonfire in darkness) where Kasdan, who is old Fox in these affairs, joins classic thriller and criminologist melodrama.</body>
</review>
