<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Un abril encantado" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Smells like bbc on all four sides. These small films are springboards to fame: soft entertainment transcendent unpretentious for a public fed up already perhaps bizarre plot machinery of E.M. Foster or for a public alien, altogether, to her.</summary>
	<body>The greedy Victorian Philo run by Ivory in the film and by the BBC on television holds an autonomous subgenre, smeared the same Excellencies, adorned with the same exquisite furniture, incorporated in the same engolado and cheesy, refined and strict, cliché of fierce moral conventions. An enchanted April is not return to Howard's End or A room with a view, or, much less, the fantastic Dubliners, but exhibits similar aesthetic and formal patterns, and dive, such as those listed in the soul more British etiquetablemente, encorsetada in their colonial desire and their imperialism of tea at five and table camilla musicada by pleasant syntactical twists: the EnglishWhen they speak, they are very his and raise the adverb to levels of phonetic hysteria as anyone on the planet.A delighted April smells like BBC on all sides: is one younger son, who has missed flight around the large room. No more boot already know that it will have a clean, sober finish, a roster of actors of the first order and a novelistic script watered by agile and added formidably care dialogue.An enchanted April is also a reflection on the myth of the voyage. Myth, on the other hand, inherent in the England of late 19th century and the 20th starts. In the middle of world war I, four women, played by different ailments, need of therapies is, decide to rent the castle of San Salvatore, on the Italian coast. Fleeing from their husbands, although they are fleeing from England, which is a more punitive and harsh husband: escape the climate and forms and overused showcase of protocols and figuramientos. The London pompous and refined, gossip, maledicente, makes these ladies of rank to take the paradise of the Italian Castle as a bulwark of their dreams, their hopes and final recompesa by all the time (lost, miserably) imagine it.In these rooms live these four ladies its wonderful April its haunted spring opening, how not, the love, the wholesomeness of the sea and its miraculous effects in some lungs burned by the fog. The roles are romantic: search the more standard meaning and we will find the romanticism that inhabits the film: in each small Flash. Evil, however, does not exist. Every thing on the site which should be: on the site which based they have tended. All leading to the sudden discovery of happiness and the (immediate) awareness of their loss.Does not take Ivory, which is already lagging, to make a decent product in this very British genre: Newell meets far. The BBC gives formidable children, curte actors worth and impregnates his seal scenes, smells and sensations that remain, indeblemente, in memory of the Viewer, whether or not the perfidious Albion.Estas son small films are springboards to fame: soft entertainment transcendent unpretentious for a public fed up already perhaps bizarre plot machinery of E.M. Foster or for a foreign audience, completely to it.</body>
</review>
