<review author="Plissken" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apocalypto is magnificent and deranged proof that Mel Gibson is about to become a character who likes to Werner Herzog.</summary>
	<body>If I were the woman or one of the children of Mel Gibson, it staying nothing quiet at night. This type makes already some time has crossed a line internal will that probably not be measured in every day just as in the film directed by. Because if the film is a psychological mirror of a director, 'The passion of the Christ' glimpse of the fundamentalism of a fanatic, and 'Apocalypto' it returns the image of a hallucinating wild dominated by primary instincts. And still they ask to be politically correct. 'Apocalypto' narrates the initiatory journey of Jaguar claw, a young Hunter who lives in a small village at an undetermined time in the pre-Columbian period. The powerful Mayan Warriors break into his life, sweeping everything in its path and capturing him as a slave. Jaguar claw will face a thousand dangers and their own fear to win the right to return to their forest.And with one premise in principle so weak and so hackneyed, what get Mel Gibson is immerse ourselves fully, as rarely before, done in a frantic struggle for survival. The word that best defines the spirit of the film is furious, and does not mask it, on the contrary. The alibi of the primitivism of the time allows Gibson get the worst of himself as person, probably, but well above that the best of himself as a filmmaker: Gibson turns what could have been another 'The emerald jungle' or 'in quest for fire' (worthy but too virtuous) in a story being that seems to spot by a shaman in the light of the fire in a cavern.In addition, the narrative virtues are multiplied by nervous digital photography Dean Semler (not by chance also responsible for 'Mad Max 2' and 'Mad Max 3') and the overwhelming Assembly of Kevin Stitt and John Wright, while so criticized anachronisms are minimized by the incredible design of production of Tom Sanders. All technical aspects scratch more at a very high level, taking into account that 'Apocalypto' was shot in natural settings in Mexico, with the difficulties that this implies.And the big question which was about the movie was the interpretations. Gibson was decided at the end by amateur actors to respond to the type needed each, and have to congratulate him on it. Perfectly defines it Max Renn in its correct analysis in Videodrome, "[...]" a few so real actors seem fused in his characters [.] "." If outside little, not limited to outlining a confrontation "wild good vs." "bad savages", but which may even find nuances in one and another side, always within the limits of what it is, an action film.As only possible failures, the historical inaccuracy, that may be offensive to defenders more stale academicism, and the simplicity of the plot, which is in turn one of their great strengths: when a jaguar and a dozen of headhunting Chase you through the jungle, is little space for philosophical delicacies.Beyond interpretations that can be (and that of always invent), 'Apocalypto' is magnificent and deranged proof that Mel Gibson is about to become a character who likes to Werner Herzog. 9.</body>
</review>
