<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Volver" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Return means to flee their own histrionics and clichés and formula it him exalted at the top of Hollywood</summary>
	<body>Rarely a very concise title sums up so many things. Almodóvar is very large. Knows remade, reform, transform, improve and dare to return to the path to that, himself, is predestined to go; the path of a great director, of a screenwriter round, intuitive, precise and consistent. Great men are only fleeing their own ghosts giving a new recital and returning to demonstrate mastery and genius. "Volver", means, among many other things, recover its Spanish audience, and not continue focusing their stories, above all, the taste of American and foreign criticism. "Back" means to flee in part of its own histrionics and clichés and formula it him exalted at the top of Hollywood. It is risk knowing that he is capable of giving with formulates it proper. And is that, "Volver", mixes drama with comedy, something very complicated to carry out successfully. Touches various topics, complicated scenes, and dares to navigate today and even to treat the social criticism in exact doses. Almodóvar, in this, his latest film, does not forget anyone and does not saturate, not exaggerated. We can taste its visual style, its control of the dramatic twists, his great leadership. It manages to be present, suggest, leave its scent, moving like a ghost without too much stress or force their personal and artistic intentions.Almodovar returns to work from the humility and honesty. It weaves a round history, a powerful and very well lubricated script. It exalts a magnificent cast of actresses and directs them as the well know. I do not understand those who insist on criticizing Penélope Cruz, who here loaded with almost all the leading role and returns, to demonstrate to the world that she is not only an actress beautiful and overwhelming presence, but an actress able to embroider the important roles. Carmen Maura returns, without complexes, to meet again and same. Carmen gets thrill, is real and wonderful, as always. And the rest of the actresses, all of them will be joining the bandwagon of brilliant performances. Lola Dueñas, Chus Lampreave, Blanca Portillo, Yohana Cobo and all others.Men, are all bad, very bad, insignificant presence, this does also as always, in every one of Almodóvar. manchego director the feminist tales, portrays in addition the people of their origins and that go and come to the capital which saw him grow. There is much autobiographical tribute and melancholy. And as the film is romantic, in la Mancha there are windmills, wind, superstition, traditions and the madness that Don Quixote was able to promote to the world. Almodóvar, you know that the film is to have simple things, portray austere places, people in the real world, but with stories and universal dramas, with poetry in all languages. Almodóvar tells the world and dives it, once again, in its own universe, a universe full of intentions, details, subtexts, and messages. Almodovar returns to prove that it is one of the best directors currently, a true lover of cinema and, quite possibly, one of the authors most sober and intelligent than our country has ever known.</body>
</review>
