<review author="Plissken" title="María Antonieta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film reveals that Yes, that is true, that Sofia Coppola is bored much.</summary>
	<body>It is as if you were watching. The young, rich and disgusted-of-both-luxury Sofia ends read ' Marie Antoinette: the journey ' Antonia Fraser, is it missing the dreamy air bed, sighs and says "Aish!" I feel so miserable and misunderstood as Marie Antoinette. "I'm going to bring to film his sad life." And will house of Francis Ford and tells him: "Dad, this year for my meets want me gifts to finance a very personal project". And Francis shivers to remember 'Hunch', but when when his daughter tells him "pooorfaaaa", it cannot be denied and produces it the film. "But on one condition, Sofia: do something to give money".And thus (I guess), Sofia is loosely based on the book by Antonia Fraser to tell the side surface of the last Queen of France in 'Marie Antoinette', his latest film and human. The story of a girl of fifteen who lands at the Court of Versailles in decadent splendor against their will, becoming first blank all the whispering and later head of Turkish (never better said) of the bloody French Revolution.But of course, the latter is not what Sophie wants to tell us. What she is interested in Marie Antoinette (Kirsten Dunst on an interpretation which confirms the legend on the blondes) is that it was young, pretty, not liked the protocols, loved go shopping and pelu, leaving party, eat cakes and flirt with young soldiers. Oh, and that was bored much, the poor. Both bored the Coppola torture with an hour and a quarter of "adaptation of Marie Antoinette to the Court" in that same thing happens again and another and again: I wake up, I am going to mass I gossip, I see the Ambassador I selves, I try my husband meets in bed, I sleep. And back to start. Her husband does not case. Their unique outputs for the depre are eating cakes, buying shoes and change her hairstyle (a speech something given to the cliché the yours, Miss Saigon.) (Coppola). Luxury and yawns, everything is one in this part of the film. Only a couple of scenes of these parranda and the character of Asia Argento are saved of the nonsense.After that time and fourth is when Sofia decides to show us the evolution of the character: of down-to-Earth and misguided Princess (really the ' Sissi Empress ', nor is nothing original) becomes Queen of France and mother almost at the same time, suffered a sudden attack of maturity and withdrew to a cottage with his daughter to play the farmers, causing even more yawns among the public. Highlights the plane in which she and her noble friends (her husband not, obviously) walk through a beautiful Lake with an expression of comparable only to my boredom in a little boat at that time. It is the phase "I'm a complicated woman" from Marie Antoinette, that is playing with your child as soon as it is pulling a Swedish officer. Her husband still going for it.For the final stretch, Sofia Coppola has already told everything that she is interested in character, which is already mother and already not spends as much at parties and champagne. so used (now yes) to historical events to wrap up the monarchy and all it represents. This is the most agile part, perhaps because it lasts about five minutes. When it comes to the truth, Sofia does not dare to lower their heroine until the end of the beheading, or fails to insert a map of a room of the shattered Versailles, so that everyone sees what was lost with the revolution. Damn poor, charged to a place and a people as "cool".Apart from such unfortunate vision of a character, Sofia Coppola has a competent operator as Lance Acord, and a production designer, k. k. Barrett, that recreates to the beast the golden cage which was Versailles (with special detail in the food). Actors represent a few dolls snobbish, decadent and carefree with similar Fortune (include Asia Argento, the only commoner of the role, Jason Schwartzman as the Bourbon stunned turn and Kirsten Dunst for his character of encephalogram cuasiplano and because get more cute than normal). And that's it.And at the end one remembers the trailer that plan with ochenteras songs and fast-paced poppy and realizes that that intention corresponds to about 10 minutes from the total of the projection, as the style is pompous and passed out in most of the film. But the Coppola has ignored his father and has been able to sell their vision of the twilight of Versailles as a fashion clip for nostalgic of the synthesizer. At least, 'Marie Antoinette' will not be what 'Hunch' was to his father, and Sofia may continue eating pastries during a good season.Finally, never so few chicha gave to write both. The film reveals that Yes, that is true, that Sofia Coppola is bored much. A 3.5.</body>
</review>
