<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Atrapa el fuego" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Misuse of time in the narrative, as well as the provision of information unnecessary and heavy, becomes a real folletín a quasi-interesting biography.</summary>
	<body>Many of the mistakes that we see today in film, have a common denominator: the false account that a good content is enough, forgetting something that can even be more interesting: a care and attractive continent. Because Lords if I choose between a ready man, and one that in addition to being intelligent has the appearance of Eric Bana, because so we are going to cheat, it will be that the I prefer the second.Jokes aside, when a viewer goes to the movies not only wants a story attractive you for whatever reason but that, in addition, want to be her know count (do not forget that even the best joke can be marred by a bland Muttley). This foreword is irrelevant to talk about the film "Catch the fire", which relates us the hardships that anyone can suffer in a dictatorial State, in this case, it's a humble black workers during apartheid. Patrick Chamusso, our protagonist, is not the result of fiction, but that the film is based on the real life of this South African who became a hero after his entry into the African National Congress (then resistance movement, now party political).So far, the thing might seem interesting, however, misuse of time in the narrative, as well as the provision of information unnecessary and heavy, becomes a quasi-interesting biography a real folletín with certain aftertaste to SOAP. To begin with, too much too much material which teaches us that Patrick was a beautiful person, with half of images would have believed me it. As much images of tortured to spare and in which not is informs us of his time locked (does a day, a week, a month?) On the other hand, only have material on income of Patrick in the ANC (and this is not an aspect as to sum it up in any military ditty). In short, too melodramatic accent and little order in the narrative structure. And I record I have not spoken on the photographs of the end credits (the actor and the real character in a hug?) (No comments).As for the actors, highlights the emergence of one of the illuminated ones of this century (and see that there are few: Bono, Susan Sarandon, Angelina Jolie, Pilar Bardem, Joaquín Sabina). We talk about the thinking good Tim Robbins, a character that has made history in the last celebration of international solidarity Madrid Film Festival with phrases as deep as "my intention was to support the festival, not leave in photos with right-wing politicians". "I feel that I have used." With barbaric acts like this, about the words. Incidentally, Mr. Robbins when you come to my country to speak on matters of policy should be documented a little more, especially if you are going to talk about a subject as sensitive as terrorism. Finally, how I love these self-appointed enlightened on the left that clean ass with tissue paper!</body>
</review>
