<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Apocalypto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Getting to know the Catholic code of Gibson I bet that not pre-Columbian america he chose at random. The message that he wanted to sneak us is, I suspect: a world without God is uninhabitable.</summary>
	<body>Mel Gibson leads to strictly one of the first principles of the good script: the hero must mistreat him. Gibson should learn others as the "Harry Potter" or the Bond series, with the exception of the last "Casino Royale". The abc's of the good script does not ask what take up such suffering desmelene. That's a stop, a bad habit that everyone you hold better or worse to the Australian.When one sees a Tarzan film, squeaking you at first glance the scenarios of cardboard stone, elephants in zoo, plastic plants and ponds who wanted to imitate African rivers. The viewer of the thirty conformed with such similar doses; the viewer today asked for more, but neither claims reality. The film caters tastes and adds some realistic detail when the demand note. I think that Gibson comes otherwise. It's approaching the world of Jesus, or the Aztec removing Middle old habits of the film, leaving only one which he believes could be reality. Why not fold films, or why the Aztec city does not seem to a city, and the road does not seem a way. Gibson tries, at first glance, not giving facilities to the Viewer.But he only tries in the first half. When speaking of powerlessness within the clan that is lived as something collective, storytelling with bonfire, the struggle between warriors and native, the journey, the eyes of the people who look to the prisoners of the cruelty of the sacrifices.The second half dispenses with the cultural contrast and us puts squarely in a narrative of always. The flight is full of evidence that speak little of another era, and much of the adventure film clichés. I guess that the producers were willing to risk only to limited extent. Either to one point in the footage.Getting to know the Catholic code of Gibson I bet that not pre-Columbian america he chose at random. The message that he wanted to sneak us is, I suspect: a world without God is uninhabitable. And as this is my page and I am not yet censorship, I take the freedom to respond to you. I do not think that the Aztecs lacked humanity and compassion from Christians. They had their human sacrifices to get rid of its surplus population, and we Europeans, we had our wars and our crusades to end up doing, with hypocrisy that Yes, the same.</body>
</review>
