<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Thanks Stallone and thanks Rocky, thanks to both, for giving us, nothing more and nothing less than a lifetime captured on celluloid. A life full of good values, sorrows and joys, real moments and, above all, of so many, so many emotions.</summary>
	<body>First of all, I apologize for extensive of this criticism and I recommend who still has not seen any of the films, including the last one, do not continue reading, because I betraying the plot of much of the saga. This is one of the sagas more successful and most famous in the history of the cinema, with all my respect to Bond, James Bond, who if the destination not remedy it soon, someday will give away me a record Guinness to be the only Western which still has not seen any of his numerous titles. Respectfully from here to his followers, also Sean Connery and the rest, but my thing is already something as a paradox of chance, a strange spate of circumstances and, lately, I recognize that there is also something of personal pride to a no doubt taste of burnt rice. I arrived very late and the incredible pirouettes of the famed English gentleman fail to really capture my interest. Rocky saga spans three decades from the first film until the last and most recent delivery. Let me start from the beginning: in 1976, an unknown actor, Sylvester Stallone, wrote a script called Paradise Alley (the street of the Paradise), inspired by a fight between Muhammad Ali and Chuck Wepner. The script fell into the hands of the producers Irwin Winkler and Robert Chartoff who, at first, were contrary to the commitment and the will of Stallone embody the Boxer protagonist. But this was really the first battle won by Stallone, who got the role and the production of his film dream. And although the film lost points against the powerful Apollo Creed, this won, however, by K. Or and in the first assault, Scorsese, who saw as Rocky was carried that year Oscar best film above its magnificent "Taxi Driver". Stallone was kept the title of your script and reserved it for another film that the same shot and played two years later and that, in our country, it became known as "Hell's kitchen". The script and the film about the boxer from Philadelphia became known as "Rocky". The Stallone film was shot in less than a month and with a modest little more than 1 million dollars budget and grossed more than 115 million just in the United States. Stunned by the Jubilee, audiences and critics, was joined in his favour and the tape became, in addition, with other two Oscars, that of best film editing and best Director of a total of 10 nominations and having received other Golden Globe Award and 6 nominations also for best film. If you ask me, I would say that "Rocky" is a wonderful drama, very well built, full of heart and epic and tells, perfectly, a story about self-improvement and the search for oneself. It is the story of an Italian-American boxer of talent, but without faith or opportunities, Rocky Balboa, who lives and earn the living in a low and depressed neighborhood of Philadelphia. It works as pluriempleado, boxing by four bitches and threatening to delinquent as a bully of little Assistant mounts. He has a crush on Adrian, sister of his friend Poli. Adrian is a very shy woman who works in a small pet store with Rocky, who will try to establish a loving relationship. Thanks to the fate, luck and partly due to its flashy nickname, "The Italian Colt" is gives you, in overnight, the opportunity of a lifetime. You can deal with the current heavyweight champion and dreaming about the title. "Rocky" story a honest, universal, of those Americans, in their national egotism and brazenly seizing the term, referred to as "The American dream". The truth is that Rocky is a good movie, but is also a film quite overrated, and proves the same Stallone with the sequel Rocky II, where he manages to break the myth of "the second parts were never good" tracing the structure and formulates it magic of the first part with admirable respect and intelligence. Obscures the development of the characters and their world and coming, even something beyond in each of the virtues of its predecessor. This second part exceeds or, at least, manages to reach the cinematic quality of the first but, however, this time did not succeed all the favor of the criticism. The public, however, received it with enough enthusiasm and raised 85 million dollars in the United States. I think that the first was as good, nor the second was so bad. I think that both reach a remarkable level and that, really, in addition to repeat in the work of writer, was surprised very positively the work of the own Stallone in the direction, that the truth is that, for 119 minutes that lasts this sequel, we arrived never miss to the director of the first part, John G. Avildsen. Avildsen is an irregular, for many mediocre, which nowadays is practically retired, but that, however, has managed to collect two titles that have changed the lives of millions of viewers of different generations: "Rocky" and "Karate Kid". With both, it has not only managed to fill movie theaters, but it has managed to motivate and to replenish life sports gyms of half the world. I must admit that even I myself came to green belt in karate (or was blue?) (Buff, nor remember already) thanks to this man. Returning to Rocky, can not ignore one of the strong pillars and one of those responsible for the success of the film and that this, thirty years later, is considered as a classic or cult classic, the masterful soundtrack to Bill Conti. The main theme, the song "Gonna Fly Now" is a linked cultural icon of life to the figure of the "Rocky" myth. Conti performed the soundtracks of all the series with the exception of the fourth installment, which on the other hand, under my opinion, was one of the best, influenced no doubt by the musical tastes and rhythms of the 80's, and that exalted and complemented the epic and the fast-paced action of the sequel. In Rocky II, film that came three years later, already 79 and with a Stallone, like his character, exalted in the success and fame, is justified effectively the conflict of the plot. The tape begins where ends the first part and we see Apollo Creed dissatisfied with his restoration of the world title (by points and far-fetched) before, the until then, complete unknown "Italian Colt". Internally, Apollo knows that it is very possible that there is someone better, a true champion, and the shadow and the growing prominence of Rocky torturing him inwardly. The character of Apollo is portrayed by the actor Carl Weathers who deservedly, becomes a prominent niche in this pugilística saga and will always be remembered as such. In this second installment unfolds much of the sincere and beautiful relationship of love between Adrian and Rocky, who after the match asks marriage and they end up marrying happily and by the Church, as a good Italian believer. One of the successes of the saga, is the give a background dramatic outspoken to scripts and offer personal conflicts to each of the characters. Stallone as writer, understands that the antagonist of Rocky, in each one of its challenges, is practically a character as important as the same Boxer. We understand the motivations and conflicts of Apollo, also of Rocky and, in addition, are drawn carefully the characters of Adrian, who in this second installment opposes the match trying to safeguard the health of her husband. The Poli, that poor Devil who is also his brother-in-law, or character of Mickey, the always endearing, and Grump coach Rocky. Women's Rocky becomes pregnant and Rocky is willing to leave boxing and work on what you can to support his family. But Rocky, although it is a very noble person, also is a very basic and uneducated person, and this becomes a problem when it comes to managing the money earned or seeking to work in anything else. From the Apollo environment is pressed to return to combat, but neither his wife nor his coach seem to support the idea. One of the best moments of the series is the scene in the landing of the House of Mickey. Rocky asks to please him return to train and coach shows you, giving you a slap in the face by surprise, that physically already not that suitable for combat. -Do you see it?, you've not even seen him come, right? And that has given it an old old man, what would happen if Apollo catch you several times? -I guess I noquearía. -No, you injure, forever. One of the eyes of Rocky has lost vision. The scene is simply anthology, along with others with some phrases like: "does Adrian, I?" do never you've asked that you stop being a woman, please? Please I ask, do not ask me to my that ceases to be a man "while Apollo ridicules it mercilessly in the media, Rocky was humiliated in the eyes of his coach working anything in the gym this." The situation is painful and excessive provocations, which causes Mickey to change its mind and decides to support him and return to train him. We see then how Rocky says "Sorry" to his wife and begins the hard training. However, Adrian will come to suffer serious health problems that will make endanger his life and that of the child of both. The tension and emotion increase, with a narrative that runs strong and balanced arrives and is perfectly transmitted to the Viewer. Apollo wants revenge, will to crush him, humiliating him and beat his own demons as well. While Apollo is trained very hard, we see a Rocky disheartened and without encouragement to be able to train with dignity, very affected by the plight of his wife. We can feel with anguish as they spend hours, days and as just the time. But this game is also one of the most exciting, sweeping and powerful moments that I've been able to find in a movie. Adrian returns itself, he was born the son, and both seem to finally be out of danger. This Rocky tired, but happy, is father for the first time and is willing to not return to antagonize his wife. It proposes to withdraw, give the match by lost, as appears to be the desire for his wife, but she understood that her husband has the heart of a true Boxer and that they need to fulfill their dream, asks you to do something for her:-want to do something for me. Come. -What. -You win. Vencer you!Then starts the music and training against the clock, and the hairs he put one as hooks. The big moment comes and Stallone has mentalizado its viewers with millimeter accuracy. The match is photographed with agility and a stunning staging and is vibrant and full of epic and excitement. Ëpica is a word that cannot be mentioned when one refers to this saga. Rocky II WINS by K. O, and who writes this criticism is, without any doubt, the best movie of all. Come the 1980s and Stallone, in its full physical and vocational, is about to live his decade of gold. In 1982 he will once again put the gloves and again, writes and directs a third installment in the saga. In the same year, another icon of action cinema, John Rambo in "Rambo", based on the best seller of David Morrell was born "First Blood" and will give standing to another millionaire saga. Rocky III is, the six parties, certainly the funniest and one of the most entertaining. The greatest success, once again, it is the election of his opponent, in this case, an amazing Mr. T (here known as d.) (A series "The A-team"), who takes his role very seriously and manages to create the figure of Clubber Lang, a ruthless, fearsome and brutal Boxer full of hatred. Stallone seems to be aware of that criticism, case of a third party, will not be of any of the forms in their favor, but continues moving tabs with great dexterity. Not ready to give up her formula secret and decides to mix the genres of action and drama. To compensate for them, he knows that he needs to sacrifice some of your chips. And if in the second part the health of Adrian and his son served to manipulate the hearts in it, use the death of the old coach as shock. The film begins with a sympathetic and almost crazy dose of humour which shows how the life of the champion has become a media circus. Includes a display with the then match, yet not so known wrestler Hulk Hogan that at times it is no less surreal. This principle, sometimes, almost humorous, this calculated and measured, to contrast with the dramatic part even with far more impact. In the moments before the match and during a discussion hot with Clubber Lang, Mickey suffered a heart attack, and although Rocky wants to suspend the match, his coach refuses and asks that you combat. In such a situation, Rocky is brutally knocked out and finished the match, in the costumes Mickey dies in her arms, believing that this has won the contest. Boxing is a sport respectful, noble and men and in Rocky III, will be Apollo, thanks to healthy admiration for who knew how win with heart and honestly and fairly, who, along with Adrian and Poli, ally to Rocky in difficult times. The training scenes and two fighting Clubber Lang, back to a great height, and this third installment returns to satisfy the general public. Rocky III becomes the film highest grossing of the three, surpassing the 125 million dollars in the United States. This third delivery, and contrary to what many people think, is for me an admirable sequel, exciting, vibrant, entertaining, with really unforgettable scenes and new musical themes such as "Eye of the tiger", which will remain forever in the history of the cinema and importantly involved in the greatness of the legend of the boxer from Philadelphia. We arrived in 1985. Stallone has just released the second highest grossing film of the year in United States (after "back to the future" by Robert Zemeckis), "Rambo, cornered II" which, on the other hand, and thanks to their dose of gratuitous violence, get sweeping Awards Razzie worst films in almost all sections, including worst picture, worst actor, and worst screenplay. Something under my humble opinion, certainly unfair if we take into account that it is a fairly correct Ribbon of military action. Times change and the prototype of heroes and villains also. The 1980s and the testosterone and fascistoid violence sells and works. Stallone can not avoid some mutation between their two most famous characters. Just as it does in Rambo II, in Rocky IV decided to largely ignore the social and dramatic part in the storyline in favor of pure action. And again as a writer and in the work of direction, get overcome again beating the third box office record. Rocky IV stands with the title of "The sports highest grossing film in history". Again get to tune the right notes and this is thanks in large part to find an attractive antagonist and live up to its predecessors. Ivan Drago, starring Dolph Lundgren, is a professional boxer from the former Soviet Union trained in futuristic art and facilities with the help of banned anabolic substances that give almost superhuman qualities. A perfect and programmed sportsman with the sole intention of humiliating the American Champion in half of the so-called cold war. This time, Stallone sacrificed a new piece, Drago fulminates and causes death in the ring to an unsuspecting Apollo who, out of nostalgia, decides to return to the ring. A stylish something more videoclipero than the previous ones, partly following the fashion of the 80 (mythical scene with Apollo Creed dressed as "Uncle Sam" and dancing with the "Living in America" James Brown) and dispensing used dialogs and the moralistic moments of the previous, Rocky IV is undoubtedly one of sports films of action more effective and adrenalíticas of the history of the cinema, and I know that it has been used, more than once, to motivate athletes of many parts prior to their sports enfrenamientos. Rocky IV, although it away style and claims much more artistic and sober style of the original, is a jewel of the entertainment and action and a real classic of the early 1980s. Him despite who gets upset. To Stallone, however, entered you the doubts with the Decade of the nineties. It seemed to be conscious, along with other actors like Arnold Schwarchenegger, that viewers gradually began to claim a change and new formulas. Heroes more sophisticated and somewhat less flat. The saga of Rocky had already given everything of themselves and Stallone felt that it was best to turn in his career. Shortly before failing a new facet as comedian with two absurdities as "Oscar" and "high or my mother shoots", Stallone decides to complete the saga of Rocky in the 1990s with a last, was even seriously tempted to let die to the hero. Returns the command in the direction to Avildsen, the director of the original, and tries to rescue the dramatic course of the first deliveries. But this time, by a total lack of clarity in their purposes and by attempting to modernize formula, this fails completely. Rocky V not only is the worst movie in the series, in light of all the previous years, but brings absolutely nothing new and only get to denigrate the fantastic character that exalted him into fame in one fell swoop. With a non-existent address, a script regrettable, boring, absurd and up anytime over one grotesque and ridiculous dialogue, Stallone, sacrificed a Rocky apuntillando addition to the worst and most unfortunate interpretation of his entire career. This time, the figure of Rocky is unbearable. He wanders without sense as a memo tarado uncontainable verbiage, that manages to fall ill for the first time and get rile anyone. And in this way, a saga that had resisted with dignity the tastes and preferences of almost two whole decades crashed miserably in the 1990s, garnering the worst reviews possible, failing completely to his followers and giving a more than sound bump at the box office. This desproposito by the lack of faith and decision, and without wishing it, seemed to be the worst end the myth of Rocky deserved. But in this 2007 premiered Rocky Balboa, this time Yes the final chapter of the saga. They have had to spend 17 years, 30 years since the first Rocky, so a Stallone with 60 years of age, try again to rescue the saga of the well and try to complete it as this deserves. Stallone has emerged very touched from the Decade of the nineties, years that have only demonstrated its growing professional decline, failure after failure, with films such as "Driven", "D-Tox", "Angelo Avengin", Taxi 3, Spy Kids 3D, and a large number of mediocre titles that departed it from the success. Rocky Balboa returns to drink directly from the same source as the first deliveries, and if those we had a loner slob who dreamed out of anonymity and succeed a against the clock as a boxer, in this we have a Rocky retired an old veteran who confronts the last quarter of his life as a famous former boxer and widower. Adrian has died of cancer, and Rocky runs a restaurant named where entertains the customers with their old war stories. The truth is that we cannot compare his personal life with own character and, in this case, your physical appearance and your current professional situation, play in favour and partly supported the credibility of what is set out in this latest film. I say partly, because we also believe that a sixty year old man receives the opportunity to fight against heavyweight champion. Although well is true that this already was almost equally unlikely in that first film in the 1970s. Stallone is conscious that, despite all their efforts, their physical power is no longer a credible and effective weapon as it once was to get offer generous dose of entertainment. Therefore decides to better concentrate seriously on the dramatic and emotional side which gives most of the footage. This time, it uses a new and powerful weapon, the nostalgia perfectly. Stallone returns to write a screenplay with craft, MIME and honesty and shows us a Rocky in its decadent phase, lonely, aging and melancholic. Rocky survives clinging to the memory of his wife and to the memory of the past, which as it is well known, were always better. Stallone, well aware of the very personal character of this project and risk taking that was the idea to embody a Rocky last and after 17 long years of absence, decides to again control the product closely and, once again, is himself who returns to perform the work of direction. This is a true success. In addition, also decides to return to work once, with a modest budget, this time for $ 24 million. The sub-plots and conflicts of the characters surrounding a Rocky in this installment are overly schematic subject a bit with pins, but fulfil its function and fail to disrupt history. I, first and foremost, highlight the scene of Rocky and poly in the factory of meat, where Rocky opens "stark" his heart, with tears in his eyes, in a genuine and really exciting monologue. Not so lucky is the final, with a training filmed with the Office of the experience, but extremely fleeting. It is missing the watch as a man of his age, struggling to return to pick up the form. Stiffness, dizziness, that aforementioned calcification of joints. Feel the countdown, the fear of ridicule, not keep up, the fear of embarrassment offer a regrettable show or be seriously injured. There is a non-existent tension dramatically and, at a stroke, we are a Rocky already in the ring. Mason Dixon is also the worse drawn and weakest in the series antagonist. Seems to discourage the power, in part to help the credibility of the whole or, perhaps, because it is no longer necessary no continuity or excessive character depth to deal with the last chapter. For all these reasons, we do not reach the combat so motivated as us were accustomed in previous clashes, and this is a too heavy burden. The match, on the other hand, nor get to reach the desired spectacle is, by far, and without the grotesque Street skirmish with Tommi Gunn in the forgettable fifth installment, made worse of all. Is foreshadow some good intentions, but the decor is pretty mediocre and the Assembly as the realization, are quite unfortunate. The modern winks and the intended style coolest of times that run with a videoclipera Edition and confusing, the show considerably impoverished. And if not, to review any of the brutal fighting of any of the previous movies. I guess that open levels and more classical installation of previous decades, show too much physical deficiencies of the Mise en scène of Sylvester Stallone today. A real shame and a great lost opportunity, the last, for after a fantastic first part of film, have been able to offer us the best installment of the saga. However, in general terms, Stallone recreates an honest, fair and exciting final chapter, with a unequivocally circular character, to reinforce the sense of roundness of a saga that has meant everything in his life. And if fortune and a broken hand (the contender for the title which was to face 30 years ago Apollo) he was then awarded the opportunity of his life and the beginning of a dream, the expected end it provides now another break by hand. In Rocky Balboa, during the match, the first of change, Dixon splits the hand with an unfortunate blow to the hip of Rocky, who are thus reduced their usual abilities in the ring, and what, on the other hand, the opportunity to a brave veteran as Rocky, match the disadvantage and give the show to stand stoically and with honor all assaults the young champion. Rocky lose points, already did that first time against Apollo, but morally, will return to win as did it then. Everything ends as it began, and entire generations of viewers have been able to grow and mature as direct witnesses of the life of a good man, a true hero done likewise. Rocky Balboa is a film of remarkable quality that closes the series with great dignity and is also a right and well-deserved tribute to the figure of Rocky and its creator. Stallone has achieved, thirty years more later, return to meet again with much of the criticism. Meanwhile, the public is responding as almost always faithfully and passionate and Rocky Balboa this being a success at the box office. Thanks Stallone and thanks Rocky, thanks to both, for giving us, nothing more and nothing less than a lifetime captured on celluloid. A life full of good values, sorrows and joys, real moments and, above all, of so many, so many emotions. I, in return, can only write me, until now, most extensive and detailed critique, written from the respect, admiration and from the heart of those who, like so many millions of viewers around the world, he laughed, cried and shouted for so many years at your side. </body>
</review>
