<review author="Yojimbo" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do is part of those independent movies that already atufan, that are no longer as indies, which should better be called of? under budget?.</summary>
	<body>They said that this film was the very best of the year. And advertising in media also. And as good supposedly independent movie, has to sell the typical scheme of rare family, with stereotypical characters wrapped in a simple one situation posed to a personal challenge and a vital lesson.The movie that a girl wants to go to a talent contest and accompany him in a dilapidated van his grandfather, choreographer and druggie, his protective mother, his teenage brother who hates everyone, his uncle in gay suicide and behind the wheel, a ridiculous father obsessed with success could be summed up.This short tale to the O.T. is part of those independent movies that already tufan, which are no longer so indies, which should better be called "under budget", which already have commercial and well-known actors trying to prove new things to gain popularity but it is that only make characters unfriendly or exaggerated so that they look at them. Of little outstanding, Steve Carell, which is the interpretive challenge of the movie that more is appreciated, in addition to being one of the better defined characters. The other roles are not more than the typical scheme of independent movie that wants to be appreciated as such. As in a history of Brooklyn still well, the moralina and moral from this film is so blatant and less elaborate than if any another film with marketing to the beast would be qualified americanada, reactionary or even facade.Come on, that this film, for me, is a perfect proof that how marketing of the "indie", marketing at the end, get some sector of public, supposedly indie, to dispose in praise, when it is nothing more than an interesting comedy with three good moments, some another sparkling dialogue and a couple of notable details.</body>
</review>
