<review author="Yojimbo" title="La ciudad perdida" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One more than remarkable film and an outstanding debut that unfortunately has gone unnoticed by the Billboard. The very best of the year.</summary>
	<body>"Works" are a litmus test. The directors are "sentenced" according to his first work. More curiosity they wake up if they are actors stuck to filmmakers. And may be qualified in a broad range of adjectives: promising, bland, genial? However I would add another adjective that defines this and other two films as A franco, 14 pesetas or the second movie of Zambrano, Habana Blues: felt.The stories that have an autobiographical touch, written and filmed with enough talent, are able to touch the sensitivity of the viewer and give the feeling that everything that is told, although he has not lived, has been real.Andy García, born in Cuba and exiled when Castro came to power, has wanted to make their particular tribute to his distant land through the story of a family that well could be yours. With a writer of exception: the late Guillermo Cabrera Infante. It is a pity that this film has taken so long to arrive in our country.The story Fellove family, wealthy and businesses in a Cuba ruled by the also dictator Batista. Within the family there are rebellious children who want a change in the country and advocate the golpismo of Fidel Castro and many other "revolutionary" factions. However Fico (Garcia), will always be on the side of his family, for better or for worse. And the family, as Batista leaving the country, begins to destroy Cuba. The character of Garcia reminds a little of Rick in Casablanca. And it is not a comparison that reste le points, of course.Although the synopsis sounds a little topical and sosa, hides a passionate and exciting film. It has an enviable cast in which spare Inés (Sastre, off the spectator of history of). Noteworthy García and infant given to Bill Murray one of the best of his career and the film characters. Without a doubt. It is humorous and almost "unreal" counterpoint in this story. But it's great and manages to raise the bar in the film.Make a movie felt also consists of wet historically, as it is the case. The film exudes tropical heat, catchy rhythms and a few recreations of characters and very successful historical situations. Nor let pass a figure as Ché, the another Fidel Castro frustrated. It may be that nothing progressive and idolized portrait of the "liberator" (jua) take back some. We already know to what.One more than remarkable film and an outstanding debut that unfortunately has gone unnoticed by the Billboard. The very best of the year.</body>
</review>
