<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Apocalypto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Epic film about the Mayan culture, recorded in maya with the intention of diverting the attention that almost nothing happens. Interesting, sometimes thrilling, sometimes sleeping, that is sure to not leave anyone indifferent.</summary>
	<body>This Mel Gibson makes some very strange things. First it makes Braveheart and freezes us the blood libeeeertaaaad coup. Later, she tells us the end of the Bible in the original languages and with more blood than in Kill Bill. And now comes to tell things of the Mayans, and as he likes to complicate the issue, makes us the film authentic Maya. Luckily they speak little.The film is about a Mayan village living happy without knowing that they are going to fall over. Overall, a bad day discover the inhabitants of another village, which has been destroyed by do not know who. Shortly after, these also destroyed them, being captured as slaves. Since that time, all Jaguar claw obsession is to escape from captivity to return with his family.The summary of the movie I noticed account that passes almost nothing in the two well long hours that lasts. For starters, the film is recorded in original Maya. If, in truth, in maya. What already pulls back. The script is good, but is that nothing happens. They pick up the village and try to escape, albeit with little enthusiasm. And when it seems that you're going to sleep, it ends. Being fair, I have to say that action becomes at times exciting, that produce you curious see if it saves or not. The landscapes are amazing, and the ambiance is very successful. That Yes, on the Mayans learn shortly, that not explained as he said once they were so advanced. Oh, and put rare names.In short, epic film about the Mayan culture, recorded in maya with the intention of diverting the attention that almost nothing happens. Interesting, sometimes thrilling, sometimes sleeping, that is sure to not leave anyone indifferent.</body>
</review>
