<review author="Yojimbo" title="Un franco, 14 pesetas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very decent film and a debut very interesting and personal, which is what gives originality and strength to this film.</summary>
	<body>The good thing about meeting people from the audiovisual sector and keep in touch with them is that can give you pleasant surprises. One, because you are invited to the premiere of a film in which are co-producers with a Madrid company composed by Eduardo Campoy and José Manuel Lorenzo. The second, because there are occasions in which they don't have to lie and deserve give them in person your congratulations.This is the case of my former colleagues from guess productions of La Coruña. The production company, led by Jorge Algora and Susana Maceiras, takes years devoted to the audiovisual sector responsible for spots, institutional videos, offering HD and high-end postproduction services? among many other things. Now have gotten involved in the production of films, starting a couple of years old with Camino de Santiago, the origin, feature-length documentary in which I participate during the filming and post-production. It was a very strong bet that had a decent result, above all by the magnificent photography, Suso Bello. Subsequently fell it to fiction, beginning with the nines lying to life and now with the debut of Carlos Iglesias in the direction of feature films: A franco, 14 pesetas.The story is simple: Martín and Pilar are a couple living in a basement in the Spain of the 60 Argüelles. But a couple of events will Martin immigrating to Switzerland in order to earn money and send it to his family in Spain. He will be with his friend Marcos and together you will see that they are not only working in Switzerland: also found another way of life which contrasts greatly with the "spanish way of life" which had at the time of the Alcántara. Lo first it transmits this film during his viewing is authenticity. Along the same lines as Habana Blues, film that gives the impression of being a very successful portrait of Cuba. Many Cubans are or have lived there in fact say that it comes very close. Because the same applies to this film. I've never been to Switzerland, but it seems that it is so well portrayed that the power of real and plausible come together to make one story more interesting.On the other hand there to highlight glitches of pace to lengthen unnecessarily the film. It is not long, but it gives the impression that the Assembly could have been more agile. The work of actors is great, the Mise en scène is worked and the setting is very successful. Mario de Benito composed a kind and melancholy music that you may have too much presence in the film, but continues to be an interesting job. Special mention to Isabel Blanco, actress who personally knows the circumstances on which is based the screenplay of the film and composed the character more grateful and better composed of all. A real gift for the actress and a totally adorable character for the Viewer. Nominations should be.Another of the most interesting aspects of the film is that it presents emigration in little "current" circumstances. It is the case of people who cannot find work and is not forced to go abroad to look for life, but for anything it has to do with the emigration we see and that many try to sell as the only: arising from absolute poverty and whose table of salvation is to go to another country with nothing. In the case of this film are about characters who are out of work and know the opportunity to continue doing what they know but in another country. But the least seen and more "educational" film aspect is the way of life of the host country and respect "imposed" and that there are also profess. It is very significant for the time in which the old woman that picks up some papers that have thrown the protagonists to the ground to throw it in the trash. If something must be thanking this film, the slap that many feel to see us more than purely cinematic aspects, is identified with the protagonists and the way of life that are: totally nice, orderly, logical and (this is already more staff) full. Best thing about the film is that all those who have not been in Switzerland we are migrants and ignorant in many sequences.In short, a very decent film and a debut very interesting and personal, which is what gives originality and strength to this film. I at least have a desire mad I go to visit Switzerland? I hope that does not in the circumstances of the protagonists.</body>
</review>
