<review author="Yojimbo" title="Hécuba, un sueño de pasión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A more oriented mitómanos documentary which is welcome.</summary>
	<body>This documentary is directed by José Luis López - Linares (winner of the Goya Award to best picture last year) and Arantxa Aguirre. For 80 minutes is a review of what it means to be an actor for the actors themselves. Anecdotes, truths such as temples and contradictions are the ingredient in this documentary, whose name takes of Greek mythology.Do Maribel Verdú, Enriqueta Carballeira, Marta Fernández Muro, Carmen Maura, Berta Riaza, Carlos Hipólito, Javier and Pilar Bardem, and my beloved Pilar López de Ayala, etc? they compose the Group of interviewees have their feelings in the beginning, how is "infected" with the virus of the interpretation and how to live each day a profession whose difficulty little can externalize until that you put in your shoes.Although the documentary knows little and has a good rhythm, I miss less testimonies of other people working with actors. As they say, they need other professionals (screenwriter, director) more to develop their profession, by what would be good have interviewed some filmmaker who turns especially with actors such as Almodóvar, for instance.Especially fun is that contrast of views on the vanity, a sin which only denies Maribel Verdú Guild of actors; the same happens with schools of interpretation, each defended by serving for much and others just the opposite.One of the criticisms made by the actors of this documentary to the public, i.e., to all of us, is that we soon forget them. And special mention to those actors who are in the world of interpretation for years and now have little opportunities. And if they have, they are not have been big stars and currantes in his moment of glory.However this documentary directors have not had the idea of putting names to multiple photographs of actors that we inserted, as well as headline some of the cinematic sequences that we see.A documentary focused on the mitómanos and people who believe that she has been infected with the virus of the interpretation that people close to the audiovisual sector, which will be, in any case, welcome the collection of testimonies.</body>
</review>
