<review author="Yojimbo" title="Glengarry Glenn Ross" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A Bible of interpretation and a remarkable film that sometimes leaves us with an open mouth.</summary>
	<body>Recently, in the already closed Daily Prices of La Coruña, I had the opportunity to acquire this film in its only Edition on dvd. Her he had been hired at the time and it had proved to be one of the worst editions on dvd that he had seen. It would be unfair if not say that it looks to be one of the first films in this format. Why has no subtitles in Castilian (although the audio in English) or not (amazing) extras the role of skip chapters during the film. Still, for the price that I purchased her worth.James Foley had hand in a surprising and very young cast. Does are obviously talking about a film of 1992: Jack Lemmon was still a second maturity, Ed Harris had hair, Al Pacino seemed a newly licensed dandy, a teenage "climbs" Kevin Spacey, Alec Baldwin had received the first fascicles of "how to do cabronazo in the film"?But we should not forget the guru that you probably gathered all: David Mamet.El great playwright and author of emblematic plays and admirable cinematographic works (many based on those scripts) is the main protagonist. Both the construction and the dialogues are a masterfully structured vehicle to give us insight into nothing dogmatic but if cruel and oppressive of absorbent and ruthless can be live to work. The great works are distinguished by simplicity, see how something humble can be great and apparently hasn't cost work carried out. This is Mamet. In this film all the characters, even glib statements, are nothing more than a metaphor. There is a great salesman that seems that doesn't sell, others instead of selling to customers sold big tradeoffs between them in order to achieve what you should do based on "suckers" and some damn chips with data from potential buyers who put in check the values of a few "greyhounds" that must be the goal rather than his third post will make them lose the job.A great movie and a great original work that lays bare all gotten manipulations and having all the dirty tricks that we can use in times of despair.With Foley collaborated Juan Ruiz Anchia, that great patriotic director of photography fully settled in USA that brings the lights and shadows of this work and a discrete James Newton Howard.Una masterpiece for those who want to learn more about how do dialogues, a Bible of interpretation and a remarkable film that sometimes leaves us with an open mouth and a smile of "fuck""go peliculón".</body>
</review>
