<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Hollywoodland" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hollywoodland would be a perfect example of that Boulevard of broken dreams in which so many aspirations end up bursting are and becoming dust.</summary>
	<body>He wanted the coincidence that this "Hollywoodland" was premiered at the Venice Film Festival, to the chita figured, just after the highly publicized "The Black Dahlia", which was a disappointment and a disappointment for the majority of critics and viewers.However, the film of Allen Coulter was excellently received by the Cowbird and company, which put it in the clouds, praising its realism, the excellence of the interpretations and the benefits of a script in a single film tells two stories, in present and past, in the classic style of "Laura" or "Outlaws", where the dead come to life thanks to the research ofin this case, a private detective.Two films, therefore, in that the stories overlap, becoming both equally attractive and interesting. On the one hand, the farcical biography of George Reeves, one of those actors in Z series that appeared in "what the wind" and hit a braguetazo with the wife of a capitoste of MGM, through which landed the role of "Superman" in a popular TV series. and nothing more. Because between the type did not have too much talent and the man of steel cast a lot, few more opportunities had show off their talent.Ben Affleck plays with dignity the role of pathetic actor-gigoló with artistic pretensions, at times lower than his film no-carrera, he decided to hit a shot and put an end to everything. Or not?Because his mother tends to think, rather, that their child was committed suicide. And that is when it enters the picture the cadaverous, ugly, attractiveness, drunk, acomplejado and complex Louis Simo, a detective of medium hair that falls in luck the case and that, using for their cause to the tabloid press, begins to play the noses of some and others, left and right. to stay single.Simo, impeccably played by an Adrien Brody that he weighs worldwide, which seems to carry it loaded to their backs, it is the prototype of uncomfortable detective and hinchapelotas who becomes obsessed with the discovery of the truth, despite who despite. And what is the truth? Suicide? Murder? That is the question. Or not. "Because what is really interesting is the Hollywood tells us his debutant film, but veteran director as to tell the dark flip side of the American dream, thanks to its recognized work as director of many chapters of the Sopranos, among other series.""Hollywoodland" would be a perfect example of that Boulevard of broken dreams in which so many aspirations end up bursting are and becoming dust. And the musical reference is not free, since much of the atmosphere of the film is achieved thanks to a soundtrack that faithfully reproduces how sounded the California at that time, with their bands of jazz and melancholy music, still far from the rock of the 1960s.The sordidness and the sadness of the lower depths and slums, the grief of the detective and the desolation of the middling actor are highlighted through a soundtrack in key jazz, with lot of metal of wind that trumpets look especially piano chords and up a whispered harp.This contrasts with the joyful and festive jazz played the big bands at luxurious parties Hollywood that appointment was the cream of the Mecca of cinema. A musical counterpoint which comes to to highlight the few lights and much more numerous shadows in which thousands of people lived the Hollywood dream.</body>
</review>
