<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do we left somewhat disappointed because, honestly, we expected more from Clint, the last classic of the American cinema, whose?Letters from Iwo Jima? already look forward, in the confidence that, this time Yes, will the true measure of what he is capable.</summary>
	<body>Reasons why "Flags of our fathers" is over disappointing us George and me, still a good movie, and on the basis that we were loaded with enthusiasm, desire and good vibración:primero.-because it is not what we had promised. And it is that long time, are telling us that this was the film about what happened on Iwo Jima. And that, later, Clint Eastwood we would tell the same story, only from the Japanese point of view. And this is not the case. Because in "Flags of our fathers", Iwo Jima is not but the scenario, the Mc Guffin, which would read Hitchcock, that serves as a starting point to tell another story, that really is the famous photo of soldiers raising the American flag and, above all, the return home of heroes, converted into cracks mediaused by the Government to raise funds to sustain the efforts of war.Second.-because the film is dispersed in various plot threads.And, therefore, the film does not have the hotplate, solvency and soundness of "Mystic river", "M$ B" or "without forgiveness", for example. On the one hand, we have the memories of war, excellently filmed, as it was presumably with a director of the Office of Clint, drinking directly from the style of Spielberg in his "saving private Ryan", passed through the sieve of scorched picture of "Jarhead".On the other hand we have the episode of the uprising of the flag, photography, etc. Thirdly, the media of the case, the relationship of the three survivors who returned home converted into heroes by the Department of State and its tour across the country collecting money. And, finally, the rest of the lives of three characters, family relations, their successes and, mostly, their vital failures.Third.-By the characters.Sincerely, Clint and his great writer could have been with the character of the serve, which is the best example of what the film wants to transmit. A guy running, much to his regret, he become hero and since as a model of a thousand different ideals, when he just wanted to be an anonymous type. And all the self-destructive impulse that accompanies him. The other two characters are more tasteless and sincerely, reach a little bored. Or, when you leave less, completely indifferent.Fourth.-because of the confusion of intentions (and hence, results) do they wanted an anti-war film, which lend pests on the war? They wanted a film that denounced this society of the image in which we live? They wanted a film to speak on the use that makes the power of citizens when they are useful for then forget about them and leave them in the lurch? Of all this there in "Flags of our fathers", but none of it is well resolved.Having said which, Jorge and I left both cold of cinema, still knowingly and in the conviction that we had seen a good movie, with ex officio and master sequences. We left somewhat disappointed because, honestly, we expected more from Clint, the last classic of the American cinema, whose "letters from Iwo Jima" already look forward, in the confidence that, this time Yes, will the true measure of what he is capable. In other words, another masterpiece undeniable. We were cited.</body>
</review>
