<review author="Yojimbo" title="La joven del agua" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story with a great deal of hope and good intentions.</summary>
	<body>Lady in the water in a few words, is a tale to the Tim Burton with a great deal of hope and good intentions to the Frank Capra. While the marketing surrounding the film sold the film of terror, the new Shyamalan is a story in every rule, a tale for adults who want to be children again and find an opportunity with a haunting Bryce Dallas Howard. Paul Giamatti, an actor of luxury after a few memorable roles in between drinks, Cinderella man or American Splendor, is disillusioned and humble protagonist acting smug way but which later became one of the most tireless fighters for "the cause".With inevitable reference to the war of Iraq, Shyamalan film is the less Shyamalan career (in the absence of the protected view). The good/bad managers is to have identity or plot tics which tend to repeat throughout his filmography, and in this case it is pleasant that almost everything you fear throughout the film (the typical questions of whether will be dead, if there will have been a leap in time, etc?) is not fulfilled: "what you see is what is". There is also a fierce criticism of the film critics, who portrays as destructive pessimistic that they pursue their prejudices.It is essential, after the forest, James Newton Howard talk about when working with this director. Each time I give more laps and I think that, while finding Neverland is a fabulous score, the work of Howard should win the statuette. It is certainly his best work, but with Lady in water it seems that you want to recover or take advantage of this masterful squandered creative for this film. Obviously not "being reached", but it manages to thrill. It should be noted the time I think most emotive film that the disk is titled as The Healing. Take note.To give you an idea of where is the director, I reproduce the phrase that appears at the end of the roll of end credits: "for my daughters." I will tell you this story once more. "But then you go to bed." A delicious tale with very few "buts".</body>
</review>
