<review author="JPastor" title="Firewall" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Where they have gone into the movies as?Games of war?, I pushed to get into this?</summary>
	<body>I just got back to House after seeing, invited by McAfee, "Firewall", the new film of Harrison Ford in which the prota makes computer security expert. Poor Harrison not too gives the pego as a freak, but is that the majority of the characters are pretty crappy. We have the unforgettable Robert Patrick (T1000) that seems to have aged 50 years, to Paul Bettany wrong malísimo that not paste or glue (at any time seems to say "I'm a ghost!") ("I'm a ghost!" as if Russell were ahead) and a cast that does not convince. The rest of the bunch of bad are a few flojeras, and an uncle of 60 years can with one half of age in a physical confrontation (in fact, with two) is not too credible. The truth is that the argument is not bad, but the movie is a little truño of life. I wanted to leave a couple of highlights to the end: to "hack" the system (call it somehow), Indiana (I do say?) Directing? I say? (Harrison) is mounted a scanner of last generation with a fax/multifunction Reader toolbar and an iPod mini. I have no idea how pussy connects one to the other (the port of the helmets of the iPod is not a port of entry, and not seen welding nothing to the proprietary Apple connector) but the thing shoots incredible way: collect 10000 account numbers of the Bank (through the screen to which the reader the scanner bar is stuck at an incredible speed) and stored in the hard disk of the iPod in the form of images. It then passes by an OCR application and ready, we have account numbers perfectly registered in our laptop. That, and the collar the dog GPS (which have them Hayles, eye) are two of the technical pillars of the plot of the movie. No comment. Buf. By the way, the movie leaves Windows XP everywhere, except (I think) in a small moment in which Harrison suddenly introduces a couple of lines through a command-line to boast how controls configuring routers that found me, so at first glance, Linux, although I'm just wrong. Where have gone to the movies "War games", which propelled me into this?</body>
</review>
