<review author="Yojimbo" title="The woodsman" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Surprising debut and a great occasion to reward Bacon with the Oscar, but if already not honored a transsexual, imagine you nominate a pederast.</summary>
	<body>Some actors have a healthy habit of investing their megasueldos in miniproducciones as stars (beyond, of course) in films who believe more interesting and will bring them more professional satisfaction.An example is Kevin Bacon, executive producer of The Woodsman (here the lumberjack: P), directed by another Director, in this case debutante, with great tact and sensitivity, Nicole Kasell.El argument, more thorny: a pederast is reintegrated into society.Since then Bacon could have been chosen a role and a less controversial topic, but that adds a point of interest and a lot of discomfort for what the film may contain. However good feel of the Director, as Niki Karo in the land of men, in this case fails to load the inks but neither redeems the character. That if you know create a tension without an explicit description that will make the Viewer is feared the worst. Or what about Bacon, accompanied by his wife in real life, Kyra Sedgwick, is the best of the film. All his work is the epicenter of a well conducted history and some times very uncomfortable, emotional and even full of rage and anger. They also have weird appearances Mos Def (of 16 streets) and Benjamin Bratt as a close relative.The film also portrays how can be the "reintegration" of a subject as this film, which not only already tries to be invisible to the rest of the world by his own guilt and remorse, but that some people leave you in peace and not make more difficult their existence with continuous rumors and gossip. Separate point is to rebuild a life, especially if you have had family. And, perhaps worst of all, check if it is able to again do something terrible to a boy or a girl. None of these elements is ignored in the film, which can be described as courageous.Surprising debut and a great occasion to reward Bacon with the Oscar, but if already not honored a transsexual, imagine you nominate a pederast.</body>
</review>
