<review author="Yojimbo" title="Dicen por ahi" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Rob Reiner a loose script makes a good address, print good pace and can take good gags to the screen.</summary>
	<body>See the Friday evening in good company Rumor has it (say), with Jennifer Aniston, Kevin Costner, Mark Ruffalo, Shirley MacLaine, Mena Suvari, Richard Jenkins? is that everytime you think? What a cast!Well, taking as premise the rumors that part of the family of Sarah (Aniston) is the portrayed in the book and film entitled the graduate, the protagonist will try by all means find the answer to a question that puts the lace to many suspicions about his family.Jennifer, as well one of my co-visionadores of the film, defined in this film is very much like the characters Meg Ryan had certain comedies as French Kiss, i.e. something hysterical but nothing burdensome, but rather funny. It does not fall in the overacting at all. In fact it is confirmed as a wonderful actress. And she is the best claim to this film. A_el_final_de this post you will find links to other actresses who have made their films a true vehicle for showcasing personal:) and professional.Then it appears, to the surprise of many, Shirley MacLaine, stretched and fairly recognizable but doing a role to suit and how not, with great talent. Kevin Costner repeats in a role somewhat similar to beyond hatred. It is "reborn" and winning integers to return with a great product in the near future (and I do not mean that helicopters of which you can see the trailer): P. His character, apart from being the typical adorable for the female audience, is the most damaged by the script and the characters, leaving him with a reputation and a totally unjust situation for him, but that bad of a loose script? you let loose.Rob Reiner a loose script makes a good address, print good pace and can take good gags to the screen. Also with this incredible cast and some that another phrase memorable for the always memorable Richard Jenkins.Entretenida and decent.</body>
</review>
