<review author="Yojimbo" title="American Dreamz" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Weitz is a perfect example of someone who succeeds thanks to the American dream that has been able to make this film.</summary>
	<body>I imagine Paul Weitz, analyzing the current situation of his country and thinking to himself: "I have to do something about that." "I have to tell the world what I see but making smile."A very laudable purpose in all those writers and directors who want to make social cinema. Yes, Yes, social cinema, as this film.We have on the one hand a current and real basis as the U.S.: a stupid President, terrorists are not so bad and may even be friendly, totally superficial social values reflected in a television with and for morons? go, like that in Spain: DPor across our clear intention to comic director when writing the script: he wants to make clear a clear critique but also a declaration of intent to provide something positive or a solution to these problems. And for that he seeks redemption for all those real characters. And of course, which covers very little press. Only you get to do some cosquillitas, a decaffeinated of international conflicts, a sticker in the portrait of some characters?American Dreamz is a kindly, topical and supposedly critical film that at times resembles a bad Spanish series of comedy (as if there were any good) and other a fun portrait of "the world upside down". However the formula "real 2 comedy" in hilarious tone not here covered and apart from not to provoke laughter, stays in a plea so pro-americano that anyone with two fingers in front will be as follows: the President of USA, surely expect much seen in the most stupid film, remains as a true hero and a great person who is only manipulateda company idiotizada by a tv program is its generational, that the superficiality which provides entertainment to that idiot society (Grant and Moore) can find their soul mate and, finally, that all the characters in the film they succeed in their own way.In fact Weitz is a perfect example of someone who succeeds thanks to the American dream that has been able to make this film. Of the pro-American pamphlets more brazen (and involuntary by a loose script with ingredients that pose uncomfortable) have been in a long time. You still smile a couple of times. Ah! And a joy is to see Dennis Quaid. The rest of the actors, flojillos, though I am amazed to Willem Dafoe as Jolie.</body>
</review>
