<review author="Yojimbo" title="Zombies party" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is one more than decent and entertaining product and that surprises with its successful tension and abundant blood and black humor.</summary>
	<body>Dawn of the dead is one more than decent and entertaining product and surprised many by his successful tension and abundant blood and black humor. And of course, if come the parodies of films many believe that they have to be in plan Scary movie (Incidentally, have no paint never stop? as long as movies that parody).However the English manage to always get an ACE of the manga. They pick up a success as the zombies, adapted it and added much more elaborate but black humor. English humor well written and scripted. And the result is Shaun of the dead, title with much more game than the Zombies "hispanicized" party.Shaun is a slob with a boring and monotonous life. He lives with a childhood friend who only plays to the console, has a girlfriend claiming more commitment, a lovely mother and a hateful stepfather. But some day, people start to do strange things. It seems that they are all sick, become them white eyes and walk clumsily. Until that Shaun and his friend realize that are surrounded by zombies spend a half-hour with some another smile and ingenious Flash very normalita. Do from "the girl in the garden", the apathetic protagonist turns into someone determined, a hero who wants to rescue his mother save his girlfriend and bring them all to a safe place up? up not sure what.Without neglecting the movies from zombies gore aspect (there are some other sequence fairly explicit and asquerosilla), this film is great for black humor that follows. If Starship Troopers was another work of a great sarcasm (confused with a fascistoid tone) in which we could see youngsters prototypical and handsome stuck to bloody and disgusting vermin cannon fodder, this film fun to see so close and vague characters stuck to heroes of middling. The script is a great comedy that exploits to the maximum the clichés of zombies; that if, leads them to its more sarcastic end without losing respect for the genre is.In fact there are some another (too dramatic but insurmountable) dramatic moment that makes fall much rhythm. But this day of revelation does finish watching with a smile and a final sketch which leaves you with the idea of some parodies can be turned into good comedies.</body>
</review>
