<review author="Yojimbo" title="Domino" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is outrageous so that has made me laugh, get me and thrill me at times.</summary>
	<body>Delirio:1. d. disturbance and mental excitement, caused by a disease or strong passion: hallucination is one of the clear signs of delirio.2. Excited state which not due to reason or to the voluntarily: This infatuation is a delirio.3. Nonsense, nonsense: this film is the delirium of a fool.Well, I think that it had never begun with a dictionary definition, but is that what can better be the last film by Tony Scott: DOMINO. Her I was waiting with eager expectation after the great fire of revenge. It already ahead much of a new style more extremist, if possible, in the use of Visual effects. This film is only a crude copy of his previous film but multiplying by 1000 dramatic Vertigo. And that is a pity, because for the first hour I put love and had a true pass, but then falls. Falls in a very insulting and shameless way that already do not know where you get. Gives me just to get out two of the guys on 90210 as comical and autoparódico element, there is a cameo appearance of Tom Waits, Christopher Walken made of hysterical funny, that Mena Suvari reappear on screen to the delight of many, there are good suicide bombers and tramas calcadas of his previous movie, Keira Knightley do so fairly well, that Mickey Rourke is okay in its roledo, that Gregson Williams copy and paste sentences of his own works, which the director has a good taste in music? It is a dramatic truño, videoclipero, and worst of all: there is no who see him. Not because it is very bad (there are quite attractive incorrect times) but because if her you are going to see the film will have to include a bag against the dizziness in the seats. It can be fatal. A film not recommended, not because it is bad, but because it can not be seen.But I liked: PEs outrageous that has made me laugh, get me and thrill me at times. What can I do? for a story that could be interesting written by evil and what little attraction so throw overboard a stylish stripping seriously misplaced.Mr Scott, recovering?Perhaps see this film again, but more than anything as Visual effects and postproduction. Come on, for professional inspiration</body>
</review>
