<review author="Yojimbo" title="Asuntos pendientes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that reveals a new twist in the modern detective plots.</summary>
	<body>At first glance, and according to other reviews, the film seemed to drink from Heat, this masterful film of Michael Mann to (how time passes) already has 11 years old. Some similarities are true, but only in its stylistic and commercial design.This film features two heavyweights of French cinema (Daniel Auteuil and Gérard Depardieu), a decent shooting sequences but far reaching the film by Mann and an atmosphere cold, blue. And end there similes. The script is very original and I presume have an autobiographical load and a personal contribution of very strong director. Very similar to cases of Habana Blues and A franco 14 pesetas. Not in vain Olivier Marchal was police while studying interpretation and made tasks of screenwriter, and surely his experiences are reflected in several moments of the film, completely original (the theft of the plate, the repudiation in an official act, etc?).The story is about two agents of polícia de different brigades that are wrong. Even the macguffin from the movie catch thieves in armored vans, the plot revolves around the envy and bad plays that certain police officers make for past reasons left to see but not are explained, which is that thank. None of the characters is a Saint, but there is a real cabronazo in history. The outstanding issues referred to in the film are quite clear as it progresses the footage. And with it increasing disbelief by cruelty without limits and a corruption and moral misery unprecedented. The strong point is a very hard, extremely plausible script.On the other hand think that the effort to write a hard story has left aside the aspect of the direction of actors, two monsters like this film are rather dull. Some portion of the footage calls the seriousness and even the apathy of an absorbent and hard work to be the protagonist, but as the characters are falling into a spiral of violence, the interpretations require much more pulse of which the director has been used. On the other hand, perhaps a few minutes, that removed the half-hour Pantry you end could accelerate and make the film more interesting.A decent film that can be seen with passion, as she was my case, and that reveals a new twist in the modern detective plots.</body>
</review>
