<review author="Yojimbo" title="El manantial" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great movie with a great climax and large current value. The man who remains incorruptible and clung to its principles has all the win? in its own way.</summary>
	<body>King Vidor directed in 1949 this magnificent film starring Gary Cooper and Patricia Neal. It is based on a novel which was adapted to screenplay by the same author, Ayn Rand.Howard Roark is a totally groundbreaking modernist architect. But really modern and groundbreaking of this man is your integrity and honor. After spending much time being rejected by their totally "revolutionary" ideas about architecture, passes to another kind of work that go you to what it has always sought to achieve: his creative freedom.One of the things that most can throw back spectators with prejudice are too direct, too poetic dialogues and with almost philosophical today sentences for today not precisely abound. However they are sparkling, beautifully written dialogues and gives the character of Cooper an entity so valuable and wonderful as the message of the movie itself. To give a reference for the quality of the dialogues could give the example of Eva naked. Another important point of the great dialogues is that they enhance much the moments in which they are used, in those who play with glances and indirect statements, as it is the case of the affair with Dominique Francon (Neal) film is a complete plea for individualism. As complete and straightforward as you can be living as you want in favour of communism. Do however the script relies on a tangible reality: the man who remains incorruptible and clung to its principles has all the win? in its own way. It may sound too naive, but the history of Roark, the architect that is not plegaba to the mandates and taste of the majority, manages to realize your dream without renouncing its convictions. But this knows that you have to pay a "social" price: staying unemployed, endure the criticism of fools who think not if same, support the charity of those who succeed without merits and worst of all, see how others who admire him and rely on it are no longer endure and yield to the mandates of most.The great Gary Cooper gives the character of Howard Roark a serenity and enviable strength, with a vital attitude as clear and coherent as simple to understand: the achievements of a society are achieved based on ideas that people can look forward to. For this reason it is essential to guarantee individual freedom in order to guarantee that all can enjoy those fruits of people with initiative and love for what they do.A full and honest character like Roark not only causes rejection in those sheep that follow the guidelines established by a majority distorted and manipulated. It is also a beacon for those that have repudiated all what they consider correct, as Dominique Francon, critique of architecture of The Banner, newspaper directed by cynic Gail Wynand (Raymond Massey). Two of them are the characters who learn more in this story, incorruptible Roark talent will be for them the ideal that neglected and courage that were non-existent.A great movie with a great climax and large current value. Very indicated for those who know that they do not fold to fashions, nor to the majority or the minority which boast of alternatives with which the time say that they were right. Good thing about individualism portrayed in this film is that if you leave prosper someone in what actually you are passionate about, everybody wins. And it is not something that defends socialism.</body>
</review>
