<review author="Yojimbo" title="El último golpe" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This entertaining comedy is more paladeable for a few who know the subject to other lay in the field.</summary>
	<body>Feel the passion of the film sometimes opt to take a step beyond who are trying to do something. And as in any other discipline, the illusion of starting a project you exceed and create you a totally indescribable euphoric State. And more even if it's an "Opera prima". This is the case of this film.This film is based on an article by Steve Fishman entitled What´s wrong with this picture? The FBI apparently masked produce a film to catch a mafioso. And it sounds like this is the argument. Alec Baldwin (Joe Devine) is a very involved with his work and has to catch a mobster who controls to truckers. Matthew Broderick (Steven Chats) is a naive lover of cinema that is moving from centuries ago his script. The FBI agent follows that many trucks are used in the shooting and therefore, if they are passing through producers and simulate that they will make a movie climb you with the hands in the dough. And at that time Devine and Chats are known.The lure of this film, like many others that portrays the world of cinema, is that many look it with more affection and see reflected experiences that many other viewers deduced as certain: the eccentricities of the world of movies, actors, actresses, of the drawbacks of the producers to the directors, etc? The most "romantic" film is addiction who feel all to create something as large as a feature film. Even when the conditions of production make shooting a sequence of a desert in a parking lot, everyone feels this sensation of being brewing something to join a team. And the magic of the film not only catch the usher of a film that premieres as director, but also a FBI agent who sees power of cajole and engage in the fruit of its decisions.It's fun to see Martian of many workers in the film. So the film is supported by an actress as versatile and great as Joan Cusack (uncredited) or Toni Collette, as well as other side who do not not bad as Calista "McBeal" Flockart, James Rebhorn or Tony Shalhoub. And as a good way of creating humor by "contrast", the director (and writer of the terminal and catch me if you can) chooses my admired Glenn Morshower as head boss of the FBI to monitor a desmadrado Baldwin. Ray Liotta and his scary face will make "balloon pinchador".That is why, at the end of this entertaining comedy is a more paladeable product for some few who know what refers to other lay in the field. And such leave final power project a negative without revealing, see it as a positive and enjoy them on a big screen with sound and everything can even forgive them. : P</body>
</review>
