<review author="Yojimbo" title="Burt Munro: un sueño, una leyenda" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film to smile and to delight us with a character full of life that runs towards his dream.</summary>
	<body>From time to time there are movies that go unnoticed with both summer blockbuster. Between impossible missions and cansinos codes between mutants and Supermen, there is room for tiny and delicious films at the time was A franco 14 pesetas.This is the case also of Burt Munro: a dream, a legend, a fairly correct but less passionate than his original title translation: The fastest Indian world´s. The film, directed by Roger Donaldson in "indie" plan, as at the time wanted to be him Philip Noyce, becomes a delight nostalgic, autumn, but full of energy with a monster of the interpretation as it is Anthony Hopkins.Como in many products that depend on a total and absolute protagonist, risks fall into gloating and excessive protagonismDespite the redundancy. A not too serious case was the superb Cast away (Castaway), with Tom Hanks colossal but the great excuse of being on a deserted island. Who might do him of antagonist? (:) The dream of Burt Munro is very simple: want to run with his 1920 Indian in Bonnieville, USA, a paradise for all those who want to break speed records. Let us not forget that we are in the 1960s and the protagonist lives in New Zealand. The only thing that is clear to Burt is that you want to run and will take necessary steps to arrive at the race. But what has lighter yet is that it should live their life and their passions. The film becomes a trip fraught with more diverse characters and comedic, emotional and even hilarious situations. So attractive is the trip that the purpose of the film goes into the background and what many feel is a real envy of the vitality that prints to Burt Hopkins through his interpretative power.It is a film to smile and to delight us with a character full of life that runs towards his dream. A great lesson of cheerful cinema without ñoñerías. A great life lesson that we can change the variable of motorcycles by any other that fill our lives.</body>
</review>
