<review author="Yojimbo" title="Matador" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In short, a pretty fun movie. Do not expect a very elaborate script, but it is written in a very original way and cause a few laughs with basis and without many of the clichés of common use.</summary>
	<body>Remove the stigma of one of the most popular secret agents in the history of the cinema is difficult, but as other professionals who don't want to stagnate, Pierce Brosnan has been able to choose a less commercial than the custom project.Matador (dispensable copy of the Almodovar film) is like A dangerous therapy but something more "indie". (Sounds like something superficial, but it was the reference that I constantly came to the head while he was in good company (including an unusual cinemas);) However, the Richard Shepard film mixes elements "deeper" and something more interesting that of the Ramis.Julian film is a Hitman who is a little tired of his nomadic life. His boredom solves with drink and women. However, some day someone remembers something he had been overlooked: his own birthday. That makes you think. And chance makes it meet Danny, a seller with very bad luck and a recent tragedy. This meeting in a bar in Mexico will change your life.The best of the film is undoubtedly the actors. And the exotic of the script that moves by many countries representing the uprooting of a nomadic lifestyle and, worst of all, isolation against which must be fought when it absorbs us work. On that basis "serious" us is an original sometimes wrong and sometimes divertimento.I am very surprised "rude" Brosnan character in one role more than interesting. And Greg Kinnear, giving the pego as the typical pardillo currant with bad luck. Hope Davis, although it comes out shortly, is always welcome, and other side giving you certain entity to the film.In short, a pretty fun movie. Do not expect a very elaborate script, but it is written in a very original way and cause a few laughs with basis and without many of the clichés of common use.</body>
</review>
