<review author="Yojimbo" title="V de Vendetta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do a worthy and politically opportunistic entertainment but? safe?.</summary>
	<body>The V is not only the initial of Vendetta. also what is for?Vigorous: the film is made with a great technical invoice. Although the film lasts about two hours and fifteen minutes, is it not long. The action sequences are spectacular, the fights are well made. It is a worthy entertainment, above the standard, with an amazing cast. To begin with, Hugo Weaving in a little grateful for the actor, but interesting role as a composition of a character through self-expression. That if those who have seen the dubbed version have not had occasion to see his work in reality. Also is a pleasure contemplate the beauty and talented Natalie Portman.?Vacuum: a priori, the most controversial element of the film was the script. Ideológico-político speech is an advertising incentive that may predispose to the most reluctant or more "revolutionaries". However the film blends many concepts, represent them with so much Manichaeism and resolved with a fantasy so characteristic of a comic that is as substantial as the popcorn that will be consumed watching this movie. Totalitarianism, fascism, freedom, terrorism, justice, revenge and fear are represented with a depth appropriate to a "botellonera" society, which is why anyone who is not accustomed to arise on a daily basis by those items the movie will seem an encyclopedia full of values. In fact, more incisive and hard criticism that could make the script is the great forgotten, but is given a finish so patronising that nonetheless seem comfortable pamphlet to the Eisenstein, that if, with a musical accompaniment tastefully chosen and extremely emotional and dramatic. Do not forget that great trick of script that benefits the protagonist to unite his revenge with his particular revolution.The main characters, both the terrorist cult, refined, generous, friendly and that does not kill innocent as the girl who learns to lose their fear to end a lever, trigger made a trip on behalf of Justice is actually to settle scores with the past. Its director, with great musical taste and good job on the Mise en scène invites us to that trip. Let us not forget that there are behind the brothers (a brother and a sister) "Guachosqui", that they wanted to start a filosófico-virtual movement and ended up with branches of intragables digital trinkets. Perhaps because of this it the rumor that Alan Moore did not want to know anything about the project as soon as he read the script runs?</body>
</review>
