<review author="Yojimbo" title="My date with Drew" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The documentary is rife with humor, enviable admiration and a rhythm.</summary>
	<body>There are some exercises which are a perfect example of ingenuity and creativity against economy. And the ves when you know that you can say "with skill get do something just broke".Brian Herzlinger is a 27 year old who can't find work and since childhood is a fan of Drew Barrymore. He was a member of her fan club, has always followed his career? and thanks to its name and a phrase that she said are encouraged to perform and document in video, with two friends, seeming impossible: stay with her. Hence the title of this documentary: My date with Drew.Pues well, in 30 days and $1100 (you have to see the documentary to find out the reasons for these curious constraints of "production") will try to stay with her, so it will be asking people to meet industry people to get in contact with her. The result? As in life, is the journey the interesting thing, the fun, the gratifying?The documentary is rife with humor, enviable admiration and a rhythm. It is real as life itself and is a wonderful trip and reflection of what many ilusionamos and some reach achieved with certain initiatives. Also browse between the waters of the "fanaticism", of the "fetishization" of people dedicated to showy work and socially known as actors. Sometimes it is inevitable to feel embarrassed of the protagonist, who comes to be depressed for the results you are getting and that allows something like inform an actress interferes in their lives.Even so, it is a documentary full of life, of illusion but not which can stay in good intentions. It is a reflection of how with little money, good friends and great enthusiasm can get things like this, which may be questionable, but which are so personal as non-transferable.I partly feel identified because, although I was lucky to meet professionals who I admire, never occurred to me documenting as Brian. And that there are many, many, many reasons to do something similar to what he has done here.On their website you can see more material. At the moment it isn't edited in our country, but if what you seek well cyberspace you you can find.</body>
</review>
