<review author="Yojimbo" title="En tierra de hombres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Niki Caro gives a Campion to all those that make portraits victimhood and simplistic.</summary>
	<body>When you see that the subject of a film like this can be summarized in "the struggle of a woman" by their dignity in a male-dominated environment, many believe, and I the first, which we find with insults to the intelligence and film as the Te doy mis ojos of Icíar Bollain, who does not hesitate to explain the inspiration of his films.However, Niki Caro, this film gives a Campion to all and all those that do portraits victimhood and simplistic situations which reflects this film. In the mid 1980s, a woman comes to work in a few mines of Wisconsin. But they are not mine to be found in Asturias, underground, in which also worked women and whose conditions are tougher than the film. The case is that Josie M'aimes (Charlize Theron), who runs away to her parents escape a husband who mistreats her, is not the first woman who comes to work at the mine where the number of men is higher. Her friend Glory (Frances McDormand), because it is in the trade union representing the women, warns him how hard this job can be.As soon as Josie enters there, is not only not supported by his father (Richard Jenkins) who also works there, but begins to suffer abuse and harassment of fellow and that other classmates see it as something normal and accepted. However Josie, with a reputation for "lightweight Helmets" girl and young mother of two kids, will try to fight to bring anyone back to do the impossible job with humiliation. You will not only find with male chauvinist a good part of the mine workers prejudices, but you will also see how fellow hide head to that complaint, fearing that his works run danger.There is no explicit beatings, not physical violence. Yes, that we usually see in news and scavengers programs of "journalists" garbage. Here the abuses are more "realistic" and credible. And I assure you that they caused in my (and surely more than one) a rage turned on that in any sequence of beating of Te I my eyes, Troglodyte (this Caveman is the only thing that was missing the title, but insurance that is not recommended).Decent against fair against miserable bastards daring against cowards. That is the subject of the film. The good pulse of the Director, a beautifully chosen and superbly directed cast (look at the sequence of just 2 minutes from Richard Jenkins before the members of the Union), shocking characters and musical moments used with great tino (Santaolalla in his line and a new song by Bob Dylan that you can hear in Radio Katana) are the ingredients to highlight a good movie that I think is being underestimated.I at least enjoyed her and her enjoy when it comes out on dvd.</body>
</review>
