<review author="Yojimbo" title="Flores rotas" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do a good film with a good dose of humour which you then plants? what pussy I laugh, if it is well sad?.</summary>
	<body>I had read great and malísimas criticism of Broken Flowers. Well, let's go by parts.No one will be surprised to write makes Jim Jarmusch film independent. Therefore, many who know that already know what they face. Especially those that are left blind by labels. For better or worse. To be considered a crappy or a masterpiece. Because I am glad to say that I am in a middle ground? pulling to good.Don Johnston is a wealthy donjuan low hours who receives a mysterious anonymous letter in which communicate you what father for 19 years and that possibly the child you are looking for. He, so apathetic as it can be interpreted a very well used Bill Murray, decides to move from the topic until his friend and neighbor, Winston (Jeffrey Wright) investigates him and gives him the idea that going to visit five women who have possibly written that letter. Five women with whom he had a relationship in the past.To begin with, the character of Murray is so bubbler that gets you. It is so useless that you do not know how to react. It seems difficult to see a donjuan during moza. His life is nonsense. Nonsense focused on a sofa in front of a stunning plasma TV where seen movies and cartoons. But when his friend Winston organized you around a scheduled journey, Don wants to resist? to 20%. In the end he made the trip. At the end you visit to Sharon Stone, Frances Conroy, an almost unrecognizable Jessica Lange and wonderful Tilda Swinton? and a fifth that makes the culmination of a cruel but fun trip and acid, as life itself.The film has its moments "BMW" to the rhythm of the wonderful music of Mulatu Astakte (as used it Woody Allen in "The curse of the Jade Scorpion"), but is certainly a trip very interesting, full of sarcasm and so varied characters, not to say freakis, that the character of Murray seems the most normal. Notably, the character of Jeffrey Wright, a wonderful secondary that deserves all the awards acquired and for having. A masterly counterpoint to the character of Murray: it is a generous, hard-working man, has 5 kids and in his spare time he plays to investigate on the internet.A good movie with a good dose of humour which you then considering "what pussy I laugh, if it is well sad". A curious anecdote is, in the final part of the film, in which it seems that everything will be resolved, there is a cameo appearance of the real son of Bill Murray, Homer Murray. The name is a good joke, huh?A film not indicated for those who didn't like hidden (cache)</body>
</review>
