<review author="Yojimbo" title="Plan oculto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is a fun and exciting story of robbers and police. Highly recommended to spend a good bit of quality.</summary>
	<body>Recently we could read that the new film by Spike Lee had been number one at the American box office. The first taquillazo of this "independent" director. Well, yesterday I could attend the preview of this film, by invitation and thank you in greatly to my friend of Vigo;) Inside Man (horrifyingly here entitled hidden Plan) could qualify as one of these turns of some directors such personal as Woody Allen with his Match Point or Cronenberg with A history of violence. They are directors (or authors, for those who prefer a "European" touch) that provided its style and showed his talent in films that could be called gender and extremely attractive. They are also a confirmation of the versatility of these filmmakers.Because the new Spike Lee film is the police project. And the truth is always appreciated the hand of someone who has style for this kind of stories. The plot begins when the character of Clive Owen plans a robbery at a bank. But it is a perfect plan. Obviously does not know anything about this plan. Denzel Washington is an inspector who touches him to deal with the situation, the bank robber has hostages. Willem Dafoe is the head of special forces and works closely with him. However the owner of the Bank, Christopher Plummer, wants to regain some of that branch and so sends to a mysterious and attractive Jodie Foster.La film is a fun and exciting story of robbers and police. Why fun? Because there are moments of genuine humor that sadly it can be real. It gives the feeling. On the other hand relies on stereotypes of the mugger Calculator but not all bad and the police honest, naive and something tontines. The interpretations are more than correct, although the character of Owen should be more frustrating because just the face is seen during the film. A hallmark of cinema?But something interesting and exciting as the robbery of a bank hostage, the film happens to have moments of irregular rhythm. On the other hand, can not miss the social criticism of Lee with minifrases and protest minipersonajes, but well, we know that with money you can take any speech and go on anything.For not disclosing anything important, film, which lasts two hours and little, takes a turn in the final half-hour which aims to make sense of what happened. The end is "moderately" surprising, right and at the height of this type of films that aims to provide a plot surprise. This what you get? with some other but. There are still many questions and doubts, especially the character of Owen, but actually gives a bit just because the writer prefers to portray the real evil in this story of little subtle but clear way for the Viewer. One may terminate the film a little fly and dissatisfied, but the balance will be positive because that has seen has the hand of Lee and has signed a more than decent entertainment.A highly recommended movie to spend a good bit of quality. Eye music Terence Blanchard (the John Williams of Spike Lee): his online very but very interesting.</body>
</review>
