<review author="Iñigo" title="Destino final 3" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The final blunder?</summary>
	<body>When one pays one entry for the film (with all that entails today), at least will meet a minimum entertainment. As superfluous and banal to be. But there are times the past years too, in which one receives the slap of reality more sad and hyperbolic. "Final Destination 3" is one of the products that easily us closer to the more precise definition of "crappy". What is robbed in the film at least helps us to graphically recreate the definitions of the Real Academia Española. here, until the divertimento hides his head out of shame to be recognized. Cannot be extended on this film criticism, since there's nothing to mention, and far less positive. Except the purely aesthetic and dramatic, aspect in which evidence its high budget (what self-worshiping brain could waste so much money by depriving us unfairly the possibility of investing in much more interesting projects and, above all, intelligent?), the rest is absolutely bland and near with stupidity.We have the Group of topically contemporary American teenagers (sometimes not so much), the hormonados and guaperas that we see in all movies of this ilk. That Yes, now with a little more variety, certainly divided between wealthy "snobs", select portion of the more purely elitist society, and "macarras". Or, rather, "posh macarro".We take a blender, join the protagonists of the plane crash with the highway accident aderezamos the ideas of the first with the brutality of the seconds and obtain the groundbreaking characters of the roller coaster. Only that here is scrunch less the brains and not built up ultra-inteligentes and elaborate theories that made fellow of previous deliveries to mock death (who was death to spend so tronchante awhile at the expense of the gentecilla!).It seems that the film wanted to be more realistic and more truthfully portray flat and simple society in the country. The film is a turn of the screw and a copy of all the elements of the two previous installments. And if they were dispensable, the third left into something purely absurd and irrelevant. Does not have the allure of "novel" (if that is you could call as well) of the first, or wild brutality and "gore" of accidents of the second, which satisfied the staunchest fans of the more morbid and violently attractive Gallery.It is for more inri, a smoothing compendium of both and nothing risky.That Yes, some accidents, without being as spectacular or wild as the second installment, satisfied that the followers of the free. But in this film until it is reduced to moments. And leads us, as their long-awaited end to a new situation of "déjà vu" and intuition of what is going to happen. The only scene that can be defined as "idea".One arises if the film degenerates to movies like this and how, should withdrawing is him to the same definition of "seventh art". At least films such as "3 Final destination" should not include in this concept. Fortunately, we still have puffs of air that allow us to breathe and enjoy the true meaning of the celluloid. Although increasingly they are diluted more and more. They say that hope is the last thing that is lost, by very bleak to be the situation. Let us hope that we should not declare a still State of alarm.A explanatory critique is not necessary in relation to what you atienes to see a movie of such characteristics. I think that the good entendedores (come on, which read simply) to see the poster already know what is inside. That Yes, never wrong come a warning that, as tobacco and similar drugs, seriously damages our health. But everyone is responsible for their actions, and if you want to enter the film leaving the encephalic mass in the tail of the box office, the truth is that it is his perfect right. Your doctor, later, are in this respect.His collection in our country, almost analogous to the taquillazo on the other side of the pond, leaving into question our supposed progress in certain aspects and demonstrates the great similarity we have cited quadrupedal ancestral peer.It is, avoiding generalised (if at this stage that is possible in the world of cinema, by the paths taken and majority percentages you have purchased), what gives us the passage of time and the establishment of new generations. We do not lose more time. It does not deserve. Simply let us give thanks James Wong by return to the first delivery address and clarify that theirs is not a coincidence and is an expert in graphic definitions.Definition of "crappy" by the RAE: "Badly done, disorderly or tasteless thing". Let's go by placing another image of a film to his side.</body>
</review>
