<review author="Yojimbo" title="Deseando amar" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A love story late, accidental and prohibited. Rather, autoprohibida, which can be the greatest difficulty that you find.</summary>
	<body>They had told me that if a love story not viewed Brokeback Mountain, I would not for love. Before this ruling categorically and agorera, someone with whom I agree (surprisingly) in cinematographic tastes, recommended me this film fervently. Already had in mind to see some of the so revered Wong Kar Wai, but their enthusiasm (and because I usually trust his opinion) managed to give him some preference.Since or for one or for another.Love is a game director. Initially, the accuracy of the Mise en scène, the presentation of characters and bases envelope which is going to spin the story are put on the table in an exemplary manner, but to the 28 minute film is confusing and it takes many turns without giving clues. From a dinner, the film becomes subtle and great excitement: play love, rebuild a love, interpret sequences of a relationship that was not warned and in which there were two victims who have joined. Both live a love caused by an infidelity. But they have in mind not be as Adulterers who have joined them. This will be a problem. As big as the love they profess.I can understand that this movie is of those films that you hate or worship. And that they make a director at one of worship or in any rule author. I I'm in the middle and do not intend to pay tribute to neither sink nor the film director with permission of both recommendations (who loved the film). Do not liked anything tics of the director, getting fades to black every few minutes, carrying out sweeps in an intimate sequence, getting musical moments sometimes meaningless and that they remembered moments "El Corte Inglés"? ICT style I took off much of what narraba.¿A their favor? It is a late, accidental and forbidden love story. Rather, autoprohibida, which can be the greatest difficulty that you find.If I have to stay with some of the film is the phrase of the female character: "Paying attention you realize things." That is why some don't notice many, although we carry sunglasses.</body>
</review>
