<review author="Yojimbo" title="Buenas noches y buena suerte" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A penalty of film for those who expected a fable for freedom, which by the way, could be applied in our country.</summary>
	<body>It had preceded trumpeted a lot, very good advertising and comments praising the critical capacity and value that has had the actor to make a film about the witch hunt and a plea for freedom.I regret to say that it has not made a film, he has tried to do two and it has been with a "specimen" of film. And of course, to opt for being a Troubadour has neglected altogether the script, which introduces us to characters that are born from the first frame as heroes, defenders of the truth and honest when they are nothing more than journalists. It is clear that American patriotic sentiment is widespread. They are not only journalists, first they are Patriots.In Europe they have idols as "rebels" like Sarandon and Robbins who are critical of Bush and his policy, like Clooney, but never cease to say that they are Patriots (although saying it only with certain Presidents already do sing their ideology). Patriot is a word in our country is a pestilent and has connotations of past times and is supposed to overcome.Why are the protagonists of this story soon Americans than journalists? and go Patriots and journalists!But Clooney has wanted to highlight that and has opted to pull newspaper library and video library to illustrate his fable about power excessive state, neglecting completely the script without giving life to the characters and ignoring the drama of the situation so that the Viewer could feel terrible at the time.It is a documentary fiction done with a large photograph, David Strathairn powerful but without life and emotion, something very disappointing for those who we expected something similar to the dilemma, another possible example of how power can crush people.In the absence of seeing the movie of Ang Lee and Truman Capote, it is of the most unfair nominations for best film and Best Original Screenplay. A penalty of film for those who expected a fable for freedom, which by the way, could be applied in our country. Guess who has the power and who the truth (something very pretentious respond but is what sells the poster for the film).</body>
</review>
