<review author="Yojimbo" title="Manuale d'amore" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pity that the title is no more than a title. It would be a best-seller.</summary>
	<body>I had the opportunity to see Manuale d? amore, an Italian comedy that is succeeding despite being a film modestito and simple. And could not be more predictable: the stages of love depicted in several historias.1-time enamoramientoTal the most complicated of narrating, develop and treat because there are so many ways and reasons to fall in love as individuals; so many ways to react as ways of being. In this case it opts for the crush. A guy has no luck in life meets by chance Giulia, a beautiful girl. He will go after it, will try to meet her and in this attempt many things change in your life, but not by chance. A nice story, the more idyllic. And perhaps the hardest creer.2. the crisisPero-what happens when the couple has decided to take the plunge and marry? What follows the beautiful stage of falling in love? Although it is not a desirable time, the next step is the crisis, in which defects are beginning to overcome the virtues. Love begins to dress of affection or even a minimum respect and may be considered to begin the twilight of the couple. Ways to resolve it? Two very simple: go ahead and try to fix the thing (with as many solutions as ways of love) or cut clean. If you opt for the first, the logical thing is to commit? 3.-couples traiciónMuchas opting to continue forward, but not exactly fixing their situation, but inertia do that nothing happens. But there comes a time in which someone looking for something out of wedlock. And when he discovers, comes? 4.-the abandonoAunque does not necessarily have to be for betrayal or infidelity. It may be that you fall in love more than another or another. And what you do? You suicidal? You follow ahead?When you realize as you've begun again the chapter 1.Obviamente the film is a thousand times better, is narrated with a lot more grace and is a perfect example of how to make a good comedy romantic with economy except for the script.Pity that the title is no more than a title. It would be a best-seller. But it would be one more, because for this, as for many other things, there are formulas nor manuals to use. A penalty?</body>
</review>
