<review author="Yojimbo" title="En la cuerda floja" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not all biopics are equal. The Office of James Mangold is outstanding and manages to not only hit with Joaquin Phoenix and Reese Witherspoon, but go a little beyond the anecdotal.</summary>
	<body>Not all biopics are equal. We can fear be moralina and narrate the typical twilight of a star, normally in drugs or several vices that then there is something, usually the love and support of someone who redeems all the evil done, both to yourself and to others.This film also goes that. However the Office of James Mangold is outstanding and get not only hit with Joaquin Phoenix and Reese Witherspoon, but also manages to go a little beyond the anecdotal, such as do country music, to focus on a life with certain trauma, which could well be the any, and how you can mix in a bad way with a change of habits such as sudden stardom.Another point in favor of this film is that it reflects not only the character of a character, but it also preaches rightly that no matter much dexterity interpretative if known exploit in your favor. And also more merit has if a style you create with this step.Another of the successes is the choice and direction of actors, both in recent Golden Globe award-winning. The interpretative duel has ups and downs, but low-lying areas are very high. There are initial moments in which the character of Cash is child, without too many features (at least from what I knew to this singer) recognizable. Then appears Reese Witherspoon (June Carter) and literally overshadows the screen to Phoenix, having between the two impressive chemistry. But then the decline of Cash is masterfully played and represents the definitive consecration of the evil Comodo as King of the movie. Special mention to Robert Patrick as the despotic father of Cash: this will be his year, I do not know why I get to my.Perhaps err on the side of corny, but it contains exciting moments such as the treatment of the family of Carter cash that a camel is closer to your home, or a declaration of marriage of the more predictable but musically moving.I'll stick with the good memory of the boot, with the music contained in the prison walls of Folsom, that at first I thought the Hall of to the side, but which were to be the drums of war in a battle to right-handers soldiers armed with a guitar and great country.</body>
</review>
