<review author="Yojimbo" title="Munich" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spielberg has managed to reach the political correctness without neglecting the necessary formal impropriety.</summary>
	<body>I was afraid but in very good company to see the new Spielberg movie. The Princess Renoir were overflowing. I terrified on the tab of the film that lasts 2 hours and 44 minutes. My mother, which I expected.For starters, Spielberg is a great director, but as I have already stated on several occasions, his films always have their hallmark based on certain moments edulcorados not to say geeks, taken directly from the philosophy of life of the great Capra.Desde announced the filming of this film I was eager to see how King Midas would be an issue as rugged as current inspired by a tragic fact happened in the 1970s and based on a novel. Of all the new path of maturity of the Jewish genius is known. Speaks of universal themes from multiple genres such as science fiction (in the hodgepodge of A.I. in the interesting Minority Report) or takes up his great vein of entertainment with films of pure evasion and emotion as catch me if you can and the war of the worlds.In Munich Mr Spielberg has managed to reach the political correctness without neglecting the necessary formal impropriety. And as all good film not only speaks of the Jewish response to the murder of their athletes, but hell of a man who is able to execute orders without moral problems until you are in a cycle of violence and paranoia without end. And obviously begins to question what makes. All this on the shoulders of a great Eric Bana.Una film wonderful with some interpretations of award but something long. Your best virtue is that it has uncovered a new creative vein that he knows resign, as I mentioned with Cronenberg and Allen, its signs and winks to step to a cruelty and realism rarely seen in his film Spielberg.It should be noted that John Williams, prolific teacher ever there, has managed to double nomination at the imminent ceremony of the Oscars, somewhat excessive that eliminates the possibility of that other good composers such as my admired Harry Gregson Williams, make a hole.</body>
</review>
