<review author="Yojimbo" title="Freaks" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mr Browning gives us to understand that many times the real monsters are not those freaks, but do normal?.</summary>
	<body>To get the day with classic this weekend I set out for Freaks, Tod Browning.Algo encouraged to see is its duration, barely at the time.The story is simple but is recounted with great skill, and simplicity (perhaps the two things go together). The dvd Edition contains a special introduction of the director that informs the viewer the nature of the term freak and his world as a collective that supports each other and who feels offended as a whole when one is despised.Precisely on that relates the story: in a circus full of attractions, particularly attract attention which are referred to as freaks or those who has unusual physical deformities.The story focuses on Hans and Frieda, a pair of dwarves who commit themselves to marry, but crosses in half the beauty of Cleopatra, a beautiful trapeze artist that Maddens Hans and turns him into a puppet. Everything flows into a cruel story of manipulation, contempt and revenge.The best of the film, and perhaps more appalling, is the parade of people mutilated and deformed. But the most impressive thing is that they are able to integrate masterful way in an argument of fiction like this.It is inevitable to compare the so-called "freaks" of that time with the current. Today the characters presented in the film would be handicapped or diminished psychic or physical and would be in very bad taste to them a commercial claim. Today we are more sophisticated and the "freaks" of today are those that make more nonsense, either because they are as Forrest Gump or want to be it; There are (or were) public forums such as the semaphore or Martian Chronicles supposed they were covered by an intended environment of equality, to all those rare people with mental problems or desire to succeed with any outrageous. But nothing further from the truth, because they were not confessed circuses for the public mockery and derision. Even "freak" is used as a distinctive feature and with pride for those who want to distinguish themselves from the rest of mortals in customs, habits, hobbies or alleged knowledge and experiences.Perhaps, and if it were not a too easy conclusion, Mr Browning gives us to understand that many times the real monsters are not those freaks, but do normal?.</body>
</review>
