<review author="Yojimbo" title="Cache Escondido" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Highly recommended to remove some cobwebs too correct movie of which we only tells that we see when paladeamos movies like this.</summary>
	<body>Michael Haneke, since it made Funny Games became one of the European Directors that I follow with more interest and this film became my favorite horror film. With this curriculum I cannot think another thing go to see his new film this Saturday at the mythical Alphaville. Missing 5 minutes for the meeting and my friends of 8 and a half had not opened yet, so I preferred to pay 6 euros and then tell the movie.Said and done. The room was 50 per cent of its capacity, something which surprised me pleasantly. And there only people with glasses of pasta. It begins the film and does so with a level that if you use any other director could tempt the instant insult. It is a fixed plane. The opening credits appear as who writes a post like this on your computer (of the most original I've seen: fast, simple and fulfilling his mission). And then it already begins the feast Haneke.Daniel Auteuil and Juliette Binoche, two heavyweights of the European cinema, pull their best weapons to please Haneke and the viewer in a new story of remorse and fear of floating in the air and can be reproduced on VHS (and not as in "The Ring"). What would you do if you receive tapes recorded from the outside of your House and teach you how sales and enter it, how to upload to the car, etc?? Is that a threat? And what is worse who does that? The uncertainty can go us mad.They say that fear comes from what is not known, but perhaps we should be afraid of what you are trying to confirm or know. Our mechanisms to rummage in our past and look for a logic perfectly manageable can have dire consequences (seems to be a phrase for the great Douglas Hal, but it has its intricacies) an ideal film for those who know that Haneke has no limits. An ideal film for those who want to be surprised by the lack of constraints of the films that end well. Or simply ending.Highly recommended to remove some cobwebs too correct movie of which we only tells that we see when paladeamos movies like this.</body>
</review>
