<review author="Yojimbo" title="Cineastas contra magnates" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The director becomes a collection of United anédoctas counted horns a documentary with a very interesting topic.</summary>
	<body>One of the Spanish documentary desire to see was filmmakers against magnates, whose inmemorizable name website, discovers us that he is a part of 2 documentaries on the same subject. The other: filmmakers in action."Rehearsal" deals with the treatment of films once completed. A lesson superbly documented on various image formats, the barrabasadas made in screening both in film and television, some technical customs harmful to the artistic health of the film as the colored films, etc? In this section do not have any hits, and very instructive for those who want to know something more of the technical aspect of cinema.However the supine clumsiness of the director makes a documentary with a very interesting topic in a collection of rare United anédoctas to horns, as if write on their blog every 15 days and then put all the post row to make a book. Suddenly, jump to the heart of the documentary: the lack of respect for the work of the director in a film. And that's when it becomes a boring, redundant and radical pastiche. And that which only lasts and a half, but boring to the stones.This sectarian documentary to the core not only focuses on the director as a single, all-powerful God of the film, but that producers do not exist, and if there are Americans, with much money and eager to destroy the way most ruin movies. The impressive collection of testimonies and interviews which brings together this long does Stanley Donen, Berlanga, Woody Allen, John Houston (Burt Lancaster?) not only is not an attractive, but that the director, Carlos Benpar, manages to turn them into a slab: don't know the substance of speech of any edit. It seems that he wants to boast of having achieved record such illustrious guests, but only reveals his clumsiness as director to not know what to choose fragments. That Yes, the most delirious is José María Nunes, a genuine radical madman.It also has "patches" of fiction who try to illustrate the concept of "the artist is everything and all it does is untouchable". In short, a plea against the industry, in favour of the cinema, of the conservation of the creative purity but it is a product of dishonest and inconsistent to 100%, that if we are going to talk about purity, I do not understand why to the gorgeous storyteller, Marta Belmonte (best film), the bends when the rest of speakers busts so horrifyingly symphonies them. Infumable. The director of "this" is quite clear: the head is Dios.Y because only the title betrays its intention: filmmakers (intention of magnificence) against Magnates (bad bad bad).I (we) however wonder: who needs more who: filmmaker mogul or Tycoon filmmaker?</body>
</review>
