<review author="Yojimbo" title="Vida y color" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It can be seen, but it is not advisable to then. Well, except for those excited to see characters involved in Republican flags.</summary>
	<body>The title of the Opera prima by Santiago Tabernero (director of the popular program version Española) and co-screenwriter of the crappy entitled asphalt makes reference to a collection of stickers of the 1970s on animals, exotic places, Anatomy, etc? This narrative device is link directly with Fede (June Valverde), young protagonist who will live in the Spain of the 75 the appearance of TV in color, Franco's death and the consequences of a terrible event in your neighborhood.This film premiered on March 5th and pretends to be (oh surprise) a new film retrospective on a historic stage never treated by our film. The novelty is it is told through the eyes of a preteen.The director seeks to combine several stories without too much success. All are interesting: while one has fun doing ideological propaganda outright in the other reserves the best cartridges to undertake very uncomfortable and unpleasant moments that if, at the expense of a morbid story but little achieved and artificial atmosphere.The best point of the film is undoubtedly the actors, starting with the rookie star, June Valverde. Carmen Machi pleasantly surprises us with a dramatic role; Nadia de Santiago, la niña de Javier no longer lives alone, suggests ways; Silvia Abascal, which is very credible, is accompanied by his sister in real life, Natalia Abascal (pictured lower between the director and his sister), as it has a desiquilibrado daughter Andrés Lima.A technical level the director been covered well the backs and photography instructs the mythic José Luis Alcaine and mounting to the excellent José Salcedo.Un disappointing debut that attempts to recreate a great story and stays in a mere loose situations puzzle, without importance for the viewer and a less insulting ending. It can be seen, but it is not advisable to then. Well, except for those excited to see characters involved in Republican flags.I do not like to be destructive in the criticism, but the film speaks for itself alone.</body>
</review>
