<review author="Jango Fett" title="Salvaje (The Wild)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Savage reveals the big problem there is today in day in the animation industry</summary>
	<body>Savage is a hybrid film between two already known, I am referring to Madagascar, Finding Nemo, and is that the influence of Madagascar well clear, a few animals that escape from the zoo in New York. And as for why Finding Nemo, this also very clear, is the story of a father looking for his son, and although this time non-fish and are lions, it is clear that we are telling the same story. And the truth is very pathetic that Disney go copying PDI and even something more surprising, copied if same, given that even "Buscando a Nemo" Pixar these act under the Disney label. Jobs to copy also decide to copy the great failure of Madagascar is to not develop the story in New York, but in the jungle and therefore repeated the same mistake that the part in the big city is much more interesting and brief than the rest of the movie. But hey, forget about that wild is a copy and look at the rest, do we find? Therefore very little truth, the characters are quite dull and hard to believe that Kiefer Sutherland put voice to the lion character animation characters usually have a personality and appearance similar to that of the person that doubles, in the wild not this happens far. The events that are happening in the story are also very repetitive of other movies, I think that since that C-3PO to the Ewoks confused it with a God has repeated itself this hundreds of times, is in fact curious to see just two days ago I saw something similar in Ice Age 2 and today again I see it in the wild. Wild highlights the great problem that there are today in day in the animation industry and is only Pixar and PDI can do good movies and the rest of animation studios are trying to just follow these leaders making similar movies but they are bland, boring and jerks sometimes as it has already happened with ValiantIce Age 2, Chicken Little and now this. And the reality is that each has found the originality and their own path, not limited to copy the big. The movie isn't bad, but isn't good, is just an hour and average of situations where nothing but nothing and only made so that children buy plush toys of the characters in the movie. And even the movie just a little unfinished form and with a not very closed end, I hope that they do not plan to make sequel. And not be fooled, if they take a child to see this movie is divertira probably, but this generation will not enjoy a great movie of animation as so many other generations have done. And it is that child not cried with Bambi, nor even with beauty and the beast, or even it will be big with Toy Story, simply see a movie the next day there will be forgotten and that when I grow up will be unable to remember if he really saw her. The only positive and remarkable detail of the movie is the choice of some very good songs (although few) for the soundtrack of the movie include issues of Coldplay or Lifehouse.</body>
</review>
