<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Apocalypto" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the great films of this year 2007 a remarkable result which can only achieve a visionary and outstanding director as Mel. We pay to your master feet.</summary>
	<body>Few times I give 5 stars to a film and this time I will do. We have a talent for the address. UNRWA Mel has done again it! It has embroidery project. It is an example to be followed by those actors that are introduced in the world of the address. Mel has exceeded the limits of what is called "Make movies". His later works, merged with a documentary that make unique your tapes.Tell what is having, not counts for a lot, but my God, as the account is abysmal, with a production of Titans and artistic direction of Oscar, Mel shows the fall of an empire through a family history, love, struggle and perseverance by beliefs.See Apocalipyto is not advisable, but essential. 90% Of the cast is also rookie and indigenous origin, and believe me that not has due be nothing easy.The fact that is shot in Maya, is one attractive but do not expect philosophical parrafadas in this language that talks are "very basic".I've loved the scarifications (reliefs) and implants indigenous, "so fashion today". They are very achieved, in some cases, I have my doubts that are part of the props of makeup, for me that had more than one and more than two reales.My discovery in this faithful is Rudy Youngblood, the actor who plays the agile and intelligent "Claw of Jaguar" which only is known "Spirit: The Seventh Fire" (African American mother and father Indian American) will give much to talk about, their interpretation is totally organic, not doubt for a moment of the image that you are selling and the physical form (absent from steroids) is a naturalness and perfection only Mel could be achieved. There are directors who care a radish if muscle is credible or not, brings them fresco showing a native with muscles that reeks of cycles, but Mel, no, the carer, mima every detail. The rotten dentures are identical to how they were great, and are in reality (for which has seen some in live once). All this is more than admirable, especially considering that this guy managed to overcome a childhood cancer. He graduated from Belton High School in 2000 and changed his surname "Gonzalez" by the current (more artistic).Another discoveries is the beautiful Dalia Hernandez (the wife of Jaguar claw, he expected to be rescued in the well of the village) who debuted in this film (by the door) and let it grow eyebrows to more accurately embody their role, I am sure that we will see it more than once?Also noteworthy was the emergence of María Isabel Díaz (Masala) which we have seen recently in "Volver" Almodóvar in where he played Regina, a neighbor of the character who plays the actress Penélope Cruz. In addition her seen in Series as Central Hospital and clunkers as "Crazy for sex" in any case this Cubana is an excellent actress and proof of this is that he has worked with the best.In conclusion one of the great films of this year 2007 (delay of months Made in Spain) a remarkable result which can only achieve a visionary and outstanding director as Mel. Do we pay to your feet teacher, Ole your lame? s.</body>
</review>
