<review author="José A. Peig" title="La pasión de Cristo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>And here comes the Gibson, as all good engañabobos trap: If you don't have the imagination and the creative talent for squeezing the testament of a genuine form history, the best option (the easiest) to make the interesting and look good, is to resort to the morbid and the viewer emotional manipulation.</summary>
	<body>There are films that seem to good movies and actually are bad or not so good as they claim. I remember that when I first saw this film I thought it was a very bad film, absolutely shameful. Now, after a thorough review, I can say that it is not as bad as it seemed, and is a perfect example of how easy that might be deceive and manipulate the Viewer. There is no doubt that "The passion of the Christ" has several points in favor: a glorious and strong start-up scene, good photography, good sense of rhythm and some moments with dramatic inspiration, without excessive sentimental. That subjective camera placed in the altar and the eyes of the God pours his first tear by the death of his incarnate Son (excellent sample of lyricism) or chilling death of the traitor Judas, at whose feet we see the decaying corpse of a donkey, preceded by a series of disturbing visions that give the film an air of dreamlike nightmare is memorable. Some critics appeal to this kind of efectistas tricks to drop the donkey that Mel Gibson offers "a personal view" of the Testament text. Vade retro, Satanás start out there. The film we are dealing with is - and is intended to be - a visual representation of the exact and fundamental content written in the New Testament concerning the last hours of the life of one of the most important myths of the history of religions: Jesus Christ. Therefore the material of which part is well known to all and the central character has a role and a characteristic that they have been taken over by each individual cavern in Western culture, whether believer or atheist. Against this background and bearing in mind that the film is not only visual representation but forms of content and the point of view of the camera, I do note that this movie is absolutely flat, empty, little brave.Because look at what makes Gibson: never represents the tragedy of Christ offering his personal point of view, simply places the camera in such a way that teaches us the box typical of Jesus dropping his preaching, or group of priests of the Sanhedrin showing bad milk and the bad baba have, or supermalos which are the Romans or the final of Pilate well-meaning gesture and we have already seen throughout the story of the film on several occasions. Therefore, the visual language of film of Gibson is absolutely conventional and not exploited or even a fraction of the huge number of suggestions that can inspire a character like Jesus, from different points of view: as archetype of spirituality or heroism, as a model of rebellion, etc. There is not a single plane or framing that tells us nothing special and to show that behind the camera there is a filmmaker creative, courageous and even great, they say some unwary. In cinema, personal recreation of the represented history is done using the point of view of the camera, among other things. Mel Gibson not goes beyond a mere illustrator of the sacred text. So, where is the merit?.And here comes the Gibson, as all good engañabobos trap: If you don't have the imagination and the creative talent for squeezing the testament of a genuine form history, the best option (the easiest) to make the interesting and look good, is to resort to the morbid and the viewer emotional manipulation: do a montage parallel to teaching the fronted a guy talking about love and universal brotherhood to see how that same character is a victim of an atrocious violence, displayed openly, suffering a torn living flesh and scandalous jets of blood splashing to the camera. To decorate the thing a little more, again is resorted to the subjective camera while the poor Jesus loses balance and forces to not hold the cruz.para that the spectator feel the pain of Christ and put in their flesh. Let us be frank; What did Gibson is a "heavy" of the martyrdom of Christ, a morbid spectacle, recreated with much sense of the theatrical, but here the intellectual or artistic values are conspicuous by their absence. "And, in a way, is a regrettable emotional manipulation of the Viewer, using a religious figures that more spiritual meanings and irrational passions generated in our society.""The passion of the Christ" is a dramatic film, nothing more. Artistically speaking it is a vague and vacuous, Gibson has gone to how easy. This is a pitifully pretentious film, fruit of a mind squared as Mel Gibson, filmmaker against which I do not have anything, but everyone knows the chabacanería and the vulgarity of his different statements or public events. Here it is intended to provide a work of art with religious and humanist, but honestly, it is not equipped with for these areas. Put a tísico Satan, black hooded and holding a baby with a man's face which monitors the agony of Christ is not to offer a personal view (worth say that this final Satanic grito-aullido after the agony and death of Jesus on the cross is more tacky that I've seen in movies, ridiculous until you find arcades), but resorting to disruptive elements copied by other authors (or the rich Catholic eschatology) that made them yours, as for example Ingmar Bergman. It is the difference between the genuine and legitimate ownership of elements and tricks others have used and the impersonal and awkward hodgepodge when Gibson falls. The use by some oniric elements Gibson is not genuine, but reeks of pretentiousness, something very hard to prove objectively, but at least this is for who writes this. Do not put in doubt or deny the ability of Gibson to stimulate the sensitivity of some viewers, but hey, no point of comparison with Bergman or David Lynch.En sum, and taking into account the various sensitivities and subjectivity, I would say that it is not a bad film, is an interesting - striking bursts - representation of the passion and death of Christ, ideal to put in class of religion or for Catholics wanting to affirm their faith by accompanying it with good dose of morbid. But this isn't a good film, because it seeks to much more than it is.</body>
</review>
