<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Babel" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The globalizing desire of Babel, far from being a strong point, it ends up burden to the whole of the story, at times, desmadejado.</summary>
	<body>The so-called trilogy of pain born of the fruitful collaboration between González Iñárritu and Guillermo Arriaga closes with Babel. This has been its most ambitious proposal, and yet is perhaps the least round. The three films trace human feelings through stories and vidas cruzadas strung out in pain. But each, according to my particular interpretation, puts the accent on specific issues such as the need to love and be loved (in love dogs), the confrontation with the abyss of death and loss (in 21 grams) and the problems of communication and social empathy of our days (now in Babel). The globalizing desire of Babel, far from being a strong point, it ends up burden to the whole of the story, at times, desmadejado. Only in sequences isolated from each story looks good cinema, and art in the epilogue of Japan, less attractive of game history, but the most poetic and powerful of the film to the dessert.Babel weaves three stories happened at remote distances between themselves United by the fragile articulation of a firearm. The film begins with the history of Afghanistan, catalyst of the events that will trigger the consequences of mixed caliber in those that occurred in the United States.UU. and Japan. A father them gives their children a rifle to be on coyotes that prey on the flock of sheep that both graze on the slopes of his house. The weapon, former property of a Japanese tourist who gave his Afghan guide after his last hunt, will be unwisely used by children. An American holiday by Afghanistan marriage is in crisis after the death of one of his sons. Neglect of children will affect them directly to them and, indirectly, their children left in the United States.UU. in charge of his Mexican nanny, the owner of the weapon in Japan and, above all, sordomuda's daughter.The film addresses such issues as ethnic prejudice of those who derive so incardinadas feelings of insecurity and fear reciprocal in multi-ethnic societies today day. But also the problems of marginalization or absence of solidarity between those who do not respond to certain canons or social requirements. The scene described in the three stories offers devastating conclusions, but also certain keys for hope indicia. Again, as in the other two films of the trilogy, the subtle guitar of Gustavo Santaolalla accentuates the most emotive sequences and interpretations returns to play a key role. Surprisingly, in this case the great work of the more unknown faces of the cast, as the Japanese Koji Yakusho and Adriana Barraza as a Mexican nanny, and they rallan estimable height more poster actors such as Brad Pitt, Cate Blanchett and Gael García Bernal. I wouldn't say that pain trilogy closes false with this Babel, but does this corollary is not at the height of the magnificent 21 grams. However, these three film of the tandem Iñárritu-Arragia dan for many movie fan conversation and, in particular, much internal reflection. We must thank the two that these three works will encourage both circumstances.</body>
</review>
