<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Things should not be as Mel Gibson in his fantastic e impressive film. There are cultural and geographical history, temporary inconsistencies. But, personally, I feel like, I am not going to the cinema to receive lessons from history.</summary>
	<body>It is true. Things should not be as Mel Gibson in his fantastic e impressive film. There are cultural and geographical history, temporary inconsistencies. But, personally, I feel like, I am not going to the cinema to receive lessons from history. So are magazines, newspapers Sunday supplements and, better still, teachers!, which in the film have an excellent tool with which support, complete and illustrate their lectures.To me, when I go to the cinema, what I like is to put me squarely in the history that I hook me excited and make me have a good time, embedded in what I have from the screen. And "Apocalypto", certainly amply meets it from the first until the last frame.The visual ability of Mel Gibson is portentosa. The type takes the film got into vein, such is its ability to transmit sensations through their films. And as a Philo has found that talk of lost cultures, repressed mutinous movements to blood and fire, heroic personal and love for the family, lost and forgotten languages. It is therefore by exploiting based on well. And it is doing beautifully.Rhythm. That would be the expression that best define this "Apocalypto", whose story takes place in a temporary spectrum so concentrated, just a couple of days, that leaves you breathless. It's like that "Last Mohican", which Gibson's movie has a multitude of Parallels, you right exhausted seeing everything what ran Daniel Day Lewis &amp; Co. In "Apocalypto", the characters run and jump all the time, a fashion which, in view of the start of the latest 007, seems that trend will mark in the coming months.More film references in this "Apocalypto": Tarzan and the African porters that fell by the cliffs and, of course, "the planet of the apes" original. And "Mad Max", of course, with its apocalyptic message, never better said. We are witnessing a brutal clash of cultures in which the noble savage faces some formidable warriors, perfect allegory of what is happening today on so many armed conflicts which would be idle to reel off. And we are witnessing a realistic recreation of what it could be big cities Mayan (or Aztec?), with its pyramids and their bloody rituals, desmembramientos and included beheadings.All this, again, cash with a pace and at a breakneck speed. I liked stakeholder, protagonists and secondary. I liked the start-up scene, costumes and feathers headdresses and the beads. I liked how the duels are resolved. I loved the escape, including jaguar. I was struck by the first foreboding encounter in the forest and I enjoyed hunting, laughter, tales and overnight in the village.Come on, that I liked everything, from beginning to end. I understand that the excesses of violence can empachar the more sensitive palates, but unfortunately, the history of mankind is tinged with blood. Specialists in Mesoamerica have pissed and criticize a certain lack of historical accuracy. Indigenous associations are mosqueadas because the vision of natives is negative. However, lovers are in luck because "Apocalypto" is simply a peliculón.</body>
</review>
