<review author="Caruco" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I believe that this type just invent a new (sub) genre: gore-historical. It will be a bocazas and an alcoholic, but by many heads to roll, other than her own. How filmed this guy!</summary>
	<body>Me I am still shaking up weeds, cleaning the mud to me, taking away some another splash of blood and, above all, the smell of (human) meat decomposition.I've seen "Apocalypto" and is that Mel Gibson is so beast. I also believe that this type just invent a new (sub) genre: gore-historical.With "Braveheart" already warned at the time that the battle scenes contain flat durillos, and is that at that time they were very gross; and in "The passion of the Christ" finally gave rein to his side more unleashed. Both Mad Max have run you into the head and body!And has created a (sub) genre again with a couple of co?! First making his characters speak in any ancient Mayan type dialect (which gets you you filled in time and place); and then showing the violence without recreate it, as more primitive and real, that reminds us that human are thus of animals, and that our ancestors, is here, in Scotland or the pre-Columbian America, were even more because his arms were perhaps less sofisdicadas.This is not to mention that with a budget of about $ 50 million it recreates a world of a late 15th century, when other directors, for example, Nancy Meyers, need double only to furnish the comfortable homes of their two protagonists in "Holiday". Heads rolling.The result would delight Truffaut in "The noble savage" (1969), and Terrence Malick, for his idyllic vision of the primitive, naive, pure community and in perfect harmony with nature; and all of this utopian world ravaged by wars in the name of progress and civilization.Also would agree even to the very Stallone and Schwarzenegger, because both the Dutch in predator (1987) as to the Johnny Rambo's "Rambo" (1982) jump les a lagrimilla of emotion when he saw this intrepid "jaguar claw" so convincingly played by Rudy Youngblood.Y is expected that you fill with enthusiasm also fans of adventure and action, and good film, because "Apocalypto" is a great movie that hooked from beginning to end. Shot in an admirable manner, relying above all on the image and striking party of plasticity even with the color of the paintings that cover the bodies of slaves: white for the job, blue for the sacrifice.Am not going to reveal anything, not even the type of nails are spent Aboriginal sewing wounds. What better discover for yourselves, but yes I leave that (human) meat decomposition flavored so well it corresponds with the vision of an empire in decline, the instinct of survival and also with the hope as an illusion which can never be defeated.It will be a bocazas and an alcoholic, but by many heads to roll, other than her own. How filmed this guy!</body>
</review>
