<review author="Caruco" title="María Antonieta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The pity is that depth, modernez and passion, in the hands of Sofia, are limited to a lavish catalog of dresses and shoes of the 18th century.</summary>
	<body>Elongated is the shadow of "The godfather", or his father, Francis Ford Coppola; that has inoculated in Sofia the passion for audiovisual art, to it has generated you amount of detractors and admirers. "" Lost in Versailles ", Sofia Coppola transports US to the France pre-and revolutionary to show us another passion from a 14 year old girl forced to leave behind all objects in his native Austria to become wife of Louis XVI and future Queen of the Gallic nation.""If have no bread to eat cakes", read a popular phrase of the time, forged by a starving people (which also named Madame Guillotine it) and attached these words to the lips of a Queen who considered frivolous, malgastadora, nimfómana and ruin. Therefore, the Coppola is human looking, tinted naivety to a historical myth treated with little MIME by history, and closing, incidentally, a kind of trilogy about girls who become women. And with eyes on "Barry Lyndon", one of his favorite films, also wide his career tanned in video clips with the groundbreaking idea of including current songs, The Strokes, New Order or Siouxie &amp; Banshees between such straitened and last fashionable melody of the Court of King Louis XV and Louis XVI.Sensitivity Sofia.La pity is that depth, modernez and passion, in the hands of Sofia, are limited to a lavish catalog of dresses and shoes of the 18th century, of festivals and sweets. "To contemplate a Kirsten Dunst walking through Versailles more lost than Scarlett Johansson in Tokyo, and to equip, or rather, remove characters and script the more minimal relevance, covering the vacuum by an aestheticism of a postcard.""Lost in Versailles", I say, "Marie Antoinette", is a leisurely proposal that not entertains, an exercise in scarcely memorable historical memory and a vision of some human beings relegated to mere comparsas by its low physical or psychological entity.But confirms the main talent of Sofia Coppola: is a Director of details, attentive to looks and gestures. In "Lost in Versailles", most are trivial, but one there is excellent as the occurrence of Marie Antoinette of applauding without having completed an opera, bypassing a life full of cumbersome protocols and ceremonies (and that it be the first look of admiration and her powerless husband do lust?).Or the gesture from the Versailles balcony real to make a bow to his revolucionado people, sign of the maturity of a character which, in their 30s, just of face to face with reality.The virtue of Sofia is the sensitivity, but if his intention was to make us see that Marie Antoinette was not so superficial, often bump!.</body>
</review>
