<review author="Berto" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the great films of the year, plays with us with impunity while us stunned attended the show, and as said Caine throughout the film, "in the end what we really like is that we cheat", and best way is to see this film.</summary>
	<body>Just start the year and already have on board one of the films that at the end of the year, and if my memory allow me, end up annexing my top ten best films of the year. The Prestige, entitled disastrously with the name of the final trick (the Prestige), here is the bet Christopher Nolan gives us before embarking again on the adventures of the Lord of the night. For this risky film, Nolan adapting a novel by Christopher Priest, in which there is the rivalry between two magicians, who by vicissitudes of life, spend from two friends to face fiercely by both the public and his own life. Explain any part of the plot of this movie can be very difficult without gutting important parts of the film, making him lose all his charm, as if they really were a good show of magic in which we are witnessing stunned as the wizard plays with us until the end leaves us with an open mouth thinking for ourselves as it could have done that in front of our own noses. This wizard is none other than its director, as well explained in the film presents us with a great global magic trick, in which after having been submitted to the characters, is telling us a story that helps us deception to finally and with a twist a lot more elaborate than any of these films that come to us from Hollywood with the typical sign of surprising end and would leave already guess towards the middle of the filmtell us an ending that makes mentally review the recesses of the film to see how the film was braided really surprise us. From the first image of the film, no apparent relation with the rest until that we realize that if it is something important back in the middle of the film, until that end which clearly Nolan seeks, as well as its protagonists, the prestige of having managed to play with us for about 2 hours and be able to get away with so difficult "trick". At the beginning the narrative may be somewhat liosa, since it uses a narrative style that vaguely reminded me to another great work of yours, Memento, and without reaching the level of this, if that performs constant jumps back and forth in time, which serves to hook more if possible to the Viewer, you expect eager for another piece of the puzzle to try to complete the puzzle that makes up the film as a whole.As for the actors in the film, I don't think that it has better right with the election of Christian Bale and Hugh Jackman to play the two rival magicians. Bale will gradually be revealed as an actor very to consider, both for its quality in the latest interpretations made, as to fill the screen and make shade to his partner, Hugh Jackman in State of grace that chains a good movie after another, and that time to time, we have two of the actors with better screening here in a not too distant future. As secondary, Scarlett Johansson, in a role too prude (do in all aspects, which has seen the movie I mean?), and forgive me the easy game of words following your wardrobe in the film, but removing any scene in which looks great guy (and often great guy), its role could have been played by any other actress, already like his character in the filmis simply in the film to help the two magicians in the realization of this great final trick by which all are waiting. Michael Caine as always, huge, very wise its role and its interpretation, something that also happens to an unrecognizable at first seen David Bowie (do your eyes betray you?), very restrained in its role of scientist Nikola Tesla, and an important part in the development of the plot, with which the film comes to take a turn toward films of science fiction that can reach misplaced the viewer in some momentsnot waiting for a foray into this genre from history that is telling us.Ultimately, and as already said at the beginning, undoubtedly one of the great films of the year, plays with us with impunity while us stunned attended the show, and as said Caine throughout the film, "in the end what we really like is that we cheat", and best way is to see this film.</body>
</review>
