<review author="Caty" title="Eragon" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Marked by a constant in his screenplay instability, it seems that always missing something and that the facts as submitted have been built lightly on paper and on screen.</summary>
	<body>The less, the struggle of some movie studios for a new success in box office is curious and so I call in the film "stages", that I may understand: premiered a film that breaks all records, became a classic in the history of the seventh art and mark a generation. Act followed, leaving 800 films on the same line and with the same plot and/or technical premises. He spent with Star Wars. spent with Matrix. He spent with the night of the dead living. passed with Seven spent with Terminator. spent with Alien. and of course, it happened with the Lord of the rings. In a way, it's already old history of supply and demand. Sometimes come worthy things, other pure shit and other products that leave you completely indifferent. In this case, and in my opinion, we are in a product which, although for nothing is a by-product, is the typical "bluff" film: adorned in the promotion until the satiety and that viewing is simply an entertaining tape to spend a pleasant time.Adapted from the eponymous play by Christopher Paolini, written in adolescence, the film deals with the story of the Dragon Riders, trained to do good and to protect the people. Men prospered and the cities grew. until that one day was born a boy named Galbatorix. Riders accepted as one more and it exceeded all skill. Equipped with a superior mind and a strong body, he highlighted among all riders. One day, in the darkness of the night, stole a dragon egg and persuaded Morzan, another rider to join the study of magic black and prohibited. Later, in a bloody battle, Galbatorix managed to dominate all and was proclaimed King of all Alagaesia.y here begins our history. Eragon, a simple peasant teen, is a blue stone in the forest and, thinking that it is a wink of good luck, it takes her to his farm. Suddenly, a dragon is born of the "stone" and marks it as its rider: since that time, Eragon makes be revived the myth of the Dragon Riders and becomes a hope against the tyranny of Galbatorix.Marcada by a constant in his screenplay instability, it seems always missing something and that the facts as submitted have been built lightly on paper and on screen. Do not think that Eragon has this evil that many adaptations suffer on their way to the celluloid, where often turns to a book of tropecientas pages into a guioncito covering just two hours of projection. I think that the error comes from the book, which suffers from a lack of originality too alarming: is a story that, although manida, promises and be carried by other paths would have not brought the Viewer to see something so typicalsometimes too typical. Being able to get much more, the film stays in the wake of films that follow to others - as mentioned above-.Anyway, it also has its positive or at least salvables points. The young Edward Speleers has a good stage presence before the cameras and seems to cope well with these. Jeremy Irons, Sienna Guillory and Robert Carlyle do not wrong and give class to this production. Saphira (female Dragon in Eragon) is also superbly built and performed by the dubbers (in the original version, lends it the voice Rachel Weisz). The special effects are interesting and with a competent soundtrack.I hope that the second installment of the series manages to mend the errors of the first and demonstrate that it is more than another one of those franchises and throw-away, despite the hint of a story completely flat (I'm afraid).</body>
</review>
