<review author="Caty" title="Matar a un Ruiseñor" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do it was one of the first films to deal with the issue of discrimination and racial intolerance, without presumptions and? ñoñerías?, a tape in which a white man educates their children teaching them to respect people, are those who, while confronted with obstacles of a petty and reticent society to accept differences.</summary>
	<body>We are faced with a sublime film, captivating, at times sensíble and at times memorable, deserves to be considered one of the best films of all time, conquers you with a simplicity that has prevailed since the beginning until the end. Adaptation of the novel by Harper Lee, tells us a drama about the best and worst of the human being and the cruelties many times we are able to commit.A very different, intriguing and original start time, brings me to tell you about the argument: it all starts in the small southern town of Maycomb, in full during the depression. Atticus Finch(Gregory_Peck_en_el_que_fue_el_papel_de_su_vida), is a humble lawyer who lives with his two sons and his employee at home without many luxuries, but with great dignity. Atticus children are obedient, responsible and educated: from small, learned the principles of Justice, equality and respect for others with his father? relationship father and children is therefore solid and strong also because Finch makes, mother and father at the same time.But all this is when our protagonist agrees to defend the black Tom Robinson(Brock_Peters), accused of raping a young white woman. Atticus then becomes the object of the hatred and racism of some inhabitants of the city, angry because Finch defends a person of color. On the other hand, at the same time trying to win the case, try to protect their children from those feelings of hatred that he is a victim. The day of the trial, Atticus proves the innocence of the accused, proving to all the hypocrisy and cynicism of such charges, simply because of the color of the skin of the person. Even so the verdict is guilty for Tom Robinson.Hay at least four great moments to highlight all the footage: 1) when the daughter of Atticus, Scout (Mary Badham), in a scene in which his father is cornered by several inhabitants of the village, the away simply taking an innocent conversation with one of them – when asked by his son, fellow in the school of Scout - and where we can see the innocence of a girl without evil faced with a person full of hatred and prejudice. (2) When Finch tells his sons the history that gives title to the film and only they understand at the end of this. ((3) The Sheriff of Maycomb, Atticus warning that "go for it" and 4) the scene of the exit of the Court of Atticus, after defending Tom Robinson, when all blacks sitting in the Hall stand and greet it with pride.We should also remember that the veteran actor Robert Duvall makes his first appearance on the big screen, in the role of Boo Radley, a young man with some mental retardation and a mysterious past that gives cause for admiration, fear and fascination by the Finch children, collecting small objects of wood and SOAP that Boo size them and deposited into the hole of a tree outside the House in this film.As the main protagonist of the movie, Gregory Peck, it must be said in its favour fully delivered to the character, with a heart and a sincerity beyond doubt, making - as I mentioned in a previous sentence - the role of his career. It is very difficult to imagine another actor playing Atticus Finch, that we should consider a true hero, a full, just and tolerant person, a lawyer of provinces with few ideals over any kind of pettiness. As it could not be less, won Oscar for that role for best actor. Mention that the film also won the statuette to the best artistic direction, a merit in history, that really viewers feel immersed in the era portrayed in all its details. "The great adapted screenplay of Horton Foote also took the statuette.""To kill a Mockingbird" was one of the first films to deal with the issue of discrimination and racial intolerance, without presumptions and "ñoñerías", a tape in which a white man educates their children teaching them to respect people, they are those who, while confronted with obstacles of a petty and reticent society to accept differences. Do ultimately, a good story, a good director, his Excellency actor and a photograph in black and white unique? It was sung had to leave a masterpiece.</body>
</review>
