<review author="Jango Fett" title="Ice age 2 el deshielo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film flat, bland, without hardly argument and bad jokes</summary>
	<body>Ice Age was a great box office success and I think a large group of fans on this saga and saga I say because Ice Age 2 will not last. However, I do not belong to this group of fans and I can hardly understand the success of these movies. Ice Age 2 is a simplistic film, with very mild jokes and even some very bad times and with a very low plot burden. The biggest problem of the film is that it works as several comics together without much relationship between them, gives the impression that in the studies of this movie they said "Let's do a movie about the thaw, that everyone does a short on the subject and then join them" and this is the impression, because many of the scenes are totally unrelated to the plot of the movie. Another big problem of Ice Age 2 is that they have become to fall again on the same stone with one, the best of the movie is the squirrel (or go to know that it is this bug) that he goes looking for his Acorn, his appearance in the movie will be about six or seven times as intervals from the rest of the film, and curiously the best two of these scenes have been chosen as trailers to promote it. In the saga Ice Age rather than resorting to fast for the trailers images as they do in most films, they pick up a scene completely, put the credits at the beginning and at the end and we have trailer. This makes you start the movie and say "This already I've seen" and the truth, I do not like much this marketing technique that used to Ice Age. And new also another error that is repeated, is that the movie is totally superficial, not play just any dramatic history as they usually do in other productions of animation, see Shrek or Finding Nemo. As this happened in one, now in two is ignored almost completely abandoned history of a female mammoth who joins the team and of the obviously are trying to introduce a love story that really gives us absolutely equal, gives us equal to that she has been abandoned or have to separate from the group or whatever, and is that the movie as I say is totally flat, do not have that sentimental touch that have most animation movies. Anyway in Ice Age 2 also becomes visible that these studies are only trying to imitate the large and not to develop their own style as they did Pixar or PDI, which is why that many characters or situations resemble other productions already views. They have even tried to introduce a music number that turns out to be disastrous at least after dubbing, would be seen in original version to check it, but it is likely that it would be just as bad, as again it seems that one of the animators said that he was going to make a musical short and what they have gotten in the movie, so works like Ice Age 2. As regards animation things have not changed much, because the characters are well done but funds are extremely ugly, in fact this was very open to criticism in one, but as this is going on the melting because it is likely that they could create landscapes green and spectacular white and flat as in the first installment and indeed this make in one of the first scenes that is when it starts melting. However it seems then that the animators got tired of work and all the scenarios are land, is not much more than paint Brown ice. In short, Ice Age 2 is in my opinion a film flat, bland, without hardly argument and with bad jokes, but is certainly going to be a box office hit for the second time. If you liked the first, you will like the second, but not bother going to see, because both are equal and commit the same errors.</body>
</review>
