<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Dreamgirls" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you enjoyed watching Crow Paz Vega, forget about the previous paragraph and go to see the film, perhaps discover what a real musical.</summary>
	<body>See a musical in the film seems to me a very risky idea if production is Spanish. Never get, to my dismay, the large amount of neural circuits that I lost after seeing one of the films over the blockbuster Spanish cinema, as well as one of the more bad: the other side of the bed. Another very different thing is to see an American musical, gentlemen, despite who gets upset, they know to make a good show and that is, first and foremost, what must be a musical.Based on a work that triumphed during the 1980s on the stages of Broadway, the film tells the sentimental and professional career of a trio of girls who aspire to succeed in the world of music.Of all is known the role played by the famous Beyoncé, however, stressed, above all, the voice of an unknown in our country, Jennifer Hudson, which was given out in a successful program on the Fox network: American Idol (an OT but big kind). For his great work, is nominated to the Oscars as best supporting actress (though it is complicated because it competes with the amazing Abigail Breslin) must also mention an important work of costume, make-up and hairdressing (a style that has been able to show us what is most innovative of the sixties and seventies, work he has also earned a nomination). The musical numbers are notable for a large set of voices that vibrate with different rhythms (rock, blues, jazz or gospel) and which are accompanied by simple choreography to that is they could have benefited more.Said good Dreamgirls, is to analyze what has lacked or left so that the final result was not as spectacular as it would have been, something which could outline in nine words: can spare you 20 minutes and more "prose" is missing. The first of the problems is common to the majority of the films that are made for several years: I don't know who came up with the idea that films should last more than two hours but sometimes the only thing that feels is a bad concept of mounting. As for the second problem, it can be described in a very simple way. Think of a singer or band of its delights. Do you have it? Now imagine enjoy the music they like during a two-hour concert. Perfect, right? Now enjoy this same concert but on DVD, our artist no longer has the magic of live and, therefore, it is possible that us it is heavier. In other words, it is not the same view the live of a musical in a theater that see it in the cinema. The first has the magic feel the action live, so, please an orgy of music and songs. The second, already lacking with such grace, so will have to incorporate more dialogues to help digest the ambiguity of a recorded performance to the public.And now finally, only I would apuntillar a clarification: If you enjoyed watching Crow Paz Vega, forget about the previous paragraph and go to see the film, perhaps discover what a real musical.</body>
</review>
