<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Lemming" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Brioso cinematic spectacle of raw digestion. Everything becomes, says of this very decent work of Moll, in a vacuum device in between the dreams and the real impostada Crazy Horse of fable and the social test to the donkey.</summary>
	<body>My ignorance in the Zoological field not repaired in the lemmings are a rodents that inhabit the Arctic tundras. Nor that carried his small back the legend that suicidaban mass. The film that takes its name from this animal, about which we hear is in a pipe, as the title is a comedy with dramatic purple (which isn't it) or a drama with comedic overtones. The invading lemming is the metaphor of the complex network of relationships that keeps a marriage stable and normal attending, among the astonishment and indignation, the clashes of another couple, their bosses, which autoinvitan to a dinner. In French cinema, the approach is not new: it's termination of a way of life and the faint but painful evidence of otherwise, less pleasant, necessarily more pungent and hostile, nests in any corner, Crouching, to waiting to occupy the space in which earlier, nowhere near, imagined to be. Theatricality is very forced very à la française, coligiendo that we are going to attend the pomp of the decline of a bourgeoisie prone, desasosegada always a tension that sometimes, generates a tremendous violence. The script desajusta of topics when it embraces, without blushing, fantasy, imagination spurred by this phantom lemming that has come from the tundra and has settled in the talks, in the desserts in all machinery and bizarre of this artifact of raw digestion, but interesting and valuable to bolster the idea that European cinema is great and can move away from American billswithout renouncing a brioso film show. There are some scenes in real action: more action in many call the mobile Van Damme.Moll, the German director of which we knew Harry, a friend who loves you, is not Claude Chabrol. Neither the now relevant Haneke. Moll is the hidden lemming in the pipe: lurks in the go world of the tubes which share with us a House and spits (the verb is acid and carefully designed) a comedy him/her, dazzling at times, archetypal in its resolution, disconcerting in all long footage offered to us.The blackness of the plot, the heightened thriller that goes on below and the metaphysical nightmare that suspends all action in a bizarre dream or fiction idea becomes an autoindulgente proposal for style, never Candida, grows more and more twisting, is taken by a rugged superposition of layers under which nestsunchanged, the seed of the disease that is destroying civilized tradition of the European family. Dinner enrarecidas like this had given in a Woody Allen in State of grace a comedy just as him/her, but aditamentada with a more accessible but equally corrosive humor. Everything becomes, says of this very decent work of Moll, in a vacuum device in between the dreams and the real impostada Crazy Horse of fable and the social test to the donkey.</body>
</review>
