<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Pequeño pero matón" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What the Wayans Brothers added to Hitchcock is a Freudian element to the British and to someone else would put the willies.</summary>
	<body>A thief of jewels rather soulless and hard hides his last theft diamond in the bag of a couple while they learn. To get it back you have to get into the happy family. The thief measured less than one meter and is disguised as baby. The couple adopted throughout the weekend.A key scene from Hitchcock's "sabotage" happens in the Palace of a Lady of society which, in reality, is a nazi spy. Two levels are mixed in the scene. On the one hand the hero wants to save his girlfriend of Nazi spies. On the other hand the hero is a dance of society with all its Protocol that can not be altered. The nazi, to catch the bride asks for a dance. The hero may not refuse because it would break with good forms of the label. When you get to the girl joins another couple innocent and leaves the Palace. The nazi may not use force, because it would break the same tag, and so on.Something similar occurs in "The purloined letter" Poe. The Minister stole the Queen the letter in front of the King, but she can not say anything, because the King should not know the incriminating letter. do? i? ek called this game "the impotent look". There is always a third element in this type of action. "Sabotage" is the good society of the Palace, in "The purloined letter" is the King. There are people that must not find out what's happening. «The other say? i? ek, not must know everything ".I like to quote Hitchcock to talk about a bad film because basically I like to give some to another noogie from time to time. The intellectual low-budget film may look the same tricks to the Hitchcock. The bully disguised as a baby is willing to use force and weapons, but when it appears the "MOM" returns to the babbling: «she not must know everything». Everytime it has diamond in his hands he must return to the farce that is a baby and loses it why? Because she is ahead.There is a famous scene of "Chained" in which Cary Grant and Ingrid Bergman are about to be discovered by the evil Sebastian. To hide that they have gone to the cellar to investigate the nazi uranium, the two pretend that they are loving and embrace. Sebastian they mislead into believing that they want. But the funny thing is that in reality the two want. do? i? ek says that movement is typical of the Hitchcock film "outside inside". The characters feign that they are something until they discover that they are that something. "Pretend that we are something occupy a place in the intersubjective network, and in the end this place becomes our true position.""Small but bully", makes the same movement in an intuitive way. The boyfriend of the couple wants to have a child but she wants to wait. When the boyfriend sees the baby to the door of his house is excited to father two days. The thief took the place of son, to get the diamond. Each one represents a role, but the film attempts to show what each other are needed at the end. They have created a symbolic network parent-child in that feel too comfortable. So they are clubbing together to celebrate.What the Wayans Brothers added to Hitchcock is a Freudian element to the British and to someone else would put the willies. The baby should sleep the first night with the couple so watch them avidly when they begin their sexual preliminary. In the morning she remembers two adventures, the boyfriend just one: the baby has fun. But in which of its two facets? It is the prison thief has taken advantage of the ambiguity which has crept into the bed of the bride? Has o made it symbolically? Has your baby been which has fun with MOM? The viewer has the possibility of making a second reading scandalous, a lecherous Oedipus completely satisfied.</body>
</review>
