<review author="José A. Peig" title="La última tentación de Cristo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the reviews of the above most surprising and original myth that you can see that this rummages in the different dimensions of the myth with a laudable intention regenerating and introspective, putting into question many dogmas and characteristics of a doctrine and a theological scheme that governs the consciences of millions of believers.</summary>
	<body>The figure of Jesus Christ has the power of fascination that transcends generations and cultures and as an object of veneration or philosophical reflection that lends itself to many lectures, reviews or manipulations according to beliefs or mental patterns of each individual or society. This cross-cultural value is not something exclusive to the Galileo born in Bethlehem, but that is a feature of the Archetypes of knowledge and the human adventure, from the great founders of religions to the heroes who have led and motivated the rich mythological background of humanity. Jesus Christ is a myth - a supposed historical base, on that subject there is and there will always be controversy - whose characteristics evoke both the human and the divine in a social environment changes, uncertainty in the future, crisis and revolution in the heyday of the Roman Empire. And hence a wealth of nuances which, well used, can be a good material to make major film, since it allows to focus the story sacred from different points of view: Jesus the man, Jesus the God, Jesus the revolutionary, the Prophet, the religious reformer, the madman who shouts in the desert, the katte. We already saw as Mel Gibson wasted his chance limited to develop a mere visual illustration of the biblical text but adding an Assembly with the sole purpose of emotionally manipulate the viewer and perpetrate tips free morbid and thus make the interesting so that everyone talk about their film.In the case of "The last temptation of Christ", we find one of the reviews of the above most surprising and original myth that you can see that this rummages in the different dimensions of the myth with a laudable intention regenerating and introspective, putting into question many dogmas and characteristics of a doctrine and a theological scheme that governs the consciences of millions of believers.Believers, but it has to be very clear that an artistic object has no more or less value according to their rebellious nature or its transgressive message according to ideologies and other phobias and aversions you collective. If someone finds or appreciates the movie of Scorsese as an "anti-Catholic" work will be a mistake, as its role as a piece of film art is the play and scavenging all metaphorical or interpretative possibilities deriving from the christic myth, proposing an approach in which the figure of Jesus unfolds in two alternatives that are two modes of interpreting (or place) his archetypal conditioncontrasted to configure your profile of multidimensional archetype, which comes to be a splendid metaphor that dissects the eternal struggle inside, the struggle between the carnal and the spiritual, the earthly and the heavenly.Therefore, the film focuses more on developing philosophical aspects than in showing a Jesus "son of God" to use. It is a film of a high density, a far cry from the requirements and business needs. In the politico-social we see a Jesus of Nazareth Builder Carpenter of the crosses to crucify Jews, placing the character in a position controversial at the social level, which is derived from an exempt from all conventionalism look at the traditional idea of Jesus as a faithful follower of tradition and the collective identity of the Israelis. In that vein, here the nazareno is not just a reformer of the tradition, but also an "outsider" that low a profile of restless spirit raises doubts about its own identity and the identity of the culture to which it belongs. The meaning and the nature of concepts such as the Messiah, God's Kingdom, release of Israel, spirit and body are addressed through a dynamic speech, in which each character represents a different Prism or a critical reinterpretation of the meaning, purpose and fundamental value of the figure of the Messiah, the Messenger of God or whatever.Tells us, by the way, the initiatory journey of a warrior in permanent struggle with himself and with others. Jesus Christ loves Magdalena but rejects the conjugal life in pursuit of a transcendent mission. It is the same image of the hero that breaks all ties to focus his life on one higher goal. Stabbing case is that here the family shows as a drag on that path to be superior, contradicting Christian and Catholic tradition that puts the family in an inescapable podium for the correct structuring of the society and the moral good. See how the Christ deceived by the devil disguised as angel is symbolizing the passivity and stagnation of old age; the family is the ballast that will ruin any claim of making God and move the foundations of humanity. This is one of their most provocative aspects and a topic which refers to the hero that destroys the bonds that bind him to the Earth in the sense of stability and conservatism of the family life. The great men that really manage to bring something to civilization, sacrifice many things to get to the sky of the myths.The complexity of discourse gives to much more, we leave here. The rest is pure film craft, the usual sober and brioso pulse of Martin Scorsese (that not great, everything must be said) to the service of a reflective vision and self-criticism. In this unfolding of Jesus behind a dialogue autorecriminativo between the social Convention and wild from abroad in their land and dissident freedom of everyone and everything: the Jesus defeated death (albeit only in the field of popular belief) gives mankind hope and a sense. The Jesus who stays at home with the women and children, aging, symbolizes the aging defeated and alienated from the problems of the world, the forgetting of dreams and ideals. Heaven and Earth, body and soul, and a self-critical Jesus Christ in the middle of the crossroads, taking advantage of this way its immense archetypal flow to show us several edges on the problems of the humán, religion and philosophy, and this is a great artistic achievement. Let us look at the words of Nikos Kazantzakis, author of the book on which the film is based: "the double personality of Christ, the suffering, both human and superhuman, of a man to reach God, has always been an enduring mystery for me." "My main desire and the source of my venturas y desventuras since childhood, has been a relentless and cruel battle between the spirit and the carne.y my soul is the field of fight where these two armies have found and fought"</body>
</review>
