<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Princesas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Princesses risks, but it loses: melts in the impostada comical in some reluctance to give a greater plot background. Without a script in which things become, the film loses unrecoverable assets. Film desguionizado.</summary>
	<body>Far from being an acid portrait of prostitution to which many would have liked to put the signature of writer-director Fernando Le칩n de Aranoa, princesses is a simple inventory of routines that populate the life of normal people who hide their sins and opens his heart to others when the circumstances so send. Leon de Aranoa is not complicated in narrative stills that compromise prominence to what he considered truly essence of his film: friendship without hesitation, slow, exquisite, two prostitutes who allied against the misery of the people and the harshness of the world that have opposite. Caye (Candela Pe침a) and Zulema (Micaela Nev치rez) bear the weight of the film, which is much and little, which is summarized in three strokes, but lastra a universe wide universally understandable feelings, perfect gestures and sincere looks great.Melancholy, tenderness, sorrow: aspects that have never left at all the cinema of this forensic society, vivisecciona the newly shot body of a city that breathes routine, incommunicado detention and disquiet in all its streets.Script, to tell the truth, there is little: there is no need. This claim of cinema pseudocumentalista, lyric the way Leon de Aranoa understands the beauty, gives a film paused in excess, overloaded on the shoulders of two actresses in State of grace, which seem to not act and estimable dignity carry load Poetics of history.Isn't Mondays in the Sun or neighborhood or the magnificent Opera prima family: princesses is minor film. More is a whim of a restless, and risky, screenwriter that a proposal with commercial scope and artistic sights as the preceding. It would seem that everything has been carried away by the desire to offer a view different from the physical fact and social of prostitution. There is too much ' Costumbrismo ': an unnecessary atiborramiento silence of complicity that we already know and left over. Sweetened as she did not need, the result is disappointing, given (will ultimately be that) of the expectations created with those aforementioned tapes and opened the illusion that Fernando Le칩n de Aranoa had a unique voice and a universe of feelings of long-haul. It has not failed himself, in my humble opinion, but it has missed the opportunity to continue risking and winning. Princesses risks, but it loses: melts in the impostada comical in some reluctance to give a greater plot background. Without a script in which things become, the film loses unrecoverable assets. Cinema desguionizado, if any, will be film, but already bordering other territories which, on occasions, provides better results with other weapons like the music (the ineffable art par excellence) or literature (absolute art par excellence).Addenda: the end is somewhat cowardly, ambiguous: perhaps the only one possible, which is a pity that I did not suffer.</body>
</review>
