<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a worthy product, to finish a saga that has fallen in love with millions of viewers, and thus is rewarded. At no time is us to trick, because we all know what we will find, and the truth is that this gesture is appreciated.</summary>
	<body>Sylvester Stallone returns to put behind the cameras, to offer us a new vision of the Italian colt, once have already passed their time of glory, to show us to the person, the former boxer that recalls with nostalgia his days as champion.Of course Sly again encased the gloves, and despite his years, it is housed in the full form. In this sixth and final part of the adventures of Rocky Balboa, Stallone shows us the life which was the heavyweight champion. Widower and directing his Italian restaurant "Adrian´s", also show us a Rocky as a concerned parent who has a serious isolation with his son, that he is ashamed of the successes of his father, to have to endure a hard slab, which supposed to be the son of a celebrity. As no, problems including solventarán as well as the film comes to the point that interests us, when Rocky by chance, eventually accepted to fight with heavyweight champion is Mason Dixon.Todo this preceded of Balboa get you the itch to return to fighting, little to be living things, and as he himself says? I think that I still have some things in the basement? so after that starting point, and thanks to a virtual match dan television facing Rocky and Mason Dixon, the promoters decide to do real. All a tuning for both boxers.At this time, it is when the nostalgia become more evident, and when tenders us the heart, observing the Colt Italian exit along the tunnel from locker rooms and hear and see the crowd having shouting the name of the champion. A very interesting point is that the image changes to high definition, so that it appears as the typical sports broadcasting, thus giving a more truthful touch. The first round is the best of the film, and is where are all our feelings about this character that we have been seeing in so many films. Below, shows the rest of the match as a video clip with a devilish pace that takes us to the last assault. In short "Rocky Balboa" is a worthy product, to finish a saga that has fallen in love with millions of viewers, and thus is rewarded. At no time is us to trick, because we all know what we're going to find in this film, and the truth is that this gesture is appreciated.Up always Rocky.</body>
</review>
