<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="El ilusionista" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Some time ago I wanted to fall in love with a fictional character and the illusionist (2006), yesterday I went. My magician...</summary>
	<body>Some time ago I wanted to fall in love with a fictional character and the illusionist (2006), yesterday I went. I.e., I always stop falling for fictional characters, the last was the nuevo-viejo James Bond, who was re-hot, but with him, it was that kind of infatuation for a clash and leak just, as usual. On the other hand, this time Yes is a crush type "I want to have all their little children". Yesterday the character of Edward Norton, the magician Eisenheim, really me hypnotised. And is that Edward Norton is not handsome, nooo, but is too attractive, I always thought, it has a mix of male well with smart well, the maximum. And in the illusionist is more attractive than ever.While this film was released almost simultaneously with another very good film of magicians (the great trick), they do not seem to much.This story is narrated by the inspector Uhl played by Paul Giamatti who already show us his interpretive quality movie recommended by EBC, American splendor. Uhl works under the direct orders of the future emperor in Vienna, the cursed Prince Leopold who has a very good characterization of Rufus Sewell, one reaches you hate.The rivalry between Eisenheim and Leopold occurs because the Prince is committed to the Countess Sophie (Jessica Biel), the love of children of Eisenheim, then just Edward. He was the son of a capintero, which had see hidden throughout his childhood and adolescence, until they were definitely separated by her family. Then Edward decides to know the world and its magic and part of Vienna, returning 15 years later converted into a great magician.The spectacle of Eisenheim becomes so famous that one night the Prince and his entourage attending see it and when the wizard asks for a voluntary "without fear of death" the Prince puts in place, more voluntaría "courageously" to his fiancée, the Countess. It is only on the stage that Edward and Sophie are recognized.But the rivalry between Eisenheim and Leopold goes beyond Sophie. The town hates and fears the abusive Leopold, while he loves Eisenheim, because they truly believe that all his illusions are true magic.At this point in which Sophie and Edward have been found and love to reborn, should see how to escape successfully, this time together. And I stop to avoid major spoilers. See it yourselves, worth it. And very careful with falling in love!Data: - the film is based on the short story "Eisenheim, the magician" by the American writer Steven Millhauser-the story is fiction, however the character of Prince Leopold was inspired by the true Prince of Vienna, Rudolph, son of Emperor Franz Joseph I.-the character of Eisenheim was based on the magician Erik Jan Hanussen, who was famous in Vienna at the beginning of the 20th century. He was assassinated by the nazis in 1933.</body>
</review>
