<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="El perfume" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I recommend with confidence this film which is full of beautiful pictures and Yes, also powerful odors. In short, a very sensual film.</summary>
	<body>One of the best things he did for my university education is putting me in the curriculum of a course, the book "El Perfume" of Patrick Süskind as compulsory text. Enjoyment and olí each page of this wonderful story.I was why me I touched up the marrow when I learned that they were going through one of my favorite books to the big screen. I know I said the same thing in my reviews of memoirs of a Geisha and pride &amp; prejudice, but I have many favorite books, I'm not cheating them!I began to see the Perfume, the story of a murderer (2006) with some suspicion because many times the film destroys to literature, but I must tell you that I finished the film quite satisfied with the excellent adaptation of the novel bestseller.Some time ago I read that uraño Süskind had rejected the proposition of adapting his best work to the film, million times and the most high-profile names of the seventh art (Stanley Kubrick, Tim Burton, Milos Forman, Ridley Scott and Martin Scorsese). However, a good day agreed that Tom Tykwer, German director of run Lola run, her lead, of course, by the Bicocca of 10 million euros in return for rights.The perfume is the story of Jean Baptiste Grenouille, born in the most pestífero place on the planet, between the viscera of the fish which his distorted mother sold in a market of the old Paris. Jean Baptiste (Ben Wishaw) has two features that make it "special": it has no smell and you can distinguish each and every one of the scents in the world with total precision. This last don leads him to be the protégé of a famous creator of perfumes (Dustin Hoffman) who retrieves the glory lost thanks to the excellent nose of Jean Baptiste. In return, he teaches you all the secrets of the business, as Jean Baptiste is trying to develop a special fragrance, with which it lives obsessed. The perfume of beauty and innocence. And this perfume has a high cost.Alan Rickman, known for his portrayal of Professor Snape in the film series Harry Potter.Recomiendo with confidence this film which is full of beautiful pictures and Yes, also powerful odors also acts. In short, a very sensual film.</body>
</review>
