<review author="Iñigo" title="Manderlay" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Who gives value and meaning to democracy?</summary>
	<body>Returns the tyrant. Returns the self-worshiping. But he also returned his genius, his great success and their reflective ability. Once again Lars Von Trier. And returns to attack us with their wild moral messages. After the first controversial installment of his trilogy about United States ("USA, land of opportunities"), "Dogville", the charismatic Danish director returns to the big screen with "Manderlay". The film was presented at the Cannes Film Festival past, and from there has begun its journey of presentation throughout Europe, achieving very good reception in certain places. and a certain fear and rejection in others (do guess what?). Lars Von Trier, in his eagerness to sow the controversy beyond where necessary and without any kind of leniency, continues its particular "moral" at the point in which ended the first "Dogville". But since then many things have changed. Nicole Kidman is not Grace, now occupies this made Bryce Dallas Howard. And not James Caan is his father, it is now the multifaceted Willem Dafoe. Any actor to support two consecutive films with Von Trier, otherwise they should ask to Björk is rather complicated. But the story follows its course. Grace (with the company from his father and his "gangsters"), after showing its true face in Dogville, continues its initiatory and supposedly innocent gait until you see with Manderlay, a place that, despite everything, the slavery prevails still chaired by the strict law of Mam. And, how not, our protagonist is established there with the selfless desire to fix everything and let the injustices and oppression do gala. But, over time, will be that the results are completely opposed to those who she had hoped. Little more than two hours they will do our dear Grace, his ego, his conscience and his intrinsic desire for authority, will realize that it is not enough to want to impersonate an entire culture and wanting to impose of oneself to question the soundness of a population. Thus, on this occasion, Grace occurs much more as a kind of leader, but on the contrary that in "Dogville", is herself who tries to force his power, not it's earn it as it did in the first chapter. It gives the feeling that the people not look at Grace to innocent appearing, trying to escape, in Dogville. Now much more believes in herself and their convictions (whether real, feigned or simply elitists), achieving the development of history, in that sense, is totally opposite of his predecessor. So you can see how from almost a first moment (from the moment that feels comfortable and integrated in the population), our protagonist is "open your eyes" to a people that was totally subject and was not able to evolve in their State of lack of freedom and devoid of any protection or license. Grace and its ethical and human condition are on duty to help this poor mass of uneducated, educate them, rediscover them and make them try the true meaning of democracy. Surely they are prepared. And if not so, tough. The truth is that in "Manderlay" to Trier is much more than the Duster in "Dogville". While latter was completely universal, certainly ambiguous and us subjected to a personal reflection morally brutal (above all for its controversial final from the ethical point of view), "Manderlay" is enclosed in a circle clearly lower. Looks reduced to an environment that smells to rotten to say enough (referring this to us, of course) and that any criticism has a place. And is that the director accuses a certain lack of tino addressing the issue with a greater objectivity and leaving us to us all that hard work. Gives the impression that it wants to on his side too blatantly to position the Viewer (though basically we know that its self-worshiping character looks forward to it every moment), something that was not happening in "Dogville". Seems that its critical stance has lost a tad, and that being direct WINS lose you in subtlety. Despite these small errors (many of them due to the personality of the director himself), fierce, audacious and ironic criticism hides a message that all of us should understand and try to learn. The ideological stance of Trier has a lucidity that nowadays hardly see in the film. We should look to Europe a few years ago to make comparisons in this regard. The controversial author (along with other names) of the "Dogme 95" movement (which itself was controversial) ruthlessly attacking a country that defines as false, hypocritical and shameless. "Dogville" was more global, here is a central (and front) attack against the fallacy of u. S. A.. Against those leaders who create a personalized and interested democracy, stealing their true meaning and reducing him to a kind of silent dictatorship. Against this voting system whose value is in question as soon as is grasping the simple difference between the truth and the number of votes, result of a selfish, manipulative and destructive human condition that, faced with a complication or ideological difference, establishes the most bitter condemnation or the quickest and most simple death penalty. Thus, Grace represents the true example of the American hero who comes, while nobody him sailing at that funeral, to save people plunged into poverty all and ruled by tyrants who shed his human condition with egregious and abusive acts. They try to impose their social and political norms of coexistence without addressing its culture or before the behaviors or traditions, or worry about the people or ask if they really wanted to change their lifestyle or it was that they wanted and were unable to cope with a very dramatic change. Thus the village, powerless against something that couldn't understand and seeing how change escaped you from the hands and it was impossible to assimilate in such a short time, ends asserting that any past was better and that bad is better known than good to know. For a time in the later works of Trier, the character does not suffer unspeakable to reach their desired goal, at least in the physical aspect, since the mental self which looms a content, detonating suffering of the interested disappointment to his person. In this regard, it should be say that the shadow of Nicole Kidman is relatively long. Its claw and potential in "Dogville" was much larger than the fragile Howard (despite the fact that the papers required or not a performance or another), that within a timely containment the mata figured. Certainly cannot be denied that the daughter of the ineffable Ron Howard (as well as the rest of the cast) raya to high level. The outline of the film is exactly equal to its predecessor in the formal and structural aspects. A fable, with included Narrator tells of a divided into chapters and entertaining way. In a wrapped "moral" with sarcasm and irony, Lars Von Trier trace the history of Grace, his arrival, the establishment, the coexistence and his subsequent departure of Manderlay as if a play were, with the already known and controversial basic scenario drawn (although not get the prominence of the first installment), their luminous games and music of Vivaldi (jumping to the Bullfighter)(, as usual it and appropriate him, their own rules for the "Dogme 95" movement), which permeates all of misleadingly reassuring environment. For the Virgin Viewer in the field will be a shocking bet, but for the connoisseurs of previous delivery, in that regard, it is not anything new. In short, a work which, without reaching the genius of its predecessor, is interesting as a forced time reflection consider our moral actions and democratic conditions. The clarity of Trier is crushing thereon, and its irreproachable moral discourse. All that, along with his irony last totally thread (tuned to the end credits with "Young Americans" as the background.) (go bad grapes spent the bastard), manage to outline us a smile, Amen deepen our human, social and political forum more internal. We could say, therefore, that has treatment of a controversial issue in a very smart way, without being pedantic, agile, thoughtful and lucid in its favour. It really forces us to learn. And, despite its length, without being so extensive as the of "Dogville", digested easily. And a very interesting fact. He is not racism as such, or by difference of race, colour or similar, but more open to human conditions of democracy and its limit of scope and credibility. Something that is really appreciated is with what comes lately. However, also are you can blame a certain and obvious bias that spoils a little austerity of his message, and appears focused and only closed in the criticism of us that makes that not us universalize both as "Dogville" its intention. And, its start-up scene and its aesthetic is obviously little original and groundbreaking, as we have already seen it beforehand, but being one realistic, it's not nearly relevant, because the characters are sufficiently profiled as forget the rest. In fact, this was the idea "saving of props" from the Danish director. Maybe many find it unbearably pretentious. What are you gonna do. It is the least we can expect from a guy like Trier. Maybe the director more pretentious and self-worshiping of the moment. But their results achieved that we forget and we can forgive it what (almost) everything. A real slap what some countries call democracy. It must be acknowledged that the good of Lars has spent at certain times. Just in case, and to not overwhelm us with so much political treatment which has lately swamped the film, Lars Von Trier has decided to delay the filming of "Von" (no "h"), the latest installment of the trilogy. And I think it was a good idea. </body>
</review>
