<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>n Yes the movie is as a great act of magic, where only the final will reveal us its own "prestige". If they have not seen it, see it, is very good. After all, the real Wizard of the story seems to be Nolan.</summary>
	<body>A few hours ago saw The Prestige (2006), translated to Spanish as El Gran trick or the Final trick. I saw on the recommendation of several editors of EBC, which is why I am surprised that this is the first review of the film in this blog (chiquita).I loved it. The performances were spectacular and the theme for me is exciting: the back of the curtain of acts of magic.I guess try to summarize the story without falling into the spoiler is quite difficult, so I will only say that you it's the battle of two young wizards by taking revenge on the other, to be the best, amaze the world with impossible trick. These magicians are Robert Angier (Hugh Jackman) "El Gran Dalton" VS Alfred Borden "The master" (Christian Bale).Two characters will be his accomplices throughout their careers: the designer/engineer tricks, Cutter (Michael Caine) and the beautiful Assistant Olivia (Scarlett Johansson).The film depicts a world of illusion, secrets, rivalry and obsession, where you cannot trust really nobody, except yourself. And only oneself can be sacrificed himself. Do if you don't understand this last line you will have to go see the movie and only then charged sentido.¿Por what the original title of the film? The Prestige or reputation. The explanation is that any act of magic consists of three parts: 1. the promise (a subject teaches). 2. The change (the object disappears). 3. The Prestige (the object reappears) and only then the wizard receives the homage of the applause. Without the prestige, the trick is worthless.The film itself is as a great act of magic, where only the final will reveal us its own "prestige". Large part of the perpetual suspense throughout the film is the work of non-linear editing in time.The director of this film (and screenwriter along with his brother Jonathan) is Christopher Nolan, who previously had worked with the duo Christian Bale and Michael Caine, leading them in Batman Begins (2005). However, the great trick does rather remind us another very good film from Nolan – Memento (2000) where the game of time back-forward is also essential. If they have not seen it, see it, is very good. After all, the real Wizard of the story seems to be Nolan.</body>
</review>
