<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="Happy feet" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Finally, let me say that history is nothing new. Of all the films animated 2006, definitely I prefer Cars.</summary>
	<body>Happy is how I would describe myself as I was traveling and I went into a city with two rooms Imax! IMAX = Maximum Image. I.e., watch movies on giant screens in 22 m x 16 m, with a quality and sound spectacular.There are few films designed for this format and are less commercial films developed for Imax (also) (although it seems that they are increasingly more.) and was fortunate to be at the premiere of the latest animated film in IMAX version: Happy Feet (2006).I thought it was a premiere global, but one of the kind Knights of EBC informs me in Peru it opens on 7 December, I imagine that you as commercial Christmas play. But I am sure that all have already seen a preview of the film of cute penguins singing well-known songs, right? In addition Happy Feet merchandising issues are everywhere.The story goes thus: each Penguin Emperor (the same as in the documentary film March of the Penguin, reviewed in EBC) has in its interior a song which will define his life romantic and family therefore. It was by their large voices that the parents of (Nicole Kidman and Hugh Jackman) Mumble, the main character, they met and fell in love and was therefore by other inexplicable that Mumble (Elijah Wood) can not sing or a note. Always Mumble is the rare Penguin Group. Instead of singing, zapatea (without shoes obviously) which is regarded as a very antisocial behaviour. He is disowned by his clan and soon is hosted by another more relaxed group of penguins (commanded by Ramón with the voice of Robin Williams). The funny thing is that these are the Latin penguins. When they stop to see us that way the Yankees?Finally, let me say that history is nothing new. It is an "ugly duckling" with more ambitions, but the songs are nice and is super good to nephews and sons guys, who's insurance will spend a good while violence-free.Now, are so much film about the emperor penguins will be having a good environmental effect? In the same movie plays the theme of humans, that be alien that can destroy the nature and also to save her.Another plus of having seen when traveling is that I could listen to the original voices, hopefully reach Peru in subtitled version. Worth, because the actors interpret all songs. Nicole Kidman already had shown us his skills of singer previously in Moulin Rouge.De all animated films of 2006, I definitely prefer Cars. If they did not see it, rent!!</body>
</review>
