<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film where million had been invested (especially in locations) for impoverished results. A total disappointment! Miami Vice with malaza m.</summary>
	<body>Long did not see a movie so bad and I feel the moral obligation to tell you: do not see Miami Vice (2006).Despite the excellent credit:-written and directed by Michael Mann, director of the highly recommended collateral (2004) and the informant (1999). Michael Mann was the producer of the television series with the same name in the 80's. Depending on the result, I think that his "homage" did not do so with too much affection-stars as detective Ricco, Jamie Foxx, who recently played brilliantly to the blind musician Ray Charles in Ray (2004), won him very precisely the Oscar and BAFTA (British Academy Award) for best performance by a male in 2005-Colin Farrell (the new world), secunda Foxxplaying her partner of work, detective Sonny. While Farrell is not no actorazo, has some weight in the industry Hollywood. one scam gentlemen! The film is nonsense from beginning to end. The dialogues are dull, technical and incoherent. The action has nothing on another Thursday. The actions are completely irrelevant and stereotypical. Situations are full of platitudes. Apparently Mann believes that the scene non-plus-ultra of eroticism should be a "grip in the shower" because her repeat with both protagonists unnecessarily. He wanted to take advantage of the set of the shower? Who knows!Those who are looking for the "beautiful blonde from Miami" even to brighten the eye, lost. Bad sexy here is Li Gong, to what you believe, has his blog. Let's see if they understand! She is not feat. Some perhaps her remember the evil Hatsumono in memoirs of a Geisha.No understand. What were all these good performers in a very mediocre production? I am thinking to buy the script for use of soporific in my sleepless nights.From what little I remember of the television series, was not anything. I do not remember that it was my favorite TV series, but it was entertaining, something that this film is definitely not.If occurs that anyway they want to go to check what I say, even by mocking the bizarre ochentera fashion, characteristic of the original TV series, therefore nor find it. Here Ricco and Sonny dress as any child of neighbour.Note that it is a film where million had been invested (especially in locations) for impoverished results. A total disappointment!</body>
</review>
