<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Marketing, film, redemption and blood on the canvas again. Metacinematográfica, convincing in its legitimate review of the cause, Rocky Balboa will provide a bit of fleeting pleasure to those who attend with an eye on the already talludito Stallone and another in the multi film of 1976.</summary>
	<body>Between 1976 (Rocky) and 1990 (Rocky V) Stallone drew already predictable and rudimentary lines of a character that would give him fame and, at the time, bitter disputes with the Guild of critique, which heaped with scorn the franchise of the Balboa Boxer to the more rickety shelf of the video store of series B more humble.The public burning of this saga miraculously saved the first installment, which earned the applause of the Academy of Hollywood (three statuettes: - Avildsen - director, editing and photography): Rocky was a noble job on the world of boxing with a Stallone still unpolished (or lack that did) in the role of the solo and stubborn Boxer extricated from the dangers of the street-based call in the ring.The other four deliveries the surplus insisted: Balboa, penniless, returning to the ring; Balboa helping a friend who, in the fourth, come in Moscow; Balboa training a young promising shadowing itself. This fifth part is substantially an equal of disposable film, but contains one sense of admirable dignity that the other lacked completely. Stallone, bad actor, is in this film old dog and knows that turning his personality in the history of the character, or vice versa, what we know, it will make the brainy boom seek three feet to the cat and discovered pasmados by the finding, which is indeed what is the true story of Sylvester Stallone, his glory and its decline, how life you can stop famous but not silly at all.This Rocky death certificate is written in a sober calligraphy and abounds, despite the sad precedent, in too many clichés: the same which was yesteryear flag, anthem and lining of all the minutes. No rhubarb warn some Lair to perpetuate the tremendous phrases which seem copied from any novelón-pastelazo series low B to what Stephanie, but in English and with canvas background.This Balboa of the 21st century is already-fondón, lives in his restaurant, widower with a son he has no account. The moral principles of this new Rocky are the pasta or the redemption: both perhaps. See one in this resucitamiento a very intelligent operation of marketing designed to dovetail with the heroes in decline at the end of life and the coming-out of the myth that returns. Stallone has done out of love for the pasta and in 2007 promises a revitalization of Rambo, which I promise not to go.Sounds inmarcesible Gonna fly now, the immortal melody from the original soundtrack and see Rocky in the staircase of the Museum of art of F ladelfía with the section of Bill Conti wind at full blast.Metacinematográfica, convincing in its legitimate review of the cause, Rocky Balboa will provide a bit of fleeting pleasure to those who attend with an eye on the already talludito Stallone and another in the multi film of 1976. What did you in 1976 when Stallone burst nose of Apollo Creed? I was in elementary and I heard Hotel California of The Eagles, but that is another story and just can count in another review. Oh, and the scenes of pure boxing are successful.</body>
</review>
