<review author="José A. Peig" title="Dogville" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do not know if Lars Von Trier is a genius, but in?Dogville? did a flawless job of creation and conceptual and technical realization, and also showed that his art is a strong catalyst for their deep spiritual concerns.</summary>
	<body>Once upon a town with their false Messiah and a girl that came from nowhere, fleeing from a darkness. A wolves averno getaway was to fall into a pit of wolves disguised. Came the time to prove the worth and the resistance of a caged collective itself by pretending, for wanting to be without being, out of fear. Everything ends with a decision whose origin lies in the deep of human consciousness, the look of a compassionate God. Consciousness can be dangerous, the flames of hell are which are hidden on the other side. It may sometimes be better not look, do not think, do not wish the good of humanity. We are too fragile to assume such responsibility.Lars Von Trier believe an allegory raw and naked from its external form to its depths. What says is too serious to be said: tell politicians, thinkers, nor any non-conformist pop singer. The truth is disguised as absorbent and devastating parable, disturbing to the receptive souls that arrive to apprehend the ultimate narrative meaning: are prisoners of a fragility that overcomes our moral and ethical codes noosphere, and can reach a point of despair so destabilizing than that same sphere of human culture ends up give way to the horror of the violenceaware and reasonably justified.The naked scenery this at the service of the naked and direct gaze with which Trier introduces us to the town that represents the whole of society, according to the proposed allegorical game. It is not any pedantry since that provision of the scenic elements allows to encompass the totality of beings and events that encourage both inside and outside the homes with a simple Assembly of frames, camera in hand, placing the viewer in a point of view (the eye of the camera) that allows you to know the life of the people without the conventional limit imposed by physical boundaries (doors)(, walls, etc). This, also, has an elementary function in the construction of history: emphasize human above a minimalist environment profiles and content, and to create a collective body that flows and interacts as a whole facing the two central characters. Great example of how to run an abstract concept (in his allegorical configuration) that gives rise to the recreation of the life of a people under a certain look omniscient, not restricted to dive, but any angle and lathe levels to any of the characters entered in the collective body. In sum, a superb orchestration and drawing of each of the elements of allegory, interconnected with dynamism to reach a powerful realistic dimension (reinforced by the movements of the hand to guide the camera).Despite its allegorical abstraction, history tells us about events that might occur anywhere in the world, in our immediate reality. The translation of an immediate allegorical space reality facilitates the game and the speech articulated in different profiles, and at the same time, gives a local significance to universal problems: hypocrisy, dissatisfaction, existential vacuum, faith or distrust in the other, the weak line that separates the purity of perversion, the shadows that cloud the distinction between victim and executionerthe danger of feel morally superior to a specific stratum of society and the danger of being too aware of this. There are certain nihilistic overtones in his conclusion: there are no more laws to which each one forges for himself, and they can justify genocide, without remorse that worth. I read somewhere that to Von Trier should be put in jail. Certainly his parable has a destructor, stabbing and openly power.Thus, if in the translation from the conceptual to the represented filmicamente is a real achievement, also triumphs in the development of the relationship between the locals and the mysterious fugitive: interactions have that point of ambiguity that requires the correct representation of a social conflict. Initial uncertainty to further harmony and coexistence, and return to the imbalance by the unknown, paranoia, malice, violence, suspicion and mistrust in a progression that is degenerating into the bitterness of treachery. The fire that destroys that micro world, which for about three hours has shown us a flow of human acts, justifies and means transparency and austerity of the stage. As a burst of pain and ignorance, it leaves you speechless. I don't know if Lars Von Trier is a genius, but in "Dogville" did a flawless job of creation and conceptual and technical realization, and also showed that his art is a strong catalyst for their deep spiritual concerns.</body>
</review>
