<review author="Elena Suárez" title="13 tzameti" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Among so much quality I only found a but it is the basis of the argument has some similarity (which not total) with a film of Spanish nationality and whose name I will not mention to avoid gutting the script. See the movie and discover what.</summary>
	<body>Number thirteen does not usually pass unnoticed by many of us, well because he admires or, on the contrary, because it is feared. For the protagonist of "Tzameti" (thirteen in Georgian) this number will mean even more, will be your Passport to an uncertain destination.Betting on the black and white, Gela Babluani, gives us an opera prima where the taste for the intimate camera and the development of narrative symbols bring us reminiscent of the best classic film of suspense. Fleeing Visual sweeteners, the narration is based under a solid script and a great acting job. This is not to say that the picture is not careful, on the contrary, it shows a delicate use of lights and subjective levels.As good film of suspense, we will have with the nerves encrespados until the end, as a result of a good use of narrative time and a work of Assembly has given as a result, and attention that this is almost impossible in the times, a work of only ninety-three minutes (Hallelujah!)Mention deserves separate, the interpretation of the protagonist, Georges Babluani (brother of the director) and it has proved its worth on their own merits. Finest close-up very hard that would be not accepted by many well known actors.All these ingredients have made him be winner of four awards in various festivals (unlike what happens with other films, these are deserved). History liked both that the director has signed a contract for a remake in United States (although I am afraid that I most like the original).Among so much quality I only found a but it is the basis of the argument has some similarity (which not total) with a film of Spanish nationality and whose name I will not mention to avoid gutting the script. See the movie and discover what.</body>
</review>
