<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Algunos hombres buenos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perfect vehicle for a brief but dazzling Jack Nicholson. Few good men is a fiasco, in a way, but Jack her successful and her raises a worthy films which may have been notorious cast and inexplicably, falling into oblivion.</summary>
	<body>It should not be cause of surprise that a film exclusively pivot on the personality of one of their players or, put another way, a film to be an actor and not we can under no circumstances imagine her without her presence. If above the character in question is secondary and only comes in whole we are witnessing a fiasco.Few good men is a fiasco, in a way, but Jack Nicholson her successful and her raises a worthy films which may have been notorious cast and inexplicably, falling into oblivion.The yankee film has experienced many times of this advertising claim. Movies of Bogart, Gregory Peck or James Dean. There is also the disks for a single song. Or books that we are only left with a phrase, with a faint glow that lingers in our memory as gold in the hand of the miser.Few good men survives for a trial where all stakeholders (including Tom Cruise) given the size and where Jack Nicholson gives life, but gives her effortlessly, imperceptibly. The deception of the hour and a half prior excuse and get one of the film (well, I yesterday saw in my dvd) with a satisfied smile: not feeling timados in excess.The script, which grows up to the formidable ultimately reveals the rigid codes of honor of the American army and how a young lawyer (Cruise) dismantles the shebang of protectionism, the discipline of silence and, above all, the untouchable status of a (repeat) Nicholson in State of grace absolute, in one of the roles adjusted to his mental mismatch, his creative genius and his dreadful nasty face.Side notable as Kiefer Sutherland or Kevin Bacon give an attractive counterpoint. Demi Moore stuffed, as almost always, and Tom Cruise, unpolished, pipiolo, is correct in his role as military principles, although frivolous at first.Years after its premiere, Cruise has high flight, while recently the distributors, the owners of the DIBs, withdrawn their trusted party because its franchises, their jumps and careers (see runs the uncle in all films) do not give box they wanted.Do Nicholson passes box nobody arises that a film will cover the usual holes of the producers, but this is known and Jack, my beloved Jack, is what it is: to make us believe that the interpretation is an art and deserves absolute praise when running with this appalling clarividencia.¿note what one of my favorite actors? Because by Jack attend the favorite video store, rent these good men or buy it. Buy cinema is an investment, although her does not consider those who write these periodicals of yellowed paper speak of indexes dow-jones and so many hundreds impossible to understand for simple minds like mine.</body>
</review>
