<review author="Jose Luis" title="Rosario Tijeras" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>By killing a man cobra 1,000,000 and bedtime with the one million and a penny</summary>
	<body>Say the gringos that current actresses mas sexis are Scarlett Johansson, Angelina Jolie, Jessica Alba, Jessica Simpson, Keira Knightley and Halle Berry. But I think that now need to consider a new actress that competes in beauty with all of them, Knights, they present Flora Martínez who from today should be remembered for his excellent work in Rosario Tijeras. And it is not only a beautiful and exuberant women, is also a brilliant actress who captures the protagonist of the film, with such force, justice, accuracy and soul, which makes the film completely credible. A Colombian actress to the fact everything from soap operas, theater in the U.S. and cinema. An actress told as the author of the novel on which is based the tape; "Flora made me feel and believe that she was the real Rosario Tijeras". They say that Rosario is the Queen of Colombia assassins. That he has killed thousands of men. That by killing a man cobra 1,000,000 and bedtime one million and a penny, because like her same says, is more difficult to love to kill. They say that their victims gives them a kiss before killing them, because she believes that any garbage deserves something before you go. They say that he has ever loved. And she said that only half of all this is truth.Based on the successful novel of the same name by author Jorge Franco, Emilio Maillé directs his first feature film after a long list of documentaries produced in different countries including France, where he resides since long ago. Making a profound, moving, heartbreaking though beautiful tape. Shaping life in the slums of the a mythical Medellin, Colombia, where the hope, the love, the passion coexist with violence and misfortune. A complex city captured with all justice and not just as a violent scenario, bajouna excellent picture that it gives us unforgettable images. The well adapted screenplay mixes perfectly the tragedy with a subplot sexy and enjoyable, you come to Rosario and helps you better understand and enjoy the film more. And while the third act is slow and repetitive, the film worth much, supported always with good performances by a multicultural cast consisting of the Colombian Manolo Cardona, Unax Ugalde Spanish and Mexican Rodrigo Oviedo. The single sequence of the ritual in the wake of one of the characters is too memorable to show clearly the Latin way of seeing life and death, a collection of desperate attempts to cover the death feast with joy, crowning the sequence with the incredible and unforgettable the streptease scene. A powerful, strong, tape that moves and it hurts, but strangely becomes love. A sample of that Latin American cinema has much rope for a while. Although the majority of viewers will only be attracted by the erotic poster (in that aspect either, nobody leave disappointed).</body>
</review>
