<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I take my hat to DiCaprio who has been working very well (infiltrated) in recent times. An actorazo that shines as the diamond around which the story revolves.</summary>
	<body>Blood diamond (2006) is a peliculón unforgettable performances of Leonardo DiCaprio as Danny Archer, a bright African mercenary, Jennifer Conelly as Maddy Bowen, a fierce journalist which seeks to contribute to a better world and Djimon Hounsou, as Solomon Vandy, a simple and good family man who became embroiled in the civil war in his country.Really, I take my hat to DiCaprio who has been working very well (infiltrated) in recent times. An actorazo that shines as the diamond around which the story revolves.I admit being very ignorant about the multiple crises in the African continent, by their own free will. I live in a country so full of crisis (Peru) which distressed me know that in other parts of the world things happen as or more terrible than my homeland and worse, I can not do anything about. But it is a selfish attitude, I know. Fortunately there are films committed as blood diamond, that help make these problems that nobody wants to see more visible.The action takes place in Sierra Leone, one of the countries affected by the civil war financed just by mining. "The rings of commitment that dream brides of America financed the deaths of thousands."In America, it's bling bling. But out here it's bling bang "Solomon Vandy is the proud father of day, an intelligent child that attends the school and who has a promising future, until the rebel (RUF) fraction takes by assault its people." The mother and daughter end up in a refugee camp, Dia is forced to join the rebel armed group and Solomon is forced to work in a mine of diamonds for rebels, where a good day is a rare pink diamond (much more valuable than common diamonds). That diamond will change their fate because it will be coveted by all parties, including the smuggler Danny Archer, with whom will pair and friendship throughout the film.Another character that is introduced into the life and heart of Danny is the journalist Maddy, who seeks to make a difference with their work. It will be essential to recover the pink diamond.Solomon is looking for his family, Danny seeks diamond and Maddy looks for a good story. To achieve its objectives the three (unlikely friends) must join in a risky adventure A highly recommended film!</body>
</review>
