<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Torrente 2: Misión en Marbella" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential film for any lover of cinema entertainment. Patriotic humor that exudes irony and dubious taste through all the pores, but that shows that the public is sufficiently intelligent to discern between fiction and reality. As well as emphasize the ditch that separates the viewer of the critic.</summary>
	<body>A few years ago they premiered this film, and remains the second highest grossing of the Spanish film. Despite this, critique the has despellajado up nausea the tape, as in everything. This makes me think that you maybe that viewers have a few tastes very different from those who must advise us to do and what not to see. It may that the viewer demand more torrents and less Garcis be? It may be that the Viewer is sufficiently intelligent to choose what really is good? Not, I worry if when it comes to criticism against the third most viewed movie in the film Spanish. To this, certainly does not affect the crisis, nor the foreign film or anything of the sort, is sold without problem.The film is about torrent, a záfio, meanest, disgusting and all the adjectives qualifiers negative potential, who lives in Marbella spending millions and millions (acquired in the first film). As melts all the capital, it has to go back to work, so it became embroiled in a conspiracy of a mad Tycoon that seeks to destroy Marbella if you don't receive a few milloncejos. You can stream and his inseparable Cuco terminating Jose Luis Moreno and his monkey? Make your bets, gentlemen.Torrent 2 was, for me, a radical change in the landscape of the Spanish film. Paid for to begin with, itself, which is already of merit. He then approached us the typical North American cinema media waste, but with characters from here, those who make grace to the public. And he taught us that second parts may be better than the first. Once Santiago Segura was spared having to show us the virtues of Torrente, weapon a kind of thread (I dare not call it script) that serves to draw thousands of hilarious moments, with characters from all the coats that fold to your wishes. Performances by Jose Luis Moreno, bad bondiano total, or Gabino Diego, who has become the paradigm of sympathetic Spanish film junkie, or Tony Leblanc, as kind of Patriarch come, preached a tape sold alone. You don't need anyone her have and that anyone sell you (and see Santiago Segura insisted to do so). A tape of the taste of the Spanish public, that hardly can be exported.In short, essential film for any lover of cinema entertainment. Patriotic humor that exudes irony and dubious taste through all the pores, but that shows that the public is sufficiently intelligent to discern between fiction and reality. As well as emphasize the ditch that separates the viewer of the critic.Genial.Besitos.P.D: I got the criticism made without referring just to the first, I believe that it marks a milestone in the Spanish film criticism, ja, ja, ja.Moments to remember: ** the presentation style James Bond with torrent hanging from a nipple. ** the first scene with cuckoo at the wheel of the coche.* "who has thrown a black pool?" says when they are bathing. ** once Cuco wakes up at the bar and asks a zumito while lifting the hand saw him being punctured the kick on the arm that while he says "Put me a zumito"", it has many vitamins". "With the hand or with the mouth?" responds cuckoo. "With your mouth?" but you're a degenerate. Ummm. "well, we will see how it is that" says torrent is unzip the bragueta.* to the end, when stream has to throw the missile into the sea and said "to the sea?" no kid, to Gibraltar! Spanish or anyone! "."** "You know that women have 5 dolls?" "The barby (touching the Chin), wrists, barriguitas (tocandole the belly) and the chochona!"** "I gave that el Fary is God!" say that your mother is a whore. "well, that not tell, that everybody already knows".</body>
</review>
