<review author="JohnTrent" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apocalypto is a remarkable film that not outstanding. Not excited, but it works perfectly. It has one effective mechanism, which is none other than the of any machine with the pieces well incorporated.</summary>
	<body>Mel Gibson, as a person, is quite incomprehensible. He is a man determined to be the worst: misogynist, racist, religious conservative ultra or homofogo are some things visible in his personality or, at least, in some of his interviews or acts in public being exposed by their inadequate words. Now, if we enter to evaluate Gibson as a filmmaker, film director, things change considerably. And it is that this tipejo is, in fact, one of the best directors that we have at present, in addition to an author like the top of a pine of the few remaining today in American commercial cinema. Possibly, next to the great but hated by many M.Night Shyamalan, one of the few hopes that we have to think than film, away from remakes, sequels and prequels you, you can bring movies involving an artistic risk, a surprising creativity and moments of cinema in capital letters without having to pull the wrong assumed pedantry of other better considered (1).It all started with a short film entitled "The man without a face", of which I remember little. It was only later with a masterpiece called "Braveheart" when it began to be taken seriously as a director, beyond his facet of grossing star. The real boom came with "The passion of Christ", a film which garnered criticism many-colored but that swept around the world making it in a real social phenomenon. Apart from her commercial success, this film already left us see its Director to a guy with clear ideas about their film, marked violence and passion, as well as a dazzling visual style that leave no one indifferent. Gibson became author and gave us another masterpiece home with prejudice by many.Now, with "Apocalypto" is confirmed as the author definitely as a differentiating label marked by a particular vision of cinema and the world (2).Note that Mel Gibson likes to talk about the human suffering through torture (3) and, if "the passion of Christ" this suffering was the basis for all the footage, in "Apocalypto" not far behind. Death, in the form of Wild Hunt, greets us from the first minute of film. It is here when we see a group of Maya, among them the protagonist, pursue an animal by the jungle to hunt him. Act later, one of them eats his testicles guided by a joke of his companions, to ensure that, in this way, you can overcome their sexual problems.Shortly after entering scene the villains of the story or, at least, the more savage and ruthless people of the history. Its intention is none other than killing the village of the protagonist and the few survivors remaining take them to their village to exterminate them through a ritual in which give their hearts to one God (which is none other than the Sun) to thus quench your thirst. Quickly, and without much more, the film will become a spectacle of action that has nothing to envy to mythical as "Rambo" or "Predator" tapes. One violent hunting the man who will bring some time spectacular and disarmingly made in the best traditions of the genre. All with a compact and (almost) perfect rhythm. It is true that, between the intentions of its director, not this tell us one hundred by hundred and a historical film, although don't forget details of all kinds, even though some are of dubious credibility. Therefore, which Gibson intended, especially since the second half of the story, is to offer us an epic story of action and adventure. And in this, is not wrong at all. "Apocalypto" provokes the viewer with its gore unleashed and without complexes, with its dazzling landscapes and his photography, occasionally, master. Giddy for their concept of the cine-espectáculo with a touch of true author so recognizable and surprised by the characterization of the characters work, careful selection of casting and the risk assumed from his own pocket to invest an amount close to $ 50 million (some say more) to carry out a talkie in the Mayan language and with unknown actors tomostly dealt with true native. In the end, "Apocalypto" balance with around 50 million dollars at the box office of United States and seems to be one even greater interest in Europe, where he began to give that talk by his violence and provocation, as was the case with "The passion of Christ", although on a lesser scale. "And this, while not spectacular, are expected figures, or even more, for a film that involves both risk and that we are discussing but that, as often happens with good cinema of author, knows how to sell through the name of your manager, which is already reason for visit to the cinema for many fans or, in any case, people wanting to check where can get with each new film.""Apocalypto" is a remarkable film that not outstanding. Not excited, but it works perfectly. It has one effective mechanism, which is none other than the of any machine with the pieces well incorporated. Come on, you have to work without problems. And is that watching movies like this, one you assail doubts about how certain levels, can shoot about how someone can create an atmosphere so hyper realistic and credible on a cavilación so difficult and controversial. In the end, this is the film of a director who knows what is hands and which camera does shake the pulse. That is why we can see in "Apocalypto" great moments of cinema without the pretentious games or falling into absurd that hamper the pace. Gibson is going to the grain and doesn't let us escape until they have spent two hours. And, returning to M.Night Shyamalan, it's two of the few directors who can be found at present, within the commercial film, that have the gift of shoot and write with innate ease, with a conspicuous devotion to cinema and what each level means. Ultimately, two directors that go hand in hand, in their respective styles, to create film quality without cumbersome lands that bathing the screen of tedium, who know how to combine the rhythm with the leisurely tone them without leaving the attempt frog, and who understand that, like other arts cinema, needs a heart when we want to do something really comes and impact to the audience. Another thing is the answer that many give them.(1) What can someone explain me why we applaud everything he does, for example, Christopher Nolan, go no further "The final trick", when the huge difference of quality and work between that film and "Apocalypto" or "The passion of the Christ" is obvious? Agreement, is matter of taste. Even so, it shows the work of a creator, someone really aware with what makes and his way to tell. I, as much as I try, can't see these virtues in the flat and empty Nolan.(2) For Mel Gibson, the world seems to be a hard and full of evil place. The violence comes from religion, of the mandates of the people unleashed in madness at the mercy of a few supposed superiors, whether worldly or supernatural. That is why "Apocalypto" continues to offer us a vision of the world that not too far from the current reality.(3) In "The man without a face" torture interior and exterior of a man destroyed by his horrible face Serbia to articulate surface fears of humans in the form of torture, one of the primary, our own; In "Braveheart" William Wallace ended up being tortured to death by fighting against the tyranny of those supposedly superior beings who before spoke; "The passion of Christ" made up the perfect explanation in images of torture par excellence of the story: that of Christ for humanity.</body>
</review>
