<review author="José A. Peig" title="Europa" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Some may find a pedantry, as often happens in any work of author online free and avant-garde European cinema. But that only tell the corny and the ignorant.</summary>
	<body>Art - referred to under a process of conscious ontological self-assertion - takes a giant step everytime an artist creates a universe. No sense devote life to art without beforehand, recognizing that this is the most noble and transcendent of human condition facet. Human potential reaches its highest goal in the creative act, that perspire thinking soul by means of which the creator projects itself into a unique world. That is, gives us a piece of something own, something that can not be felt or understood in the conventional level of communication. "In this way, the non-transferable becomes transferable, and art, while communication Act, becomes a path of brotherhood between the sentient beings and creators.""Europe", Lars Von Trier, is a single object by its meaning and its form. The fundamental idea of the base text is an immersion into the depths of the mind of the omniscient Narrator made explicit through voice-over (Max Von Sydow in the original). Are hidden in the mind of Trier fears, ghosts and concerns those who are parading disguised as bitter tears for the European continent and its unhappy history recent and present. Although the plot is situated in the nazi Germany in post-war situations, words, gestures, the frames of conspiracy, hatred and irrationality that motivate different entities involving the essence of the human characters, are elements of the immediate present, passing through the war in the Balkans or any latent conflict between "our" and "others" that still threaten the peaceful coexistence of parts of Europe (Ireland)(, Basque country). Therefore, a part of the thematic content consists of an elegiac crying around universal conflicts from a contemporary framework.In another layer of content, appears a reason constant in the Filmography of Danish filmmaker, the figure of the lost innocent among the forest of conflict, victim of the interests of others, known as Leo Kessner. It is to the same time, protagonist and impartial observer, realization of the consciousness of the Viewer, which is being guided by the voiceover according the journey proposed by Trier. A trip full of shadows and ghosts that atosigan with his role of corrupt characters or slaves of their murder or complicity with the agencies involved in the war.This is another of the basic constituents of the content: its major dreamlike, own an atmosphere imagined by Franz Kafka, and here Trier sets the pulse of your camera in a visual space that contains the maximum possible information for the purpose: the depth of field and the different profiles to scene management always seeks to Leo Kessner position at a point of neutrality with respect to the remaining set, but, above all, emphasizes the feeling of drowning between harassment, imperatives and the deception perpetrated by this set of entities Kafkianos.En as to the writing, the script collects various thematic and emotional still: satirical or sarcastic tones, melancholy, disappointment, Apocalypse, paranoia, love, unrequited love, appreciation, contempt. It's fascinating to magnificently structured are all that amount of tones and Lars Von Trier succeeds through a simple story of love and disappointment in an atmosphere of ideological hostilities, nothing original in this sense. The significance of Europe lies not in the history, but the how is addressed: the visual imagination of Trier is evident in many levels, close-ups and the use of chromatic resources to create different dimensions narratives within the same story and the same scene, which occurs in a deliberate ambigüedad-confusión between the real and the Unrealthus accentuating the dream-like nature of the representation. The final destruction is preceded by tensions within psychological Leo Kessner, which exceeded by the banality and stupidity perceived peers, decides that, at the end and after the genocide is the only way out, following the thread most turbulent of the concerns of Trier, as we saw with regard to "Dogville".In view of all this, "Europe" comes to be an intellectual and creative of its author, capricious game in the choice of themes and forms used, huge variety, but not last its construction and intention, which is the communicate a universe of images stemming from his nightmares and the worst autobiographical memories, organized and represented by Dante allegory on the conflicts in our modern civilization and about the dangers of incommunicado detention and loneliness. Rather, the danger of misunderstanding, which is the factor that can make, any of us, in a desperate escape, take the decision to activate the pump that gives way to the horror. Finishing, and in response to your great qualities in the order theme (for complex topics with an effective structure), visual polychromy in keeping with the multifaceted narrative and emotional States representation, to be equipped with a personal stamp which it makes a unique piece, and considering that the art should produce genuine works, works which is said in colloquial expression: "only he could a work like that", i.e. that part of the idiosyncrasies of the author is given us through his aesthetic production (gives us, in a way, a vision of the world which enriches and extends from the own spectator, why has much more intellectual value that limited to offer a vision Mannerist or giving, i.e. a vision not creative and fossilized), as occurs in the speech of Spielberg in "Saving private ryan", which is nothing more than a mere copy of the American State speech. (Art is much more than that.) from "Images and words" we are left with no choice but to the qualify to "Europe", unquestionable and absolute, as a work of art.Some may find a pedantry, as often happens in any work of author online free and avant-garde European cinema. But that only tell the corny and the ignorant.</body>
</review>
