<review author="José A. Peig" title="Volver" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Putting the look in its four female protagonists, none is without form an integral part of a narrative that progresses from a starting point to an ending in which the four reunited-discover-be reconciled with something or someone, giving way to a different State.</summary>
	<body>With the time Pedro Almodóvar has become an icon and figure the Spanish industry media on which have been said and written perhaps too much fanfare understandable taking into account the ideological positioning and the constant bombardment to tale of the awards, the galas, the tributes, bla bla bla bla. From a certain intellectual sector - very grounded in the Internet network - has been custom underline the overvaluation of its role as a filmmaker, but it should get nuances to not mislead too. If someone wants to place Almodovar in a position of "great film", obviously hang him the epithet of "overrated filmmaker" will be a great success. If we compare his work with prevailing mediocrity in the Spanish film, Almodovar, without doubt, among the Spanish filmmakers most talented and significant of the last thirty years.First and foremost, Almodóvar makes film, and precision rather than claim they do. It should start from an inescapable knowledge: that a film with a well-organized structure is already almost a good movie (in the absence of analysis of contents and meanings). In "Volver", as in a large part of the Filmography of the director manchego, was a el igual que en una gran parte de la filmografía de el director manchego, se hace ago patent immediately touch and care of the characters in relation to the story you want to tell. Putting the look in its four female protagonists, none of them ceases to be an integral part of a narrative that progresses from a starting point (in which the four are in a very specific and defined psychological state through facts and words) until a final in which the four reunited-discover-be reconciled with something or someone, giving way to a different State.That is telling a story, and Almodovar does so with an honesty and a commendable clarity of ideas. It is not a capricious filmmaker, but has a few stories to him more than anyone affect you and you are interested in (loaded with pain by the hidden past or present agonizing inanity and disorientation), and than any viewer who has the ability to perceive "in tune" with the sensitivity of the author can enjoy equally.Yes, "Volver", he is not a genius, it's a typical story about a hidden past that from one moment in which certain variables affect and they break into the routine of events (the death of aunt), progresivamense is revealing, starting with images in a cemetery in which evokes a crucial fact. And that is the reason that drags us throughout the development. The image that closes the film shows us, and ultimately an alma en pena (Carmen Maura moving inland the manchega casona, suppressing tears because "the ghosts never cry," a few words at all arbitrary, that are defining the psychological state of the character, and also with the appropriate turn metaphorical) that encloses a dramatic story and is doomed to pay their debts, its particular cemetery. Beginning and end of the visual narrative overlap in the configuration of the meaning, the endpoint showing that Almodovar knows to use the language of cinema for a few purposes very specific and personal, his film is intimate, you take or you leave it.It is very commendable treatment and the orchestration of the female cast (as usual in Almodovar), as we have said, he is not extra or missing anything. The story is tragic, the characters are equipped with that dimension of the real to away them from the mere scheme, and all their reactions are consistent with its features. What gives more versatility throughout this set is the look halfway between the coldness and sensitivity. It is a film about a deep Spain, with its folklore and its myths, its everyday discontents, subjected to a treatment of bitter nostalgia, with these La Mancha village houses that saved the past, that Almodovar recreates with flat overall, the courtyard of the corridors, the winds that sweep the streets photographs of those who are no longer lights, the superstition of the neighbors.I.e., a narrative scheme so clear and concise, Almodóvar added his own Poetics, fruit of its landscapes, autobiographical roots. and your pain. Will not go down in history as a genius, probably given more awards you deserve (and those yet to come), but no longer a narrator with an exquisite by their own landscapes taste, whether a particular geographic area or a female soul (their interior landscapes). Therefore, his films have character of author, and we have a good exponent of his film in "Volver".</body>
</review>
