<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Noche en el museo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>His figures not wrecking you the Museum has to investigate about them: have to learn history, paleontology, natural sciences. Culture becomes, with this formula, a survival kit.</summary>
	<body>Films as "Night at the Museum", or "Jurassic Park" and books like "The Da Vinci Code" want to approach the world of mass tastes and culture. Do something similar to the MOM that adds cream to the yogurt that does not want to eat the child. The danger is that the child will stay with the cream and leave the yogurt. Many will leave the film without remembering Attila, the Romans or the old West, and remember that the Tyrannosaurus moving the tail like a poodle. Which, on the other hand is an incredible success.Who has seen the trailer for "Night at the Museum" already known throughout the film. Ben Stiller is working on night duty and discovers that the Museum back to life when it becomes night, cowboys miniatures, miniatures of Romans, the figure of wax Theodor Roosevelt, the skeleton of the Tyrannosaurus, the statue of the island of Java, an African jungle, guardians of the mummy of a Pharaoh, Attila and his Huns four. What is explaining to our rational minds such wonder? In addition, course, the desire that all us devour something strange happens when we are forced to go to a Museum and we die of boredom. The film does not offer the explanation to very advanced footage, appears confident that the show can sustain long time without explanation, and it is right.The welfare of the movie spirit consists of convincing us that museums are valuable, and that culture does something, against all the evidence offered by the television in the opposite direction. The game intends to prove it is ingenious. Ben Stiller has to keep in order the Museum if you don't want that they fired. His figures not wrecking you the plant has to investigate about them: have to learn history, paleontology, natural sciences. Culture becomes, with this formula, a survival kit. It becomes something terribly concrete, a kind of round of questions and answers, more akin to a television contest to a book of truth. But the idea works.Even a dramatic arc, the protagonist has an evolution. With so many accessories, no wonder that it has been a taquillazo. Ben Stiller is a loser fails to a permanent job and his son asks him why is not like the others. The journey is, for him, demonstrate that it is special. The side, real or figures, menudean filled with complaints and problems. And the second success of construction is the way that the plot has answer for everyone. Not let or one just forgotten.Perhaps the film is not a good argument to demonstrate how useful are the museums. To my me reaffirms that they are a suckling pig, because everything that happens only happens in the movies. But what does get a snapshot of the sensation is a riot and tranquility which was reached after negotiations with everyone. After connecting.</body>
</review>
