<review author="Caruco" title="Más extraño que la ficción" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do envisions us aquelllo that we can save the life, in the form of? nuances, anomalies and suggestions? a film like this or to discover.</summary>
	<body>A tragedy always gives packing and depth to a work. And if not that should ask Shakespeare, the Greek classics or Harold Crick, this third an individual for anything well-known or popular, more a solo and bland finance inspector, a bureaucrat delivered to thousands of daily rituals that constantly recur in their grey existence.And in fact, never know you if they do not see "Stranger than fiction". But what is important here is to emphasize that Harold Crick (a tight Will Ferrell) also subscribe this opinion to feet letter, although this will suposiera put an end to his own life.The second point is that screenwriter Charlie Kaufman and his philosophical, amateur to the metalanguage, original and reflective comedies of the type "Forget about me", "Adaptation (the Orchid thief)" or "as being John Malkovich," has left an imitator, Zach Helm, who by the way does not anything wrong with "Stranger than fiction".Its crazy argument, properly seasoned with a notable amount of romanticism, begins by raising the maximum power the idea of the writer or artist, as creator or demiurge. A sort of God that can play, happily or not, with the fate of his creatures.As a life-saving.In this case a depressive writer, Karen Eiffel (Emma Thompson), with crisis of inspiration and a muse, Penny Escher (Queen Latifah), imposed by Decree of his publishing house. And Karen, either by chance or by inexplicable divina-creadora intervention, will give a turnaround to its existence, along with his less fictional character than I would like. Tested the inexorable certainty of death, you will see that life can also have another bright side.Perhaps this is not the pleasure of another illustrious colleague, Professor, writer and psychiatrist Jules Hilbert (Dustin Hoffman), but at least the passionate and rebellious owner of a humble restaurant, Ana Pascal (Maggie Gyllenhaal), insurance that would appreciate that not all masterpiece is fatally marked by the funeral.Anyway, do not even need to worry about trying to decipher this criticism, but if you want to see a film original and different, as well as notable as the best film of Marc Forster ("Monster's ball", "Finding Neverland" or "Transit"), her would not escape.Speaks of works and characters of reality and destiny, the sublime and the mundane, even watches, wristwatches and electric guitars, and as much as the black shadow of death plan on their frames, also envisions us aquelllo that can save us life, is in the form "shades, anomalies and suggestions" or a film like this to discover.</body>
</review>
