<review author="Caruco" title="13 tzameti" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Deserves its distinction for his portrayal of a (sub) cold world and immutable, full of dirty games, unfortunately, even demasiadado with reality.</summary>
	<body>His number is 13 but numbers, have all to become a cult film, if it is that already it is not. "Tzameti" is this issue in Georgian; "do do a tribute from the director, newcomer Géla Babluani, its grounding in this co-production with France, and wander with this title throughout the world, with a stop in Hollywood, where the Americans are already thinking to create your particular? remake?.""13 Tzameti" is like a Quentin Tarantino to the poor, or a Roman Polanski reminiscing its beginnings to submergirse in the most twisted of the mind.If your presentation is somewhat disappointing, and delinquent to change the crux of the plot drags us towards the total angustía. A feeling increased with the picture in white and black and almost thirty minutes of footage that not only placed his terrified protagonist (Georges Babluani), a young worker of 22 years, drenched in sweat and in the crosshairs of a macabre bet, but also the same Viewer as if he had a loaded gun pointing him in the temple.An unforgiving world.Get easy money carries enormous risks is as true as there are mob with the limits of moral trastocados in search of strong feelings.The longing of each and the precariousness of others become human lives mere pieces or pawns, or "13 Tzameti" in any war. Maybe that it is it recreate too in his home with all kinds of characters that appear and disappear, with these looks, and games of persecutions and forgetfulness. Do do also that music has a tone? amateur?, more appropriate for a short film, reinforcing the idea that its proposal is somewhat stretched.But before the shortage of means, and the abundance of some of the results, this game of horror by the uncanny and the weaknesses of human nature, well deserves its distinction for his portrayal of a (sub) cold world and immutable, full of dirty games, unfortunately, even demasiadado with reality. And step that serves to make Eli Roth, and his "Hostel," take good note, or so that the Tenerifian Juan Carlos Fresnadillo maintain "intact" its capability to create more movies.</body>
</review>
