<review author="Javier Moreno" title="Harry poter y el caliz de fuego" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting adaptation of the novel by Rowling</summary>
	<body>No. This time I will use a film as a pretext to expose my ideas or thoughts not more insane/rational/foolish. This time, and I swear before the sacred Lovecraft Necronomicon, I will talk about the film itself (for the first time and hoping to not serve as precedent), although it's obvious that I prefer a movie make me reflect on any aspect that it is appointment. Maybe someday talk about everything which means the series of Rowling novels (walks that I have things to talk about) a less mythological perspective and more profound.Am assuming that I am a genuine fan of the books, I love them, find me the very best that has come in fantasy, with a main character really interesting and tormented at all levels by all its morphisms is implying. Delivery of the basis, as when adapting a book to the big screen, what interests me less is its possible fidelity or not (although it would be a real hypocritical if you deny that I it a damn). Birth of the basis, as what more I like to see in an adaptation, we see reflected in images which books I suggested with words.After these premises, indicated as a prelude, the adaptations of Columbus seemed quite interesting, in accordance with what the books tell and reflecting on images everything you enjoyed in each of the two volumes brought to the big screen by director only at home. Also I would like to indicate, that the third movie, directed by Alfonso Cuaron, albeit at technical level I found rather surprising (except for that anorexico werewolf), I ended up not convince, but it defrauded me a lot, because I did not see the spirit of the novel reflected on the screen. Rowling can tell he loves the movie and thousand things more, but if to my get me a cheque for 10 million of dollars on the table, I say if necessary that God exists by far to betray all the novel implied.With these brief reviews, and as stated, after the fiasco with Harry Potter and the prisoner of Azkaban, I have gone to the cinema, without any information (not wanted to feel me influenced to any level, nor predisposed to feel disappointed, nor predisposed to feel satisfied) to see the fourth film of the orphaned Wizard. Which I found in the movie?, well not much, what more me to surprised is a book of 650 pages, even having ignored certain passages, have been more correctly synthesized in 150 minutes of film, I found a director Mike Newell (Director among others of four weddings and a funeral, and a priori the least suitable for a movie like this), which managed to move the global idea that inspired the novel to 35 mm. Amazing without a doubt. Also I found with a few individuals represented in the previous movies the characters of the novels acting minimally, while Daniel Radcliffe has less talent than the spider which finding Moody launches the unforgivable curses. Long - inevitable - visual effect, absolutely appalling and excellent occasions (with particular reference to the Hungarian colacuerno), good narrative pace, and some scenes that required of more footage (especially the attack of the mortifagos, which with great left his entrance onstage, one wants much more). In the USA the film been qualified PG-13, in Spain PG-7. Well, it is true that it is very dark (something on the other part heir to the spirit of the novel - and I am repeating with the fucking spirit-), has "terrific" moments like the aforementioned appearance of the mortifagos in the quidditch World Cup and has funny moments. This is the movie, fans more radical Harry Potter will her love, the fans more purists repudiated, among the less radical there will be people that likes and another to which leave indifferent, and to not have read the novels because them seem entertaining. I, that being a follower of the books, prefer to place me in a term means, nor as incredible as I'm reading out there, nor as bad as it could be expected coming from the director that comes. An interesting film which in my view improves a lot fiasco Cuarón. all forms, in 20 years, we will see if the film saga of the London magician continues being remembered or be forgotten more absolute. It will be worth seeing it, if I can think fast... I am among those who think that films not aguantarán the passage of time as if will make it the novels.Finally, recommendations for the producers, the orden del fenix forget David Yates and contratad to Guillermo del Toro, for the half blood prince I yet by a Shane Carruth (director of Prime) and for the seventh book, even without having it read, Darren Aronofsky, which a time most claim the urgent release of The fountain, that server, since he saw Requiem for a dream, craving see this director's third masterpiece as destroyer.PS: If no Aronofsky, a Takashi Miike serious tremendous.</body>
</review>
