<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Hostel" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film of the pile that will delight lovers of the genre</summary>
	<body>Hand in hand with Quentin Tarantino, Eli Roth presents a new version of the classics of the horror film, in which a group of young ends up in a little village in which nothing is what it seems and that won't them be easy escape. Normally the scenario used to set these films usually deep America, but in this case and to give a more exotic touch have decided to move to Europe, specifically to Eslovaquia.El origin of the film comes because Roth they commented that there is the possibility of killing someone for 10,000 dollars. This is possible (or so they say) in Thailand, Act followed Roth was petrified and thought that it would be a perfect argument for his next movie. After these comments you can already imagine the argument: a group of kids (two Americans and an icelander) run through Europe in search of sex and being in Amsterdam them recommend go to a small Slovak town where beautiful women become mad by foreigners, especially by the Americans. As it was predictable, our protagonists are in your search, and also in a predictable way, will find much more than sexual pleasure.I have to say and thank that the film is not as strong as they sell it. It has your doses of guts, but it isn't that abounds more nor the most unpleasant ones, that what is really scary is that facts may occur in reality as those who tell us, and to some extent it would be easy they deliberately.Eli Roth tells us anything new, nor innovates in a quite exhausted genre, but it makes a review of classics such as the Texas Chainsaw Massacre including some ingredients of Asian film. In this regard is to comment on the cameo by director Takashi Miike (one of the greatest exponents of the genre) playing a sadistic client from the hunting of luxury. There is nothing to highlight, except the beauty in the flat acting and discovery of the actress Czech Barbara Nedeljakova, that the portrait of the characters is nothing of the topic.It must be said that Roth combines at certain times the horror with comedy, giving a couple of touches of black humor are welcome. A good contribution, who knew perfectly exploit Chicho Ibáñez-Serrador, is the figure of the child entity and personification of evil, being them the protagonists of a couple of great moments of the film.There are two very different parts: the first devoted to show the travel and behavior of the protagonists and already a second in which happiness becomes horror. Jay Hernandez is the only that has a role somewhat more dynamic and profound, it tells us a fact he had when he was young and that later will try to redeem, thus demonstrating an act of value that many others had declined. But despite this it remains one mere character more, rather flat. Tarantino and his team have been able to sell the bike, because many people have the idea that it is another great film, and when they see the title that accredits the direction the creator of Cavin Fever then are a disappointment. Another point in its favor has been the way to advertise it as the work more beast lapped ever, which will drag to many young and not so young, to see what they expect to be the most bloody feast in the history of the cinema. In short, a film of the pile that will delight lovers of the genre and that will surprise the new generations. Finally say that they do you not very good Slovakia, and as a curiosity advertising comment that there are many Americans that are wondering if there really is this country of Eastern Europe. If it is that at the end as in Spain anywhere.</body>
</review>
