<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The main problem with the film, and that lastra to the dessert, is little harmony on the pace of the story because of a poorly structured temporary jumps.</summary>
	<body>Flags of our fathers is not the new instant classic of Eastwood which many had hoped. Offers moments isolated magnificent film, war scenes as spectacular as raw (the footsteps of Spielberg is perceptible in them), an elegant photograph of shadows to Million Dollar Baby style and sound accompaniment of the parsimonious notes of the own Eastwood. But the film as a whole does not offer as many good movies as the quoted work or the Mystic River excellent carats. The possibility of a rapid recovery should be at least even through letters from Iwo Jima, a proposal of starting more original to take the unusual point of view of the American war contender.The tape assumes a fairly conventional narrative pattern: the son of one of the soldiers who posed for the famous photo of Joe Rosenthal crawls the role played by his father and his companions in the war of the Pacific and, in particular, after the historical snapshot. In his research for his book discover the bleak truth buried by time and the silence of the protagonists of the facts. And you ascertain how this photo was turned into a banner by the military establishments in order to raise funds for a war that was leaving exhausted the national coffers. Also see how the image of three soldiers reluctantly in the case of two of them, was used for a mammoth marketing campaign war in which there were no objections to lie, exaggerate and, above all, disrespect the memory of comrades fallen in combat.Thus the tape offers a critical discourse in the revision of the promotional campaign, but, above all, intended to pay homage to those who fought in that Sangria which was the island of Iwo Jima campaign. So the sparkling images of the soldiers converted to rock stars during his pilgrimage across the country have a dark and bloody underside: of countless casualties of beardless unable to overwhelm the Japanese soldiers. The main problem with the film, and that lastra to the dessert, is little harmony on the pace of the story because of a poorly structured temporary jumps. Thus, when the film delves into the drama of the triumphal return of the three soldiers, we return suddenly to the horror of the war that's when in when they supervenes them to each of them. And these two temporal dimensions, in addition, adds a third: that of the present tense with the son of the soldier 'Doc' Bradley (Ryan Phillippe) interviewing war veterans for his book. Therefore, although it does turn out to be interesting, the penultimate proposal of Eastwood (of greater budget of his career as director) isn't blessed by his mastery of recent times. Perhaps letters from Iwo Jima (nominated for the Academy Award for best film) to return the best version of the director of San Francisco.</body>
</review>
