<review author="Iñigo" title="La ciencia del sueño" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Gondry persevering, reinventing and staying in the attempt.</summary>
	<body>In an attempt to continue with his bizarre visual ideas, already established in "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind", Gondry braid a story in which the Ditto, precisely, occupies a segundísimo plane. "Sure, Charlie Kaufman was not present was expected.""The Science of Sleep" speaks of the need to dream, to create our own inner world, to defend ourselves against the boredom of the outside world, of a stagnant and decadent reality in the routine. And the need to fight for love. Once again.The author of the "Human Nature" horny launches a visually interesting proposal, but with a somewhat lacking script hook and stands as a clear example of return to the last path creating a continuation with its own identity.But the main reason why a movie buff comes to watch a film of Gondry is see how manages without the genius of Kaufman. Had to check if the French director is able to get away with a film project with all his weight, beyond of proposed videocliperas for MTV. And to its form, is possibly making a hole. But still interesting, fails to rid of his past. Nor by the side of Kaufman of MTV.When one sits down to see "The science of the dream", you cannot avoid thinking about films of the extent of the own "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind" of the same director before us (albeit with the invaluable help of one of the most transgressors writers of recent times) or "Punch Drunk Love" by Paul Thomas Anderson.And it is that the shadow of the teachers is too elongated.Gondry proposal here is almost the same as his previous film. A peculiar, convoluted, fun, modern way of defining romanticism. Reinventing the romantic genre. Exceed its barriers taking everything to the limit. But the invention is already patented. And the irregularity makes an excessive Act of presence.Although, at times, the feeling of "déjà vu" leaves the viewer a light aura of torpor, which causes certain bumps in the viewing of the film and avoids that we continue the story with total interest (eyelids weigh too), are well some hilarious moments, situations and bizarre scenes and ingenious gags that we raise at once and start to laugh.His absurd, metaphorically surreal humor while already exploited, indeed it generates reared situations in tronchante and delirious. You do not know where to put when Stéphane opens his mouth to release one of their brutal occurrences. Gael García Bernal does a great job, as well as quite distanced from their previous jobs. Shows like a fish in water in an area unknown to him: that of the absurd comedy.But he is not the only deranged mental "The Science of Sleep". The staff side is an authentic Gallery of "freaks", which give us phrases and situations more ludicrous and laughable.It is not humorous and witty point the only thing remarkable film. Also, the visual aspect is interesting. From decorated cardboard/stone, simulating movements close to a "stop-motion" rarefied up situational imagery of more curious.Gondry draws on expertise to give us an image for nothing abusive from the dramatic point of view, nor free. It exercises a great developer power to follow in detail the course of history and its meaning.And he ends up giving the work a relatively intimate character. This way Gondry last proposal could be defined. Unlike his previous film, this focuses more on fun and optimism. Less melancholy. More child (some would say that it sins in excess of naïve). More tender. And, indeed, without his magic and genius.Yes. "The science of sleep" is simply an attempt to continue the trail that a director is intended to leave. Why not he ceases to be fun and interesting, but after a certain time, one forgets what he has seen. Or "Punch Drunk Love" nor, of course, "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind" leave that we forget them.Gondry, on this occasion, has failed to give the final touch to make it something else. In one major film.It has become a valid attempt to but I try relatively unsuccessful at the end and all. Gives the feeling that the film lacks soul and, therefore, beyond survival of our eyes.Time will tell if its separation from Kaufman to gain greater prominence with his films has been fruitful. Or if instead and as a co-star Spike Jonze, should have opted for the genius and the "security" of protection of a screenwriter with innate talent. But? has someone said that Gondry may not have? Everything remains to be seen. And everything will end settling where deserves.Hopefully not fall into his own trap and let his past to focus a little on his own personality of "cinema" that he intends to create.So far, is is already winning its first defenders and his early detractors. Point forced all Director that comes out a little than usual.</body>
</review>
