<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Klimt" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Too many Visual pretensions to disguise a little work of documentation and, gentlemen, in this case gender submitted to us it is a biography.</summary>
	<body>I remember the criticism that, a few months ago he received the film "Goya's ghosts"; most were not very good and almost all were based on a false concept according to which the work intended to be a biography of the excellent painter and clear, from this point of view was poor, and even incorrect. At the time, I said that the film was not, under any circumstances, a biography, but that, based on the philosophy and life of the painter, Milos Forman, was able to introduce a historical character in an imaginary plot (something that is not as simple as it seems). Having said that, you ask everyone, and tale of what is it now? So very simple, these same critics that cursed both the direction of the Lord form, talked about wonders at the exit of the pass press "Klimt", a biography rather chaotic on one of the most outstanding painters of the 19th century.Well, my first recommendation is that if you don't know the work and life of the painter, you have two options: either documented on the life of Klimt or not you go see the movie. Do notice you, if he comes to see her without knowing data about the artist, come with the same notions, well, not exaggerate? You will know something more: painted nude ladies, had a great friend with right to rubbing, his art didn't like some of his contemporaries and syphilis badly damaged his nervous system. In addition to this content, you will see a stunning work of art. Both the picture and the colors are extremely cared to bring us into the symbolism of Gustav Klimt, but otherwise, the film has more mistakes than successes: true is that this painter was known for his love for the female body and that there are a lot of oil paintings and drawings on the physiognomy of the woman with all luxury of details, but is not less false that not only selected for this thin young but, also, he showed us the ajado body of elderly or the redondeces of pregnant women.It is true that he had a great friendship (perhaps more) with Emile Louise Flogë and, for this reason, it is said that when the painter died of an apoplexy attack asked to bring her to his side, data that the director not him interested, for him Klimt died saying "flowers".Klimt had a great fondness for his mother, and after his death, his palette became more sober and dark, because it is not important for Raoul Ruiz, moreover, we conclude the film simply mother and sister shared illness and hallucinations.So we could follow a few points but I do not intend to bore you too much, so, to sum up, too many Visual claims to disguise a little work of documentation and, gentlemen, in this case gender submitted to us it is a biography.</body>
</review>
