<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perfect screenplay in which all parts make up a watch mechanism. ?The prestige? It is a glorious, surround, touch and great film.</summary>
	<body>Infamante form holder a memorable film, possibly motivated by the fear of the Distributor to the Hispanic staff thought that it was a progresista-solidaria recreation of the sinking of the oil tanker off the Galician coast and the subsequent repercussions had to the Government of Chema Graznar. And it is that the lack of imagination of the patriotic "titrators" is unfortunate and pathetic. That we have a magic film because it hala, to put a "trick" in the title, won't nobody calling deception, precisely when the deceit and simulation are at the root of the latest film by Christopher Nolan, one of the most interesting Directors we have active and that, by shooting films of superheroes, as the last Batman; or police, as "Memento" or "Insomnia"; or fantastic cutting, like this "The prestige", happening too unnoticed among the common viewers and, of course, academies and associations that give the annual awards of the thing.Having said which, move on to describing the huge, powerful and potent virtues of this "The prestige", a film with many edges, folds, shadows and nasty as that other marvelous "War of the Roses". And is that when two artists begin to climb to the top, are many sensations and feelings that intersect with each other, from the admiration and recognition of envy, hatred and the desire to destroy the adversary, see you sunk, crushed, devastated and wiped out. "El Dorado", one of the great masterpieces of Howard Hawks, match two gunmen. One of them, Nelse Mcleod, asks John Wayne the opportunity to join their group. The refusal of Wayne Nelse espeta you something such as: "Perhaps better as well." "When two men as we ride together, always arise the issue of who is the best." And on that basis is built "The prestige": two magicians of remarkable talent who work together are separated by a tragic accident, starting a destructive rivalry that will take them to grown and go up to the heavens in his art and to sink and enfangar to disgusting in their personal relationship since then. With a fascinating fragmented narrative based on continuous jumps in time and thanks to a majestic interpretative work both the main actors and each side luxury? unpayable Michael Caine and David Bowie, with a perfect script in which all parts make up a mechanism of watchmaking that works with Swiss precision and an environmental dirty realism that serves to emphasize the vileness and the corruption of the characters; "The prestige" is a glorious, surround, touch and great film which, without Manichaeism, becomes a prodigious set of mirrors that is perfectly represented the contradictory essence of the human being.It seems that Nolan, Bale and Caine repeat together in "The dark knight", the highly anticipated sequel to his also splendid "Batman begins", in which duality also plays, of course, an essential role and already we are hoping, admiration, rendered all the viewers we have hallucinated with "The Prestige". Hopefully not be waiting very long.PS-does anyone know if the title of "The dark knight" refers to the famous graphic novel by Frank Miller, which has both excited readers of comics of the last twenty years?</body>
</review>
