<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Noche en el museo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film that gives the viewer exactly what it promises. Neither more nor less. A divertimento of white glove that makes having a fun time. A film see, smile and forget the progress.</summary>
	<body>Preceded by a huge promotional campaign, bulb and nurturing of the assistance to the cinema, has proven to be more effective, has been released "Night at the Museum", an entertainment which works perfectly as white comedy, aimed at all audiences.Playing with the most modern special effects and with an actor pigeonholed in its role of friendly, expert and well-intentioned post-adolescente 40s, "Night at the Museum" is a perfect example of screwball comedy in which characters are given call, shock and truncheons of all kinds, tartazos and smacks included, showing the classic humor always continues to charm.Anecdote: a mocetón, hired as night watchman at the Museum of Natural History realizes that the figures, animals and other natures killed, embalsamadas, desiccated, momificadas and enceradas of the Museum, when the night falls come to life, vitality, overflowing, chaotic and somewhat destructive dams. Skeleton of Tyrannosaurus Rex that both game gave Howard Hawks in "Bringing up baby" passing by the fierce Lions or those monkeys always horny and playful, the accumulation of clichés of the comedic film is as constant as it is successful.And little more can be said of a film that gives the viewer exactly what it promises. Neither more nor less. A divertimento of white glove that makes having a fun time. A film see, smile and forget the progress not uncomfortable does not bother to, not tired. And, interestingly, will be a film that beat box office records, something very enlightening on the apachorrada society in which we live, without wanting to heat the head, without wanting to see annoyed, zaherido or bothered in everyday well-being. "Night at the Museum", the technical perfection at the service of a film for children that, curiously, drag to masses of adult cinema. What was said. The sign of the times, that is how many of the viewers of this film also Iran, for example, to see "Apocalypto", "Flags of our fathers" or "The queen", to give three examples of films currently in billboard that talk about the things that we pass or we have spent in our recent history? That is the question.</body>
</review>
