<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film of smoke, impostada legerdemain, cold fabulation, everything that should not be good cinema of magicians.</summary>
	<body>To dovetail with the illusionist, compleméntandola without underfoot, both occupying different zones of a same narrative angle, the final trick (Prestige) are clamping on the Bulletin Board as a title interesting, worthy of a sober manufacturing and an absolutely splendid campus (Christian Bale, Hugh Jackman, Michael Caine, Scarlett Johansson). Directs Christopher Nolan, who delivered the lavish and elucidates Memento, insomnia thriller (with a very palatable and surprising Al Pacino and Robin Williams, in roles of a containment proverbial being who they are) and this latest installment of Batman, away from the cliché of the politics of Hollywood and heels, with fortune, to the more shrewd study of the characters and a conscious of forms departure classic superheroes to reinvent (did)(, I have no doubt) gender. Because in view of all this, the final trick (the Prestige) should have been a peliculón or, at least, a film with mimbres quality, entertaining, with enough references for the movie buff demanding and all commercial shrapnel for the consumer of film more passive, less delivered to find under stones Scorpions of genius.That hope blurs shortly move footage which to me I felt like confused, embarrullado, devoid of hook, cold maybe. It comes to spend with that of the magic tricks that once had been the "prestige", as they say on the tape, nothing is already relevant. And Nolan makes lavish tricks, brewing a vigorous staging that is not without bright elements (there are a Gothic tone, an aftertaste almost unhealthy by diving in the most perverse roots of revenge), but that falls (with noise, I would say) in the final stretch: when the hole cards are placed face-up and we are witnessing the rationalization of fantasy.Bale and Jackman are well below what we expect. Caine plays. Scarlett Johannson not just find the definitive role and languishes as ayudante-amante of the two magicians in a strange role, not just produce empathy in the Viewer.The magic and science not never matrimonian: repel each other. Everything that you love and for its magical then brings disappointment and disenchantment in the rational. Go into more detail would reveal the plot byways that make bearable (say than just bearable) (excessive) footage.Or what happens (not I have it clear) is that my entenderas have been today to a level below than usual, which also say that it is much, and whatever Nolan account and how account you I have been half. Without making effervescence in my brain. Without waking my intelligence. And we need to be very smart to watch a movie like this? I think that no, the truth. Intelligence, the fair. Only a stay awake, a wanting to catch the details, a not to abandon the plot because there is in excess, traps, tricks, how not, which then become simplicities of little wit, tricks of a writer that him has been the large excess matter and then, in the end, the trick failed close it as they send the canons of the magic, while we see the root, the seed, the secret.Bowie appears makes sure everything has a morbid plus: one cannot help (I, at least, could not, fascinated to see the great Duke white, the absolute genius of music, to the legendary Chameleon of the vanguard of the rock of the last three decades) feel a tingle in the pit of the stomach so that at the end of the film grabbed my bookshelf CDs and heard (of the pull) Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders of Mars... and oh my god, hence thanked him Nolan, magic, film that there is music and that perhaps the film has only served to remind me that there are perfect discs, sleeping the dream of waiting until that hand accomplice removed from its case, and introduces, greedy, deleitosa, sinfully in the player tray behind it allgrabs the potentiometer of the amplifier, monitors the family isn't too close and leaves that the decibels (say now that during appalling awhile) flood the air, disappear overnight, leaving in my memory jubilation and joy, love and reconciliation with the world and its barbaric. I've written film or I've written of the Bowie? Well I have it very clear.</body>
</review>
