<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Hollywoodland" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do a more than remarkable film to know the bitter back hidden under the? glamour? and the luxury of those golden years of cinema.</summary>
	<body>The dirt of the shining world of stars have not always washed at home. At times, the film industry has airy their own shames through what better do: movies. Probably on the cusp of this theme work is always the classic Wilder Sunset Boulevard (the twilight of the gods). Also Robert Altman (in the game of Hollywood) portrayed the misery of those directing the roost of this factory of illusions capable of generating so much garbage inside doors with acidity. Hollywoodland, first feature of the television Director Allen Coulter (12 episodes of the Sopranos and one of A six feet under, among other series, guarantee you), is also a story about these sinks based on the sad true story of the murder-suicide of George Reeves, actor who became famous for his role in the series the adventure of Superman.La strange death of Reeves to 45 years of age always lent to various scenarios. The? official? He came to say that the actor, embittered by his typecasting in the television role of Superman and after giving to finished his career as a film actor, decided to put an end to his life of a shot. But doubts never came to dissipate, and surrounding them tour the central nucleus of Hoollywoodland. A private detective without major cases on his table, Louis Simo (Adrien Brody), sees the perfect occasion to lift flight given the far-reaching media of the case in this investigation. But, as he explores the life of Reeves, more parallels can be found with his own personal drama: divorced his wife, with a son that little known and a mistress/Secretary that fool you. Thus, sequences of life of Reeves mingle with Simo and tone of thriller of the research with the drama of the histories of both characters.The work of Coulter in the realization is neat, but the best of this tape are magnificent interpretations of the cast. Starting with the best job in the career of Ben Affleck, an actor that some already doubted that it possessed such a condition. The Californian won the Volpi Cup and was nominated in the Golden Globe on a paper full of nuances to give life to Reeves, "an man? do says Affleck?" They called him?"Do the honest george?, and tried to always let move well to others, though in a sense it was to feel loved himself". Also adds the actor, who was thoroughly documented for his character, who "was generous and borrowed more money than actually had (?)" but was not perfect; "it was ambitious and impatient and may be something superficial." The rest of the cast, Adrien Brody is as well as almost always, something that is not news in his case, a gorgeous Diane Lane demonstrates that improves as actress as a good wine and Bob Hoskins returns to exhibit his talent for a usual role therein, of the fearsome big fish that does not threaten in vain. Do do in short, a remarkable film to know the bitter back hidden under the? glamour? and the luxury of those golden years of cinema.</body>
</review>
