<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I do not think that it is the best of any of the two, but it is a good film, especially if you're a fan of the war genre and you like e.g. La Delgada red line.</summary>
	<body>Flags of Our Fathers (2006) translated in Peru as the conquest of the Honor and Spain, more literally, as the flags of our fathers is the first part of an interesting proposal of director Clint Eastwood to tell the story of the battle of Iwo Jima (vital in World War II) from two points of view: the United States, which corresponds to this film and the Japanesethat befits the film letters from Iwo Jima.Miren the image of the poster. How many times have seen this image? I guess that many, then EE.UU. It is full of monuments that represent. I think that this photo of a group of soldiers working together to put the flag on a hill just take on Iwo Jima, is as famous as the first man on the Moon by placing the American flag. And both pictures have been accused of being mere mounts to the collective control and increasing the patriotic feeling. And it is that the images are so powerful.Flags of Our Fathers tells the story about is image and its protagonists through the voice of one of his sons, the son of the soldier nurse, John "doc" Bradley, played by Ryan Phillipe (crimes of the mind).Without like me nothing the war genre, I think that is a very good film, with characters well built and powerful and violent images, that show us as war has more victims than those who die in it.The film is based on the bestseller of James Bradley and Ron Powers that when Clint Eastwood read wanted turned into film. However, the rights had already been acquired by Steven Spielberg. After a while Eastwood and Spielberg crossed in a 2004 Oscar afterparty and Spielberg agreed to shoot the film as a producer if Eastwood was Director. And when Eastwood proposed filming the Japanese version of the matter also agreed. Good things can happen when two great together.I do not think that it is the best of any of the two, but it is a good film, especially if you're a fan of the war genre and you like e.g. La Delgada red line. For my part, I think that I will not see the counterpart, letters from Iwo Jima.</body>
</review>
