<review author="José A. Peig" title="Inteligencia artificial" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Intelligence is Artificial, Steven Spielberg, probably the most underestimated film of recent years, but now, since certain sectors moviegoers, is us it is warning is announced as a future masterpiece, a classic for posterity, a jewel squandered and America in our time.</summary>
	<body>The genre of science fiction is a suggestive instrument to explore the wishes and concerns of the human soul, especially within the framework of the space age, opening up an infinite number of possibilities in the creative field, a projection of fantasies or fears or an excuse to develop the potential of the new firing techniques, everything has been and will be. "Artificial Intelligence", by Steven Spielberg, is probably the most underestimated film of recent years, but now, since certain sectors moviegoers, is us it is warning is announced as a future masterpiece, a classic for posterity, a jewel squandered and America in our time. From the hand of science fiction more philosophical and poetic, never before abandonment and the realization of unattainable dreams had a treatment so direct, heartbreaking and felt in this story about an entity who dreams to become what is not, a distinctly religious idea and one of the basic pillars of a very dense conceptual framework. Our goal, however, is not give lessons in philosophy. Let us focus on the immediate content. Fairy tale twilight?. Metaphor about God and man?. Both things at the same time. The story is divided into three segments that offer a contrast at different levels: after the prologue that leads us on the philosophical discourse to develop, the first segment (the warmth of family, home, peace and security environments), second segment (the dangers of the world, the darkness of a forest, loneliness, violence), third segment (journey to the "end of the world")(return to the origin, end of the search). Different parties serve as a structure for channelling a vital process that encompasses various facets and levels of human existence, represented in the life of the niño-robot: its creation, of the initial rejection of the progressive acceptance of his family, the awakening of the consciousness that ama (imprint), the inherent dangers of being sensitive and aware (the idea that love makes us vulnerable)(, jealousy, fear of staying alone, the fear of death), the discovery of the differential fact and the search for a higher status (becoming "a child of truth"), the loneliness and the search for a meaning to life. As we can see, Spielberg moves in convoluted terrain, themes and critical reasons for a filmmaker who prefers the spectacle and excitement with a dense and complex content, in intellectual values. Now however, as we will explain later, in this case has the ability to combine all that so get to take it to the ground that you are interested in without too much mess up. It has been said and written many times, and is necessary to repeat it once again: the first segment of the narration, about the first forty minutes (from inception to the level which shows the image of David reflected in the mirror of the car) is a true wonder and virguería narrative, which is very useful as exemplary in all schools of cinema exhibition: it is an example of effectiveness and ability, a cinematographic language so devoid of unnecessary artifice as illustrative of the plot and emotional content that contains and unfolds along the first fragment. The story of a family who has lost his "real" son and adopts a "artificial" child, the progression from initial rejection in Monica (mother), appreciation and subsequent acceptance (process which culminates in an act so everyday as a dinner, a spaghetti hanging in the corner of the lip, which leads to spontaneous David laughter)(, a sign of humanity that ends with move to the family), the jealousy that accentuate the vulnerability of David, the misunderstanding and the most absolute helplessness depicted in this image of the mirror away gradually, darkens, becomes deeply dramatic. One of the most beautiful moments of the film (and one of the best moments of the Filmography of Spielberg), deserves special mention the imprint that glows in the consciousness of David through invocation and recitation of unconnected words: the hand of Monica in the neck of David, the hieratic and deadpan posture of the child against the expression of fear in the face of the mother, the time in which the face of David transfiguring from the hieratic empty feelings until sensitive of being aware that she loves and that, Furthermore, this will be his tragedy, knows that he loves. The wonderful frame of Spielberg shows us the embrace between mother and son in a central position, bathed by the light of a window. Concise visual imagination of Mr Spielberg, but in addition, direct, honest, efficient and simple, communicating what deserves to be expressed under a prism of intimate sensibility. Spielberg, is too often accused of being tear or "ñoño", big mistake, at least in the film we are discussing today, there is nothing more than sincere sensitivity. And which is it created, that go through the scene in question, among others. (Sure, most of the public and critics need to explain the difference between emotional manipulation and sensitivity). Without hardly dialogues, without explanation, reiterations or unnecessary underlined, through plans and frames containing the visual information needed to understand what is happening and understand why Monica thinks what think, why his thoughts on David begin to change, why the brother feels jealousy, why David feels different and needs a fantasy in the form of fairy tale to justify his desires. The huge visual expressiveness of Spielberg is also evident in the scene in which David submerged at the bottom of a swimming pool, after involuntary assault on the brother because of a fear caused by an excess of vulnerability in the invocation of the imprint, prior to the pain of the knife: the subjective camera puts us in the perspective of Davidalone and helpless with regard to human, waters which impedes that perception serve as a symbolic expression of his alienated State, the desestructuración-desconexión among his intimate world and the world of others. Then comes the general plan of the pool with David alone and lost in its Center, with open arms, hoping an affection has no, the perfect visual expression of helplessness. I said: there are so many the cinematic qualities of those first forty minutes that we would be eternal. The second part of the story, perhaps the most problematic, tells the adventure of David to find the blue fairy. In contrast to the home and family, after being abandoned, David confronts a dark and hostile world: the wolves that chase the protagonists through forest, the dustbin of the "Mecca", the Moon emerging threatening in a horizon of shrubs, the fair of the meat. A curious mixture of elements of science fiction and the clichés of the traditional fairy tale, although there is nothing that is fascinating beyond look subjective of each spectator. In this piece, the visual imagination of Spielberg is reduced to the possibilities of an atmosphere that generates a strange mixture between the cybernetic and the ensoñador: Tedy bear running through the hills in search of David, a cradle song that sounds from the top, the raucous rock at the fair of the meat. all this gives rise to many impressions and suggestions, but the decor isn't at the height of the material used. I.e., Spielberg, without losing the narrative strength, not maximized the chances of certain passages. The passage of the fair of the flesh, certainly grotesque, but if what Spielberg intended was to provoke empathy and drama in the mind of the Viewer, the failure is complete. The executed droids are reduced to a bunch of animated gadgets without a personality that is significant, therefore, fails to generate an emotional connection in this regard. This is one of the usual criticisms: the tone used by Spielberg in the passage of the fair of the meat is not appropriate, the characterization of the robots mutilated and tortured (?) is too banal, when no child, for a scene that would have a much more sordid tone. But look, the goal of the film, and the scene above a purported drama is the reflect that David is a robot unlike the others, he is the robot with a soul, the rest are junk. Precisely for this reason, the girl identifies David in the cell. As we see, although the scene of the fair of the meat will probably never us be satisfactory enough, Spielberg not deviates a bit of essential purpose. Gigolo Joe deserves a paragraph separate. It is not a character that has too much weight in the narrative, simply makes the function of accompanies David in their quest. But the truth is that its got, his couplets, the stunts and the cold bonhomie of its gestures hide a unforgettable character, or, if less, leaves a very good taste, although that is a character that integrates with the story picking it up with pins: look at how and where disappears from the narrative. I said: caught with pins. Ending the second segment, we have the impression that drags on too long, they occur too much surplus: the arrival to Rouge City, a futuristic variant of Blade Runner but brings nothing new to the narrative or the design, the visit to the well-known doctor of science philosophical fiction went to Disney's own iconography. The problem is not the well-known doctor, the problem is the design and the setting of the scene (the tone), very infantilizada and, consequently, devoid of that fascinating power to be the oracles, even more so the Oracle who shall indicate the path to the origin and the end. The reunion with Professor Hobby (the creator), which embodies the essential discourse: dreams and religious faith as distinctive attribute of the human species. The agony of David is the agony of the human being, that it wants to be more than it is and believe in things that do not exist, the great human error. David discovers his origin, as Adam facing the creator becomes aware of being the first of a new kind of droids. In this order of things is one of the most important meanings of the tape: somehow, "Artificial Intelligence" tells a process of expansion of the consciousness of the niño-robot, from the inert, artificial and empty life of a mechanical doll until the discovery of conscious love, resulting in the revelation of his true creator, its purpose and origin. It is not so much a religious movie as mystique. Devastating images of New York City devastated by waters accompany the loneliness of David. His encounter with the blue fairy in the submerged depths of the city, is not devoid of a great lyricism; its appearance between the darkness of the waters, and the image of the face of David that becomes one with the fairy blue reflected in the glass of the vehicle, is another great moment of visual inspiration, unifies to be he yearns with what desired, the beginning and the end of the dream. Many moviegoers have opined that the film should have finished at that point, with David front to the fairy of stone and cardboard, hoping for a response that will never come. They forget, in this case, that Spielberg is a filmmaker of dreams, and is a constant in his filmography: what reality can not give us, we can achieve it in the dream, in hope, in another life, in another world. Not in vain, Stanley Kubrick commissioned the project to Spielberg because he knew the story of Brian Aldiss to fit better with the sensitivity of the American director. On the other hand, we tend to think that David has a too one-dimensional facet, which does not correspond to the intended speech; i.e. at any given time, the stepfather of David says that's "if it is capable of love also may feel hatred". But it turns out that David is a loving being in essence, their actions are almost exclusively oriented towards the love and tenderness. Do exist, therefore an inconsistency between the discourse and the story? Is David a too flat character? In principle seems to be Yes, but let us not forget the scene in which David is facing one of its replicas; When it is aware if not the only, it tilting with violence against his counterpart. "It will never be yours". Jealousy are born of love, and lead to hatred. But it is nothing more than a timely moment, the character is not over curdling a complex profile. Although Spielberg meets a minimum with regard to the personality of David, not he ceases to be a too simple profile for a complex content and a thorny ground. This is one of the defects of the film. It is not that David is a character badly built in a functional sense, but the film would have been much better if had added you more edges, more ambiguity, more dynamism to its development. In certain aspects and passages of the film, the complexity of discourse and the plot reasons encounter with an address too flat (a complex content needs more than an attractive frame and some moments of pure sensationalism, to understand us). Following the rescue undertaken by a new group of droids, two thousand years later, David gets modified to the blue fairy stone and cardboard, and this, in another bleak scene, it cracks and reveals her falsehood. David discovers that the blue fairy is as artificial as himself. Metaphor of the human being against the false gods and the end of hope: that the gods can give us our dreams. Spielberg doesn't support the harsh reality and needs a happy ending. The last plot Pirouette hand of science fiction more toned, and has been widely discussed. Taking care that we are dealing with a metaphoric fairy tale, has no sense to say that such Pirouette breaks the rules of the genre or the overall tone; reproduce the life of a dead person recovering the information of his conscience in the fabric of spacetime is no more implausible than the fact of manufacturing robots endowed with consciousness. It is, therefore, nothing forced, and in addition serves to channel the history towards the end desired by the author, and in this area soon or nothing can be said the critic. Let us not forget; in the context of the fantasy genre, it isn't more courageous or has greater intellectual value a realistic ending to an idealized ending, we would be, in any case, speaking of two different intellectual equal speeches provided filmmaker respects the tone and laws with which this building his narration. You could even say that a happy ending is a creative act of value: Spielberg wants to succeed the hope placed in dreams, and thus shows it us openly. It is the nature of the work which will define the rules and criteria for assessment, and Spielberg is not intended to show a harsh resolution, but hopeful. The encounter of David with his mother, and the tears of one against the words of love that had always wanted to listen to, justify the Odyssey. It is the moment of happiness that articulates with the great moral dilemma posed in the prologue: how much responsibility requires the establishment of an entity capable of love, which needs a correspondence?. And yet, the end is not as happy as it seems: the last dream of Monica hope dies. Monica was just a memory recovered during a single day from among the thousands of times and memories lost in the cosmos. David, as a single specimen, with the human race has disappeared, only it is loneliness and sleep? That is the profound despair that it beats at the end: that there is no choice but to dream to live of the wishes, and ultimately, David is alone in a vacuum cosmos of any entity that may correspond to their nature. Halfway between hope and desolation, Spielberg concludes his story with an end of meaning polyhedral, building a lyrical work, sincere sensitivity, and the sense of helplessness that can get to experiment with the viewing of this film is unmatched with any other piece of the fantasy genre. Her beauty is beyond current and immediate perception that we now give him. They are analysts and fans of the future who placed it in the position it deserves. "Artificial Intelligence" is the current equivalent to "Blade Runner". I.e., a film of fantástico-filosófico genus which has been made very little case in his day, but will it become a classic and a work of vital worship. Time to time. </body>
</review>
