<review author="Puspus" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Which clichés abound, then Yes. Given some side pity, then also. That everything follows true whiff to eighties movie, of course. But Stallone is very decent as protagonist and very intelligent as director.</summary>
	<body>Direct and sencillota as a punch in the jaw, "Rocky Balboa" means the return to the screens of the unparalleled Sylvester Stallone. Undisputed star in the 1980s, tramp without direction in the 1990s and mysterious unknown today, the "Italian Colt" bequeathed us with this film his film Testament. And it is that the sixth installment of Rocky could well be understood, not only as the end of a saga, but also as the farewell of the venerable fibriliation voice actor. Not by another thing the movie is loaded with nostalgia. Nostalgia for a time that never again, where the box office always responded and worldwide chanted his name; Nostalgia for a face that had not yet shown the ravages of botox and the scalpel. Nostalgia, finally, by those muscles that were betraying him with the passage of time, to become the unfortunate flap now looking. As the old Balboa customers of his restaurant, Stallone gets tired in that first hour full of crepuscular dialogues, platitudes and cheap fussiness, but it is a toll to be paid so that the feelings overflowing in his exciting second half. And it is ringing the "Gonna fly now" and llenár you the eyes of tears, Lene. Which clichés abound, then Yes. Given some side pity, then also. That everything follows true whiff to eighties movie, of course. But Stallone is very decent as protagonist and very intelligent as director. Recover that old film for all ages, truffles of good advice and best feelings, and get the applause of the public in this impossible final match where, to not miss, there is no shortage or logos the PayPerView and HBO. The script is insane, we know it, but the movie unsuspectedly works and is so easy to digest that nobody get angry. Children, believe in fairies and not fuméis crack, tells it your dear Uncle Rocky.</body>
</review>
