<review author="Puspus" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unfortunately for Nolan, his new show isn't at the height of his ambition and presents numerous errors that tarnished, at least partially, its final result.</summary>
	<body>Something must have happened to Christopher Nolan to interest both by the characters tormented, set to fire by the death of a loved one. Both the protagonist of "Memento" and the renovated Bruce Wayne of "Batman Begins", passing by the Police guilty of "Insomnia", all are traumatized by the murder of someone close. And this is repeated with the nineteenth-century magician it nails Hugh Jackman in this entertaining "The final trick". They are the marks of the Nolan House. As the careful photography, the leisurely pace (sometimes too), the superb direction of actors, the segmentation of the narrative "tempo". and we cannot forget that, that vocation always play with the Viewer. "The final trick" has been conceived as a gigantic, monstrous, magic number. Michael Caine, at the beginning of the tape, already warns us: "I want that you are vigilant," inviting us in this way to participate in it. And from there, starts the function. Three acts: "The presentation", where the main characters of the story, their different characters, know your goals. "The performance", in which the script tricks begin to happen is and the story revolves, turns and spins until it almost gave of face to face against the floor. And finally, "the prestige", or what is the same: the conclusion, that last great trick that should leave with their mouths open and make us break out in a tremendous ovation. Unfortunately for Nolan, his new show isn't at the height of his ambition and presents numerous errors that tarnished, at least partially, its final result. To begin with, the personalities of the two magicians in question (despite being correctly interpreted) are seen very on top. Their motivations, their paranoia, aren't me real and take away this dramatic load to the film. Second, according to the mandatory nut laps are multiplying, merman also in credibility and capacity for surprise.Bad thing this for a complicated toy that should be exciting. But the greater failure of the film, what he denied that coveted applause, he resides in its last second, in that "chis-pún" in which Chris Nolan has based much of his film. The "Prestige" of this feature entitled "The final trick" probably yes do us open the eyes of astonishment, but I am afraid that it will not anyone satisfied.It is not acceptable that a film that has kept in a realistic line throughout its extensive footage is discovered, at its peak as an absurd sci-fi fantasy. This is a trap not deserved that loads the good presentation of the set. In this regard, Nolan is a bit like the character of Hugh Jackman: lacks magic but knows how to sell his show. We will see in the second Batman.</body>
</review>
