<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Noche en el museo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film devoid of ambitions beyond the healthy divertimento (very healthy) and some complicity with culture as a pretext.</summary>
	<body>Sandwiched in a suit of divertimento teenager or child, the film can entertain adult audiences, but I doubt that someone with true goer interest go to see it except that he carried the troop of kids, children, nephews, neighbors or the fourth primary class. Night at the Museum meets more than its playful task: there is a dazzling special effects-generous serving, a fast-paced script and a self-assurance, in general, welcomed in these times of very thought cinema even when recipients will be children (the hood, the Shrek or the Nemo were animated artifacts of dubious child affiliation because transpiraban nasty adult on many sides).Shawn Levy, before we knew by the Pink Panther or twelve at home is responsible for this film: moves by ground Subscriber, know the trade of Carpenter's fair attraction. We cannot demand you what you demand to Martin Scorsese or Todd Solondz. Levy joins this segment more genuine household consumption-oriented film validísimo: everything is festive, everything is left lead by mansa political correctness and, moreover, the script (which in its simplicity cela varied records and proposes a wide range of readings) gives a suggestive look through the history, although it is history walk at home and not to inquire beyond the greetings of the Romans or the rudimentary gestures of the men of the caverns. This simplistic pedagogy not abounds in cinema for children: at the exit of the film, one he explained to another that the Romans had a "terrific" army and that mammoths and dinosaurs (in its entendederas) had never coincided in the history. As it can be. The case is that a film, one without excessive pretensions of sustainability, had raised so sparsely regular dialogue that already only therefore by this unprecedented counterpoint, everything worth and not we could, with sincerity, battered so wise reflective exercise.Sad consequence would be that culture was by these filters yankees of popcorn and massive blockbuster: culture comes from other sides, or must come from other sides, but night at the Museum, at least raises a dialogue between reality and fiction that aims to link the more frivolous fringes of that culture, its limbs, but why not (in these times of libresco decay)(in general) less important.Ben Stiller makes great what he knows: putting faces, give his comic bis in generous portions. This poor father in distress delocalised worldwide, needs those nights in the Museum so that her son will take into consideration: this cheap psychology plus not disarm the fabulous fireworks of special effects when all the wax museum figures brought to magical life and campan at your leisure, anarchistic and stubborn, carrying their topics to hilarious ends: there is a scene (the best, no doubt) in which the night guard Larry acts as a psychoanalyst of Attila and makes it cry like a kid. Fresh air, missing makes.And if you don't have nephews, sons or relatives to young who give a great bit of film, you go. Perhaps not regret at all and leave rejuvenated as when those Saturday morning sessions made him feel that the world was perfect and it didn't get fooled by a story. A good: an absolute llena-cines (never on a Sunday morning session I have seen the film to which come so full, so alive, so full)</body>
</review>
