<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Más extraño que la ficción" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Imagine that a Santiago Nasar leave him read the principle of "Chronicle of a death foretold". The poor man seek desperately to Garcia Marquez that he changed the end, and hence also the title.</summary>
	<body>«The day that would kill, Santiago Nasar stood at 5.30 in the morning to wait for the ship that arrived the obispo.»»Imagine that a Santiago Nasar leave him read the principle of "Chronicle of a death foretold". The poor man seek desperately to Garcia Marquez that he changed the end, and hence also the title. This is what happens to the protagonist of "more stranger than fiction". will Ferrer discovers that it is part of a novel in which is going to die, but do not know who is the writer, so he visits a Professor of literature. The Professor shows you that you cannot change the end because the tragedy is a masterpiece with this ending.The question is often not openly raise, but each movie makes it between the lines. In "Infiltrated" Scorsese makes us suffer every moment for the fate of the Fink good and bad. Charges to one with a wrong decision, and however everyone applauds. In "Apocalipto", the protagonist has the death on the heels, a slip and Mel Gibson can kill him in every scene. If he is still alive, or if he kills him, he responds to a pact with the Viewer. An implicit Covenant. "More strange than fiction" is a discussion out loud about this Pact.When Will Ferrer discover that it is in a novel and attends the Professor he asks if it is a comedy or a tragedy. Depending on that one or the other, he's going to live or not. So says tracks that has two pages of your book. When the girl replied evil, puts a stick to the tragedy, when it seems that agree you, it puts it in the comedy. The girl does not understand the sticks in his notebook. This list is an occurrence.The idea of talking about narration in a narrative seems Andy Kauffman. Unamuno had it before but he let her in occurrence. "More strange than fiction" makes it dramatically, a discussion between a character and its author. The love story seems a formality, but ultimately endearing. The clock that gives unity to the matches is manual, but grace. "Stranger than fiction" it seems an exercise, but it works as a film.</body>
</review>
