<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Terciopelo azul" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lynch gives us a superb lesson in how to tell a story. Blue Velvet is Thriller author, shrewd x-ray of the idyllic America, spasm of the soul.</summary>
	<body>In the films of David Lynch there is always a moral mismatch, a kind of dissonance which, in extreme cases, gift to the viewer trained with a grandiose spectacle of perversion, of twisting, but Lynch never falls on the chabacano, licentious free consent frivolities, feelings of flat nature is never allowed: everything in it tends to the convulsive, everything hence estruondosamente to the anomaly. Therein lies its uniqueness and its unquestioned voice in the film the last nearly thirty years.His journey as a director is a random trip to gloomy of the human soul, a thorough tour by Vice, sin, solitude and anguish: as a Tom Waits, which acodara in the bar of a bar and sing / did the Angers of the body, the spasms of the soul and the darkness of the heart.Nobody as Lynch to transmit sensations, colors and environments: "the world is strange", says a character in blue velvet and us will not head the ear cut into the turf as a premonition of what is going to continue, this parade of characters on the edge of madness or crazy in possession of an exact awareness of his blunder.Provided that Lynch has control over the final process of their work, we should expect much height or products much depth, authentic, visceral, delivered from his Vertigo cinema. That happened with blue velvet.Lynch came to Dune, which was a huge disaster. Dino de Laurentiis, producer, vowed not to return to count on a haunted, as said in press and David sware to not have a man so short sighted, but probably neither of them expressed with this semantic sweetness. Everything was a lie: come to see in this film and the producer decided to assume his mistake in Dune and give the Director carte blanche to make the film wanted. Fortunately. A winding camera travels through the comfort of a comfortable street of family housing. We are in Lumbort, a timber town that seems painted to Lynch him recast with its palette of colors. Everything is security, placid security. The human ear in the grass in the garden, while Bobby Vinton reels the immortal Blue velvet, returns us to the brain of Lynch, his iconography rupture to his pact with the twisted. An old man has what looks like a heart attack: obstruction of its hose is the collapse of his heart in a great concise graphical decision-making.Jeffrey (Kyle MacLachlan) here begins to penetrate into the same hell. He will be the driver of that shared hell that makes her perfect world stable girlfriend (the here great Laura Dern) are tambalee to enter a world rogue of sadomasochism, cabaret and light of brothel embody Dorothy Vallens (Isabella Rossellini) and Frank Booth (Dennis Hopper), singer of club and crazed drug dealer, respectively. Jeffrey is the voyeur expressed surprise that, but unable to look the other way. His eye is ours: surprise, ours. Jeffrey, unwittingly, invests the real investigator: escruta visible to find cercenado, ears in the grass, which should not be, but appears.The sickly tone of color, the risky use of the music, which at all times directed the scale of feelings which are acquired, as the dark plot progresses, all the protagonists. Then Tarantino or Scorsese used with equal talent score, the soundtrack, but here the songs is masterful. What counts blue velvet is the mask of the idyllic America, its failure, the sweetened wrapper and bile flowing like a poison below, although Lynch gives us a superb lesson in how to tell a story (an abduction, say) and assuming, as dupes spectators, that the story could not have been told otherwise. I think that is the magic of a director. And Lynch him (at least here) is to a very great extent.And has one of the best endings I've seen: a sudden return to the place where we start, a denial to the tremendous about what we have seen. As if Tom Waits is lowered to tell us the numen which illuminates it and confessed us, between bourbon and puff of cigar, even though it says that not drinking and that already smokes, all the secrets of his heart wild, rotten and only. Trinan birds and the world keeps turning while we attended a malignant beauty slut session. The world is strange.</body>
</review>
