<review author="Raúl Rubio" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>They can spare you as about ten minutes of footage. Are you to decide if the movie is good or not, to my I liked, and what also narrated.</summary>
	<body>It is clear that I am not going to enlighten anyone at this point in the film if I make a comment about if Clint Eastwood (Million Dollar Baby) is a good director or not, is why what I am not neither annoy me because I lose the time, but if I can say that you for this film it has decided to not having a particularly spectacular castDespite lead it Ryan Phillippe (chaos), actor who I have mediocre but that also excels, and accompany him Paul Walker (the proof of the crime) of which anything is can comment, because that just squeal a couple of words on the tape. It is clear that Eastwood does not need nothing but shake his wand so that what logic would be a chaos begins to take sense if only, and I think it is, not for history which has, if not as, and from that perspective the account, many consider in the resemblance of the staging of another known film dealing also with incombustible WWII, but here there is not bitter that may be a war that is already counted in the other, in save soldier Ryan, here delves more, and is trying to throw a little bit of that background that covers the track central great circus show, bands and Fireworks, is not more than simply the great savior of Nazi-occupied Europecommanded by their great generals as they did something more than one century with its 7th Cavalry.The history that tells us, is as simple and everyday, as some soldiers converted into heroes in order to get and manipulate the masses to be able continue to finance its war, and so have the control and power needed to reach where today they have arrived. Gives us to see that once things were not so different from current, soldiers turned into heroes of the time, what they were or not, they end up being forgotten both by his country by his Government, because the important thing is not the individual, is dead or not in compliance with its duty to defend the homeland, the important thing is the goal that is marked, and we must achieve this it any way whatsoever, even if we have to play the bass drum and tambourine marking the passage of the "Heroes" more cowards of the conflict. The aim is that people go to war mass and also her finance for the benefit of those who declare, already said the enlightened absolutists, "Everything for the people, but without the people".There is only one aspect more than I'm going to highlight of the film, and is that in my opinion to Eastwood can spare you as about ten minutes of footage, those that agglutinate sentimentaloides stories of those that he likes his friend Spielberg. Sean you to decide if the movie is good or not, to my I liked, and also what narrated, what if I believe that it is essential, is to see its media naranja to make a global computation of outcomes.</body>
</review>
