<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apocalypto will delight all lovers of strong emotions and good cinema.</summary>
	<body>Mel Gibson returns to give us a lesson of film "Apocalypto" in this case. This actor, Australian director, many things can blame you, but no one can deny what his talent behind the camera. It is one of the best narrators that we can currently find, and their images have an amazing strength. If in his previous proposal revealed us the passion of Christ, and what life was like at that time, now shows the Mayan culture. It is visually spectacular, and must thank you shot in natural settings, and we can thus show more credibly the ups and downs of this civilization.Filmed in maya, and reaching the screens without bending, "Apocalypto" surrounds us since the first frames in a fantasy world, in which will be presenting us the different characters, with which convey us the message that fear is not going anywhere. Fear is a disease that corrodes inside and with that you can not live. Something that will have to take into account our protagonist, if you want to be able to continue enjoying their existence.After this start, us occurs to the other civilization, with which we will be the rest of the footage. Travel, slaves, prophecies, sacrifices, and finally, survival.Gibson shows us an amazing and thrilling end of film. A very physical film, where barely there are dialogs and introduces us squarely in the jungle, showing us the capabilities and limits of human beings to survive. There are several messages that can be drawn, since need us a God to guide us and take an appropriate course, that evil is among us and that we must overcome it supporting us and helping us in family. Also is the quote that opens the movie, which tells us that any great civilisation succumbs not by a foreign power but because previously has been destroyed inside.There will be people to draw other interpretations, but the main thing is that Gibson tells a story in an amazing way. It has strong, as moments that in "The passion of the Christ" which show us how hard and bloody that were at that time."Finally, there is a brutal picture (and not) by violence which takes place at the end of the movie and I am obviously not going to gutting.""Apocalypto" will delight all lovers of strong emotions and good cinema.</body>
</review>
