<review author="Plissken" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>'Blood diamond' is a higher than the average of the Hollywood of now, with an utterly protagonist Duo and entertainment checked with agility and brilliance. Pity that claims transcend undermine it in part at the end.</summary>
	<body>Many still wonder why Leonardo Di Caprio has not been nominated for an Oscar for his very good work in 'The departed'. The answer is, naturally, in 'Blood diamond', the last film of Edward Zwick, of profession his epic dramas, and excellent vehicle for performances of its two nominated players.In troubled Sierra Leone for 1998, the civil war is at its height. The thousands of diamonds smuggled out of the country financed equally to the Government troops and the guerrillas of the FUR and drown the people in his own blood. A South African soldier of fortune, a fisherman who seeks his family and a American journalist are caught up in the search of a large pink diamond, which can get them hell they are.Few buts you can be Zwick on this occasion, perhaps the same as always, but something less. His style (especially his best-known filmography) is defined from their first major production, 'Days of glory': staging grandiose, protagonists with own moral codes which are transformed in the middle of major conflicts, secondary that portray people foot. all very correct, very neat, that Yes. 'Blood diamond' is a return of the screw to the scheme, a dish with all the ingredients but a little bit more crude. And luckily, because talk about something so tremendous as the massacres in Africa or child soldiers needed to put all eggs in one basket. And Zwick surprised me by showing without fuss one of today's greatest atrocities, see kids of 10 years shooting entire villages without mercy. Good for him. But neither remata the task this time.The treatment of the extreme situation that recounts is right and shaky in the first half of the film. Of the hand of Solomon Vandy (arrogant, powerful Djimon Hounsou) know the tragedy of the millions of refugees who see how civil war destroys their lives on behalf of a revolution that never comes. Later, Danny Archer (excellent Di Caprio with included South African accent) emerges as the mercenary gambling and selfish, capable of sacrificing anyone with such to achieve its objective. Both are survivors, in constant danger and with different but complementary interests at times. Unlike them his attitude towards life (and death), but joins them his strength of will. And always they are in tension, distrust each other. Great couple, the greater success of the film.But there comes a time, after showing the horror of this war, in which the plot should move towards somewhere. And it is here where it appears the reporter Maddy Bowen (correct Jennifer Conelly), to operate the change in the heart of the antihero Archer. It is there where 'Diamond blood' loses bellows as violent action film to turn towards the humanitarian thinking. And while Archer continues without losing its essence of mercenary without scruples (see Di Caprio firing to point-blank to children by heavily armed to be, is shocking), the film will be preparing for a final third that follows the canons of Hollywood. It is effective, but stop risking morally. And the epilogue, well then, very consistent either with the real story, I believe that there is extra. As action movie, of course, I prefer barbarism without adulterating 'Apocalypto', by very incorrect to be.Technically, Zwick demonstrates that he knows to move in renditions of this style without problems. It also has the valuable help of Eduardo Serra in photography, Dan Weil in the design of production and James Newton Howard in music. The result is brilliant, of course.Total, which contrary to what suggested topical trailer, 'Blood diamond' is entertainment higher than the average of the Hollywood of now, with an utterly Duo (best in V.O., I sense) protagonist and checked with agility and brilliance. Pity that claims transcend undermine it in part at the end. A 7.</body>
</review>
