<review author="Noa" title="María Antonieta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Marie Antoinette" is a delight for the senses, a merit for this undervalued work.</summary>
	<body>If a trilogy on human pain, "Marie Antoinette" was closed with "Babel", gets the snap (not is if final) of the intimate trio of Sofia Coppola. Women looking for its identity, its role in the world.The Coppolina leads to sweeping passions and fierce hatred. But let us not forget that it marked a milestone in modern cinema, makes what pleases (Yes, thanks in part to his surname) and moves in their sauce telling the stories want you.His film is essentially contemplative, a film of images and sensations, which almost always to the pretentiousness by his pose gafapasta and trend it is cool, kitsch, psychedelic and other chachiguays words, but below this apparent superficiality of plastic beauties and semilíricas visions is a space for human feeling, that causes us a strange attraction to their characters and stories that they have.With "Marie Antoinette" the Hijísima to discover us the other side of the historical figure of the Queen Consort of France, leaving outside Palace historical events that were taking place on the eve of the revolution. It aims to that we live in Versailles with a timeless adolescent educated between cottons.The film starts in Austria when Marie Antoinette is moved to France with just 14 years to enter into marriage with the WIMP of Louis XVI. Already in Versailles, must adapt to mode of Palace life, where pomposity, the luxury and the waste of whims is provide on a regular basis. In the meantime see how he is unable to provide an heir to the Crown because of her husband (marriage takes several years to accomplish). Meanwhile the young will enjoy all the luxuries afforded in the company of a small Court of bad reputation makes the times of colleagues in raids in celebrations of champagne and strawberries, appetizing cakes, cut letters, majestic dresses and expensive shoes, hence his nickname as "Madame deficit". The packaging of this brave and controversial film is overwhelming, the art direction, sets, costumes, make-up, hairdressing. everything is sublime.Is my opinion about the movie will cause several fainting and many hurtful laughter but to my Mari Sofi convinces me, I like the stories you want to convey, that, Yes, the film is quite snobbish or I I swear by shoelaces in broken my Converse All Star white and empty of historical interior fittings to call biopic, but not empty of content that precious narrative moments abound, and therefore good film (see the ellipsis of the tables, the balcony scene or sequence of the end). I liked "Marie Antoinette", although not to throw rockets of pleasure, free corsets, historical figure he portrays brave to innovate in the Mise en scène, I like because Sofia Carmina Coppola continues sensations, not as timeless and successful as his major work "Lost in Translation", but get that his "Marie Antoinette" is a delight for the senses, a merit for this undervalued work. long live the cock!</body>
</review>
