<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If not for the final half-hour, we could be talking about a passable películilla.</summary>
	<body>After years of failure and no producers or managers who bet him, Sylvester Stallone has launched a recovery operation which aims to recover part of the lost glory.The first step in this process has been the realization of the sixth part of the adventures of the character more glory has been reported: "Rocky Balboa".Today it is hard to imagine it, but in 1976 Stallone, an actor and screenwriter unknown, conquered the Americans with the story of a small-time Boxer which presents the opportunity to celebrate the match of his life.It was the film United States, depressed after the defeat in the war of the Viet Nam needed. Stallone was nominated for best actor and original screenplay at the ceremony of the Oscars that year, something only achieved hitherto Charles Chaplin and Orson Welles with "The great dictator" and "Citizen Kane" respectively. The truth is that over time, these comparisons sound ridiculous but it was.For his return, Stallone has opted not to take risks and bet on insurance retaking the scheme of the first Rocky, at least at the beginning. Indeed, the first hour is quite more dignified than be expected and moves in a field not far from the independent low-budget drama. Thus, with containment, is how accomplished Stallone the best moments of the projection.The trouble is that in the final half-hour decides that you have to be satisfied to a certain type of Viewer (who cannot be satisfied so? I wonder I) and begins a montage chaotic, confusing and meaningless that eliminates completely excitement that could raise the more than predictable outcome of the tape.If not for the final half hour, could be talking about a passable películilla, despite its flaws, but size final nonsense, and the fact that over no auction history definitely (to do this better that I had not done anything) do me tip the balance towards a clear hold.</body>
</review>
