<review author="Iñigo" title="El aficionado (amator)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>How far can a camera get? You have the permission moral filming everything that your lens can be seen?</summary>
	<body>One of the first films of fiction that addressed the genius Kieslowski. During all the footage you can see its special approach to film, still a very different work and less aesthetics and poetic than what would be later. It is a simple structure, but his reason is quite complex and can lead to various ramblings. It is not surprising that for many, in a first viewing, be something difficult to follow and experience a slow development which does not leave guess what Management intends to take or what tries to explain us. And is that most of Kieslowski films have their ultimate meaning once finished. At the same time that you start to raise the film, reflect deeply on it and attach it to the real life is when get to understand the way the director wanted to draw. Despite the above-mentioned difficulty, "The fan" is probably the most direct work of Kieslowski. Some dialogs were written between the director and Jerzy Stuhr, actor of the film (Filip). And the result was a film of clear autobiographical character. Kieslowski turn the camera towards his own person, is something that all fans know. Always makes it a very subtle form, so that the viewer itself can investigate, since initially not noticing it. Never shows, simply whispers. Each and every one of his works speak of portions of his personality, and in a comprehensive manner, all look the same direction: the freedom and love. Drawn both in various ways, but always as a backdrop. And "Amator" is no exception. On the contrary. The protagonist us gets on the skin of a filmmaker in his first steps, with its virtues and defects, its facilities and difficulties. Obviously, although never openly recognize it (never spoke of his own person), all footage refers to their complicated early, their moral fears and confrontation of ethical principles that always referred at the time of filming. In many interviews he claimed that usually fell him wanting to leave his films without ending, it could not shoot real tears of the actors, who was unable to portray their suffering (paradoxically - a word that is repeated in the work and person of the Polish director-, did it better than anyone) that regarded this as an attack on the intimate life of people, and that their moral principles were on a tightrope on numerous occasions. And this is something true in a social and political framework such as the Poland of the time. Censorship and communism could be used against persons filmed any question in films and documentaries. Communism spoke of freedom, but free will was nothing more than a lie. A utopia. The fact that the Polish director previously shot documentary foreshadowed the reason for many of their moral constraints and internal struggles. For this reason, Kieslowski always posed the difficulty of filming, the right to exercise as a kind of God to translate the reality in his works. How far can we get our morals? Can we record something that can be used against the people? Can we shoot a real death? No should we let people die without that inner peace is downgraded?Thus, the film is about the vicissitudes of a person which starts with a camera only to shoot your baby, to take its own micro-mundo and hide it in your family. Not that the world sees. But it will gradually immersing in the world of the filmmaker, shooting documentaries, recording movies. And its moral and human principles are called into question. When it comes to show the public their concerns to life real main problems arise. How far can you go shooting?The film is ideal for filmmakers "amateurs", in order to understand the complexity of filming and to apply certain techniques, not just mechanics a bit, but also human. The axis of "El fan" could live together as regards the power of a camera. Its power to display, but also its inevitable to destroy. So the film will masterfully developed, starting with the innocence of a beginner and continuing with his shyness and doubts, all this resulting in destruction and loss of everything that loves. It is as if the camera subyugara everything that concerns the character's real life, as if the lens has the power, through fiction, alter reality, to damage. Therefore, it moves in special way the way that Filip loses his family, his work, and one of his friends. Because of him? Of them? From the camera? This only will you discover when turn the lens to itself. Then you will understand everything filmed, his work starts and ends in his own person. It means that decisions should not be taken lightly, that the cruelty and humanism must live together in each and every one of our relations. The world fades away to her around, but then, in the solitude of his loss, may know that the sole owner of his life must be himself. He is only responsible for its own acts, never of outsiders. Freedom always present in the work of Kieslowski. In this work, in addition to merge the pessimism of knowledge and the optimism of the desire, we can observe that Polish director boasts their new political and social ideologies. Censorship is present on several occasions throughout the footage with the co-worker of Filip, with her daughter, surrounding him in his everyday life. The co-worker is the ideal example of ethical and moral film doubt. Use as a means to a person, to move, or simply show the reality as it is, portraying the life of a person with difficulties. But then not you are using?It is obvious to anyone listening speaking to Kieslowski, many times you hurt filming scraps of reality through the camera, he considered it too dangerous and powerful environment. I could not decide on the realities of such persons, flatly stated that he had no such right. In addition, as I said, all of that could be used against people who was in charge of the project or simply appeared in it. The opening scene in which the Hawk attacking a defenseless bird is a clear example of the concerns of Kieslowski in those times (of which in subsequent years renegaría). He is a clear metaphor (remember the nightmare of Irka) which reflects the struggle between that has the power and those who are below, the fight between the carrier of the camera (a kind of power that allows to play with the filmed) and the characters of that reality are filmed. Characters who, like the bird, can be damaged by this filming. The eternal struggle between the individual (the director) and collective (real-life). Always present in the film moral struggle. In this fraught with social and political context of censorship, his documentaries did rather than rummaging in a wound that it considered very deep inside (affected him personally to an extent that made change radically the way they express themselves publicly). And, on more than one occasion, the eternal question of "who really belongs the film" assails us (something that also happens in the present, no mistake). Who has the ultimate decision on final details of the film? It is clear that that invests the money (when there is no other way to obtain it), commercially, had the last word (in the case which concerns us at least). And more in such a situation, which again emerge feeling appearing in more films of Kieslowski that we are puppets that we pendemos of a thread. But this thread can be moved by our will. There, in the end, is something that is yours, owned by Filip: their own learning, the knowledge that he is only responsible for what record when he appears in that environment. With regard to the technical level of the film, the cast large unknown that scratch at high level. Especially Jerzy Stuhr, who already appeared in different recordings of Kieslowski as "The Calm" or "Decalogue". It is admirable how Kieslowski makes so much with so few resources, with an absolutely aseptic projection, no effects or shock of any kind. A clear visual limitation, but is at a segundísimo level and not the result of the work more expensive for nothing. It lacks the visual magic of "The double life of Veronica" or the "Three colors" trilogy, but it is entirely logical because of its budget. "Camera Buff" was the film that launched Kieslowski to success (very relative and limited in space, by then), and despite the shortcomings already commented, enabled you progress in the cinematographic field and research in the human soul, in deepest feelings, already by a precocious, musical and poetic aesthetic. In short, a work very interesting to get fully into morality and ideology of a filmmaker. Maybe it is difficult to savor in its fullness in a first viewing, but if we make forced reflection that it deserves, we will arrive to participate in its depth. It may be the only point against the same, it is a type of film that you don't enjoy the first time, because you do not know exactly in which direction we want to take Kieslowski. Fact does not assert, for nothing, that is the most complex film of the late Polish director. The legacy of Kieslowski is something cinema appreciates and needs (especially to remind us that the era in which burst was one of the poorest for which has become the seventh art) and that, in its style, anyone can recover. For many, it is the masterpiece of the so-called movement in Poland as "cinema of moral concern", of which Kieslowski was one of its fundamental banners, along with the initiatory film covering the criticism that concerns us. The Viewer is which has the last word and be granted (or not) meaning to the film, as in ethical pedantry or forklift reflection. There is no other carrier of the camera other than that of our own lens. </body>
</review>
