<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Miguel y William" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ines Paris paid with Miguel and William profound tribute to the two largest geniuses of world literature.</summary>
	<body>The comedy has always been one of the most cultivated in the Spanish film genres, and indeed, some of the greatest works of our cinematography are comedies. Through them, many of the larger Spanish filmmakers have developed their ingenuity, some dodging censorship under the innocence of laughter.However, in recent years, comedy is a rare bird in the national scene, with the exception the uncouth and rude examples that predominate in the genus worldwide. Daniela Fejerman and Inés Paris have been responsible for two of the best comic works of recent years, and now comes the first work solo of one of them, Agnes Paris. First and foremost, Agnes Paris honors with Miguel and William a deep two elders geniuses of world literature, two privileged minds of the Siglo de Oro: Miguel de Cervantes Saavedra and William Shakespeare. It does imagining a hypothetical encounter between the two, at the beginning of the 16th century, I find that it will be possible thanks to Eleanor (Elena Anaya), daughter of a wealthy merchant, looking for an author to write a work for her and thus to fulfill his wish of becoming an actress. Despite the general tone of comedy which has Michael and William, Inés Paris is also a portrait of the Castilla grim and dominated by religion and superstition, where women were regarded as second-class citizens; In short, an outline of that full of misgivings newly unified Kingdom with Aragon, the embryo of the Spain that we know today. In this aspect, is inevitable comparison with some great Super production era, located a century later in time, and let to the understanding of each what movie comes out victorious in the lid. Turning to the tape, it's a relative comedy, with some very humorous moments, although it is those who are with a permanent smile, sometimes bittersweet. Miguel and William is a proposed fresh and different from the typical stories prefabricated about great authors of that Hollywood cinema era we used to give. The script is flexible and original, and one of their greatest strengths are constant references to the not yet written works of the two literary geniuses. The film has good pace, as it requires a comedy, and its precise footage makes that not become heavy at any time. The technical aspects are very careful, among which highlights a great art direction, which makes credible historical reenactment. Between an excellent cast (what about José María Pou or Geraldine Chaplin), highlights a radiant, fresh and fun Elena Anaya, confirming his great interpretive skills, and Juan Luis Galiardo, than anything more come fills the screen, and is impossible to imagine someone more in the skin of the one-armed man of Lepanto. It also draws attention to Carolina Lapausa, young actress tanned in the theatre which will give much to talk about in the future. Miguel and William is an entertaining film, that will make the viewer have a very nice time, but that above all serves as a great tribute to two geniuses who, coincidentally, died the same day of the same month, in the same year. And as I wrote one of them, well is it just well.</body>
</review>
