<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Shin Chan ¡Los adultos contraatacan!" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pure trash in which a child apologiza all possible swearing before the impassivity of the agencies which then boast of protecting minors and defend their interests. But of course, it is always easier to blame the prevailing slavajismo in many schools teachers...</summary>
	<body>If were not enough withstand the series on a national station mornings and in more than one of the thematic channels, they now move back to the cinema to the nasty, rude, poorly educated and uncouth Shin Chan, that disgusting child that makes getting drunk, showing their intimate parts and making constant obviously a way of life. In an era in which has even set a schedule protected for children (where have place all the clunkers programs which are dedicated to discuss who has more silicone or challenge people to demonstrate to a machine with who have been lying), must not tolerate the existence of these productions.Frankly I do not know what you are children to these drawings. They are poorly made, the stories are absurd and instilled values of more negative for some minds in training. This great fame of the bug it is attributable to the scoundrels of the programmers of television stations, which seems not to have children, or they must import them very little. Anything goes to get audience. The absurd argument consists in bringing to Shin Chan to lead a group that aims to counter a gang dedicated to drugging the adults so that they behave like infants. Many aberrations are committed under the guise of freedom of expression, and one of them is allowing the issuance of this garbage. But no Government is capable of risking him wary of retrograde to a measure that would protect the mental health of children. Also have much blame some parents who allow their children to bathe of this dirt. But of course, if the child is problematic, it is easier to blame the teachers.</body>
</review>
