<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Noviembre" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film of high level of Spanish film that shows that a good idea can have a low budget. Social criticism that makes us feel very alive and shows us a world unknown to most. Of essential impossible and utopian utopias.</summary>
	<body>The first time I had contact with November was thanks to the video store in the neighborhood, dead and buried long ago. It was one of those tapes that you see for your own quota of patriotic cinema, that you take by not find anything you want less, or that you have a silly day and you want to redeem the world. Now her I longer have, given that it left me very perplexed, I needed to have it. As an anecdote, not I realized that was a documentary invented until near the end (neurons, listen to me!).The film is Alfredo (Oscar Jaenada) which is a murcian young arrived in Madrid to study fine arts. Shortly after being in school, is giving account there will not learn what the want. He is interested in another type of art, an art that really reaches the public, away from commercial, that you you can find anywhere, anytime. Ultimately, a free art, subject only to the creative abilities of the authors. Little by little, his idea is gaining momentum to form a theater group that strangest and most original film call November. what. How to burn it is documentary, although what counts is invented. A bold person would realize nothing more start, given that the dates do not agree, to me it took me nearly ninety minutes. The argument is very original, showing some utopian ideas carried the end getting a despiertar of the senses. The cast of actors say he is taken, on the one hand consecrated which are the documentary and the other young people, who are curious to see the evolution that have followed. On the negative side, it has a small loss of pace, perhaps caused by an excess of representations.In short, film of high level of Spanish film that shows that a good idea can have a low budget. Social criticism that makes us feel very alive and shows us a world unknown to most. Of essential impossible and utopian utopias.</body>
</review>
