<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A magnificent Ribbon in all its audiovisual and interesting scaffolding in his account, clearly divided into two.</summary>
	<body>"A great civilization not is conquered from the outside until that has not destroyed itself from within", with this quote from the French historian w. Durant starts Mel Gibson's new movie. The prologue to a tape which is more crushing by its visual power is that his underlying message condensed in the previous quote. A risky bet by a director alien fashion industry or commercial interference. Because you have to be very out of all this to make a film about the end of the once powerful Mayan civilization, do so in yucatec and with a cast of actors without previous experience recruited from Mexico, New Mexico, Southern California, throughout Central America and Canada. And the result is a magnificent Ribbon in all its audiovisual and interesting scaffolding in his account, clearly divided into two: the presentation of the tribal life of a village, and the destruction of it at the hands of an invading force decimated by diseases which, with AWE, blamed the fury of their gods.Before that point, Gibson makes an approach with greater desire for possible verismo to the daily life of the members of a Mayan village: dedicated to hunting and raising their children. Take your time the film is to describe the life in which respect for the laws of nature and elders are revered as a source of wisdom. But the seeds of a terrible fate is already planted in the prologue when Jaguar Paw (Rudy Youngblood) provides for a fact that the restless during a day of hunting. For the first time in his life the fear seizes him strangely; an unpleasant feeling that his father warns him severely as if it were a plague can infect his people.And with fear he will attend the Viewer to the savage destruction of the village of Jaguar Paw. That's where a second part of the story begins more familiar to the Viewer, with the typical structure of a tape of action but, in this case, wrapped all over it by a few powerful images shot with the nerve who handles with absolute dexterity the language of cinema. The wealth of resources that are shot persecutions and struggles are hardly unique. And still not disappears in this part of the whole poetic halo.In this adrenalítica part of the footage, Paw will attend to the cruel destruction of his people and to the terrible neglect after being captured all adults. They will be driven to a large Mayan city in full decline, hit by the disease, corruption and slavery. Women will be sold as slaves, while the men will be driven to a great pirámide-altar to be sacrificed as offerings to Kukulkan, the great God of the Sun, who beg for an end to drought and pests. The fate, in the form of eclipse, saves the shoes to our protagonist, who has a powerful reason in his village to fight for his life until exhaustion.As if it were a hunt in which the roles of Hunter and prey invest constantly, Paw will be prosecuted by his captors once get escape. In this part, the general tone of the film, following the explicit violence is heightened. A violence that has caused many controversies, not only for being excessive to repulsion, but because those who are considered to be heirs of the past qualify the film as a defamation of the Mayan civilization.I do not know to what extent historical accuracy has faltered for succumbing to that side as 'gore' of Gibson. For example, in the article that link they talk about that describe "the Mayans as practitioners of human sacrifice,." to get the heart of the victim in a public spectacle at the top of a pyramid This was a ritual not maya and Aztec, a well-known fact for any student of Mesoamerican history (..) "." However, the story as a whole is more than notable and in his epilogue remacha the argument expressed in the appointment of Durant.</body>
</review>
