<review author="Chuchi" title="V de Vendetta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You can get to like even to those who do not read comics</summary>
	<body>Provided that we are going to see a movie based on a comic we fear that they have changed many things for the original. Later, depending on the quality of the film we can be more or less comfortable in the seat, and it is that if the movie is good always concessions can be made. This is what I think happens with "V for Vendetta". At the time I di graphic novel a note of 9'5, the highest of which I have taken from this blog on movies, books or comics that have enjoyed (or not). And in fact, I expressed my doubts about what might come out on the big screen.As well, my movie I liked, and much; Despite some negative reviews that I had read out there went forward to film. And while it is not as good as the comic (it was very difficult, admit it) Yes it is entertaining. I have to say that the character of V hooked me from the first moment, and while they change some things on the comic (not desvelaremos what) at many times the things happen as seen in the work of Alan Moore. Obviously, omitted a number of details that would have been very well, and in other cases has been very on tiptoe, which gives the film an excessive speed (its main drawback). And it is that in a matter of two hours they narrate to us facts that occur throughout a year. In addition, without solution of continuity, or abysmally type "three months later" constantly, that had Yes, slowed the emotion.The performance of Natalie Portman to my I liked, and I think that this is her you can desencasillar of her role as Amidala definitely. Shocking, and impressive especially since the spectacular "shaved". Hugo Weaving, the remembered Matrix agent Smith or Elrond in 'The Lord of the Rings'. because the truth is that it was very difficult to interpret a role where not seen the face in no time. Their gestures should be expressive enough to convey the desired emotions, and it succeeds. That Yes, we must say that it would have been very well see the original version to listen to his intonation, his voice. but it is at least the dubbing is very good. Really, get what is sought, by far: get excited, get involved with a guy who is retarded but that arouses sympathy from the beginning.On the other hand, I can tell you that I saw the film with people who had not read the comic and film caught them in offside in this pair of unexpected twists paste during the plot, he surprised really, so this film can get to like even to those who do not read comics.Highlight two things to finish: it shows the hand of the Wachowski despite not directing, even with the famous "Matrix effect" sometime. But in my not caused laughter which seems to have been caused to other persons. On the contrary, I took it as a nod, and in addition, do not abuse it. And the soundtrack to Dario Marianelli has seemed very good to the film. Thrilled in the moments that should do it. well, I've already done with her.In short, it does not reach the comic, but I liked it much. So I I do between the 7'5 and 8. I'll be benevolent, not as some university professors.</body>
</review>
