<review author="Silvia" title="María Antonieta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The final product has no quality that might be required to the creator of the magnificent Lost in translation. In short: a history that not just boot and once gets it just half gas.</summary>
	<body>Luxuries, champagne, jewellery, scandals, gossip, culinary, clothing feasts made with the finest fabrics, dances and festivities until sunset. The winner of an Oscar Sofia Coppola's new film reflects perfectly the excesses that lived at the Court of Versailles in the 18th century, an extreme luxury radically different from the deplorable living conditions of the rest of the French population, a luxury that led to doom to the monarchs of the place.The story, Starring Kirsten Dunst and Jason Schwartzman, focuses on the figure of Marie Antoinette, a woman who had what quickly leaving his childhood to become Queen of France. The film begins with the journey of the girl of his Austria home to the Court of Versailles where her fiance was waiting for marriage, a marriage which would be satisfied the political interests of both countries. But such an Alliance would not be effective until not born the heir of the Crown, a child that would take to birth due to the powerlessness of the Prince. It's a film risky as close to the 18th century, usually represented in very straitened way. And it is that Kings can also be impotent, although the official history is generally too complacent and tend to fudge a little reality to avoid display less convenicionales according to what. But Soffia Coppola dares to present us a vision very personal and realistic of what happened at the time of the opulent French court.The setting of the Court is perfectly recreated, spared on costumes or show all that opulence and recreating at levels notably long? very in the style of the Director - to appreciate every detail perfectly. Now, we need to ask is really essential for the understanding of the plot almost exact repetition of some scenes. The first hour of the film is completely redundant as that is an unnecessary Recreation: is necessary to repeat three times a sequence to make clear the lack of sexual understanding among the Princes?Another controversial point is the soundtrack of the film, we are accustomed to associate a type of music to an era in particular. In this case it opts for a soundtrack great but totally inadequate, according to my point of view, for the kind of film in which we find ourselves. The soundtrack includes groups such as The Strokes, The Cure, New Order and Phoenix, Siouxie And The Banshees modern. While it is true that sometimes some songs not squeaking so much, others seem to completely out of tune (as happens in the dance scene). As regards interpretations, Kirsten Dunst seems to have stalled in their role of superficial teenager. Indeed the role of a Queen who evade their responsibilities and problems in a frivolous and wasteful way look that it comes as a ring to the finger. Of the other characters there is nothing to highlight given that they are a mere accompaniment of the protagonist. However, what is commendable is the will of the Director of experimentation and reinterpretation of history, the problem is that the final product does not have the quality that might be required to the creator of the magnificent Lost in translation. In short: a history that not just boot and once gets it just half gas.</body>
</review>
