<review author="Silvia" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Christopher Nolan gives us a story perfectly set and twist of amazing script which shows the danger of the obsessions, which can lead to tragedy.</summary>
	<body>"Every great magic trick consists in three acts." The first is called 'The briefing': the magician shows something that seems ordinary, but of course,. It is not. The second act is called 'The action': the magician makes the ordinary is transformed into something special. Now, if you are looking for the secret. "you will not find, is why there is a third act called 'The Prestige': this is the part with the unexpected twists, where life hangs on a thread, and then you see something shocking that you had never seen before". With these words he explains Michael Caine the functioning of the shows of magic at the beginning of the film The Prestige, but that has reached our screens with the title 'The final trick' (the Spanish horrendous translation).Two magicians (Hugh Jackman and Christian Bale), both the same wizard and colleagues initially, apprentices begin to hate after a tragic accident. Their rivalry to get the best magic trick takes them to try to boycott constantly, this obsession to be the best you will have unexpected consequences. A struggle for achieving professional success that will make us ask ourselves every moment what character is less negligible until we realize that they are morally just as petty.Obviously masculine interpretations (Jackman, Bale and Michael Caine always correct) take the leading role. As in the case of many directors, it seems that Nolan continues to trend to reducing the female characters who become mere objects of accompaniment of the protagonists. Scarlett Johanson seems to have the sole task of wearing his corset in the film. Only the character of the wife of Bale is granted a role in which they can Excel more (not too).In what perhaps fails the film is in the enjoyment of the shows of magic because the Viewer is too busy attempting to decipher the trick to fool him. In addition, the fact that the Viewer is explain the trick of almost all the shows (less than the most important, obviously) subtract emotion to the matter. Something that was not the case in the illusionist. Another problem is that at times the film becomes something repetitive, that it takes many turns on the same idea of the obsession to know the final trick.Do however, the script no longer surprising that the director is always saved? as the Magi - an ACE in the sleeve to keep the attention of the Viewer. The film perfectly fulfills the role of any show of magic: constantly mislead a viewer throughout the film which will be wondering what will happen despuésLa film and laughter hides a terrifying message: to succeed in life everything is lawful. The end justifies the means for these magicians that are worth of deception and manipulation to achieve their goals. An aggressive fight to reach fame, to be recognized as the best in society. A competitiveness that do not understand friendship, love or any other aspect that is not related to the social prestige. A fight in which endangers the own personal relationships and even the physical integrity of the competitors.Christopher Nolan gives us a story perfectly set and twist of amazing script which shows the danger of the obsessions, which can lead to tragedy. As universal feelings as the envy, resentment, competitiveness and ambition are experienced to the limit by the two protagonists until its moral destruction. Because the road to the success of the two protagonists is also the path towards their personal destruction.</body>
</review>
