<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Quo vadis, baby?" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do Quo vadis baby?, in spite of its limitations, no longer a worthy film of intrigue and mystery</summary>
	<body>In film, like everything else in life, the best one can do is not to pigeonhole, people did not know in advance what's new that will offer a director. Thus, if you have a radical change of registration, no one will be surprised drastically. And this is the case of Gabriele Salvatores, with his latest work, Quo Vadis Baby?, surprises both to public criticism, since it's a history of mistereio and intrigue, with dramatic poso that Yes. Italy the film has been a great success, so much that it is planned to do a television series from the character. Giorgia Cantini (Angela Baraldi) is a detective ruda, scruffy and almost social life, until he receives a package which will give a turn to his life. The package contains the newspaper his sister Ada (Claudia Zanella) recorded on video tape, and Giorgia searched them a reason to explain the why her sister committed suicide 16 years ago. Soon, Giorgia discovers that the seemingly perfect life of Ada was not such, and had a lover, the mysterious to perhaps involved in his death. Thus begins a search that will make Giorgia reconsider his life and face the truth that has been hidden all these years. Gabriele Salvatores offers us a proposal interesting and attractive, at least in principle, and not only the typical story of mystery. Unfortunately, in a few minutes that attraction is diluted, the pace seems to stop in the space time continuum, and the tape falls into the predictable and the obvious. Salvatores navigates between two waters, between the pure and simple thriller and social background, the message that contains the film, and this dualism ends up significantly affect the story. Do Quo Vadis Baby?, despite its limitations, it is still a more than worthy film of intrigue and mystery, it will keep entertaining the Viewer, but that he will forget her five minutes out of the film.</body>
</review>
