<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Memento" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Polymorphic, quite intelligent, constructive, great film.</summary>
	<body>Movies with plot lines apparently dispersed in the end converge have never been my movie fan devotion santo: occasionally, the director just delivering with greater vigor to the formal pirotecnica than to refined and consistent thread natural things.Pulp fiction did the miracle of my reconciliation with that film divergences, looks that cross and revoked destinations just affiliated with the same narrative structure.Christopher Nolan in Memento is a recommended exercise of rewinding to know, at the end of the movie, what happened at the beginning. Far that this resource probably unnecessary, excessive ballast the final result of the film, here it catapult it to absolute levels of dramatic depth so that Memento is not conceived unless everything is so so abrupt.This abolition of the temporary line sits on the very nature of the character: Leonard Shelby (a dedicated Guy Pierce) suffers from a disease that makes him impossible to remember more recent events. This reality fractured in the mind of Leonard is the fractured reality of film: his obsession with dismantling the chronological level and fatigue to the Viewer (blessed fatigue) with a puzzle of Cartesian aesthetics closer to the literature of Cortázar as of the writing of the most utilitarian Hollywood.Go to the topic of the narrative deslavazamiento, insist too much in his amnesia as engine of criminal investigation, is subtracting hits, underestimate a very elaborate exercise in composition which leaves the obvious open fields, the doubts necessary so that no evidence is blunt and all agree to the fragile territory of speculation: we do not know for sure if the murderer (John g.) dies everytime Leonard da with a John G., but better not to reveal more of the plot, which is sufficiently esquinada, intelligent and perverse to catch our attention (and then our surrender without conditions) during these two more than recommended hours of film.Hybrid film between the eighties video and film noir of school, Memento is the Chronicle of a moral imbalance, the history of a revenge (the wife of Leonard is murdered and raped). Was filmed in a short month and despite receiving an excessive number of poor reviews (remarked the fact the plot hubbub prevented acquire a sharp knowledge of where was the story, which I felt was obstacle for take the film seriously as I wrote at the beginning of this review), won the battle of the public and is today, so few years after its premiere, cult film by the very original in its approach.Only we who lost, writes Jorge Luís Borges masterfully. Leonard has the physical object of photography, epidermal writing he better of prontuario actions: the routine as a method of composition of the reality. And such an inventory of resources must, in addition, guide you through the tangle of the (bizarre, polyhedral) research that leads to reveal us reason why we have at the beginning of the film a man with his head open and who was the murderer and rapist of his wife resulting than at the end (or principle) warned that perhaps (and I'm not counting anything relevant) everything is a Baroque puzzle in which the Editor knows in advance that the missing piece not It is on the table, but in his pocket.</body>
</review>
