<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Ases calientes" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>My desfavoritismo for this film being clear, I must say that I do not believe that you go you poorly at the box office because their dynamic Visual games tend to be digested quite easily by the adolescent population.</summary>
	<body>There are arguments that require a lot of violence (the Godfather, 1972) and violence without any kind of argument (a Clockwork Orange, 1971). This section could include the last film by Joe Carnahan, "Hot ACEs", alleged action comedy where we can find a deal with such familiar faces such as Ben Affleck, Andy Garcia, Ray Liotta or singer Alicia Keys.La narrative unfolds through several groups of killers who, knowing potential winners of a million of dollars, trying to put an end to the life of a quite disgusting magicianto which the police protect that he testificará against the mafia. The fun will begin when all end up together in the hotel where the alleged victim is hidden. Each draw there worst of if same and, alongside this, array sufficient for ending a barracks of the civil guard. In a story like this we cannot forget we introduce extremely violent and surreal characters because this is very funny and smells like what some call independent cinema (concept, incidentally, never understood that: independent of what or who). In the end, give a twist to the plot and we believe that we have an acceptable script, we, which commonly been called have faith.No doubt, this type of feature films has a quite exponential advantage: If you don't know how to solve a dramatic situation, charge you some of its protagonists, if you don't know how to solve two situations, charge you more. And said and done because as I would say my mother "here are not saved nor pointer". Ultimately, kilos of meat for hamburgers accompanied by their corresponding liters of ketchup and seasoned with a supposed black humor; set which bears more resemblance with a video-clip of the MTV that with a feature length action.My desfavoritismo for this film being clear, I must say that I do not believe that you go you poorly at the box office because their dynamic Visual games tend to be digested quite easily by the adolescent population (as occurs with certain types of food).</body>
</review>
