<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Quo vadis, baby?" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The title does not deserve the repudiation all because (I insist) has ways of another film. Worthy Telefilm, small film, entertainment video store, in any case.</summary>
	<body>Do I saw this Quo vadis, baby? with some reluctance: it came the title, more debtor of the comedietas of crude humor and scurfy eroticism of an Ozores than of what the film intends to, a thriller or an intimate drama, there's both. Disappointment took to arrive, but attended your appointment: not can one hold good feelings, let go by the intuitions and suspect, between the marasmus of dish or heavy, European cinema film of interest to gain my (lately negative and extremely) opinion of Italian cinema, which once sought me so many good moments when one of watch movies with some regularity and lot of passion in this.Quo vadis, baby? It is a strange hybrid between the detective story, careful detail and predictable, but sobrellevable script, and the depth with pretensions of the drama of characters, where I let me carry by Cassavetes or Ivory and not by Salvatores, which wants to give much in much scope and is just few meters.It seems (that impression I had during the last half stretch of the film) that the director has pulled some solucionario problems and has tackled by the shortest route, which usually coincides with the worst and the most obvious. Saved the boot, which is twisted with threads more personal and where are reflected more earthly concerns of an overly moved by the telefilms director, valid school for some tiny demands and tours short film.The title does not deserve the repudiation all because (I insist) has ways of another film, which already we would like, but we do not see. The argument could have been stretched to round out a pure noir and ignore any dramatic intention: we already know that the detectives are harsh and tender at the same time and that, as said Ruben Blades in his immortal Pedro Navaja, "if were you born pa' Hammer of Heaven you fall nails".These nails leave the coffin to half close or half open, but the corpse not atufa too much: is left wanting, cares about desentumecer his devastated body and make the Viewer (with a healthy Samaritan spirit) leave the film confident that next time (her will) not give opportunities so nefarious titles. There is much film to see: tonight, go no further, shooting to see Babel, which everyone has opinion of the tape and I, two candles, can not enter the coffee talks with friends.</body>
</review>
