<review author="Plissken" title="Captivity" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When you already expect surprises in the old world of the psychokillers, comes 'Captivity', capable of making you laugh with its slapdash occurrences.</summary>
	<body>Jennifer, a young model, and Gary, a young driver, are captured and locked up in a hideout by a mysterious psychopath which will be devoted to exploit their deepest fears and anticipate their movements. Can Jennifer and Gary escape from the clutches of her cruel captor?Up there, the synopsis of 'Captivity', the last film by Roland Joffé, Yes, that of 'La Mission' and 'The cries of silence'. Screenplay Larry Cohen, the legendary creator of 'Invaders', 'I'm alive', 'Maniac Cop', 'The flying serpent' or more recently 'last call' signs. We could expect a good movie, right?Well not. 'Captivity' is the umpteenth rehash of 'Seven', with all the clichés that we have been seeing / suffering from Fincher's. Credits included. It also has details that make it a parody of the genre, probably without the minimum intention that its creators.The case is that 'Captivity' boots with a minimum of intrigue and good work by Joffé, showing a brutal death in charge of the calibration of turn and extracts from the abduction of Jennifer with certain taste and pace. But as the film progresses, the tone of psicothriller is diluted between large marcianadas (a New York Police that read in Greek "because he studied Greek") and not least big blunders (an expert on psychopaths that ten seconds of entering gate puts the police on the exact track of the kidnapper), and ends up being one of the nominees for comedy of the year by dint of pure nonsense. All this without any effort to be original (already named 'Seven' and 'Saw' are relating very, very direct). Special mention deserve the classic script twists, tramposísimos (and without any intention that are obvious, as opposed to the 'The Prestige') and the moments of comedy absurd (incredible intuition of the policemen, who A) give the key to find the suspect looking a showcase or B) are evidence of the crime changing channel on TV!). To make matters worse, comes the end of the film you realize that the first scene has absolutely nothing to do with the rest of the film, is a pegote put to give a 'Hostel' touch. What could be painful.And there are more, but there is no question of making more blood.In the section on interpretations of bland to the offensive. Elisa Cuthbert is blonde topical jamona top model and Daniel Gillies no less topical maromo seductive and hot-headed driver. Michael Harney and Laz Alonso are one of the most absurd couples of polis of recent history. The rest of the cast is worthy of a telefilm of William Baldwin shot in Barcelona, as much.When you already expect surprises in the old world of the psychokillers, comes 'Captivity', capable of making you laugh with its slapdash occurrences. A 2, per the Cuthbert and laughter.</body>
</review>
