<review author="Plissken" title="Miguel y William" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The blunder of the indent of Inés Paris is put the focus on Leonor, the true protagonist, and forget for too many minutes the two authors, engaged side comedians of a hors d'oeuvres pulling to vulgar comparsas.</summary>
	<body>Miguel de Cervantes, born in 1564, died in 1616. William Shakespeare, born in 1547, died in 1616. 'Miguel and William', Spanish production that starts in London in the year of Grace's. 1500?Anyway, maybe I'm wrong. Or maybe Agnes Paris, its Director and writer, we want to make it clear in advance that the proposal is to play to apparent anachronism, as it already did with the same character in ' Shakespeare in love'. What matters is that the starting point is interesting: Will Shakespeare travels to Castile in pursuit of his love interest Leonor, betrothed to the powerful Duke of Obando. There he will fight please its nothing less than with Miguel de Cervantes, in a journey that will serve to give both the best of themselves as writers.And taking into account that the film struggles, and much, to stand out from the seedy tone of the Spanish comedy in recent years, one would expect a duel of wits between these two central characters with the excuse of the Lady in question. But the blunder of the indent of Inés Paris is put the focus on Leonor, the true protagonist, and forget for too many minutes the two authors, engaged side comedians of a hors d'oeuvres pulling to vulgar comparsas.Thus, what started as a fun attempt to anachronistic comedy with modern characters in an ancient world, has just developed as 'Celeste is not a color', more or less. Leonor (squishy and very llorona Elena Anaya) is independent women and owner of their destination, but which protects tooth and nail his virginity (?); Shakespeare (tiresome Will Kemp) is a guiri buffoon who just wants to write comedies, and devotes his time to declare lover of Leonor and, meanwhile, to throw the yew trees to medium female cast. Miguel de Cervantes (Juan Luis Galiardo shutdown) is a tax-collector married and disenchanted with the writing that falls in love with Eleanor to the hear verses that he believes it. The Duke de Obando (guiñolesco José María Pou) is jealous and nasty, promised that welcomes in his castle to the two suitors of Eleanor (?). Others, because of filling: Malena Alterio makes his Bethlehem of 'Here no hay quien viva' take a leap of 400 years in time and like the Cinderella sister; Geraldine Chaplin, buf, how bad will be the thing to do what it does here; the only one that deserves special mention is Miriam Giovanelli, the girl of the unforgettable short 'already not walking' of Luiso Berdejo, and he wins here to others by a landslide, with a role more absurd, just base presence on screen. The best of the film, no doubt.Then there is the alleged strong point of the film, literary references. Some are subtle and work within the narrative. Others are stuck to shoehorn for whatever you have read 'Don Quixote', 'Othello', 'much ado about nothing' or 'Richard III' to recognize and say "ja - ja, I know where it comes that", without bothering to integrate them into the plot. In my opinion, is the another weak point of the film, not to exploit this resource to fund.Finally, as much claim to sophisticated comedy and there are so many details of brush in a film of Ozores (two pisados zurullos, a fart, two lovers retozando and a third woman under the same bed, a dwarf, an aunt bathing). The difference is that Ozores with absolute conviction, and Agnes Paris makes it because if not it does not boot the smile of the staff.In the technical section, correct setting (although noticeable limitations, especially in the boot in London and the horrendous pictures of time), photography pulling normalita and topical music (flamenquito/medieval mix).We still do not give signs of intelligence above the average in the patriotic comedy. To see if 'Cinema days' (the film, not the vehicle for showcasing of Antonio Gasset) got up the flight. A 4.</body>
</review>
