<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Bobby" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film pivots between the tribute to the ideological legacy of Bobby Kennedy and the nostalgic memories of a few years key in American history from the political and social point of view.</summary>
	<body>The large number of choral tapes that are populating the Billboard lately is curious. I do not think that the Crash phenomenon has been the trigger for the same, but I begin to suspect that many have chosen this formula attracted by the whiff of the Golden statuette. Bobby, the third film directed by Emilio Estévez, strong bet for a fragmented story following the footsteps of an indisimulada influence recognized by the own Estévez, that of the master of the historias-mosaico, Robert Altman.La tape pivots between the tribute to the ideological legacy of Senator Robert Francis 'Bobby' Kennedy and the nostalgic memories of a few years key in American history from the political and social point of view. At that stage were born groups for female liberation, in the fight against racism or the 'hippy' movement, among other counter-cultural manifestations. The environment was also the breeding ground which promoted sexual liberation and psychedelic experimentation with drugs of the 1960s and 1970s. But, as also portrays the film, in those years the population had a strong political awareness spurred by protests against the war of Viet Nam. People harbored Frank hopes on a change to overcome various fronts open in his country. And Bobby Kennedy, as if it were the last burning clove that grab after the assassinations of JFK and Martin Luther King, personified and encompassed the yearnings of change for a divided country.Thus the tape concentrates the story of various personal stories about the hours before the murder of the Senator from New York and democratic candidate for the presidential elections. Sequences of each of the stories are interspersed with each other and with footage of some of the speeches and public acts of Kennedy. All distilled spirit of hope that permeates the story, but only get some thrill. Therefore, the success of some are shadowed by other lax, and the set of the film perhaps is burdened by an excess of political discourse, while the bottom of the same is shareable to 100 percent.Estévez, with the complicit support of a Pleiad of stars and friends, has embarked on a very personal project what is perhaps his best film as a filmmaker but stays at several steps of excellence.</body>
</review>
