<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="En busca de la felicidad" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In search of happiness is another of so many films dedicated to selling the American dream to the world.</summary>
	<body>That the reality surpasses fiction, also be a very recurring topic in many cases is true, like what reads another hackneyed phrase, that art imitates life. There are occasions in which a real event is so incredible that it seems removed from the mind of a writer, and coincidences of life, most likely this true event will end up giving rise to some "inspired by a true story" movie. Well, that is the case of in search of happiness, although the fact upon which it is based is not one of those stories that become headline news in half the world.Chris Gardner (Will Smith) is a man dragging a bad economic situation following a bad investment in medical devices. However, and despite the precarious, it attempts to improve his life thanks to his innate ability for mathematics and a programme of training of an important agency of values. The truth is that the tape is closer to the melodrama of "use and throw" that to something else, with all due respect to the real Chris Gardner, which has a cameo in the final scenes. It is a byproduct genuinely Hollywood, with the only raison d ' être of show and export the validity and force of the American dream, because any person, if it is proposed and acts with perseverance, is capable of achieving a priori unattainable goals. Well, there is actually another goal, something else in the meantime concealed cheap edulcoramiento, and is the search by the protagonist of a new nomination to the Oscar, and who knows if the same statuette. However, Will Smith is not commensurate with the circumstances and the wild promotion of which has been the subject, and performs an interpretation flat, without transmitting any type of emotion or feeling. The script is nothing more than another crude copy of typical human (so fashionable lately) overcoming stories, full of phrases gandilocuentes and empty, of clichés, ridiculous situations (that scene of the Rubik's cube in the taxi please!). The characters are one stereotype after the other, and that nobody expected the slightest developments therein. Say that in search of happiness is expected soon from the same trailer, any viewer is able to mentally draw the knot and outcome of the plot.Ultimately, in search of happiness is another of so many films dedicated to sell to the world the American dream, but on the road they forget to mention certain details such as the fate or a person's innate ability and that others do not possess.</body>
</review>
