<review author="Jose Contreras" title="En busca de la felicidad" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are people who need adversity to live. People that delivers the application when the deadline has passed, but you need it desperately, people expected the embargo to pay the Bill, people who go stressed to the quote when you have time to prepare it. There are people that kicks with calamities.</summary>
	<body>The French Revolution and the American Constitution were inspired by earlier thinkers such as John Locke (1632-1704), formulating his social contract rights to freedom, life and property. Thomas Jefferson added the list to the American Constitution in the version of Samuel Johnson, which had changed the third for the right to happiness. And this is how it is today.Says Javier Ocaña in the country the films starting with "Based on a true story" announce a farfetched story. We would come if you play the primitive to a hero of a movie out of the film outraged. And however it plays every week.Chris Gardner, the protagonist of "In search of happiness" is a man in distress. His wife leaves him with a five-year-old boy, he sells bone scanners. You need to sell two to pay the rent and to muddle through. Put fines will be collecting as seals. The world is cahoots against him, a day is a trap, another day is a hippy who stole a scanner, another day is the police, and another is the landlord who fails to pay, or a friend who does not return him a debt. Sometimes, it happens from time to time, something good.On the other side is his dream. Chris was good at school, and dreams of becoming a broker. Take your request and does everything so that a signature accept it in a course. But do this course means spending six months without charge and he has to keep a child. 20 Candidates who have just the course only will hire one.Muccino tells a wonderful story of calamities. Create a character with hook knows fit blows and who knows making fun of their own misery when he can, as in the interview: ("what'd you if a man submit to the interview without shirt and we gave the post?") But he can't reward it. You don't know because you don't know it thoroughly. Muccino has not known to many Chris Gardners. There are people who need adversity to live. People that delivers the application when the deadline has passed, but you need it desperately, people expected the embargo to pay the Bill, people who go stressed to the quote when you have time to prepare it. There are people that kicks with calamities. Give them a life quiet, a good job, a calendar with all calculated and you've finished with them. If Muccino wants a happy ending (the real end, already know, are unlikely), can not tame the hero, because we have come to love him with their adrenaline chutes and their misfortunes.</body>
</review>
