<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie that appeals to nostalgia for a character that has had a decent Colophon, much better than the street fight with the grandson of John Wayne.</summary>
	<body>Two moments define perfection mean this Rocky Balboa sexagenarian of turn of the century. On the one hand, the end of the film, with the home recordings of tourists, in Philadelphia, climbing running the famous stairs and when come up, they are to jump in plan champion, throwing blows from boxing to air, emulating Rocky.A see. An exercise in honesty: you, you and you that you'd fighting against Apollo Cread and you have believed for a couple of hours than the cold war could win on a ring, if you go to the icy Philadelphia do not would do exactly like tourists at the end of "Rocky Balboa"? Something will be right?The other defining moment is marked by one of the television commentators, alborozado, when you cannot avoid a smile while he says: "I grew up watching Rocky Balboa fighting." "I never thought that he would have the opportunity to transmit one of their matches." And that is what happens to viewers, who never we considered the possibility, after that infumable Cairn which was "Rocky V" to see again to the Italian Colt uploaded in a ring.We go to movies, therefore in a kind of homage to a youth was that us and, suddenly, we get to the meeting in the form of expert Boxer and notorious example, well-meaning middle, majete apañao. And, look, Stallone has been smart enough to write a script simple, coherent and white glove in which all are well: whites and blacks, young and old, parents and children, the living and the dead.Written and filmed as an auto-homenaje to a character who is in the history of the film on their own merits (let us not forget that the first Rocky knocked at the Academy nothing less than the Taxi driver of Scorsese), "Rocky Balboa" makes you smile often, convinces with that philosophy of self-help on open it-path-in-the-life-a-blows and you excited with the expected training base hit pieces of meat, lifting of barrels of beer and esforzadas races under the snow, stairs up, to this music that all ritmillo left tatareando the film.A movie that appeals to nostalgia for a character that has had a decent Colophon, much better than the street fight with the grandson of John Wayne, and that, in the heat of the post movie beers, led us to good group of buddies, Paco, John, Henry, Nacho and Isaac, to remember those night evenings watching television, enjoying with TysonHollyfield, Foreman, De la Hoya, Chaves, Poli Díaz or Lenox Lewis.Y is that, in the end, the good of Rocky, as the grandpas of the announcement of a car, is right: there is no boxers as the then.</body>
</review>
