<review author="Caruco" title="Dreamgirls" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A music pure and hard, done with delicacy and passion, and to savour with the same requirements.</summary>
	<body>Along with the western in its purest form, the other film genre that does not enjoy at all in the favor of the public present, above all non-American, is the musical. If you are not a lover of the musical the likelihood that likes "Dreamgirls" are reduced to the infimum.And incidentally has all the possibilities of losing one of the best adaptations of a Broadway musical film, in this case, inspired by the trajectory of the Supremes. It also presents another hurdle, the downturn of notable interest from almost start the footage to the 20 minute scattering in terms of characters and situations. But, by magic, and against all odds, manages to climb dramatically before screening time.And this thanks to the talent of a choreography, sets, costumes and poses so studied, colorful and imaginative as sunsets at the service of the story. And also, without which "Dreamgirls" would not be anything, thanks to the talent in the Mise en scène of Bill Condon and interpretations, particularly Jennifer Hudson, new from American star idol, the O.T. to the American, and he starred in a number of separation with the rest of the group, which leaves alone exhibiting their arts.Elegance and passion.What is staging the passion for music, even disregarding, or passing on tiptoe with mild strokes, with what was the tumultuous historical context of the times: Martin Luther King, race riots, Viet Nam, protests youth? Anything!, the plot and the characters go to theirs.Possessive and inhuman, relentless music producers embodied in Curtis Taylor (Jamie Foxx), that make us see the coldness and lack of scruples towards people, not towards the money of the savvy of the record scene.Or the contrast between true talent, incarnated by Effie (Jennifer Hudson), overshadowed before the beautiful image that can sell of Deena Jones (off Beyoncé Knowles).If even Eddie Murphie is sober and restrained in his interpretation (why not deserves an Academy Award), putting all the meat, and voice, on the grill. To highlight the look of determination and helplessness, when it comes to injecting coca before their friends, that summarizes everything what is fragile in its character. (Attention: spoiler!) Later, left in the hands of his musical patron, Curtis Taylor, focus you a fade in black which is a drop of the withering curtain premonition. (End of the spoiler)The worst a deslabazado Assembly that jump, or dance, a character and fact to another, which makes passing the years without us we inmutemos. But a musical pure and hard (the sequence of the "theft" of the song is anthology), done with delicacy and passion, and to savour with the same requirements. Douglas Sirk would be proud.</body>
</review>
