<review author="Caruco" title="El libro negro" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a domesticated, happy Verhoeven back home and, as a rookie, apply to please with a telefilm of luxury.</summary>
	<body>After more than 6 years back Paul Verhoeven, and also involves the return of the Dutch to Europe. Some topics we tend to apply to films made in Hollywood, which is limited to follow guidelines, only seeks to sell or limits the creative capacity of the author take overland passage.Because it could dispatch this criticism by saying that "The black book" is a drama of intrigue, sex, love, loyalties and betrayals with Nazism and the resistance as a backdrop, and as effective as simple. And although there are elements of the film, they are much less abundant, risky, daring, provocative and non-conformist than be expected.Any of his works in the United States contains more interest, with the exception of the disappointing "Hollow man", that this work told with a neatness and formal beauty as remarkable as it anodina. Its virtues are limited to comply as entertainment, to discover a good actress, Carice van Houten, and a couple or three scenes and notable ideas, without which, it would be a film as flat as the concept of globe that were our forefathers. survivors!Paul Verhoeven has become to like, and not clash too with a story of espionage and passions that contemplates, far, Hitchcock on his horizon.It is the sequence of the protagonist, a sort of mata-hari marbling in the headquarters of the Gestapo in the invaded Holland, tiñiéndose the hair of their most intimate parts of rubio to raise its charms as men consuming; submitting good Nazis, because not all were in favor of the horrors of Hitler; or the controversy include the humiliations of the population violated the collaborators, tired of so much time of invasion and fears, once finished the contest.But its archetype is that of the Nice couché paper, where even a barrel of human feces is so embellished it seems delicious chocolate. Unfortunately, there is also the idea that wars never end, in a spiral of violence and intolerance infinite. And the need for survival, understanding thereby the ability to adapt to circumstances but at the same time being true to oneself. It is in a way more compromised, as Rachel, the protagonist, or more frivolous, as his friend, Ronnie (Halina Rejin). But it is not the best Verhoeven, is a domesticated, happy Verhoeven back home and, as a rookie, apply to please with a telefilm of luxury.</body>
</review>
