<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Vidas cruzadas (Short cuts)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Acid collage of American society (and was not Bush yet). In these times of cinema desguionizado Short cuts is a plea of the importance of having a text height.</summary>
	<body>There are who admires to the now sadly deceased Robert Altman for his heroic attitude of filmmaker upstream, ácrata, decadent, and not atinan to see that above this politicization of his film it beats, beautiful, neat, remarkable insights that eludes any concession to free (except the very regrettable Pret-a.porter) and is offered free, complex, intelectualizado without being airtight in no time.Short cuts (Vidas cruzadas) is a history still ably engarzadas: the argumentative framework is of a thick fabric, but the puzzle assembles with precision and Altman cuenta-historias gives us in consciousness with a history full of life, that exhales life, that touches us all and that everyone can be part of our story, fragment of our own lives.The routine of the characters, which are many and varied coat becomes epic: twin routine and epic, confused, are the grey picture of the plumbate homeland of the director, which castigates as a Michael Moore more lyrical, less cold.By Vidas cruzadas it walks a long dozen beings thinks, bland, losers, marked by the failure, involuntary bulwarks of a moral bragada in daily battles against loneliness and disappointment. And in one or another way, the world of Altman (or the short stories by Raymond Carver on which is based the film caters people broken by pain, but sometimes oblivious to his evidence in their lives: only at the end ultimately recognize him, as the drug addict who only gets serious with his addiction when he suffers a trip too interrupter.) There are small more frivolous dropouts and irreparable losses, but they are varnished by fine indifference of a director who gets no hand in what counts and let everything flow naturally: what makes appalling vision of this film is a genius ability to mount all the stories and that they are, in the end, a. The choral film by Robert Altman is the reference in which Paul Haggis (Crash) should drink before addressing his November (unfairly) film. Paul Thomas Anderson and his well above Magnolia (with the best Tom Cruise in front of a camera that I have seen).Altman leave no one only: or a pastry, inconsustancial, seemingly unnecessary, seems obviable, although only ten minutes out on screen. Until the earthquake of the end is a character.Vidas cruzadas or Short Cuts (short cuts, a title of a great sonancia in Spanish) is a wonderful collage of stories: the deliberate fragmentation of its plot, the excessive acting machinery, settled later in a well greased ascent to the outcome, which also brings its moralina, but did not say what should not.In these times of cinema desguionizado (that is my claim in the desert from a lone Viewer), Vidas cruzadas is acid allegation of the importance of having a text height. I have not read as a whole the work of Carver, but some of the stories that guide the film. Then each opposing history that more you like (or conmocione you more, anyway.) I'll stick with the police who plays Tim Robbins, detestable, cabronazo until the climax, and his history of marital reconciliation truly unusual ways.Won the Golden Lion at the Venice Film Festival, which also granted, unusually, the prize for best interpretation to the cast. . A special category that also gave the cast interpretive award created for lives crusades at the Golden Globes. Altman aspired (failing) to the Academy Award for best director.</body>
</review>
