<review author="Iñigo" title="Sin fin (Bez Konca)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is it possible to separate the private life of political life without conflict? Can you choose without betraying? Is it possible to forget...?</summary>
	<body>Krzysztof Kieslowski: "freedom is a contradictory concept with human nature." Any election entails a restriction and denial of other possibilities, that they become unworkable since that time. Freedom for Kieslowski supposed something unattainable, that the human being is limited, but also was an illusion. And in its innermost Forum always her I was looking for, understanding and understanding. To empathize with Kieslowski (as much as possible) we will have to understand that, despite his actual resignation, he was eager to dreaming something naive as theoretically unreachable. All yearn to attain a certain degree of fullness. The real issue, according to the director himself, was not whether we are or are not free, but if you really want to be. If we are indeed prepared to unleash the chains of our inevitable condition human. If we want to separate us from the road that comes from factory. Our elections are of great importance in this, starting from a point of view "virginal" and non-existent, which only could be achieved with our demise, logically. All those reflections fatally drove the film that we are dealing with. "Without end" is certainly the most pessimistic work of Kieslowski, its darker creation in search of small crevices to freedom, to the ingenuity of a few dreams that end up bursting in our own face. "Bez Konca" implies an earlier and a later in the films of Polish director (many of his films could acquire the meaning, but none in a way so vital and radical like this). It involves placing in the jaws of the policy more inside that never, for, leaving them (if it is possible to do with life), never to return. This film would be the beginning of the relationship between Kieslowski and Piesiewicz, future co-writer also in works by the likes of "The double life of Veronica", "Blue", "White" or "Red". "Without end" would be the prelude to the mythical "Decalogue" (also with the hand of fellow Piesiewicz), masterpiece in films of Kieslowski. It is evident here the suffering of the author in first person. The painful consequences of living under martial law, feel the repression towards the Trade Union "Solidarity", completely forbidden within that framework. The light of the creation of art as a form of human expression of ideas as a form of social awareness and complaint; all of them inexorably become our worst enemy and lead us to our own condemnation. Any decision will result in an error that we chained for life. And the only loophole, if there is really one that is valid, is death. We could say that it is the film in which Kieslowski is dangerously more accountability. All done, looks back at his past, deeds and creations, become dark and pessimism takes over in excess of its person, creating a film that "alive" all hope fades. Indeed, the worst moment of his life made this a truculenta film of resignation. "Endless" has links in common with the "Blue" future, many will say. History, its characters, its development. But they're simple appearances. Both end up in a sharp curve. However, one overlooking the sea, to hope. Another gives the abyss. "No End" Ulla and Julie in "Blue", after the death of their husbands, try to find an escape route, either through sex or loneliness. On this tour you will find with various details (sometimes invaluable for us) that will show them that freedom is "damaged", which is something much more complex of what many we try to make it clear. Kieslowski reconciled with love and freedom (and already detached from any political aura), after the aforementioned slump, us returns to show his innocence, stolen by a moment in "Endless", and once again believe in the human being in "Blue" (already from the "Decalogue" trusts timidly him). But in the movie before us, dazed, decomposed, it is suspicious of any election in search of freedom. The politics and society of the time weighed too much on already exhausted shoulders. Therefore, and more than ever, here the answers will not be easy to come up. Moreover, there will be no answers. He himself was unaware of the direction to take. The film becomes dense, very uncomfortable, we will not know what to grab us. All symbols and metaphors are incredibly elusive, from the mousetrap to the mysterious and seemingly "empty" apparitions of the deceased husband. But everything has a meaning beyond of the metaphysical or spiritual, showing us clearly, on this occasion, the inability among the private and political life. The public and personal, choice, join resulting in inefficiency in the search for a separation between the two. It tells us there is no effective freedom. Women, axis main but not only, hesitant, does not know which direction give his life. Not realizing initially that, Ulla ends up accepting that he needs her husband, her life without him is completely unfathomable (which happens to the setback in "Blue") and that you can not forget him. There is no sex that tape. And in its internal Forum, despite its efforts, it does not want to ignore him. Their desperation is imminent, and their accountability looms. Meanwhile, the husband, aware of its own despair, notes. More cryptic than ever, Kieslowski doubt and makes doubt to the worker (Artur Barcis), another of the key players in the entirety of the Filmography of the director. A character who does not know if staying or leaving, feeling that any decision will lead you to your personal prison. The shackles of a misguided policy will be that we ourselves find to our particular treason. Polish tilting brutally against communism, again, and again, had to pay the price (as happens in "The random") of alienating the senior leaders, that skeptics about the possibility of a hidden criticism failed to understand, decided to censor the film. "Endless" is a film full of messages, symbolism, coincidences, opportunities, beliefs, faith, personal beliefs and freedoms in search of love. It is a complex movie like that more in his work, because it does not give or intend to give answers. It is the Kieslowski closer, closer to the limit, causing at times, logical discomfort not understand if you're not prepared to understand that there is nothing to understand, and that, indeed, exceeds this limit approaching himself hell. But no one said that the journey was easy. Ulla and Barcis are real examples. Both are auto condemn. On the one hand, looms the renunciation of survival as only way to preserve dignity. But is it valid? It is, at the same time, worthy? It is simply another loophole, that will not allow us to find our desired response. On the other, we see hesitation vital of the character of Barcis, perfectly adaptable to the own Kieslowski, paradoxical, contradictory, human, therefore. This worker who knows the limitation of elections in one organic so little environment, consumed inside, but at the same time resigned, and that, throughout all of the "Decalogue" appears as soul penalty, consciousness of Kieslowski, silent Adviser of the protagonists, trying to bring its experience in peak times, limit, that is a decision. However, it won't do anything. It will be. The decision will only be ours. When it asks for help, despair makes an appearance. As Ulla in the time which is aimed at us, the viewers, in search of an explanation. She does not understand, but we can not provide answers. Who knows if in the darkness and rot that surrounds us in the future, we will find subterfuge. Innocence stained green. Vitreous point that our happiness (or part of it) has room. In the same way as Kieslowski, unfathomable, vast, impenetrable, so it kept in its interior. Imperative, forced, necessary that the viewer will dominate and know join the film if it does not suffer an insurmountable bewilderment. And, therefore, an unwavering torpor. In the same way, it is also basic to be knowledgeable of the life trajectory of the artist, their political and social experiences, otherwise not be can understand their position nor their ideas. Dark phase of the Polish director, until the creation of the "Decalogue" focused their films in the moral, ethical, social and political in search of a possible and relative freedom. Since then total emphasis will be on the spiritual, human and transcendent, leaving aside political "platitudes". But always present random, volitional decisions, love and freedom. An inseparable whole. It should be noted in "No End" the presence of a large Grayzna Szapolowska, present in titles later as "Not Amarás", which performed a commendable performance, contained, replete with necessary gestures, endowed with a great success. "Bez Konca" stands as a turning point and, apparently, also as a Union of vital characters from then in the surroundings of Kieslowski. In addition to co-screenwriter Piesiewicz, here also known that would, subsequently, his inseparable musical collaborator: exceptional Zbigniew Preisner. With him got unforgettable masterpieces. In this film stands out with a mysterious, disturbing and captivating beginning and a no less mysterious and dark finish (with that pace.) (do funeral?). Concluding. Disturbing and reflective film of the late Polish director, which, though Sin somewhat pessimistic and Maverick, continues to be a very personal work and an exercise of great film knowing. Will not be his greatest success, but it is a step in his delicious filmography. A situation unique to know in his image and likeness, better than anyone, we do not know anything. To be safer than anyone else that we are not in absolute insurance. To search for a truth that was not: our truth. </body>
</review>
