<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Big fish" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential film in any deuvedeteca self-respecting. A delicious work of perfect manufacture, with a script full of intimate and emotional moments and outstanding. To see a thousand times.</summary>
	<body>Tim Burton is a very peculiar film, at least for me. It makes very strange films, of incredible and absurd characters scenarios. He may like you or not, but we must acknowledge the originality and quality of their work. And every movie that passes, I think that you get much better top it off. In addition, his films do not lose validity over the years, are completely timeless. Gives equal when they asked, have such quality that they can be immortal, as is demonstrated in Big Fish.La film is about a man who tells stories that seem little real. Stories incredible and impossible that everybody dazzle. To all? Well, unless all your child than on the verge of being a father, is has enough of the "lies" of his father. It seems unfair that he had to live his father involved in this charade that creates and why he hates. Reaching the end of the life of the account tales, they meet again, and this time something has changed.Puff, what about Big Fish? It has a start something slow, with a multitude of stories incredible arriving to be even "lacking imagination" in absurd resulting. But as the story progresses, and discovers that not everything is false, that the protagonist does nothing more than adorn the reality, that enrich the facts to make them more attractive, the film manages to trap you in their networks. Get get you that sensitive vein that we all have, to make us ready for a very emotional ending that unleashed the most basic emotions. Tim Burton since then me has already taken the measure.In short, essential film in any deuvedeteca self-respecting. A delicious work of perfect manufacture, with a script full of intimate and emotional moments and outstanding. To see a thousand times.</body>
</review>
