<review author="Nico" title="V de Vendetta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are few things that excited me but a motrollón of explosions to the rhythm of Tchaikovsky is something that get me fiber</summary>
	<body>If there is is something of what I'm proud of my prejudices. I do not know if they are the engine of the world but at least in my life. Movies that I do not see because "Cove" fame of the director throws me back, others I see only because the director of photography is the same as the HEAT drives that I do not hear because I do not like the typography of the cover, etc?The only reason that had to make an entry on V for Vendetta in July 2005 was because Natalie Portman went out in it with the shaven head. Or the Alan Moore comic, I have not read but I will do it, or the script of the Wachosky brothers or Gee. I wanted see Natalie rápada head and as the rest of things seemed totally secondary I did not bother to read what was the movie, where it was set or what criticism he had received; I to mine. It seems that V for Vendetta has not aroused much excitement because we put in the smallest room of cinemas to see. He filled obviously because its dimensions were as the Hall of my house. Am not going to make a summary for sure that everyone has read the comic (I'm an ignorant on this topic, so I would appreciate any advice.) (Hágamos of the comments something useful!) and because it would be absurd. But if someone is interested my opinion, say that I had at various times tachycardias, spasms, got me goose bumps on several occasions and I cried at the end. There are few things that excited me but a motrollón of explosions to the rhythm of Tchaikovsky is something that get me the fiber. Anyway, because I don't like tattoos but if not I would be one in front of V for Vendetta.Ya I have said before that I'm an ignoramus in which comics refers in that and other many things (go) but do not understand how a film that was shot in May-June of 2005 can be based on a graphic work where part of the attacks on the London underground that took place in July of that same year. May I have bad dates, may the writers to make last minute changes and used a real event as a base, or that the fiction of Alan Moore became a reality on July 7 year pásado. View the photo I guess that it will not need say are worth to pay 6 euros, but you aborrezcas the movie (which is very unlikely if you have a minimum sensitivity and Encephalic mass), only to see that head without hair.</body>
</review>
