<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Raices profundas" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film emotional, essential, human... It is a western, but it could have been a rural drama of our deepest Spain or a thriller of mafia with a courageous visitor and a sensitive child.</summary>
	<body>I saw Shane (Shane) twenty years ago. Perhaps more. Her scheduled the solemn and only Spanish TV in hours afternoon and brasero. Equal until it rained. So I learned to see film: to love him. I remember huge evenings with Oliver Twist or Ben-Hur or David Coppefield. None of this is already the épila and youth of today whose heroes are made of metal or manga Japanese, which I hate so much, but I will not here to pontificate on my vices because they are also so very nasty - who am I to say otherwise - as those of cualquiera.uno saw (continues by the same rope) that the programmer programmed (forgive the phonetic loop). My supply of films dependent entirely others lacks a video (vhs, beta, 2000, words already in unknown to these generations living Blue ray and HDD) or not to go to the big screen film wherever he wanted to. These are other times. one sees what he wants, to some extent. You rent or buy or gives it a cable or satellite channel to affordable schedules and repeatedly. Serves all this sentimental tirade to locate Shane in the context I want to: Shane is the film of children or, at least, of mine. I was the blond boy from Alabama farm whose parents, honest and good at not being able to, cannot with the tyranny of a bearded and greasy chieftain who wants to lend them so his cows send more peacefully. I was the boy fascinated by the language of weapons that forged his identity with the epic of the retired and erratic gunman also seeking its identity in the innocent child eyes. Reciprocal play, complicit, beautiful.Then I do not escudriñaba the film: not looking for codes and hidden languages, copyright sign and three feet to the cat in the picture. None of that mattered: what wholesomeness was the story, which should be well spot (one has always been abundantly demanding in that).Didn't I to William Manning in the character of the gunman of Alan Ladd. Yes, the Manning of without forgiveness, on the other hand, still did not exist. The infinite by John Ford seed did not recognize because he had simply not seen the diligence or Centaurs of the desert, but I noticed that that end was, by necessity, an end of much height: there was the boy and his hero, firing, after Wilson (the mercenary hired that poured blood afraid the wayward reluctant settlers to leave) had been crushed by the fastest gun by Shaneto which it would not see never.How beautiful is the cinema. What Nice is Alabama. Eternal human emotional, essential cinema. It is a western, but it could have been a rural drama of our deepest Spain or a thriller of mafia with a courageous visitor and a sensitive child.</body>
</review>
