<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Gibson retrieves the adventure film, the magnificent, classic... Do not muffled spirit, impressionable heart and leave others from saying them the luck had to miss her.</summary>
	<body>What Mel Gibson is proposing is a journey to a rush of peyote or one of its many lisergias by excess of ego, but Apocalypto is an absolute masterpiece, a multidisciplinary device which extracts the best film adventures of all the history of the cinema, which is already history, to leave so exhausted and satisfied, perfectly sobering of jungle and primitive pride by grace of a prodigious Assembly language as known, but revisited here with cunning, skill and hand ferrea so leave everything perfect. Giblson needed very little to go by the hills of the Yucatán and check a blockbusters of Maya in danger which had only satisfied teen troop gore with shaft golosa.Apocalypto speaks of many things, but never serves educational speaker of a time (Mayan civilization) by much that some have wanted to disassemble this cool shed film pure and hard speeches which appeal more to the absurd controversy. Not go to movies (I, at least, am not going never film) that teach me how was the life of the eunuchs or soldiers of Christ or the troops of Hitler in Stalingrad. It is not to ignore all this rich cultural tools: I appreciate that learning never spare is worth more to be playful and festively, but the film (or literature) is fiction and Apocalypto exhumes fiction: fiction dripping you all the jungle lianas and all the litres of blood that Gibson had to buy on the Internet so that the film is so quite raw. Without the harshness, I am afraid, just not us her would have believed. I think. And twin to the belief goes my enjoyment in the cinema. For a long time that two hours not spent in ten minutes. Is there a better critique of a film?I read that the Maya accomplished astronomers not should catch them by surprise an eclipse, as it happens in the film. It is possible that they were accomplished astronomers, but eclipse is the Gibson mcguffin for Jaguar claw has one hundred minutes of film so that all enjoy with his jungle Vertigo, with his career for life, by his courage and his wife, that a submarine son shines in an apotheosis of rain. You can not ask more.I also read that it was predictable and simple, linear and voyeuristic. I'd say: it is explicit, pornographic in his solid sample of details and very escoradamente, epic because our hero corridor is the demiurge, the possible God, the man who has come to the world to not be snatch life, although a small army of bloody give her yours to run a revenge and consummate a whim.Gibson has recovered the history (or history) of the Mayans, but what it tells is the story of humanity, which is the survival of one cafre interference and other animal. To wrap up the plot, Gibson does not comes to mind another thing that give us a serving of Spanish ships on the beach: as if we we seriously in the mirror, but claw of Jaguar and his family have it clear: will hide in the forest and find a new beginning. (Do not muffled spirit, impressionable heart and leave others from saying them the fate that had as the miss it)</body>
</review>
