<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In short, we could say that the final trick: the Prestige is an excellent movie that mixes with magic and style varied themes and which, moreover, enjoys some absolutely brilliant performances and a script that deserves everything.</summary>
	<body>While he concluded the year 2006, we had the "luck" to watch two films with the theme of magic by in the Middle called the illusionist and Scoop. After these simple entertainment, people (including me to me, of course), anxious, expected the release of the latest film by Christopher Nolan, the final trick: the prestige. And here is my critique of the film, which without a doubt, I have enjoyed it as if it were in full magic show. Memento premiered in 2000 and was a huge success. And it is his incredible originality left open-mouthed to anyone that see. Before this film, Christopher Nolan had directed Following, or the same as a novice film experiment (with critical acclaim, that Yes). Two years later the success of his second film, Nolan led a brilliant film - which however not surpassed the previous - with Al Pacino and Robin Williams as protagonists. Insomnia was titled and its distressing atmosphere and this practically perfect staging made us reach the conclusion that this young director was, undoubtedly, a prodigy. In 2005 he released Batman Begins, which was another disproportionate success (after being a hair ignored the Pacino). I must admit that it is not a bad film, but it could have been much better, more personal. But staff have the final trick: the prestige, the last tape of the director, which supposed to be, without almost any rulings, their second best film after Memento. The final trick: prestige stands out basically for its originality, both in the history in such environment. I could say that this peculiar way of counting and mood stories Nolan are entirely personal, or at least it seems to. This dark and gloomy atmosphere, atmospheres which seems trapping you, the narrow alleys which seem to have no exit and these characters so characterized by its failures than one way or another are rewarded either, those seeking revenge. Here are examples as Leonard Selvy, an amnesiac man who tries to take revenge on the man who murdered his wife or other characters such as Batman or Pacino in insomnia, rather than revenge, decides to hide a fact that if it comes to light will be harmed. In the final trick: the prestige the topics dealt with, mainly, are the envy and rivalry, among many others. The protagonists, after spending a period of friendship, by a terrible consequence begin to hate until you reach unexpected limits. This would be the main subject of the work of Nolan. Although, as I said, this is only the main, since there is, in this magnificent film, a series of extremely sensitive issues which, if they are not treated with such delicacy, can collapse the film. But luckily Christopher Nolan (and his brother Johnatan) have been able to create this story so exciting and complex in a formidable manner, brushing the perfection. Topics such as insanity, wisdom, common sense, the perfection and overcoming, the triumph, intelligence or the very prestige make the film complemented details and facts which benefit the complexity of history.On the other hand, I find that it has sold exceisividad this so seemingly dazzling final trick. As you know, the original title of the film is The prestige (Prestige), thing that it does so in view this "surprise" ending, but I think that the main theme of the film, apart from "be vigilant", as us warns Michael Caine at the beginning of the film, in an absolutely incredible way (pay attention to the image that appears then and remember it until that then serve you)It is the simplicity of things either, the apparent complexity of everything. The obsession which leads to complicate ourselves while, things that are really simple to see, do not see them. So, rather than concluding tricks (that there too many or rather, they are foreseeable, the Nolan film wants to show you just that and can that someone you disappointed by the absence of this surprise ending (unless not so guess - wholly, or partially - before that happens, which I rather doubt).) But not so the film is interesting. Quite the contrary! I prefer at least a final is designed with reasoning and has a credible conclusion not appearing a 90 degree turn which does not match anything. So the end of the final trick: the Prestige is unexpected.Part of the script, the work of Christopher Nolan has many positive aspects. One of them is the setting. The film is is situated at the beginning of the 20th century, in London, therefore the streets, the surroundings, the theatres and all buildings have been be built especially for the film. Anyway, that is not a modern (but yes with touches of science fiction) wizards and therefore have needed sets of large (and quality). Another highlight is the great photography. Wally Pfister is responsible for creating unique, totally overwhelming (and at the same time hopeful) sensations. I recommend you pay attention to the numbers of magic, where the photographic director may look filming some magnificent flat filled with personality and above all, with an exquisite taste (look at Hugh Jackman beneath the stage, pretending they applaud him, with light coming out from the Woods.) (Perhaps one of the sequences with one of the best planes). Then there are the Assembly and Edition, of which I can only say that they deserve at least a nomination for a prize (to secure Oscar that no, so have already announced the nominees). And finally, to say that the soundtrack of David Julyan is formidable, because it fits a finger to the footage as a ring. Attentive, above all, to the final, totally exciting topic. After mentioning all the technical aspects, it would be unfair to not nominate all performers that appear in the film, because they bring a higher density and depth to the story. First of all to the two protagonists of the film name: Hugh Jackman and Christian Bale. Two authentic teachers of the interpretation that, curiously, in this film is where look more. You have to pay attention to the intense dialogues that occur at the bottom and also in the penetrating eyes that are made between the two. And within the side, all luxury, highlight first and foremost to Michael Caine. What about this actor? Well that here, despite not appear too, and offers a brilliant interpretation, endowed with intelligence and, above all, common sense. The female cast is not that it is too extensive, but it is true that both Scarlett Johansson and Piper Perabo interpret two key characters from the film, so it makes them more important, then. Finally, highlight the appearances of David Bowie and Andy Serkins on other two roles which also have much to say in the history. The final trick: prestige lacks important failures, so we can say that it almost reaches the master. It doesn't perhaps be for the excess of details that make the film empache of so many of them and be a bit overwhelming (in a more or less positive sense, because at least is appreciated to enjoy such formidable script, although it has its excesses).In short, we could say that the final trick: the Prestige is an excellent movie that mixes with magic and style varied themes and which, moreover, enjoys some absolutely brilliant performances and a script that deserves everything.</body>
</review>
