<review author="Yojimbo" title="Elizabethtown" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Give them my congratulations to all the players. They are great and you know them go excellently.</summary>
	<body>Dear C.C.Te I write this letter because I feel the need to express my fascination with your Elizabethtown in a more direct way than with an ordinary criticism.Since I saw the trailer for your movie I knew that it was going to be a new nostalgic gem. Between your great merits is convert a reality that sometimes exceeds US and us is totally strange, alienating and surreal in original situations that, at least to me, causing a very pleasant surprise.I was always fascinated by the way you have the Americans to "celebrate" the death. These chapels is not estilan. It must be our religious heritage that prevents us from seeing fondly and rejoice having shared moments with someone whom we wanted to. Toca here crying. Weep and lament. But I have always preferred to your style: already is sad to lose someone, so why not focus on a loving tribute and talk about good experiences with that person (if they exist)?But the death of your story is just an excuse. A great excuse to tell us that we take advantage of the time we have to enjoy it with who we want to. But not crazy. Not to the "almost famous". One could say that there talking of "burn life" to the maximum. It is not the same as the route by car from Orlando Bloom (tell him from me that here is quite well and who can not complain of projects that offer), with this wonderful company. You forgive you've put to flight attendant Kirsten. It is not to have any problem with them, just that at first believed me the rather than vital philosopher. Also forgive you some that another childish sentence and Declaration of intent ñoña in the mouth of the protagonists. There are pretty tacky, even disappointing moments for someone who knows how to write as well as you. But I have no doubt that you have done so on purpose. I do not I like, that is all.Along with Michael Mann I think ye are two current directors who have better musical sense in his films. I am not referring to original music, that also, but to make an outstanding selection of little-known songs and make them as yours, or so of the film that is not conceived these sequences without them.Your movie is a mirror. Many we have surreal situations throughout our lives: the same at a funeral you give someone a cigarette and then he as a sign of gratitude invites you to a beer and buy you another box of tobacco. Because your movie is truffled of such situations. And they are fun. Very funny. And best of all, you help the history and us to enjoy it.Give them my congratulations to all the players. They are great and you know them go excellently.That is why I write this letter. I think you're one of the best current writers and one of the most interesting and original of our time. I hope you are not with many problems for upcoming films. I do not think that Cruise you back at any time. It is that ye do good crumbs. And Tom always seemed to me a guy with good sense of smell to work with professionals.Cuidate much and hope we be surprised with your next film.Hugs, YojimboP.D. Someday I want to what makes Orlando at the end of the movie.And at the end of the road find me what he.</body>
</review>
