<review author="Yojimbo" title="Batalla en el cielo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Compared to his previous work can be more accessible, more simple and less complex and complete. It is a different film. And what of different beat it pulse.</summary>
	<body>I had the opportunity to meet the director thanks to a work that we carry out in his time for his first feature film, Japan, a tough history performed by non-professional actors and that principle could prove very difficult screening by its aesthetics and rhythm.Shot on Super16mm with Scope (very well used and photographed) format, the film can be described as rare experience. Although it would understand that many viewers take them back this kind of film I have to confess that I saw with interest.He won the Golden camera at Cannes 2002, award which relaunched his career and succeeded in this film which premiered on October 14 in few rooms (only in Alphaville and Verdi) has had the opportunity to compete in this festival and presented at San Sebastian. the history of this film distributed by the always "indie" Golem is not easily summarized. He could tell that it is on a chauffeur (Marcos Hernández) and a morbid love affair with the daughter of his "master", a wealthy and beautiful young (Anapola Mushkadiz) dedicated to prostitution by taste. Marcos and his wife have kidnapped the baby from her family for a ransom, but the baby dies, something causing a deep sense of guilt to confess though can't you in frameworks. And everything leads to a tragic end.In few lines could thus gutting the film.But we must see it. I repeat that my I was mesmerizing. There are flat long, almost endless, but they do not tire.Sometimes seems to embrace the documentary style but without being so. Do sometimes tempts our patience and good taste with a couple of scenes of real fellatio (some of them surplus to not negatively predispose the Viewer)? but it is unclassifiable. And you can love or hate it. I prefer to stay in a term half and give a 7 because it is a film that comes out totally of schemes and is not be a crappy or an experiment of video art insufferable.Compared to his previous work can be more accessible, more simple and less complex and complete, but still continues to be a work needing view because I do not believe that there are history or prejudices in 99% of the viewers towards this kind of movies. It is a different film. And what of different beat it pulse.</body>
</review>
