<review author="Marta" title="V de Vendetta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite resentment of the big blockbusters based on comics this movie seems great</summary>
	<body>The truth is that I begin to be a little tired of this fashion to bring comic books to the big screen. It is not, in itself, have nothing against it, but these "streaks" (disasters, giant and dangerous animals, epic stories, etc) I get a little nervous. Creative problems or bet on insurance? I do not know, but it seems that they will not stop until that have adapted all adaptable. In the end, it doesn't matter. In recent years we have seen, to remember, "Batman", "X-Men" (1, 2 and 3, which is now), "A history of violence", "Fantastic four", "Spiderman", "Sin City", "Ghost World", "Hulk" and much more. Some leave much to be desired and others are quite well. "V for Vendetta" is the last adaptation I've seen and belongs to the second group. In fact, it is one of the films I have liked lately. Those who knew the comic do not seem to be too satisfied with his passage to the film. That, anyway, I am not surprised, because we often make adaptations - comics, books, works of theatre or whatever - disappoint fans of the original product. Film has its limitations and, usually, it is difficult not to leave something behind, not to mention that everyone makes their own idea of how is the story and this does not usually coincide with what it then see on the screen.I had not read the comic, so, first, I cannot comment on it, and second, I care a whit whether or not it is well adapted. I care about the film, and the film seems wonderful. As I said before, is the best I've seen lately, and that I tend to be leery of the big blockbusters based on comics. An interesting story, although, of course, it's not the most original of the world: on "1984" is evident. Fascinating characters, a good performance and a unique aesthetic. The only thing that I have left are those Pat "Matrix" which has at times - these Wachowski were due to forget that they were doing another film-but even abused this kind of efectistas resources. History and image are above the effects, something that for me is essential. I read in some places the film criticism by the subject of terrorism. Since then, it was clear that that would happen, though filmmakers (they are the Wachowski, is James McTeigue, which is not very clear who takes the reins here) have been secured to cover their backs. The debate arises from the movie itself, and the argument "them I have become what I am" is explicit and explosions do not seem to affect to any civilian. On the other hand, is that it sometimes seems that people know not to differentiate between the film and real life, very current though analogies of the film. Well, the criticism is always good, but take a movie as if it were a "Handbook for living" seems a little exaggerated. Not I tell you anything more about the argument because I think that it is a pleasure to watch a movie without knowing exactly what is going. I will only say that go you criticisms to the Government, media, revolutions and charismatic characters you like. There is that.</body>
</review>
