<review author="Rafa Martín" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Gibson performed a kind of cinema that serves much more instinct than intelligence. It is not an extraordinary film, but yes it is a great, great experience.</summary>
	<body>My favorite movie of 2006 together with children of men, that does not mean to be so "good film" as infiltrators or The Queen, for instance. Contradictory? Yes but Apocalypto, as well as the genius of Cuarón, not adheres to the usual film standards. Don't use this word very often because I am suspicious of the meaning, but "visceral" is an adjective that this wonder comes as ring to the finger: an exhibition of strength of 125 minutes where the image takes over and makes the decline of civilization maya in the best adventure film of the past twenty years, at the height of Master &amp; Commander (saving the differences) and sister of the equally fascinating La Selva Esmeralda.No blood both a sociological study as a truly brutal hosts, Apocalypto Odyssey presents a fundamental idea: keep things simple. Gibson has been called fascist, reactionary, religious fanatic, but is also a traditionalist in the best sense of the word: one who despises authority and civilization when they are missing their main objective, and not only hamper the development of the man that he annihilated. So Jaguar claw, his family and his tribe living in peace and harmony, until some idiots theoretically more developed kidnap them and offer them as sacrifices human to control the population. What fucking, do ein?. As for Gibson rules change by the time Jaguar claw escapes and poured over the heads of the wretched pursuing more donkey revenge seen in years on a cinema screen. Reader friend: Gibson is Charles Dickens nor Camilo José Cela, to see wonderful you surgery and lengthy dissertations of society, for that is Babel, surely that project in the room of to the side what do do when pursued you a troop of Maya? Run, obvious.Like his previous film, the passion of the Christ, Apocalypto is shot entirely in their original language, in this case mauya with subtitles. It is one of the small luxuries that its director and producer can afford and could frankly, have been folded perfectly (although we would lose the effort of its protagonists to speak that language, which has not on the other hand to the ear, unlike the Aramaic). However, is part of the way Martin Riggs into the world in which these people live, where peace, harmony and the messing of the tribe of Jaguar claw (which highlights the scenes where tease her partner Mellado, unable to have children, so it is forced to eat tapir balls)(, sounds like) contrast with the environment full of the great maya city, from whose main pyramid a priest bastard is dedicated to get the heart to la peña and slice them the head in front of a Queen who seems a clone of Paris Hilton and a small Prince, fat as a seal and with a face of child bastard that makes you want to pull down stairs.Essentially, Gibson relies on the power of visual of one of the best sunsets in scene of the year. No frills many, out of the use of the slow, but there are many turnkey digital camera that puts us directly on the skin of the characters. Is a film that leaves no also spend much time since it begins until it ends: the Odyssey of Jaguar claw hardly lasts a day, and there is no many ellipsis of time, which causes sensation of exhaustion and claustrophobia (there are scenes that last nearly quarter of hour, twenty minutes), but this man knows to shoot: the picture is excellent and the soundtrack, although it is everywhere, accompanies the action without being annoying. Wealth is in limelight, gestures and looks (great Rudy Youngblood) and the use of the colors (slaves painted white, which are going to be slaughtered, covered in blue; and Jaguar claw covered in black mud, in the last moments of the film).But again, this is an action movie, where the good guys are very good and the bad are some real bastards, in particular eye in the Centre and zero Wolf (do you ever seen so acojonante name?). Everything is black and white for Gibson, what's complicated life. That is why what the film attacks directly to the thirst for blood of the Viewer. Warning: this movie is violent. Not artistically violent as what Tarantino. Non-subnormalmente violent as what makes Eli Roth. I mean brutally violent. Shattered skulls, devoradas sides by wild animals, human graves, empalamientos, arrows in the coco, stabbed and the hosts fist of life, without much recreate, but cut a hair that I mean. And as far as action is concerned, I assure you, Apocalypto barely known rival: is frantic, fast, and some scenes are simply acojonantes everything that relates to their last 40 minutes, in which a game of seven warriors tries to give especially hunting Jaguar claw, that attempts to return to what's left of his people to save his wife and his son.Damien King, in a video clip of his new reggaeton theme "your breasts are hot, hot".This movie is a real experience for the senses. Regardless of what Gibson in real life (where are you treated as a moscón that disrupts the quiet life of the politically correct), this guy has found his own voice, in a moment of his career that has reached a point in which can do what pleases real. Instead of playing football in the big leagues, this guy is dedicated to make the kind of films that he wants to see, what makes it a true outsider in the industry, capable of connecting with the public because not complicated life the least and performs a kind of cinema that serves much more instinct than intelligence. It is not an extraordinary film, but yes it is a great, great experience.</body>
</review>
