<review author="Yojimbo" title="Princesas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The day that we know make this quality and invoice but not many movies?Queens? and?Princesses? It should be a double celebration, because people will go to see more movies Spanish and at the same time less propaganda.</summary>
	<body>This is the first time I scored things during a film screening: didn't forget any detail to discuss it here.To start going with great suspicion to see the new film by Ken Loach Spanish. Sorry for the comparison, but himself is become that, is not a nickname say you hate. In fact the director is who seems to hate the world in the living and the living to make their social complaints. And it seems that it uses marginal as allies for their ideological frustrations to explain in his films.To begin with, the script remains committed to crucify and condemn in the most absolute hell to their "heroines". And the hell he is responsible for well, reflect in some situations of true form (for example, sequences in the Casa de Campo with license plates of cars hidden under a pixel). And Don Fernando is responsible for not giving their protagonists escape chance. And perfectly exemplifies it the definition of "Princess" who gives the character of Candela Peña all prostitutes apart from fascists are victims. The character of Candela Peña noble intends to enlarge the breasts. But implies that it is temporary. That should be his lie, because a character who has a goal clear but have to do something horrible would like to leave it with the utmost urgency. And this is not the case.The character of Micaela Nevárez is the more credible as a Dominican without papers to which he is not forced to prostitution. But it also acts as a "praying mantis".The trouble with pamphleteering film is there who creates them.And they don't separate any favors who portrays.And in this case, as De Aranoa want to dignify them and turn them into heroines (makes a parallel on Superman better used than in Kill Bill 2), not only write philosophical phrases that loose when it comes to coffee table about God and life, but that also puts them of teachers of sexuality (trembles Lorena Berdún) or introduces some enviable character within the profession, as the darling of any Minister who gives them a limousine ride.There is no shortage of stories not developed (like candle and Micaela) with their "boyfriends" that could Suomi director's ideological discourse.But importantly, the good thing about the film, which are a couple of things: the actresses and the Mise en scène. This time Fernando León has dared to take the camera on his shoulder and makes it a less stiff staging. The actresses are award, and it will be highlight discoveries of Antonio Durán Morris and Llum Barrera as excellent side.The film can also count on the privilege that Manu Chao has composed a song for the movie "Call Me Street", play on words almost worthy of Medem. Resumiendo, the day we can make movies of this quality and invoice but not so many "Queens" and "Princess" will have to do a double celebration, because people will go to see more movies Spanish and at the same time less propaganda.</body>
</review>
