<review author="Yojimbo" title="Coach Carter" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is certainly not a movie for personal use. And if not, how can we explain that an American movie ends up with a defeat of the protagonists? in extremis?</summary>
	<body>Based on facts (although sometimes little credible). Coach Carter is the story of Ken Carter, a player and coach of renown that happens to teach to a disastrous basketball team. And when there is chaos there to put a little order, the character of Samuel l. Jackson imposes it by establishing respect and discipline. And the first point that distinguishes this film is funny its initiative: by signing a contract to train them. A contract in which undertake to logical and understandable basic rules: get minimum notes, attend classes and sit in the first ranks wear a tie. This last point can already be the perfect excuse for some mendrugo to qualify for "facha". Well mendrugo, I recommend that you keep not reading, you shalt enfermito: P funny Lo of the film is that the inevitable but necessary "self-improvement" history is not with too much Manichaeism. It does not carry situations extreme where many viewers we miss the hands to the head or rebufamos of disbelief and boredom by knowing in advance what will happen. This film is a tad different.Despite multiple claims racial (and racist) in some cases, be welcomed personal progression of the team and some of its players, their "tripping" with the early successes and the consequences entailed by see you get something.But basketball is not the subject of the film, but the personal fulfillment. It is not about winning, as well confused the coach at one point in the film, but earn merits to improve our lives and have more opportunities. It is clear that the setting can remain a little distant, but is can draw good lessons from this story. While there he portrayed a horrific education when in slums a high percentage of youth ends in jail or dead, merely arise not to follow a life which is practically already given is a challenge. And a challenge for many other people who may be in the same situation but not in the same circumstances.It is certainly not a movie for personal use. And if not, how can we explain that an American movie ends up with a defeat of the protagonists "in extremis"? Normally it is upside down? is not it?</body>
</review>
