<review author="Yojimbo" title="León y Olvido" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film that achieved the opposite of what is intended to, and precisely does not do any favors to the people with Down syndrome.</summary>
	<body>There are films that I call "kamikazes" or suicide bombers. They are those which from its approach are intended to be bad, possessing the commitment of people who believe in it and still sign above for its quality in carrying out his death certificate. But her they sign in an industry which called as such.This should be the case. But the "authors" and "festivalitos" it gives them by giving awards and praise.This film shot entirely in La Coruña has a distant intention to make a tender and emotional portrait about two brothers, one of them with Down syndrome. And the truth is that the idea is original. And actor, Guillem Jiménez, is not bad. But the intention has not.At least in the film.The ability of the director lies in getting laughter trying to do something serious.Want to do a portrait of integration and propaganda at the expense of people with Down syndrome, but spared no mediocrity to write hilarious sequences such as the Civil Guard, the outburst exhibitionist?It is a film that achieved the opposite of what is intended to, and precisely does disservice to people with syndrome of Down.Por other side note the poor performance of Marta Larralde, actress who usually convincing in a role that does not follow guideline any falling unsympathetic, that does not have a "curve" defined nor justified and maintains an incestuous relationship with her brother.Gary Piquer making decent pimp (not lost the acting and the setting in scene of the robbery to his girlfriends shop) passes without penalty or glory.And already not me sequencing with the picture (is not illuminated, but alumbrada), mounting, etc?I am sure that there will be more than one person who would not be in the opening credits.One hour and forty and so many minutes. A recommendation for those who have to see her: Please id with the predisposition to see a bad movie that wants to be good (has won a few awards) and accompanied by look. And to have a good time, because certainly not going to see a movie complaint, but "Rain man" to the Galician.</body>
</review>
