<review author="Yojimbo" title="Mar adentro" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>They decided to leave the film as a pamphleteering plea to suicide. I do not know you, but regardless of my opinion on euthanasia there is nothing that most fuck me me manipulated emotionally with a cheater script.</summary>
	<body>What mainly remains in the minds of viewers is what counts the film: history. And to be more specific, the story and its focus.Alejandro Amenábar is a great director with a lot of talent, and I must admit that from the time that it was announced that it was set to direct this story surprised me pleasantly this turn of theme. Until the moment the more I liked him was Abre los ojos, of course with a much more original than thesis approach or Los Otros.Pero Mar Adentro is his wife film. And it was a success?One, they chose a story and a real character in a controversial situation for Spanish society, which would ensure the homeland public interest.Two, the good do Amenábar and the fact of joining with the impressive Bardem is a tandem may be sold as well as Spielberg-Cruise. At least within our borders.Not only got unanimous approval of critics and the public, but it was also taken as reference moral to unleash the euthanasia controversy again and picked up many awards by your great Bill (including the Oscar).Do but still think this movie as a bad film perfectly hecha.¿Por what?Precisely because the two previous points.First: he chose the story of Ramon Sampedro as a martyr for a cause such as euthanasia ("set of methods that produce a death without suffering, to shorten the torment of agony or very painful and irreversible disease.") (Great encyclopedia Larousse). This "character" was erected as a leader of this cause, but he really wanted to commit suicide.I.e., I wanted an "assisted suicide". It is not a play on words. It was just that. And it is clear that he, like Maggie in Million Dollar Baby, might have been suicide at any time. In a rude manner, but could have if its intention had been real.In this film of Eastwood already leaves Amenábar in evidence (of attitudes).And if we already start to deceive with the theme, we are wrong.Secondly, precisely because of the good do Amenábar and Bardem get a manipulative play emotional and conceptually. I cried and I laughed as I saw. I left lead by heart, but turn the lights I felt anger. And much. For if you fall in the logic of the film, you realize that sells the suicide as the only alternative to the quadriplegics. And it is precisely the opposite. 99% Of the people who are in the same situation that the protagonist wants to live, that is why the case of Sampedro was much vaunted.But anything to get in the movie someone in the same situation of the protagonist, but with the opposite attitude? If. A priest. Go by God (never better said). but couldn't be anyone other than religious? Someone as Ramon?No.se end you the movie. So they decided to leave the film as a pamphleteering plea to suicide (with marketing added the new superstar Ramona Maneiro confessing that she helped him die and accompanying his confession with books and spaces in the newspapers for his opinion).I do not know you, but regardless of my opinion on euthanasia there is nothing that most fuck me me manipulated emotionally with a cheater script. And as I care more what I have her think bad.</body>
</review>
