<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="V de Vendetta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Highly recommended movie, with a very elaborate plot that makes that we are looking forward to know the outcome from the first frame</summary>
	<body>A thorough study of the poster may annoy us throughout the film. So I recommend that if you want to see the movie, not mireis that this deserves the poster bears a lot as to which os they spoil nothing of it. What is more, not deberiaís or read critical, is going to be they unveil you something this essential film. By the way, is from the creators of Matrix (although much milder and I dare say that better than the last two deliveries). And that I don't tell you that it comes from a comic.The film is developed in a futuristic England that has become a police state. United States is mired in an internal civil war and England has become a superpower. Within the reigning chaos by the new regime (motivated by a terrorist attack that exalted the current leader) comes a figure calling himself "V" it's overthrow by all means to power. In these, a young woman is going to be raped by a sort of police force when the mysterious "V" makes them a cut of hair to the flying knife that leaves them nickel. Who will be "V"? or better yet what is all this?.Well, we have a movie of those that better not blinking because you lose details and, although at the end put all the pieces in place, much better follow from the origin. The story they tell us is really good, with futuristic (though not much) scenarios that give the pego perfectly. In addition, as "V" have mask, therefore not we can criticize him nothing for the performance by the actor who plays. And we highlight the Mise en scène that has, with a few very interesting photography details that make this a great movie. In the bad, that spare you half an hour of roll. It is not be wrong this time, but gives a court action that you can get out of the movie.In short, highly recommended movie, with a very elaborate plot that makes that we are looking forward to know the outcome from the first frame. By the way, the end is great, those who you would like to see all films.</body>
</review>
