<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Campamento Jesús" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One is embarrassed by those children who applies cruel brainwashed and forced to follow, with suffering, the desquiciados principles of this new formula of Western fundamentalism.</summary>
	<body>Imagine that one day, while watching the news or documentary from the history channel, assists perplexed to the homogeneous and radical formation of the Hitler youth or in the present tense, some Muslim children trained by Taliban. Probably think it's horrible to educate in this way to the innocent mind of a child still in the throes of training, and also think to do would be impossible the implementation of similar tactics among children and adolescents in our 'advanced and democratic' societies. But if you are lucky enough to be able to view the clairvoyant and splendid documentary Jesus camp (Jesus Camp), nominated for an Oscar for his category this year above him seems more debatable.The documentary by Heidi Ewing and Rachel Grady is shot in the United States.UU. and focusing on the rampant and powerful citizens community created around the Evangelical Church. Specifically, the film narrates how are recruited children for about 10 years and lower ages for the encampment of North Dakota, Kids of fire, directed by Becky Smith. Once there, one presence, with no less perplexity to the above view the initial recruitment phase, how these children are being raised in 'alleged' Christian values with the more radical religious fundamentalism practices.They urge to regain control of his country, to the cry that are soldiers of Christ, to avoid 'pollution' from non-Christian ethnicities such as Muslim or otherwise. They worship which step of Holy week a photograph of President Bush (declared follower of Evangelicals) and ask Jesus that you enlighten this to put the entire nation under Dios ("one nation under God"). These messages are presented in spectacular 'shows' similar to a concert, with light and sound effects, some children who come to enter into a trance at the moment Summit of the Act. It is crying live tear when they pray and repent of their sins, or is how their bodies convulse as if diese them St. Vitus dance when the Holy Spirit will be joining them.But the documentary goes beyond, and shows how after all this religious movement, there is a manifest interest in hoarding the political control of the country's main institutions. Indeed this, and no other, the main message that machaconamente repeated in much of acts of cerebral centrifuge, asking for vote way outright for groups of power similar to which leads Bush in the White House. Thus, these religious 'shows' refers more power and to identify the enemy (those who did not embrace the faith, i.e., different) to homogenize society on their evangelical principles. So there are many differences between movements such as this and, for example, others as Aryan supremacy.In the documentary, the counterpoint to this group put him from the influential radio show Ring of Fire, by Robert f. Kennedy Jr. and Mike Papantonio. In space warns about the brutal growth of this movement, which reaches between 80 and 100 million noteamericanos. Allegedly this group knows how the constitutional separation of State and religion and how take advantage of the tender minds of children to spread his message of division between generations.Completed the documentary, one forgives, between hallucination and dread, about the fact that someone with similar ideas is the President of the leading power in the world. But, above all, one is embarrassed by those children who applies cruel brainwashed and forced to follow, with suffering, the desquiciados principles of this new formula of Western fundamentalism.</body>
</review>
