<review author="Nobody's perfect" title="13 tzameti" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The term thriller falls short when it comes to frame this film that recovers the best of the genre of film noir, which is approaching from a new approach.</summary>
	<body>Do the directorial debut of director of Georgian origin? although settled in France - Géla Babluani is a striking and brilliant tale full of rawness and tension that make this film a strong promise of recent times. Filmed in black and white, with the characteristic visual stylization of the best film noir, which adds some "dirt" on the image that makes it off in realism, 13 Tzameti gradually introduces us, with a formal touch expressionist, in an environment increasingly squalid and suffocating, corrupted and degraded, town of "characters vampire who feed on the blood of others". In every film noir movie, the criminal act is the crux of the plot? disservice to makes the trailer for the film the viewer gutting it - that the director approaching gradually getting to create ever greater expectation. Babluani shows us how its protagonist/anti-hero (played by George Babluani, brother of the director) is approaching towards him, the crux of the argument, or rather is involved in it, voluntarily and involuntarily at the same time. Reaching a point where there is no possible return into something that started almost as a single game, follow the instructions in a letter addressed to someone else. The viewer with ability to empathize with the main character can end up accumulating high levels of tension and nervousness grabbed to the armchair, imbued with an atmosphere of growing claustrophobic as the screenplay progresses. The characters are minimally profiled in the objective and material issues of their lives. Little is known of their motivations. However, they are deeply analyzed in his psychology and embody perfectly (perhaps by this biographical minimalism) the sensation of absolute solitude, isolation, uprooting and helplessness. Characters who commit the most despicable acts, without any moral question. It is that, at the end and all, what impact us. The perversion of a human being completely dehumanised. The end result is a shocking metaphor for the absence of morality and conscience that can reign in human nature. This way became the film in an arid and harsh criticism of the morality of the society, without any concession to the hope of trust in goodness or reason for the man. Without mercy, unadorned, 13 Tzameti shows us the worst of what is capable human beings, in their not so much money, that yearning also, but of extreme sensations that escape from normality and approaching the darker morbidity. The merit is that everything is possible and credible. Is the man a wolf to man? Bablauni answered in the affirmative to the question with this film. Pure pessimistic fatalism brought to the screen with great skill.</body>
</review>
