<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Días de cine" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do Cinema days opens Friday in many rooms, but if the blog to blog work? It will not last long.</summary>
	<body>The team of the other side of the bed, the two sides of the bed and football days mark another originality, cinema days. And it is what promises, nothing. The action is situated on this occasion in the late 1970s where a neurotic film director tries to make a demanding film with a singer who lived his best years as a child prodigy. The pressures of censorship, which puts the pasta and others, make the original idea of the filmmaker - Alberto San Juan - a film of uncover with Martian invasions and other these rants.So at first glance the goer informed well observed, except cañís annotations, the script looks like too much to Ed Wood - one of my favorite movies. But San Juan is Johnny Depp or David Serrano is Tim Burton. They are not even the Ozores brothers who did these things, but at the time had grace. And this film is the kind with two moderately fortunate jokes that appear in the trailer.The main failure that have had this time, is that the public who go looking for another unlikely vaudeville of torbe's couples will find with a melodrama with folk overtones. As well as the characters in his previous works were more or less identifiable stereotypes with the Viewer, in cinema days the time, situations and the characterizations - rub that in some cases the Carnivalesque - will not come to that sector.Do on vis to vis with Serrano, told me that his main references were the aforementioned Ed Wood and? Bullets over Broadway! and he was so taste, Hey. Even in his megalomania reached compare acting to San Juan with Woody Allen. And he proclaimed his teachers Berlanga and Azcona. As ugly as these events was said the director of the film that write you it the direction of his camel, because I enmudecí.That Yes. Gave the nail when I asked him if he made films that he would like to see in the cinema is recurring when you have nothing to ask - and answered me that did not know, that to him him out as well. As churros, I was about to add. As snap said that the last film Spanish that I had seen, not like anything and I did not want to give the title. I suspect that you referred to that acábabamos see was ten minutes.PD: what I must highlight positive is the performance of Nathalie Poza and Fernando Tejero. Do are great as folk of Valladolid and? the artist MOM?. Others - Malena Alterio, Miguel Rellán, San Juan?-are well clear, but their roles are always, be they already know. As the garlic they repeat.Do PDI: days of film Debuts Friday in many rooms, but if the blog to blog work? It will not last long.</body>
</review>
