<review author="Florinda Chic" title="13 tzameti" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>As a perverse tale Babluani presents its own Alicia travelling to the other side of the mirror and taking tea with dozens of crazy Milliner.</summary>
	<body>When you have nothing to lose, that could have been the promo of this magnificent French film. 13 Tzameti speaks of descents to hell, searches of treasures, fear and varmints. As a tale perverse - but most are - Babluani presents its own Alicia travelling to the other side of the mirror and taking tea with dozens of crazy Milliner.If - as it was not my case - the spectator comes without having seen or the trailer he enjoyed best the first minutes of the film. If I get to know that it was so revealing, not I hang up, it would have instead hung to the architects of the same. My apologies for this.Which nobody expected, after the entrance to the sickly universe in which delves inadvertently the protagonist, big surprises of script or unexpected turns. Babluani in its complexity, has made a simple film and takes it calmly using numerous subjective levels. A Spanish director - which I will not mention to not give clues - tried this same subject and I must say, that it took party in my opinion. But it is evident that the intention of the French is not the same, the footage we anguish but absolutely minimal form.In this case, highlight the excellent photography is not a discrete form of score I've bored. The film is narrated in an exquisite black and white that left spectators but me personally I am excited to. So a 10 to 13 Tzameti, which - I'm-: tzameti is 13 in Georgian, homage of the filmmaker to his frivolous natalPD City: in the Renoir, Saturday, at 22 in the evening, watching this movie two armchairs in front of me? It was Pedrooooooooooooo. I, that I always wanted to be a girl Almodóvar as Bibí, as Miguel Bosé, go with Madonna in a limousine and have breakfast in Tiffanny´s with the I was very tempted to wish him luck for the Goya tell that I didn't talk to her, ask her brand of lacquer? What was that it set me. I remained insolitamente in silence though out, my companions looked at me, they say diossssssss is truth?</body>
</review>
