<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>His great triumph is the film as an allegation have been raised without forgetting of quality film-making</summary>
	<body>Dear Mr Edward Zwick: you don't know who I am I am and probably never know never. I'm just a poor goer that goes to you with the firm intention to offer you my most sincere apologies. Apologies I think necessary because for months, I have argued that you wasn't the right director to carry out a project with a theme and a very attractive actors.A few days ago, thanks to the kindness of Warner Bros. Spain and the mediation of muchocine.net, had the opportunity of seeing "Blood diamond" (Blood Diamond). My initial expectations, find me with a correct film devoid of force not could have been more wrong.Always blamed you to his films a lack of passion which, in my view, was necessary for the stories that shows: "Legends of the fall" was the great work which should have been halfway and another, to a lesser extent because their script seems lower, it could be said of "The last samurai". Don't me wrong, they are good movies, but they are not great films.In contrast, "Blood diamond"? This is cinema of truth. There they showed you all the passion that the film required. Perhaps his style is not so striking and recognizable as Spielberg and Scorsese; you are more invisible to the Viewer, but this time has given the best of himself and has managed to bring out the best in others (something very important in a director).It is true that help a great script by Charles Leavitt, entering fully on the essentials of the subject treat, without wasting time on unnecessary explanations. A script that explains the characters perfectly. A script without phrases more or less. A nearly perfect script that, perhaps, only you pantry two or three pages final (although I may not be annoying). But we destripemos nothing, that you never know who we can be reading.I congratulate you, Mr Zwick, because I believe that its actors have never been so well. The three main actors are great actors and that they are good is not difficult, it is true, but what worthwhile is not that they are good but what good are. Djimon Hounsou and Leonardo DiCaprio are incredible live their roles and make them us live, they fill the screen in an interpretative duel in height in which us Smash in the face so far that can reach a human being, albeit for very different reasons.I set aside to a Jennifer Connelly, forgotten in the awards this year, which is as well as fellow and has even greater role than I expected. To make matters worse, his scenes with DiCaprio are pure chemistry, something very difficult to see today in the cinema because it is often forgotten that the chemistry is something that comes from the brain, is the result of intelligence and cannot be achieved simply with join two hot body and show some skin. And you know, the writer knows that his actors know it; Why DiCaprio and Connelly throw sparks in this confrontation that remain among the most radical pragmatism and idealism more combative. I know I repeat myself but I can't find another way of saying it: the actors in your film eat the screen.Could tell the wonderful photography Eduardo Serra, soundtrack James Newton Howard, impressive sound or the Assembly of a Steven Rosenblum at the third maybe wins the oscar; they are all very important part in the creation of some of the most memorable action scenes of recent years.What I would be very difficult to explain, Mr Zwick, is exciting to me was his film, the heartbreaking and emotional are some of their scenes or to what extent enjoyed and suffered at the same time, seeing this portrait of what have done you to Africa for everyone. All this without feeling, at any time, that were selling me a pamphlet.Because that success in the initial approach is its great triumph: the movie as an allegation have been raised without forgetting to do whatever you have to do; film quality.Therefore, thank you Mr Zwick and we again apologize for my lack of confidence.Sincerely: Jeremy Fox.PD: If you ask my opinion, I would give his film a 9.5 on 10.PD 2: I know, he has not asked me my opinion, but the lovers are so hubristic.PS 3: in moonfleet.es can see the poster in the film Spanish if it is of interest.</body>
</review>
