<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Cry Wolf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film Institute kids giving almost the age of eternal COU repeaters, who invent a macabre game that seems to become a reality. A surprising blend of juvenile horror genre has been with a script easy to follow, a few actors that give the paste and a tension that keeps you awake.</summary>
	<body>I said my teenage sister, "take me to see that the girl with a knife on the puddle of blood" (Cry Wolf, actually said that descriptive gender does not use it much). And I thought I my himself "before I pluck an egg and I insert it by where it spoil the cucumbers". But hey, as is that these movies of fear for teenagers are cortitos, and sometimes have to invest in hermanismo, because there was no other remedy that see it.The film is a group of Institute students invent a game following a murder mystery in the village. The game consists of creating a serial killer fake, based on an email invented, to have fun with each other. But the thing is twisted when mysterious things begin to happen. Ah, I forgot that, is a closed group of friends where it comes a new. It will be an important fact? Habré wanted you give an arcane touch to something that doesn't? Keep reading and you will know.Watch that I went with reluctance, that did if not accentuate that footage progressed and all topics were coming out. Furthermore, with good possibilities to get naked, not leaving or one, which is why my morale was declining. But hey, with a not too bad actors, a protagonist that not is if acts well but has a miradita to. and an argument that holds, because the thing pulled to the front. And coming to the end, when in the two minute you said "That's the bad" you the doubts arise, then look back and say horrified "I liked Cry Wolf". Surprising, since then.In short, Film Institute kids giving almost the age of eternal COU repeaters (if I'm old, what?), who invent a macabre game that seems to become a reality. A surprising blend of juvenile horror genre has been with a script easy to follow, a few actors that give the paste and a tension that keeps you awake.I confess, I liked.Besitos.P.D: Here's an excerpt from my meeting with moviegoers anónimo:Tito Chinchan: good afternoon, my name is Tito Chinchan. moviegoers anonymous: Buenaaaaas taaaardes, Tito.TC: come to confensar something that torments me.CA: Diiiinos, Tito.TC: not it and explain it.CA: Not you preoooooocupes, Tiiiiiiiito.TC: is that. I liked Cry Wolf!CA: Ohhhh, córcholis, by the duchies of Garci, as it has happened?TC: No thing, save me, want to enjoy with Kurosawa and company.CA: We will see that it can be done.</body>
</review>
