<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El ángel exterminador" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Infinitely rich, distinct, surreal film risky until exhaustion. The film is essential to healthy dialogue mesa-camilla then.</summary>
	<body>Random not presented Buñuel with faith: nor agreed. That sort of intolerance in the theological field formed a single work that came to represent, in part, the convulsive panorama political and ideological of the Spain that Don Luis was forced to flee. All this hectic ideology of militant apostasy and aesthetic anarchy have are added formidably written in the exterminating Angel, which is worth as much as a vehicle strictly film which as a personality profile complex carved in adversity and in certain school of free thought and almost unique talent (Lorca, Dalí, Alberti).The enormous ability of Buñuel (and infinite risk that contracts) is to make plausible entirely absurd, rayana situation in the injustice: a large group of guests invited by the burghers Nóbile can not (in literal form) leave a room even though no physical evidence prevented an act so basic and simple. "The natural course of those days of confinement them is a wild instinct for survival that collides head-on with the Protocol and the educated and civilized ways exhibited before the desastramiento of the situation."During the filming of "Viridiana" I met the writer José Bergamín, who told me that he intended to write a play with the title of "The exterminating Angel". I told him that it was a magnificent title and that if he was going down the street and saw announced, would come to see the show. As Bergamín never wrote the work, I wrote asking for the rights of the title. "Replied me that I didn't need to ask them, given that those words appeared in the book of revelation." The origin of the title thus explained Buñuel. The exterminating Angel is the Chronicle of a shipwreck. Indeed the work which is freely based called "The castaways of Providence Street", never written, but prefigured in the mind of Buñuel, Luis Alcoriza, his right hand in all the Mexican experience. And we must understand the film as a shipwreck and how survivors must learn to communicate to achieve out of the confinement and leave the island / room. It would have been better make history in England (had Buñuel) because the society there is extremely educated and all that education and refinement much suited the plot of the film, which came to be the simple idea that, under appropriate conditions, the human being is capable of more perverse, but she is attributed (by nature, by culture) the most sublime things. In very summary words, the exterminating Angel is a portrait of the human, but screened by surrealist evidence decadence. Panic, fear of death or loneliness may be waste of a surreal way of understanding reality. There are philosophers whose absolute writing revolves around the idea of absurdity that is death: life is an inertia, life is a continuum, and not a continuum which can be (unrealistically) fragmented, mutilated.The guests are deplorable, superior in an almost nazi sense of the term: the effort of Buñuel gazes up the impossible the aborregamiento of an embebecida and haughty, cultured aristocracy who despises all forms alien to their benefit, its strict protocol. It may seem a joke who attend the film with an excess of critical (or movie buff) spirit. You have to want to go beyond and understand that Buñuel made an activities, a slapstick, a descent to the embarrassment that the world has encopetada rabble that looks of glancing to others by the mere fact of is different. This 21st century newly lighting already has been filling the term "otherness", which is a Word, a semantic resource horrifying to designate the evidence of the other, their interference in our world, that can (all) also be yours.Film indispensable to then make healthy dialogue mesa-camilla: gives equal that we liked much, little or that we consider that it is a real pain unbearable. Everything is accepted. It just has a little of everything and brings together film in height and immeasurable boredom. To me the review filled me with joy (many before then) of a film I saw in times of University with the food by gongorinas fever head and an exalted sense of injustice in the world. Other times they are now or are always the same and travisten to confuse our generational daze.</body>
</review>
