<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El nombre de la rosa" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Medieval thriller of theological crimes, film noir with Gothic purple, very well done commercial cinema for enjoyment of the parish of lovers of Sherlock Holmes, by Borges and Caravaggio. Does anyone give more?</summary>
	<body>For a time was very considered that having read the name of the rose. Umberto Eco was a writer with more shadows lights for the general public and was the first time (not then the last) that a Professor of semiotics enfangaba in fictions rather than encouraging as it was, that is, brainy unaffordable for the uninitiated title essay (reader in fable, apocalyptic and integrated or works open). They were all books of head of the College of letters or the always curious reader, hardened in thought, tireless diver filigree of, in the words of a good friend, the backroom of the language. After the book, best-seller, boom, milestone in the literature of consumption of the eighties, ECHO threw this acquired new fame and gave birth to their Apostilles to the name of the Rose: booklet of varia lesson in which the writer, as an extra on the dvd that we consume, interrogating the reader, questioned the nature of the fact of reading and gave, to galore, punches, files, anecdotarios, unrelated to the plot of the book, but interlocking chapters therein. And all this mass of reflections of literary writing about the film rope? A little of all that is the film that aroma of the same character (joyously semiotic, as I would like to echo) culturalist as the book. Annaud does not fall into the trap of making a film about a book: is obviously unnecessary, and Moreover, useless. Annaud recreates a detective-medievalist universe dirty, rough, relegating the abundant latines of the book and its corporeal theological discourse to mild strokes that do not alter, at any time, the agile spirit of his work. Let's say that the Eco Apostilles aquilinocarsin (very metaphorically written) in the movie: all thins, everything is simplified, everything is contaminated by a formidable precision, which differentiates cinema (Word in movement) with the literature (Word that requires the necessary decoder, i.e. the reader complicit).Annaud is ambitious: raises his film as a very demanding RAID in history and far from trying to monopolize a project that it was especially gratifying was accompanied by a director of photography mythical (Tonino Delli Colli) who drank in Rembrandt, Caravaggio to imbue its light the darkness of the abbeys of the middle ages. The plot of the name of the rose is very simple: on the eve of a Benedictine Abbey in a theological Summit some monks appear ominously killed. Friar William of Baskerville and his young disciple Adso of Melk seen the malign influence of a book. Crimes, books: nothing new.Behind there is a stark vision of the tyranny of the Catholic Church and the notable role of monasteries in transmitting (or hide or neuter) a culture. Own Librarian (magnificent tribute to Jorge Luis Borges) is blind. And the book that is cause of all the crimes is one of Aristoteles on laughter because to say Jorge of Burgos, the blind librarian cited above, laughter foreshadows the knowledge, its truth more playful and less controllable, and but do the longest review I transcribe what he says about it because there is no waste: "Laughter releases the villager in the fear of the devil, because on the feast of fools also the devil seems poor and stupid, and, therefore, controllable." But this book could teach that freedom from fear of the devil is an act of wisdom. When he laughs, while the wine gorgotea in his throat, the villager feels master, because he has invested relationships of domination: but this book podríaenseñar to the learned ingenious, and since then illustrious artifices that legitimize such investment. It would then be transformed into operation of the intellect what in the unthinkable gesture of the villager still, and fortunately, is the belly operation. That laughter is the man's own is a sign of our limitation as sinners. But how many corrupt minds like yours of this book drawn the extreme conclusion, according to which the laughter would be the end of the man! For some moments, laughter distracts the villager of fear. But the law is imposed through fear, whose real name is fear of God. And this book could skip the luciferin spark that go a new fire around the world; and the laughter would be the new art, ignored even by Prometheus, capable of annihilating the fear. "The villager who laughs, while he laughs, not cares die?"An absolutely masterful Sean Connery makes Friar William of Baskerville and gives the character of a lightweight spark of grace, eloquence and naturalness. Not so with a rookie Christian Slater in the role of the apprentice, whose hieratismo (then amplified with the years) equal should be up.</body>
</review>
