<review author="Pablo" title="Hostel" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film gore correct policticamente disappointed by a little attractive and fairly simple plot</summary>
	<body>Wrapped under the mantle of Tarantino Presents comes to us a tape of the director of Cabin Fever which seeks to transport us to the dirtiest human instincts via a very well filmed horror film but with a fairly weak script. "We are facing the second film as Eli Roth director, inspired by real events that a coversación surguierón with his friend Harry Knowles (webmaster of Aintitcoolnews.com)."We were talking about the more sickly things that could be found on the Internet. Something that was beyond the already usual fatal accident skateboard or about those two girls Japanese vomiting each at the mouth of the other in a bathtub when Harry I spend a link to a website where for only $10,000, in Thailand, anyone who were willing you could join a room"give him a loaded pistol and provide another human being to kill him".Roth had the revelation of creating a film in which three students begin to make backpack tourism until that without realizing account are victims of a murky business which consists of torturing to death a human being for a substantial amount of money.After being a day talking with his friend Quentin Tarantino, Eli finished telling him the new approach of his film. Tarantino reportedly "went crazy". "Quentin is an animated person, and never had seen him so excited for something." Do you said something as well as:? damn! You have to write that script! It is the most fucking terrifying idea I have heard in a long time for a film of fear! "Leave aside everything with what you are now, and start to write that script but already."Inspired by the enthusiasm of Tarantino, Roth disconnected the phone, shut down the mail, locked herself in the Office and began frantically writing. "He called Quentin every two or three days, when I atascaba at some point in history, and he understandably reassured me and told me that he was going in the right direction or helped me move forward," remember Roth. "It was amazing to have someone like him as a sounding board". I found myself writing twenty pages daily. "He could not stop."Finally we can say that Eli to created a film gore correct policticamente in which the marketing and distribution of this create in the viewer a few spirits who are disappointed with a little attractive and fairly simple plot. The first half-hour reminds the American Pie films, the Femina emerging are only saved from this first part which are a real treat for the eyes. The torture scenes are very small and barely spent all its potential, also most of the scenes that announce the official posters do not go into the film.</body>
</review>
