<review author="Iñigo" title="Hostel" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When there is not much more to offer, more practical usually approaching people with renowned or draw attention to trying to sow panic</summary>
	<body>Eli Roth, sponsored again by a major character, in this case the ineffable Quentin Tarantino, insists draw attention and create controversy in any way possible to attract viewers to the viewing of his works. When there is not much more to offer, more practical usually approaching people with renowned or draw attention to trying to sow panic. Both cases occur in the person of Eli Roth.En her film debut, "Cabin Fever", be covered by the figure of David Lynch was a point in his favor. To note that the name of a genius as Lynch is involved, in some form, in the project, many will be launched to watch her, even just by mere curiosity. And this is its major asset.The truth is that Eli Roth needs a powerful campaign accompanying so his films do not go unnoticed and remain in the most absolute of the oversights. Be produced by a controversial director, create a stir on the terrible and controversial theme of the film and preach the five continents is without doubt, a very effective way of achieving its purpose interested.It is the young director not more than another fan of the grotesque, staunch follower of worship near what today is called "geek" and see persecutor of Fame in world magazines and newspapers that want to become in the world of cinema. A world that, in one way or another, is attracted to. Captures fans, feeds his ego, earn money and be labra controversial future for their next projects to check. Yes, it has been achieved because the spectators fall into their trap. The damage is done.Already be we had been selling "Hostel" for quite some time as one of the most violent and brutal years, movies not suitable for the most sensitive stomachs. And, indeed, there is something like that. But, as usual, advertising brings everything to a close to the disproportionate limit. As I said, their own ideas very few. If any. But what little they have need to squeeze it to the maximum. And Eli Roth has been able to get juice. While "Cabin Fever" was a conglomeration of elements of many directors dealing with terror from a different point of view (see own David Lynch, Cronenberg, Hooper, etc.), becoming a product seemingly so appealing as little original, "Hostel" is a much more simple, direct work in certain aspects.What at first occurs suddenly as a purely teen film, of those that make think that to reflect the social life of young people there rather than develop the plot on the basis of sex (or rather, the desire to get it) and the party slowly will becoming the explicit film that actually is. Thus, the route of the mindless of turn (leading them to Slovakia) is presented as a paradise for those who dream to shoot their hormones of the free and easy way.It impresses the ease with which to manage all their desires. And that rises and low slippage and fun is reflected on the screen of a purely unreal form that manages to bring to every tourist in search of easy sex. A pamphlet for more planes of mind. And effective, of course. Although, of course, rather than impress, such display of easily makes us doubt.A little more than usual (while the viewer in sight again and again these rants of the protagonists) it takes to get the turning point of the film. But it comes. Then, logically, the brutality we harassed and already does not give us breathing space.At the same speed that the characters are disappearing, the climax of violence increases their heights. And then, the speed of the events is extreme. There are no concessions of any kind. Eli Roth tries to us sumerjamos in this bleak environment without possible return. And if you have, our thoughts will prevent that we can escape.Discover the real plot, and torture, humiliation and brutal and incoherent beatings never cease to happen is. Some manage to escape, but it is to ask if it was really worth having escaped. The clearest example is the eastern part of the "unbearable" scene in the film and most will already recognize the flight. Example that makes us reflect, even on the importance that today given to the physicist. If you look in a mirror and you see deformed, mutilated or stripped of one of your visible parts. life cannot go on. It is too heavy and painful to lead throughout an existence.The film seems to save a point of social interest, but as soon as he looks over her head, her returns to hide sharply. A simple concession to the Gallery, on the other hand, makes us reflect on violence and the nonsense that the world is turning. Do not know if one acts thus pure pleasure, amusement, frustration or causes the same offending individual is unknown.The violence is in any corner waiting for us. As the gang of kids of Bratislava. But let us not delude ourselves or look for five-legged cat. The film is simply a Museum of violence, intrigue and high tension which may engage us in the sofa as easily as do we lift him or look the other way. Its premise, despite possibly social notes, is as simple as the cause to the Viewer. But the eternal search of terror lost in the films that do not be fooled. Here terror there. Setting, bestiality and suspense that will get good dose. But even the staunchest followers of "gore", which boasted the advertising for the film before us, will be disappointed by the lack of content (with the exception of a couple of scenes).What is clear is that the sensitive stomachs and easy to impress hearts feel nausea on more than one occasion. It becomes unbearable not visually, but psychologically.In short, an absolutely flat, simple, surplus, free and unpleasant film that all they can offer is entertainment and tension. It does not say anything new and the word "idea" is conspicuous by its absence. It has an interesting invoice, some credible performances, a very successful ambiance and an in crescendo of history which is degenerating more and more in what is predictable as final. Without going any further, surely the own Tarantino saw more than satiated his violent palate. In fact, the film baby much more pure violence of the director of "Reservoir Dogs".Let everything in a fad is actually her. Exactly in the same way that prevails the Tarantino film in our time. Maybe you are much more interest fans of latest movies as "Saw" (which, in comparison to this, up might seem large jewelry) or similar. It is certainly a new and widespread wave which seems to have no place in the contemporary concept of cinema.Everything is forgotten and the hostel, little by little, will be losing customers. Later, maybe reservations are are depleted again. Everything is a matter of see our progress and wait for the evolution of the palates of the Viewer. You never know. Meanwhile we are going to continue torturing. If it is possible to Americans, that, as in the film, they are worth more points (black humor satire sponsored by the creators of "Hostel"). What is clear is that not they will no longer us surprise. And misleading advertising either.</body>
</review>
