<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Match point" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great Woody Allen</summary>
	<body>Is known that portrays the bourgeoisie as very few and that its regularity, associated with his prolific career as a filmmaker, rises it at the top. I have weakness by Allen, am not going to hide it. It is a counter of stories is exalted in his craft and his style visual with every one of his movies. This time is the turn of portraying the English gentry with a love story in quite conventional principle that also develops quite slowly. The director changes Jazz by the Opera House and wheel for the first time in England. Her portrays just as the can do, showing places typical, charismatic, but always without abusing and concentrated on support with the locations that the upper class environment. Johnatan Rhys Meyers embodies the young protagonist and does a good job, but sometimes come you to notice somewhat limited with these eyes all the time of falling asleep. Emily Mortimer, beautiful and successful in his role as wife of the protagonist. Scarlett Johansson leaves, as on the other hand also was expected, disarmingly sexy in her role as fatal, mysterious woman vulnerable to equal parts, closing this triangle of passion, deception and sex. On the other hand, other actors are also formidable, as Matthew Goode, in its sauce making little boy Pope.After seeing the movie, may not be very original point that this film is obviously and largely indebted of the previous "Crimes and misdemeanours", but maybe if it is compared with "The sixth sense". "Match Point" is narrated with pulse but with great parsimony. A rhythm that makes us wish that events happen once and for all. A sudden plot twist at the end, as the tape of M.Night Shyamalan, will be in charge of return to the tempo and make us vibrate. In "Match Point" also closes the history with the sports metaphor with which begins and one falls surrendered before the wisdom, the control and the hand of Allen, an intelligent writer, an orchestra conductor restless, extremely intuitive and truly loving their craft and each one of his own works.Nor hides his influences, or lack making: Dovstoievski, Bergman, Hitchcock, and much of the own Woody Allen for a very successful reflection on the fate, fate, the meaning of life, justice, morality, guilt, selfishness, love, sex and the nature of the social and professional advancement.Don't have to prove anything to anyone after their nearly three dozen films, but is appreciated and feels with each viewing, its willingness to continue being genuine and faithful and for not wanting to or allow disappoint his followers to maintain a remarkable quality in each of your appointments. Each autumn a very special gift always. Thanks Woody.</body>
</review>
