<review author="Red Stovall" title="Plan oculto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The expertise of Lee in the staging and the millimeter screenplay by Russell Gewirtz make us forget the little originality in its history</summary>
	<body>Many times they have compared to Spike Lee with Woody Allen. Well, I think that certain films Lee can be compared with the Allen, because actually there is something the film of the director New York film Lee. But I think that this last has been able to continue their own way without the influence of Allen, especially in his last films, where we are with the wonderful 'La last night'. In addition, anda that not leave you imitators to Woody Allen, like to focus only on read. 'Inside Man', which has been gruesomely translated in our country as 'Hidden Plan' it starts with the robbery to a Bank, which quickly becomes a situation with hostages. In the workplace make Act of presence order forces, with detective Frazier to head. However, the case does not seem the typical case of kidnapping or robbery, as evidenced by the appearance place of Madeline White, someone watching over the interests of a third character that has a lot to hide.Since then the argument is nothing out of this world, and not intended. The expertise of Lee in the start-up scene and the millimeter screenplay by Russell Gewirtz make us forget the little originality in its history, and give us a thriller as few do today. Full of emotion, good characters and above all who are attentive to the screen, without us we deslumbremos with explosions, shots and persecution. Quite an achievement, the truth.One of the things that draws most attention is its extensive gallery of characters, all very different among themselves, and with different interests. Lee shows great intelligence and a shuffle in Jodie Foster a character that can handle all the roost, so the forces of order are challenged to have someone unknown above them. By the way, Foster comes incredibly beautiful all trajeada. Leaves little but it is noted, though his character is a bit bland.Denzel Washington plays a detective in his first major case, and the actor is almost as always: protesting and seeking the truth. We get what is expected of him, and even in certain scenes are going ahead of him, to the anticipate their reactions, although I do not say this as a defect, but rather the opposite.For me who takes the cake is Clive Owen, with a more interesting character, and which never came to know much. This is one of the successes, his enigmatic personality remains enigmatic at the conclusion of the film, and we were eager to know more. Owen is an actor who does not seem as good as many people say, but here it is it gets. The home, with him talking to the Viewer, is simply spectacular.On the side we find the great Christopher Plummer, lately not to work, demonstrating that it arrives with his mere presence. Also get Willen Dafoe, although its presence in the cast seems simply a box office claim that his character does not stand out. Or who knows, maybe Lee intended precisely that, which a character nothing remarkable it interpreted someone well known, which would be a point in favor of the film.Where the film is a true joy is in the staging of Lee, completely sober and elegant, although sometime is going hand in hand with some slightly dramatic sequence, especially one in a moment of maximum climax, in which Washington is moving at full speed in the foreground. The sequence has Coif, is well done, but no longer a whim of its director, and that really adds nothing to the film. On the other hand, within the Bank, Lee passes as a dwarf doing a lot of planes sequence that are a true joy. Lee gives a rhythm to the truly enviable film. We take into account that the film lasts two hours and that is much footage, which never becomes boring due to the excellent Assembly (already could learn others).Finally highlight the soundtrack of the always interesting Terence Blanchard, and the song called Chaiyya Chaiyya Bollywood Joint, performed by Sapna Awasthi and Sukhwinder Singh, which opens and closes the film. A film of course is the very best that are now on the Bulletin Board, next to these two wonders 'V for Vendetta' and '16 streets'. Magnificent.</body>
</review>
