<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Dreamgirls" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Acceptable, without fanfare, musically more than correct, but empty, food of self-love, cluttered places common in the genre.</summary>
	<body>The hagiographic so in vogue Chronicle does in this viewer a devout fan: tend to avoid that kind of film that grows around a myth or, in his absence, about a character with public draft, whose notoriety and relevance supplies the shortcomings of history because, after all, everyone knows where is history going and does not require too much cleanliness in his evidence as hot gunpowder. Dreamgirls meets the exact conditions for being candidate to not see her ever, while the Tamla Motown music excites me (these The Dreams are a very acceptable shadowing of those The Supremes and Jennifer Hudson is a vocally credible Diana Ross) and the cast has enough bells as not fail sound unless you put in the cinema queue. I walked in these for a few days, but then the temptation (good name) led me as res to the slaughterhouse of the armchair. Dreamgirls is not Chicago, that I was unbearable. Not Cotton Club, which I admire. Bob Fosse made the acid All that jazz (starts the show) in the past and now the Hollywood machine makes musicals because it must revive some genera that occasionally become lost, joyously wounded in the showcases of the history of cinema, without any luminary with sense of smell put the pasta to make a deal with nombradía and a director with size (again) the popcorn and coca-cola make couple in the row seven. Despite this thrashing of semantic sticks, Dreamgirls is not a bad film: it could have been even one exceptional if not observe too much certain irregularities of planning, some collapse in the argument and, above all, a debit excessive to all topics than on cinema of musicians who escalafonan until that shine, glittering in the stardom of the fame and the money have been written. We have the trio of gold with their already very expected roles: the innocent, the discrete and the carnivorous. We have an abuse of musical numbers as necessary to resolve what the script does. Finally, we have an atmosphere so impostada and mannered that seems that we are watching a movie. (The good, at least) cinema should move away from the idea that we are witnessing a monumental deception. Cinema deceives, but have to disguise the lie so that everything is affordable to our astonishment. Gives equal to leave astronauts, aliens at a bowling alley or yankees in King Arthur's Court. We are for what we are: to have fun, to enjoy. Dreamgirls, in this storyline, not take advantage of the excellent material available and crashes, without much noise, everything is written against the clichés of the prodigious machinery of the system, who always knows where to push to give the product headquarters to Word of mouth, and in the end, as happened to me, all leave our small crematística contribution.Diana Ross will be very happy because his career, always so ailing again in dance. Greasy rhythm and blues of Detroit will again sell discs here and on their land because music knows no labels of the geographies where it is good and it is great I agree. Jennifer Hudson sings beautifully and see the movie brings of Rondon the idea of later purchase the cd with the original soundtrack. That is all very well, but Dreamgirls is, in its most artistic background, hollow: can spare you many minutes and many others missing. Vale that Eddy Murphy demonstrate that he is a great actor after three hundred films where he has done the fool, the fat, the clever and the giggles or Jamie Foxx continue demonstrating that this is their natural (as in the also irregular and plumbate Ray) environment, but might have found a film bolder, less chic.The ramblings philosophical of All that jazz are here as far as Vladivostok, in whose rooms her exhibit for the greater glory of the Siberian Viewer, I think I say OK. I, just in case, pointed out in the book of obligations find on the shelf my copy of the tape of Fosse and there all my love (by others, limited) musical or music lover biopic will be fully satisfied. Or Moulin rouge in order to hear one of my favorite songs (Your song by Elton John) melifluamente carried the theatrical paroxysm by Nicole Kidman and Ewan McGregor.</body>
</review>
