<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Eyes wide shut" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Strange film that closes the cycle Stanley Kubrick, who proposed to make one of each gender. This is the "mental straw" gender that will go down in history by the censorship which had, by Nikole in balls and by the tremendous celebration that reflects that it leaves you thinking "why have I those friends?"</summary>
	<body>Watch that he had "seen" times this movie. Specifically could say it that the film is an aunt with fat tits, then Nicole coming out vistiendose, then smoke a joint and are goats, then there are in a huge orgy, finally a woman is dead to end suddenly. Because today have seen it with my half Zucchini and it is that you between the moments of jumping nipple breasts also had dialogue. What madness.The film is a typical American family, where he is a prestigious medical father of a family with a daughter. It is that his marital life is something cold, which have small extramarital tryst ending no curdling. Total, smoke a joint and she tells him that he has an erotic dream with a sailor that gives gustito there. He obfuscates and goes vague by the city with prostitutes and pianists, until it reaches the orgy. And little more happens, ah, if that then get a type that looks like Cesar Alierta (viva don Cesar gives us eating, living).After reading the synopsis, you need to make critical? The film is the kind that everything is hinted but said nothing. Of these as I would say Gila "here someone has killed someone" by what I have not heard well. It looks like the script isn't concluso, that it has cut, or is for intelligent people. The photographic subject, therefore very cool, with good levels of female breasts that defy the basic laws of gravity. The theme song a little more rare, at times thought that my neighbor was playing the piano of the balls, with chan chaaaan resembling when you throw a cat on a piano. And the end is one of those Chin pún, its finished. No you've heard? Ah, feels.In short, strange film that closes the cycle Stanley Kubrick, what is proposed to make one of each gender. This is the "mental straw" gender that will go down in history by the censorship which had, by Nikole in balls and by the tremendous celebration that reflects that it leaves you thinking "why have I those friends?".</body>
</review>
