<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Apocalypto" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A thrilling movie that will keep viewers stuck in the seat until the end of the function.</summary>
	<body>Temporarily abandoned his career as an actor, Mel Gibson has become one of the most interesting today and one of the most independent directors: he put the money and do what they want. Why his films, especially the last two, are as personal and risky.Be an actor as famous as he brings with it a dangerous burden: a movie directed by Mel Gibson demands of the viewer an important lack of prejudice. Prejudice, based on the other hand, almost all in its alleged ideology (as if the ideology affected the quality of the film). My recommendation to all, is forget who is behind the cameras and enjoy the visual spectacle that supposes "Apocalypto".I will not go to tell you the synopsis of the film, it suffices to know that it is an adventure set in pre-Columbian America, but yes I would like to clarify some aspects for which the film has been attacked.Gibson has always presented his film as a Ribbon of adventures, not as a historical treatise on the Mayan culture. Who wants to see her in that way that forget the matter. Despite this, yes there are aspects that are well reflected. The Mayans, indeed, had extensive knowledge of astronomy, as I could be watching the movie, in a sequence that can remind "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court". Moreover, despite what has been said in many ways, the Yucatecan Maya is not a dead language; It is still spoken today by more than 800,000 people.Returning to the film I must say that it's perfect for Gibson, which is no coincidence, not in vain, he is co-author of the wonderful script with Farhad Safinia. A script full of excitement and adventure in which allow even the luxury to a humorous and ironic nod to the Viewer. One of them has become one of the most discussed moments of the film: a final joke of mister Gibson who took me totally by surprise.His movies, as I say very visual and physical, is ideal to put us squarely in the vital adventure of the protagonist and to make us feel as ours a story that is, ultimately, about feelings very basic and elementary: survival, fear, family, love?Some of what almost nobody will speak when you comment this film, are impressive performances of the cast. The actors are so well that no one is going to give importance because they interpret with such realism to the Mayans of the era who people think watching authentic Mayan rather than people of the 21st century. The problem would be highlighting one of the players above others, that doesn't confirm that Gibson is a wonderful director of actors (remember to Maia Morgenstern in "The passion of the Christ" yet I am thrilled).There will be people who complains of shocking violence that runs throughout the film and which, to tell the truth, the director recreates in some moments. But I think that such violence is so justified by history that counts, its use becomes something natural and perfectly understandable.If I have to say what I least liked the film, would argue that the entry into the city is a bit long for more and can tire a tad. But it is the only downturn in pace of a hectic movie that will keep viewers stuck in the seat until the end of the function.I ardo in desire to know which will be the next challenge for the director Gibson. I know sure is, the day of the premiere, I'll be in the front row to see it.Moonfleet.es rating: 9 out of 10.</body>
</review>
