<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very impressed I have been with blood diamond. Edward Zwick - experienced in epic tragedies - takes us back to the recent past of Sierra Leone during the civil war.</summary>
	<body>Very impressed I have been with blood diamond. Edward Zwick - experienced in epic tragedies - takes us back to the recent past of Sierra Leone during the civil war. In this chaotic context one soldier - rather than fortune, misfortune-, a villager desperate and an American journalist are trying to find a diamond, as a ticket back to sanity.What I liked it - and disgusted by truthful - has been they display which makes the director of baby killers, child soldiers are trained killers who were drug and manipulates that combat in the conflict with less than twelve years. The film impresses and stir consciences and stomachs mainly does not leave indifferent.With regard to the purely artistic issues, DiCaprio, smells like Oscar. To me personally, despite their efforts, I fails to convince at all even in this role. I see very last thread in some scenes and provides other as improvised? demolition man?, in my opinion, quite exaggerated.The movie is long, warn, but as several frames at the same time develop and do not let happen things, is not heavy at any time. The picture of the girl with the Pearl Earring - Eduardo Serra - shows all the beauty of the unfortunately belligerent area. It has some time video, supported by the music of James Newton Howard, which is somewhat pretentious but it serves to relax tension accumulated. However, if something spare you the film it is the Hollywood touch.I mean, the pseudo flirting between DiCaprio and Connelly is worth and not strain. Do do stage is less suitable for these ventures and sucks producer claiming:? Let's get a girl mona albeit with shoehorn? - as the doctor in Prison Break, more or less-. The other aspect that chirriado me is the epilogue, which will be real, but it is pretty bows and seems hatched by former producer.Except these two buts, a film of the not to miss that will be released, I sense that in many cinemas, this Friday.PS: After seeing the film and absolutely aware, would like to use this platform to tell my numerous suitors and admirers: I do not regaléis more diamonds, please. Do do Diamond? s aren? t a girl? s best friend.</body>
</review>
