<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Hostel" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What Nice moral dilemma we have lost favour the thin guts...</summary>
	<body>Seeing the posters who have made this film, I realize that graphic designers of them have much more imagination than the writers. By the way, in the poster of the guy with the chainsaw, and the boot will call friends at the bar "the stumps". Boy, not cogas chainsaw by the skewers!The film is about three young people, two Americans and an icelander, which are holidays for Central Europe, in search of earthly pleasures that gives life. Total, not considered sufficient to tremendous women and drugs which are in Amsterdam, they decide to go to Slovakia, instructed by a strange type with the sick nose for women more beautiful than anyone to "mounted" ever. Total, they go that far country (which seems rather medieval to present) and staying in a "Hostel" (hence the name of the movie, which is called hostel or fonda or youth hostel). And there begin to happen strange things, as they bind to a tremendous mujeronas, for example.Well, this film is a pretty big hodgepodge, who has been given much publicity, but which has four things. History could have been very interesting, especially if we look at the moral dilemma from which comes this film do you leave kill for money?. But as the director has focused on the picadillo and the thick guts, we are therefore left without debate. The characters deserve to die from the first image that out, but I have to admit that his general behavior is quite correct (with the exception of the final absurdity). Picadillo scenes leave me cold pussy, expected me much more disgusting, and I have to admit that it impressed me a lot more the birth of my wife as "gore" than the simplería of special effects that we have here. Saves out a few good aunts, ending as we like everyone, although the events that leave you thinking "do the director think we are asshole?".In short, well done picadillo, but chopped without a good script that endorse. If you like al gore, put you in a page of internal medicine rather than watch this movie. If you like terror, take an Eastern type "The ring" or something like "who can kill a child?". If you want to get to give birth to a film, not you miss this.</body>
</review>
