<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Dreamgirls" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Dreamgirls, is more than a story with musical numbers, a succession of songs with true plot filling between them</summary>
	<body>As every year, in the months of January and February, most favorite movies of face to the Oscar promptly meet your appointment with the Spanish cinemas. Although this time several of the most nominated films were released in the course of the calendar year, as infiltrators, the Queen, little Miss Sunshine or Babel. What is almost inescapable is among the favourites a musical, or at any rate a biopic (biographical film) musical, and Dreamgirls is the example of this season.Dreamgirls is based on a Broadway musical virtually forgotten, which in turn was freely inspired in the journey of the musical group The Supremes and their leader, Diana Ross. Bill Condon was very impressed by this musical, and hardened in the genus after the indent of Chicago, undertakes its film adaptation. The Dreamettes is a group formed by three friends who want to succeed in the music, and by accidents of fate, are hired to do the vocals of James "Thunder" Early (Eddie Murphy). Hence they give the jump to stardom, but they will soon begin the struggles of egos and clashes. The musical is one of the film genres that more passions rise, both among his admirers as among his detractors, and therefore there is always someone to praise the virtues of Dreamgirls (in their right is). But honestly, Dreamgirls, is more than a story with musical numbers, a succession of songs with true plot filling between them. Some of the musical numbers are well made, but it end up becoming unbearable soon, even for the more staunch lover of the genre. A lack of pace and a more than excessive length do the rest. It is a film made as means of showcasing the great diva Beyoncé Knowles, who succeed in the music of him is not enough, as well as the new star of American media, Jennifer Hudson, winner of American Idol. The sad reality is that Beyoncé, whose vocal talent is cuestioable, has lines of dialogue in the footage, and the few who has little demonstrates his total inability to interpretative. The próximamante oscarizada Jennifer Hudson, alias "triunfita", although it does not reach the ends of the Knowles, nor falls short, making an interpretation flat, devoid of feeling or emotion. Eddie Murphy is in his normal line, the only one that makes a true interpretation, and also good work is Jamie Foxx. There will be more than one spectator, be amazed before such cluster of absurdities, it will throw to the desperate ground, shouting things like someone I boot the eyes! or whispering to his seat-mate please, kill me already and please end my ordeal. The big question is why a filmmaker who has made gods and monsters can get to fall so low?, doubt that it may never be resolved.</body>
</review>
