<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="V de Vendetta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Under a crude appearance, a consumer product gratísimo, able to move to the greedy public experiences ideologically strong beats and another, who only want a well-made movie that distract two hours of the deadly tedium of some winter afternoons.</summary>
	<body>Behind V for Vendetta is Orwell, who served as my first serious readings. There is also a healthy exercise of contravening rules that strikes as fundamental in society of well-being (téorico) of our civilization. Contravention of the legitimacy of a State (though it's right and apparent democratic formulas in pursuit) and headquarters overlooks the terrorism: is credited as legitimate and we even agree that, occasionally, all words manifested hollow when they collide (frontal and brutally) against the blind inertia of a rotten power of a rogue State who has betrayed their chartersits basic organizational structure for the sake of barbarism, whatever his visible mask. And then what we are talking about? V for Vendetta vindica fascism, individual decision-making affecting others for the sake of an unjustified sense of order that probably nobody else shares? To not shock in excess bienpensantes minds and into the pockets of the distributors who will dispose of the film, the work of Alan Moore's graphic cartoonist whose work were also brought to the film the League of extraordinary gentlemen and from hell, was significantly lightened: it disarms of its nasty and invests a mediocre (but tolerable) rebellion against the Governmentthat it strangles the citizen, as we see, and stolen canallamente freedom.Without falling into the pop pose, which would have been perhaps more predictable, V for Vendetta uses a rich visual structure where raw ideology on the action and where the characters, without being neither deep nor worthy of Shakespeare, meet the demanding Viewer seeking a dramatic sediment according to the risk of the proposal. This modern Robin Hood which is V, autodeclarado liberator of the people oppressed and decided boldly to put a bomb under the British Parliament train, is also forced an Evey (Natalie Portman) guardian pure and neutral, it ignores the folds of policy and just as we knew during all the footage, identified with V to the point of being able to continue his work in his absence.All very subversive, although flavoured with a very striking cast (Hugo Weaving, Natalie Portman, Stephen Rea, John Hurt and Stephen Fry). All very anarchic, although relativized by the obvious odor of correction policy in these turbulent times.Written by Wachowsky brothers and produced by James McTeigue, Assistant of direction of the famous and overrated series Matrix, V for Vendetta is a regular work that touches and raises a dialogue. As there are few films regualres, which move and provoked a dialogue, one of the best films this reasonably critical Viewer has seen in recent times, though this time has been the broker dvd and not the appetizing big screen declare V for Vendetta. Moreover, chapeau.</body>
</review>
