<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Blood diamond is one of many films that are worth a theoretical desire of awareness and denounces as a mere excuse to offer countless gunfights and action scenes.</summary>
	<body>In recent years the film seems to have returned a social conscience who had lost for quite some time, and fortunately increasingly more committed films or they carried the great forgotten made public or few acquaintances. And if there is a region of the Earth that humans have had historically remote and forgotten, and largely still, is the black continent, Africa. Everything which has affected Africa, from the brutalities committed during the European domain until the conflicts caused by the lack of foresight of the post-colonial cast, have stayed in second place to end up in oblivion.Edward Zwick rescues that forgotten civil war that shook Sierra Leone less than a decade ago, and does so through one of the protagonists of the conflict, illegal trafficking in diamonds. Danny Archer (Leonardo DiCaprio) is a mercenary and smuggler of diamonds who works for a large multinational. Solomon Vandy (Djimon Hounsou) is a peaceful fisherman forced to work in the mines of the rebels, where he finds and hides a large diamond. With the help of a journalist, Maddy Bowen (Jennifer Connelly), both begin a flight to recover the precious stone and thus escape from their respective hell. The film, a story designed to play the chord of the viewer and try to raise it starts with this approach, despite the redundancy, on the problems that as a pest plague Africa. However, blood diamond is one of many films that are worth a theoretical desire of awareness and complaint as merely an excuse to offer a host of shootings and scenes of action, to which more spectacular. Edward Zwick, whose skill in the director Chair happens unnoticed, passes on tiptoe by matters more spiny, without getting wet and without offering anything new to justify the payment of the entrance. The screenplay by Charles Leavitt makes water on all four sides, which is replete with situations that border on the absurd. What could not miss is the typical rigorous humano-lacrimógeno conflict, represented on this occasion by Djimon Hounsou's character and his son, whose climax is one of the most ridiculous scenes of the film. The characters are flat, and although they have a certain evolution over the course of the plot, this is very obvious and predictable. On its protagonists, little you can expect from Leonardo DiCaprio, whose interpretation despite not ceasing to be correct, is somewhat empty and distant. Djimon Hounsou does a good job, but without fanfare, while Jennifer Connelly, in addition to not disheveled whatever happens, don't know or hold the camera in a convincing way.Blood diamond is one of those movies that are worth a story that really deserves to be told to transform it into a scene of action after another. It is a pity that with the available means preferred to make the tape to the purest style of Hollywood leaving aside intended to deepen in a forgotten conflict.</body>
</review>
