<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La ley del silencio" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Peliculón with capital letters, those that can bring to the modern public to the classics. If we also aderezamos her with the controversy of its director Elia Kazan during the witch hunt, and Marlon Brando more handsome that might have been, because already we have everything.</summary>
	<body>The film has a special magic as well we know, but if us intent to see what lies behind each filming, each manager, each actor, probably part of that magic would disappear. Many actors have been despicable, the best shooting were a hell and the directors have not been better. Fortunately what we have left is his work. In this film, peliculón, rather, is a reflection, even a yield of its director. Shows how an informer is good and that it must fight for what each considers just. Respectable, but opinion.The film is a former boxer Terry Malloy (Marlon Brando) who loses his key match, so it is sentenced to work for a gangster who is in control of the most important port in the world. Kill without any tapujo any teamster who wants to denounce him, which is why Terry has become involved in a murder. From meet the sister of the victim, and a wrestler cure for freedoms, began a process of transformation to overthrow the Empire that has mounted the underworld.There was a time in which the players were expressive in their faces, their skins looked like tanned in my battles and his gestures allow us to glimpse a richness of life. This film is one of that style. Each of the characters, up to the secondary, has interest and importance in the argument. We'd like to know more about them and we realize quickly that represent real people. The port setting is very successful, with a very good picture. Marlon Brando acts as the gods, and that it is difficult with such a good actor. And the argument has it all, everything you need to be one of the best films of all time.In short, peliculón capitalized, of those that can bring to the public modern to classics. If we also aderezamos her with the controversy of its director Elia Kazan during the witch hunt, and Marlon Brando more handsome that might have been, because already we have everything.To buy the Tin of the Fnac, that adds nothing, but it looks good on the shelf.Besitos.Momentos to remember: ** the opening scene of the jump of the paloma.* the end, with a Marlon Brando finishing what they started. ** the conversation with his brother in the coche.* the scene that comes by force in the room, to show their amor.* the harangue of the priest in the puerto.* the struggle for work, humiliating workers if necesario.* is when you enter at the palomar and discovers that his admirer he has killed all the pigeons.</body>
</review>
