<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El crepúsculo de los dioses" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the two or three favorite movies of this chronicler and more acidic look that the film has written about himself. Needed revision to greater joy of the soul. Movie fan jewel. Finally.... superb sample of human genius</summary>
	<body>1. "Is still wonderful, isn't it?"And without dialogues! "The history of Sunset Boulevard (being the title here tax superb, the twilight of the gods, the English original is masterful) is narrated by a dead that we see in the first frames floating in a historiated pool of a Hollywood mansion." Joe Gillis (William Holden) is the voice that tells their own death or the story of a writer of second row, eaten by debts, which accidentally takes refuge in the mansion of a silent film diva, insane, fueled by nostalgia and psychotic in her decadent soledad (Gloria Swanson).The crepíusculo of the gods is a treasure for the devoted collector of images of the seventh art. To Scarlett O'Hara swearing with a handful of Earth in the hands against the ochre horizon, vowing that not olverá to go hungry or the Rick of Casablanca with the French inspector consenting to the beginning of a great friendship while a plane part in the fog, join Norman Desmond (immortal Swanson, incredible, prodigious) down the staircase to be arrested by the police between flashes and lights. As a diva in a film festival.Have seen before a travelling to remove his hat (Billy Wilder was always one): a caravan of police cars approaching the mansion with that voice in off telling: "Yes, this is Sunset Boulevard, Los Angeles, California." They are around five in the morning. It is the homicide Brigade, supplemented by detectives and journalists. They have reported a murder in one of these huge houses of the 10,000 Apple. You can read in the editions of the night, they will tell you on the radio and see on television because an old star is involved, a major star. ". The voice stops before his corpse in the pool. Never before the film had dared to tell us the end with both explicit harshness: the protagonist is the muerto.2. "We needed no dialogues". We had faces! "Wilder had, in the words of William Holden, blades razor in the brain." They just agreed to get the film, who was born silenced for a short and was recorded in secret. The director misled Meyer, the Almighty producer of the underground Hollywood glamour, telling her that it was another, and with another argument, which was being filmed. The reason comes from the nature of the film and its carnalmente homicidal purpose transgreosra, canibal almost. It chronicled the decline of the silent film era and counter-insurgency in acid and bloody way in the ways of Hollywood, your pathetic life codes and the atrophication of the film industry, who preferred not to risk for the sake of political correctness and to the liking of the public never too demanding.The screenplay by Wilder and Charles Brackett perverted the classical structure of film writing. Perhaps for the first time in a very forceful way. It is not only the fact is narrated by who already know who has died but also by the desire to speak of the film within the film and talk with acrimony, harshly, without mincing words in the language. This metalinguistic added formidably later explicitly by the Coens in Barton Fink is reinforced with the successful inclusion of silent film heavyweights, loans generous to give more verismo as cash. It is Erich Von Stroheim (legendary German director of the greed, 1.927 tape) and Cecil B. de Mille (adoptive father of this first-time film coming out of the laboratory for flood screens, which here makes himself, how not, with its natural and curious mode of dress, boots high and gestures of a safari Hunter).Seasoned of fatalism, the script is pure film noir or film black lightened with a Greek drama of much height, although Wilder lighten some topics of one and another and becomes convinced that maybe a very lewd portrait of Hollywood, which he knew well by his screenwriter stage, could not agree that the film had the blessing of the heads.His daring is to slap the Hollywood classic, aristocratic and fetén and not arredra Wilder in pull repertoire also classic and aristrocrático and so are witnessing an amazing letters starting with Buster Keaton's head of cards or the already mentioned Von Stroheim or De Mille. The sordidness in the narrated or continuous recourse of the flashback, a novelty in the usual way of telling things in the film then give the film an artistic tone: as if Wilder had noticed that that material in your hands could revolutionize the history of the Cine.No there is nothing rough in the relationship of norm and Joe: the splendor of the divahis belief in that bright yet late and the failure of the screenwriter (another nod to the mediocrity of the mercenary screenwriter for the worst films of the own subway at the time) do not never acquire a solid, autonomous entity. Standard is a victim of technology (then the video kill the radio star, but that's another story) and are detained in a mansion: it binds to the bovine old with his famous films, it embadurna with all the oils in the world. Cosmetics, makeup, informs us of the true condition of Norma Desmond: it is not the film, it is not the abandonment of the noise of the flashes and the claquetas, is the time, the pressing, that is the real cause of his insanity. The years have devastated his sanity. Lives with whom her first husband and now it's the perfect, cynical and efficient Butler to drunkenness. The arrival of Joe, representing the outside world uncovers his eagerness to asleep by greening fugal fame, the noise of the flashes and the claquetas, time regained such vez.3. "Still I am large;!" "is the film that has made small!"The twilight of the gods, together perhaps to Citizen Kane, is the film has given rise to more bibliography. Wilder wanted Greta Garbo, but already withdrawn, refused the offer. Mary Pickford, another silent glory, demanded more of the account. I wanted a biopic to use and a film about the twilight of an archetype. Mae West, that AVID of male lagartona, alleged that she was younger than Norma Desmond in the script. Gloria Swanson, pushed by George Cukor, was chosen. The transition from silent to sound took it badly and retired to live succulent rents appearing in theatre, radio, or the new Queen, television. For Gillis, before Holden, Montgomery Clift, who argued that his fans, Legion, not paraded him forgive you flirtease on screen with a wrinkled grotesque. Fred MacMurray, liked by Wilder, was rejected by Meyer. Gene Kelly was not a recognizable style in his vertigionosa career film. William Holden was not considered by the director a competent actor. Even in a journal he attacked frontally by saying it was a mediocre actor of serie B, but it ended up accepting and surrendered to her superb performance. But among all, is Gloria Swanson that gives dramatic support to the film: which keeps intact, who has recorded his face stretched, his gestures of exquisite loca, glamour and pathos, the sublime madness and forgotten love in our memory of cinema. Bette Davis would have been a fantastic Norma Desmond, said I. The Repertoire of gestural nuances of the Swanson is the usual inventory of all those actresses of the silent, who said with a grimace which then needed two verbs and adjectives nine. Its perfect parade of ICT has become the history of the cine.4. "Fuck you" A curiosity: the twilight of the gods had a private pass prior to their distribution. It is natural. Louis B. Mayer, the boss of the underground, approached Wilder and he snapped: "you, bastard bastard, has brought to the film industry." Her has been dragged through the mud. It has bitten the hand that made him someone and also gave him to eat. Should be alquitranar him, fledging him and throw the country. "." Wilder replied only: "Fuck you".Another: The first idea of Wilder was to make the film begin with the body of Joe Gillis in the mortuary, under the sheet. talking about. He was convinced by Buckett, his alter-ego in the writing, that that was going to make that everything was taken to chacota.Addenda or PostScript, or what was missing: only by the breathtaking fall of Gloria Swanson by the staircase when you are going to be stopped is worth the penalty the film. This image lingers in the memory of this writer as the blue sky or the Moon cut in the roof of my house. Above, we know that he has killed perhaps so modified the lights the benefit and the flashes of journalists parpadeen as bullets. I read that all the reporters of that scene were not actors but real reporters. And then there is the formidable dead, the talkative body, giving an acid rebound in healthy irony, clean rawness in its Parliament.In year 2,230, the twilight of the gods will be the film was at 1,950 and which has been this evening when I had the absolute pleasure of reverse her. And will...</body>
</review>
