<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Tetsuo, the iron man" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mescolanza of biological with the metal, a metallurgical poem anti-nature hybridization, the first in the history of cinema. Cyberpunk to complete a century. Screws, mutilations, drills Symphony limited partnership for revolver innocent stomach.</summary>
	<body>There are things that one understands, but that fascinate him. Religion is the reasoned inaprehensible. Bertrand Russell said that faith was chantajeada intelligence or the abducted common sense. Under this strict context, Tetsuo is a rare bird in the film one can see and does not resemble anything none another film, although share identical patterns and a pretty similar sense of the grotesque spectacle and the fascinating guignol of all radicalism.Tetsuo is radical: love or repels barbarically. I zozobro between repulsion and this strange affinity to the consent to the idea that, not being bad, the proposal is amazing, fantastic, bombastic and dreadful as a roller coaster on the crest of a tsunami.The Japanese go somewhat against the grain of the Western film and it is this latter, more tired of searching and not finding new models of exploitation, seeking in its particular iconography innovative trends that show the European public, or to the American. Hence we have to Scorsese and infiltrators, is a New Yorker reading and nicholsiana of a product of Hong Kong than not we had excessive news if Scorsese had not seen spark in their frames. Hong Kong is not Japan, but Asia is Asia.Tetsuo is delicately abnormal: fragmented, revolutionary in its planteamiento-nudo - outcome and, as David Lynch, unsettling and addictive. I've never used the adjective "pleasant" because Tetsuo is not a tart to the desktop after a fillet with Roquefort cheese with a good rioja. It seems an experimental shake manga, Iron Maiden and psychedelic screws.The fetish of the metal is not degustable dish, although we have seen characters from Scorsese make similar brutalities. Up the tormented brain Lynch, already mentioned, gives us martyrdoms and aberrations that not conspicuous in this artifact uncontrolled and toxic.The first thing that draws attention is that black and dirty white and a very particular way of telling the story: there is no almost dialogue, a loud music us acongoja (literally) and the characters seem to ghosts, accelerated spectra, minimum vital entities moved by the whim of some rudimentary God and bastard which infringe them thousand small pains and some gigantic torment to not get it to banalities. This man who gets metal in the body which savor an apple pie is the icon of the moral depravity of man or not is none of this and only we are witnessing, puzzled, amazed also, to new models to ensure us pleasure already that we have (natural sex, with her spasms and their cramps) are shrinking their ability to satisfy us. Or is that the Japanese multitecnificados, hipermotivados by the noisy machines revolution, have erected metal in their fundamental God and offered these sacrifices to please him like the Mayans of Gibson extracted hearts of the people to give taste to their cosmic deities.Not frivolous with this gratuitous violence: abuse, recent fashion invent new languages to talk about violence, that is old and has aroused the interest of all the generations of human beings on this dog world have been, but Tetsuo, the iron man, applies to who need escape during awhile (lasts an hour) of all narrative and discursive conventions of classic cinema (ranging from evil to Bambi thirst) is detestable and want (and should want of heart because if it is not going to leave the experiment played) go beyond, dive into territories not hollados. I saw in my video store there is a Tetsuo II: body hammer. Won't discover it: can lose me something big. My annual horror ration is covered. Shinya Tsukamoto will not be my favorite director, but will turn into my list of tormented tormented favorite (Lynch, Lynch, Lynch, are no longer only).This mescolanza of biological with metal, this hybridization anti-nature gives a metallurgical poem, the first of the history of cinema. Cyberpunk to complete a century.Screws, mutilations, drills Symphony limited partnership for revolver innocent stomach. It is worth the trouble? Somehow, of course, although after this massive intake of sensory gruesomeness it is possible to remove the Bookshelf home Titanic dvd and let us lead by the melifluo song of sirens of his tragedy.</body>
</review>
