<review author="Raccord" title="Azuloscurocasinegro" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Comparisons are odious, but I liked it much more than?Do again? Almodóvar</summary>
	<body>"Dark blue, CasiNegro" is the directorial debut of Madrid director Daniel Sánchez Arévalo, known and award-winning short films. Despite being a "small" film without a big budget, nor a spectacular cast, won several Golden Biznagas at the recent Festival de Málaga (included in the special prize of the jury). Despite having a so horrifyingly bad title, and a poster of those that you never fijarías has caused a phenomenon mouth quite considerable, especially in the blogosphere, which prompted me to see her. And I did not disappoint at all. I know that comparisons are odious, but I liked pretty rather than "Volver" Almodovar, which competed directly on the Bulletin Board in recent weeks. A film that breathes freshness and talent, in these times in which does not seem that we are good of these qualities in Spain (if not I think, look at those who were winners in the Goya).Jorge (Quim Gutierrez) is a block of apartments goalkeeper, employment he inherited from his father, when he contracted Alzheimer's. He is a young boy and with willpower (Tamagotchi business career, while caring for his father, and his work in the goal) but lives in a world without opportunities to achieve a better life. His girlfriend is in Germany studying, and his brother in prison; so it only can share their sorrows with his friend Israel (Raúl Arévalo). But one day, Antonio (Antonio de la Torre), his brother, released from prison, and tells him that she has met a girl very special in the theater in the prison workshop. Jorge has to do a very important favor to that girl, that can save your life.Coldly analyzing, neither the plot nor the dialogues are very achieved, but the film follows truth; as if these stories they had been passed to your neighbors, and your not having apercibido. In addition, the characters are very well characterized and their motivations are embodied with a lot of tenderness and sense of humor. It has a couple of really exciting moments, along with others that cause a lot of laughs. The soundtrack for Pascal Gaigne is also much higher than the average. Very good film, but with the feeling that if this director/screenwriter continues to film, "Do dark blue?" will not be far the best of his career. To see if other than your also going to see it. A great movie.</body>
</review>
