<review author="Kiko de España" title="Días de cine" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Only works in that first hour quickly and (very) funny (at times), because from ecuador cinema days turns into a failed drama of complaint which is boring to the stones.</summary>
	<body>Friday, February 9. 16 hours.Room 1-diamond of blood. Available seats: 2Sala 145-days of cinema. Available seats: todasYo in my thirteen and also Animalario fan, this kind of freakshow (and the quarry of the most complete players in Spain) that were invented on tables already centuries ago Andrés Lima &amp; CIA (I recommend the book beautiful stories of entertainment on the daily exist, edited by Plaza Janés humiliation) and are passed from time to time to the big screen to enjoy his followersmanaging to come out victorious most of the time.But look at you by donde.1977, Federico Solá (a sometimes immense Alberto San Juan) prepares Encerrados at the mine, a project of social denunciation which, according to his friend Manolo (a Luis Bermejo as serious as serious to do another film) needs a star, Silvia Conde, ex-niñaprodigio and folk in hours low, (played by an excessively "felt" Nathalie Poza) it does not convince the director at all and that in addition it would not accommodate in such a project.From there is trying to create an absurd comedy with marxianos dyes on a sloppy shooting with a director of photography (and mother) alcoholic (and mother), an Assistant Director 100% real (desaprovechadísimo Diego Martín) and of course, a producer hijoputa (Miguel Rellán, grande has always been) well, because the film cinema days only works in that first hour quickly and (very) funny (at times), because from the cinema days ecuador becomes a failed drama of complaint which is boring to the stones, because even the stones are ready to move from a horny cartoon to a boring melodrama.Side usual as Javi Gutierrez and a Fernando Tejero pulling to regrettable repeating the same phrases nearly two hours and not help the film dates back the flight, cameos of Coque Malla and Roberto Alamo at least four roles, included.</body>
</review>
