<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Bobby" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bobby is a magnificent film, without hardly important failures, with an absolutely brilliant ensemble cast and a direction and a script that deserve a big aplasuo. Follow thus, Emilio!</summary>
	<body>As you have seen, I will film in cinema. Tomorrow, will certainly go to see secret games and Sunday blood diamond. And yesterday, he played Bobby, directed by Emilio Estevez. First of all, to say that we we have a magnificent film, with more than good intentions and a cast, that certainly deserves to receive the name of outstanding.Talk about policy, ladies and gentlemen, is very, very difficult. Or rather: portray the American policy in a cinema screen is incredibly complicated. One can express their views through the absolute patriotism (behold films such as Braveheart, Mel Gibson) either show his more democratic side as, in this case, Emilio Estévez. I, personal and obviously I decanted by the ideals of the second, and that is why I have enjoyed (especially in its final part) with Bobby, the film more mature (and famous), from quite little, great director.Though one, also, can portray their political thoughts focusing only on the events, or by adding to the political plot a series of stories Dakar with a mildly political message each. And Estévez, to finish, the film uses two aspects with their respective importance: the assassination of Robert f. Kennedy and the lives of each one of the people who were in the hotel where he died. And this, the truth is that it only does that improve the quality of the film. Moreover, leaving the traditional structure of a film about a political event, band begins narrating everything that happened the day before, and, to conclude, the assassination, giving way to a totally wonderful Kennedy speech (in off). So we have a screenplay, written by Estévez, quite incredible, written to measure, almost perfect. Perhaps the only judgment that would find you would be that slight downturn in rhythm in the middle of the footage or the bias given to the stories, though perhaps it takes reason counting more some than others, because they are of utmost importance and more profitable.All good film script deserves a good deal. And behold, probably the best deal of the year. Say that each of the performers appearing on Bobby is sublime, but I would especially highlight some: Anthony Hopkins, showing his great interpretive skills, for the umpteenth time, and here, playing the role of a veteran Butler of the hotel, which has experienced many important moments in history; Sharon Stone, leaving crossing legs and absurd sequels, getting into one of the more elaborate roles of the script and offering us a matchless performance; William H. Macy, playing a not very common in his filmography, because he plays the owner of the hotel, with a lover by in the Middle; Christian Slater, oddly enough, is splendid. Although his role is not pleasant, the interpretation which gives us is incredible; Laurence Fishburne, in one of his best roles, giving life to a chef with a personality and morality that exceed normal. Probably the character that I liked most; Freddy Rodriguez, also, in its best performance, full of sensitivity and, at the same time, security; Lindsay Lohan, definitely the best role that has made to date. Its role is charming, brave, risky, full of passion, etc; Helen Hunt as a couple of Martin Sheen. Both are splendid, although their roles do not have too much depth (and this is precisely what you want to achieve the director); and all the others, as I have said, are also splendid, as Demi Moore (although either you believe it), own Emilio Estévez, Elijah Wood, Brian Geraghty and Shia LaBeouf (those who take a joint over), Nick Cannon, Heather Graham or Jacob Vargas (the Mexican who fights with Fishburne in the kitchen).Apart from the impressive script and the outstanding cast, Bobby presents some technical aspects as unbeatable. Since the perfectionist photography, carried out by Michael Barrett, the amazing Assembly, made with precision and rhythmic sense. Also highlights the music of Mark Isham, although I prefer the song Never gonna break my faith (nominated for a Golden Globe).In short, we could say that Bobby is a magnificent film, without just bugs important, with an absolutely brilliant ensemble cast and a direction and a script that deserve a big aplasuo. Follow thus, Emilio!</body>
</review>
