<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="En busca de la felicidad" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is quite good, although it has a primary flaw: lacks it personality.</summary>
	<body>There are ways and ways, views and opinions. Gabriele Muccino, director of in search of happiness, doesn't seem to have, with this film, nor a way to clear or clear personal opinions. It is not that it is criticizing the film bad not. The film is quite good, although it has a primary flaw: lacks it personality. Perhaps others think that it may be one of the most poignant, tragic and personal films year-round. My opinion is as follows: This personality added provides, only, the star of the film (in all senses) that: Will Smith. So what here has its own life is the actor protagonist and not the film that appears. And then, I might add: in search of happiness is a correct history based on the same always, dream American, and interpretive weighing on it if he was he would not absolutely nothing. how many times have seen a film that addresses the theme of the American dream? Tens. Have we how many times have seen Will Smith doing a poignant performance? Never. So, in short, say that the film in question is quite irregular. A story everybody knows how (and not when) will end. And everyone I refer to all those that realize how simple it is the idea of Muccino. Is it that there is no original screenwriters in Hollywood, even though people say that not be them comes nothing but remakes? Speaking of writers, I think that it would have been great the election of Paul Haggis, simply because it would have provided her with force and originality to the story. It is also true that it is based on a real event (how not!) and that it is sometimes difficult to write a script about an event that already happened with innovative touches. But it is that here, except the magic square, there is not a single scene with innovative air. In short, that it could have benefited much more. Apart from this defect of originality, in search of happiness has other weak points: the film depicts certain aspects of a somewhat repetitive form, as for example, the scenes in which the protagonist loses the machine to sell.But after renumbered all of these negative features, I must admit that the film has also, quite a few positive things. First of all, and without exception, appoint Mr Will Smith, which gives us his best performance to date, endowed with wit, charisma, realism and emotion. Their appearances, which appear during the footage are always pleasant to see, like the dialogues that engaged, superbly written. So the weight of in search of happiness falls, undoubtedly, in the hands of this, now, his Excellency actor named Will Smith. The penalty is that the other side actors don't is look so much like him, although I have to say that their interpretations are, nor much less, bad. Both Tandie Newton, playing the role of mother endowed with an incredible drama (although to me, personally, I do not like as it is treated), as Jaden Smith, which he plays the son of Smith in the reality and fiction in an exceptional way, they offer us some brilliant performances, although a little scarce.In short, say that in search of happiness (The Pursuit of Happyness - what great detail the of the and!-) is a very correct film with overcoming oneself and the American dream as a strength within the theme, and an interpretative jewel: Will Smith. I don't know if it deserves the Oscar, but certainly the nomination Yes.</body>
</review>
