<review author="Iñigo" title="Funny Games" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He has fun, you fun. All we have fun.</summary>
	<body>Do you dare to enter a story that you are as guilty as anyone more.Do you dare to feel the fear, feel very closely the reality that no one is free from sin and suffering.Do you dare to look inside you, betray you, you recreate your unjustified violence.Do you dare to play. It is already too late. You were playing much before what he thought.Once again, the Austrian director hits hard in the consciousness of the Viewer, do with it what good seems it.When one is to reflect, realizes perfect that has fallen in his experiment, in his particular trap for human.Haneke is the puppeteer, demonic Acrobat who notes, manipulated to show the reality. Us puppets, obliged to open the eyes although we look to other side.With a lucidity that gives real fear, terrifying, dreadful, Michael Haneke doesn't let us escape. There is no possible excuse before his master exercise of personal imprisonment.The only way to escape is pressing the "stop" button of our players or leave of the projection room. Although if we neglect the tape to the best returns to play before our eyes.If we have seen the film, whether we like it or not, have succumbed. It has come out with his own. "The reason lies in the true sense of the film."Funny Games (fun games) "is not entertainment film, while it entertains to perfection to achieve its purpose.""Funny Games" is not at all, violent film, despite its storyline. It shows nothing. Violence is contained, frivolous, psychological: the most hurtful."The unique thirst for aggression, anger, cruelty, we ourselves.""Funny Games" is autorreflexivo cinema.Using winks, looks, gestures of "criminals", Haneke makes us accomplices of their misdeeds. He manages to us we feel true murderers.Two kids educated a priori, the typical couple, the smartass and silly, the Laurel and Hardy. Figuratively well settled (by what the golf course).Young people kill, hit play. Only get bored. There is no apparent reason to do so. There is no relationship, or mobile.It is a nonsense that we, the viewers, we recreate. Although, being part of the plot, maybe it is complicated to us, we do not want to continue with the macabre game. Lie. Let us not deceive ourselves. We want the murderer him sticking a shot throughout the body. We want to continue, we want revenge.Even if you know the reason, like them, we want to see violence, we want to be violent.Then, when we jumped with joy and gloating to justice, the director introduces one of their ACEs (for many very questionable) and leaves the public face of idiot astonishment and disappointment.Ultimately, what we are celebrating is a crime.In earthly life, in the films of fiction, at all times, we cry revenge. We wish that the to make the pay, but, if possible, with blood from through.Shots, shots, machetes, a feast for the senses. The cause of that our environment is becoming what it is becoming.Haneke could discern a Philo in all that and created a necessary film, a film that manages to see our own reflection on the screen, and nerve us of what we are visionando. Yes. Those of us. It is high time that we realize.The two companions of game are taking it with some leniency, very verge with the comic. However, by the other side, the tragedy be felt with the fingertips. This mixture makes something really controversial film (provocative if possible). It amuses us? Us terrified? is it contradictory to have to resort to a film of such spirit to condemn the violence in today's society? Seriously think about it, and meditate if there really are more accurate and lucid, otherwise not be manida, obvious or glib relate things. Focusing on the fact that, of course, in the film just shown. To the contrary: is evita.¿No is manipulative to become complicit through signs, innuendo, for then, by contrast, reprimand him such attitude to the Viewer? This is based on the game, gentlemen. Pretenciosa, self-worshiping, mocking, joke, lack of respect for the audience? Maybe it is that you harassed us recognize that we are as well.Haneke is a bastard. But a bastard without paint. In the background, even if it is embarrassing, we know that fundamentals not missing.The rest: oppressive, tyrannical, draconian, asphyxiating levels. We do not know at what point can explode before the coolness and calm, paused, quiet shooting sequences that, in essence, are brutal. Haneke House voltage to one hundred percent. Or music is not necessary to ensure that the director we brought an uncomfortable, close to the unbearable atmosphere.All a macedonia that led to the very same Susanne Lothar to undergo psychiatric treatment.As additional data, the American "remake" of "Funny Games" for expected this year, with a cast headed by Naomi Watts and Tim Roth.Una news bleak, if not because the director will be the same Austrian filmmaker. Anyway, seems to me very little necessary, unless it is done to teach cinema at the other side of the pond. And coming from who comes, don't exclude this option. what think, hence the film? It is a masterpiece and, without a doubt, one of the films of greater foresight of earlier decades.Do you dare to Michael Haneke take you the hair. With me it has achieved, there is no possible return. But I love.</body>
</review>
