<review author="Caruco" title="En busca de la felicidad" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do deserves to be above other similar proposals that reach us from? the industry?.</summary>
	<body>The cube of rubik or a poster of the mythical "raging bull" as a distinctive symbols of an era, early 1980s; and an actor Will Smith as another cinematographic icon, this current, or 90 at the beginning of the 21st century, because of his popularity and be a value guaranteed at the box office.All places us squarely for "In search of happiness", or the latest in drama of human interest belonging to the subgenus called "based on actual events"; and also, another shows more (see "Night at the Museum"), of the sub-subgénero of father troubled with problems to find your site in the world and with child of by means, or rather, to slopes.It will Smith is Chris Gardner, a family guy who in 1981 had water up to the neck of bills and debts, having invested until his last penny in some expensive bone scanners that almost no doctor wanted to acquire.Dragging up and down, those ubiquitous white briefcases of 20 pounds with a wife tired for a life that is already not makes happy (Thandie Newton), and a creature of 5 years covering everything from their perspective pure and naive, Gardner should deal with a thousand hardships to fulfill their dreams: a job as a broker on Wall Street, and stay with his son.Does the film meets all the requirements of a drama? made in Hollywood? to make an impact easily at the hearing, but it Will has resorted to an Italian director Gabriele Muccino ("the last Kiss"), hoping to give the product a different packaging.Fleeing from "felycidad."It doesn't matter that the film has its pitfalls. It will Smith is too nice and his character too smart that we come to doubt that it is an outside series that, sooner or later will reach their goals. "It is not an obstacle Will appear practically on 100 percent of all scenes, only giving in some moments to give some to another level the child, perhaps falling into the account which is his own son (Christopher Syre Smith), also named Christopher in the film"."In search of happiness" gets even by insistence that we metamos in the skin of this poor devil, or not so, called Gardner; We vibremos and we keep in tension in our seats during the nearly two hours of projection. All seasoned with a good invoice, fair dose of sentimentality, even a hilarious joke about shirts and pants, and a notable music composed by Andrea war (which I'm just listening to write these lines).The touch of sarcasm, surely unintended, is that "happiness" or that "achieving the"American dream", happens not only in staying together with his son but also in the pursuit of money, and to someday have a beautiful mansion in which to raise their offspring (outside of this neighborhood where write"felycidad", thus, incorrectly, with the first"i"in Greek)."And curiosity is this person prototype made to suffer, to be always in tension and to the brink of collapse. The test is that labour broker is not precisely of those who put one relaxed and comfortable.Taking into account the type of film that is, and the optimal achievement of their results, well he deserves place above other similar proposals that reach us from "the industry".</body>
</review>
