<review author="Caruco" title="Noche en el museo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Moderately meets its objectives, including smiles, even leaves us a flavor similar to the titles is made in the 80's.</summary>
	<body>If someone expects a solid or committed food, this is not his film. It is a comedy American, with many Visual effects, protagonidada by Ben Stiller, and aimed at the family audience. No more surprises than the check which is the level of special effects, if Ben Stiller, accompanied by his inseparable Owen Wilson, suffer the evil of the comedian with "tiresome" grimaces or see if it achieves to boot, at least some smile.Try to give what offers, in generous doses and perhaps too commissioning children look. But it contains the added lure of running into us with a particularísmo formed trio of thugs no less than by Dick Van Dyke ("Mary Poppins"), 80 years! behind him, and made a kid, even scoring a few passes of dance; Billy Cobbs (secondary luxury in titles as "Cotton club" or "The color of money"), 70 years, and the small great Mickey Rooney, nothing less than 85 years!, and made a grumpy's more sympathetic.They are not the only actors "resurrected" for the occasion. We also have a Robin Williams (overcome their problems with alcohol), in plan beloved colleague, that embodies, and never better said, to the figure of Theodore Roosevelt.Aventuras at the great Museum.The invention allows paraded before our eyes all sorts of historical figures, including a Columbus speaking on Genoese, Pharaohs and ordas, barbarians, Romans, jeans, Maya and Neanderthal men. And other animal species more sympathetic or dangerous from a thug mono cappuccino, until tiranosauros-rex, Lions, Mammoths or reptiles.This is the fauna that inhabits the vast Museum of Natural history in New York, with allowing to set up that premise, or feeling, passing there one night must be disturbing, especially if some of the objects starts to come alive.The Mise en scène by Shawn Levy ("the Pink Panther") is as functional as effective trying to both the script and the star of Ben Stiller reluzcan without squeaking and the accumulation of so many effects not getting tired, too.Moderately meets its objectives, including smiles, and even leaves us a taste, but not the same greatness, similar to the adventure and fantasy titles were made in the 1980s. Not in vain Chris Columbus, screenwriter of "Gremlins", "The secret of the pyramid" or "The goonies", and director of "Adventures in the big city" or "Solo at home" (1991), is after the production.Otherwise take Ben Stiller become a father of family and man, failed, without work stable, divorced and with a boy who longs to admire his father. And which, together with Federico Luppi, eventually finding their "place in the world," in the most incredible way and incidentally, to make all round, also in a guide of the Museum of very good looking (Carla Gugino).</body>
</review>
