<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The hollow voice that loose sentences of catechism was, the UNFPA, the star. There was a girl to make work a romance. It is actually not, to hold the banner that whites can fix Africa with a couple of laws. That maja, she.</summary>
	<body>"Blood diamond" has the appeal of having chosen a framework little visited by the film, the press or by the hand of God, the mines of diamonds from Sierra Leone, the wars between rebels and the Government troops and the giant Guinea refugee camps. Solomon Vandy is an African family father who suffers in his flesh struggles between factions to control the power, and, above all, the mines. The rebels arrive in her village with their machine guns and give it to choose between "manga short or long sleeves", a macabre sarcasm with the have to choose where you will cut the hand. Chance or luck, takes him to work a diamond mine where is the stone that serves as a plot thread of the story. Everyone wants that diamond, but he just wants to return to be with his family.DiCaprio plays a mercenary without scruples that acts as an intermediary between Western greed and cruelty of African guerrillas. He changed arms for diamonds. In jail he heard an officer of diamond of Solomon and followed. DiCaprio plays the character can do more for returned.In a beach bar, DiCaprio meets the girl and discusses with her principles. It's the journalist who interprets Jennifer Connelly. Maddy Bowen represents the conscience, the West which wants to help, hope that someone do something to change things.The film is excessive, too long, too ambitious. After the generous show of war and despair Zwick returns to their messages, which is a form of contempt for history.You do not know very well who is "good", and that is a bug. It is the story of an African father looking for his family? Yes, but the father bother us when he stands in the purposes of the dealer. DiCaprio is the protagonist almost all the time, because we are concerned to get the piedar. We don't know why Solomon trusts him.We should expect the end to realize that the girl is good. The hollow voice that loose sentences of catechism was, the UNFPA, the star. There was a girl to make work a romance. It is actually not, to hold the banner that whites can fix Africa with a couple of laws. That maja, she.</body>
</review>
