<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Muerte de un ciclista" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential film any film lover should have on their shelves. It is not a film only for film buffs stalwarts of whiskers yellow smoking Duchies, if not for a much wider audience, simply looking for a good movie to do a Sunday afternoon.</summary>
	<body>Not be as long that leads this box in most hidden shelf, without anyone mancillase the impeccable plastiquito Sunday gift that covered. Until today, that in an outburst of love for patriotic cinema, we have taken the scissors after giving seven unsuccessful morsels, and we got the DVD of his involuntary confinement. And what if I am glad I did.The film is an adulterous couple who in one of his trips by car kill an unnamed cyclist. At first, he tries to help, but she convinces him to escape. She is a married woman of upper-class, while he is an Assistant Professor of middle class. At a party who assists her, a friend makes a strange comment, which makes them think that they were seen and that they know his secret. From this moment begins a story about morality, deception and betrayal, culminating in a final apotheosis.Movies like these show the quality of our cinema, which in time could clearly compete with which we came from the other side of the pond. A very well braided history, with parallel plots and characters very well defined, certainly helps the quality of actors. In addition to a great film, it shows an image of the Spain of the time. These differences of postwar which later wanted to deepen, achieving a total boredom in viewers. Here neither judged nor will stop judging, displayed simply social strata, differences and customs, and all that in or eighty minutes. Can who give more?In short, essential film that all film lover should have on their shelves. It is not a film only for film buffs stalwarts of whiskers yellow smoking Duchies, if not for a much wider audience, simply looking for a good movie to do a Sunday afternoon.</body>
</review>
