<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Shortbus" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The bigoted Viewer or you feel rejection to contemplate pornography not aguantar치 or three minutes of projection. The cured of ghosts will enjoy a fun film that speaks for all of us at some point in our lives.</summary>
	<body>Do three years Michael Winterbottom inaugurated with 9 songs what one might call? indie-porn?, independent film with numerous explicit sex scenes. The film showed plainly the exchange of fluids of a couple that combine this activity with go from concert to concert. The sex in this tape - large silences - was pure exhibition at the service of a plot without rhyme or reason.Everything that was superfluous and free in the above sense of the excellent Shortbus cobra. The director signed a comedy that could well have done some sueltecitos Robert Altman or Woody Allen. Does John Cameron Mitchell, shows sex Yes, but in all its splendor: solo sex, sex to escape from loneliness, group sex? but as a vehicle to express the emotional situation of each character, not as they excuse to show flesh.The shortbus of the title is the name given to the bus carried school children with difficulties that need more attention and the club libertine where the protagonists come together. In this place all can give free rein to their fantasies. There agree a gay couple in search of a third party which avive their relationship, a sex counselor anorg치smica and a dominatrice unable to maintain emotional bond with any human being without the whip in his hand.In general, lost souls and bodies. As a New York Fund which, as one of the characters says is the city where goes the people to redeem their sins. And speaking of sins, this film contains lots: ejaculations, cunnilingus, fellatio, sodomy? nothing is hinted, is live sex.The bigoted Viewer or you feel rejection to contemplate pornography not aguantar치 or three minutes of projection. The cured of ghosts will enjoy a fun film that speaks for all of us at some point in our lives. But saying that Shortbus is pornography, is like saying that eating, drinking, love is a film about Asian cuisine. I am much more injured in my sensitivity when I look on the big screen the Bacchanalian gore of Mel Gibson - for example - that genital feasts, but I am so rare and spirited.I would also point out that I do not agree with sentences of advertising claim of this tape:?Do if Almod칩var rodase for the first time, you do this film?. Not to mention. More or less daring scenes of Pepi Luci Bom or labyrinth of passion were pure provocation and transgression in a given historical moment. In Shortbus no bad taste of any kind, as there it in the bed of two lovers.</body>
</review>
