<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Noche en el museo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is the end the most child point throughout the film, but despite this?Night at the Museum? does becomes an interesting and recommended product for all those who enjoy adventures in the style of?Jumanji?</summary>
	<body>The simple idea of that at night, when all visitors are gone, the figures of a museum come to life, it is something that draws attention and that in one way or another, all us you have raised or thought about many things. This is the start of this film by Shawn Levy, (twelve in house, the Pink Panther), which has a very interesting cast and consecrated as Ben Stiller, Robin Williams, Carla Gugino, Owen Wilson, Dick Van Dike, Mickey Rooney and Bill Cobbs among others. Larry Daley, played by Stiller, is a divorced father, tired of walking work at work, and at the prospect of having to move and fail to see his son, decides to accept the post of night watchman at the Museum of natural history in New York. Once there you will know the vigilant old (Van Dike, Cobbs and the mythical Rooney) which will give you a couple of tips before leaving you "solo".After get used to the place and start to make the goose, Stiller realizes that something is not quite normal, and that all the creatures of the Museum come alive at night. From a Tyrannosaurus Rex to tiny legions of Romans, jeans and indigenous Maya, Attila and the Huns, passing by Vikings, Mammoths, Neanderthals and President Roosevelt, played by Robin Williams. Clear reminiscent of "Jumanji", although at a lower level, "Night at the Museum" is presented as an entertaining adventure for all ages, that it will be great seeing everything that happens in this Museum, and partly wishing that I had had this when we were small. Daley will need to deal with all the problems generated by the tenants of the Museum, as well as other plots and conflicts will arise, and that you will have to deal with before dawn.It is true that there are some gaps, rather loose parts of script or up inconsistencies, but no one comes or is intended to meet "The godfather", and especially the public to whom it is intended is not so demanding, abundantly and so the objectives and fields in which you have to highlight, it does. "Night at the Museum" has a few very good special effects, however has the supervisor of this Department of the trilogy of "The Lord of the rings", as well as the company "Rhythm &amp; Hues", responsible for of "the Chronicles of Narnia: the lion, the Witch and the wardrobe".It also enhance production and art, team recreate a Museum of these dimensions is not easy task.The end is the most child throughout the film, but despite this, "Night at the Museum" becomes an interesting and recommended product for all those who enjoy adventure "Jumanji" style, at the same time that they remembered the stories and tales of his childhood and that they do not fail to enjoy this stage of their lives.</body>
</review>
