<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Tirante el blanco" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The plot weakens at all times and seems to move by way of vaudeville cheap and devoid of emotion</summary>
	<body>Little has served its Director have caressed this project for nearly 4 decades and having a budget of 15 million euros for its realization. Saving Alatriste, this one of the most expensive productions in the history of the Spanish cinema, and since they mentioned the title of Agustín Díaz Yanes, seems that we will have to wait for its premiere to see a proper film set in the past with characters of weight. After 24 films, Tirant Lo Blanc again an adaptation, this time of a classic romance published in Valencia in 1490 by Joanot Martorell. Vicente Aranda finds it ironic and sensual, something that has tried to move through images and a screenplay poor that it focuses in the raids of the Court and in the virginity of a Princess as insurance of life of a people and their rulers. Exceptions as Juana la loca, from lovers, filmed in 1991, Catalan seems not right in his dramas, which are always lame (the case of Carmen), are unnecessarily stretched (Turkish passion) or end up solving with late accelerated after a coherent development (libertarian).Aranda covers only part of the novel, in which there are ingredients of adventure, mystery and policy, and is not to emphasise the strong erotic charge of its pages? not talking sensuality precisely - but that surrounding it revolves around the plot of the movie. Sad IE it before a filmmaker as smart, but not surprising with its new proposal: sex openly and without encouragement seem shy, little contextualized, a stance that is offset with a modern, curious language even, and the funny portrait of the mandate of the intriguing women in maintaining the health of the Empire, contrary to the established male order.The ladies of the Court are those who make policy and these actresses, which try to Eaglets a plot that weakens at all times, resembling circular vaudeville as a cheap and devoid of emotion. Much more Leonor Watling and Ingrid Rubio (two sides of the same coin) to Victoria Abril and newcomer Esther Nubiola? of it explains, the April - fail the attention by professional merits. This point is aggravated by the misguided male cast, headed by an expressionless Caspar Zafer and Rafael Amargo. The first as the Knight that comes to Constantinople to fight against the invaders and the second giving life to the Grand Turk. They blamed the result to the problems of production and it is true that things were not arranged as initially promised the veteran filmmaker: change Sicily by Istanbul at the last minute is just one example of the sweat that has because of cost. But we must judge by what we see on the screen and the result, however much that hurts us to be one of the greats of European cinema, is not much.</body>
</review>
