<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Días de cine" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Days of the cinema is one of the worst Spanish films of recent years, which spare you vulgarity and missing above all dignity</summary>
	<body>One of the greatest burdens suffered by art and Spanish culture in the 20th century has been the Franco dictatorship and its censorship. And as any art, the film was one of the main victims of this ballast. Not only because they tighten the freedom and creativity of our filmmakers, such as Bardem and Berlanga, but by the imposition of a kind of cinema that ex post has already called "the españoladas". Do the films of the prodigies as Joselito or Marisol, the folkloric, Paco Martínez Soria, Gracita Morales? and a long list of others have done much harm to the health of our film. During the transition came a phase opposite to the previous with the arrival of freedom, but also harmful to the Spanish cinema, "uncover", and at that time situated David Serrano new locked days of cinema. after the success of football days, Serrano offers us a story telling the difficulties of Frederick (Alberto San Juan) to shoot his first movie as a director. Silvia count (Nathalie Poza) and his producer José María Culebras (Miguel Rellán), this project is the last chance to return to the cinema, or bid at least him farewell with dignity. David Serrano raises his new job as a tribute in a tone of comedy to the directors of that time, true heroes of our cinematography, who fought against everything and everyone in order to carry out his work. The initial idea is good, but Serrano their development fails him, and committed a serious sin, not taking seriously what counts. The tape is intended to cover both the comedy incongruous as the pure human drama, and you know the saying. If that were the worst of the evils of days of the cinema, viewers still could feel fortunate, but unfortunately it isn't. The script, in which he has participated Alberto San Juan, is nothing more than a succession of absurdities, to which worse, while the characters are just puppets empty, without depth or development. The comic elements of the film are nothing more than crude humor, easy jokes, absurd situations coming to provoke the embarrassment, and that leave the works of Spain uncover at summits of the intelligent comedy. The dramatic moments are to go to cry bitterly, because it does not have intensity or convey the most basic of emotions. Semenjante panorama, little or nothing can be done actors, although comforting return to Michael Byrne. days of cinema screens is one of the worst Spanish films of recent years, which spare you vulgarity and missing above all dignity. As a comedy, it doesn't not shred of grace, and as human and social drama, is laughable. Let us hope that from this good idea carried a tape that take seriously the story telling, and to do so with what has lacked to days of the cinema, dignity.</body>
</review>
