<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Ordet. La palabra" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Arriesgadísimo cinema, denial of the film almost because minimally cares of the usual conventions of film as art and is carried away by the spirit, by the word, by the theatrical...</summary>
	<body>Ordet is not a film for those who do not have a certain commitment to cinema as a vehicle of spiritual satisfaction. I am not referring to the film as a transmitter of values or cinema as mere show of mass moving in search of a purpose or film as candy to sweeten Sunday mornings with the family.Ordet is evidence that miracles exist: human behavior conforms to some spiritual canons and there are directors who have the sufficient sensitivity (and the appropriate master) for explicit with a minimum elements a philosophy, a metaphysics. Borgin, a peasant family politically correct and most beloved, addresses his life of bucolic retreat to the inevitable by a son obsessed by religion. There is a resurrection that we do not know if it sticks to the efficient reading of the word of God or a departure from script of the Danish Dreyer, who was a believer in volume and lomo and wrote screenplays such as who makes a pastoral or raises his Canticle that God give headquarters and hear his appeal. The father is the religious reference family and somehow transmitted these concerns to his eldest son: Johannes reads like a maniac to Kieerkegaard and it is believed, at times, Jesucristo. Ordet (the word) tells what all feel regardless of our moral filiation. Mine, for other scarce, if not, null, was left to carry the voice of Johannes apastelada and I consentí the flush of faith even by the two sparse hour. . Have faith, understood, not strictly due to mandate or religious devotion. Not this review has proposed doing an essay on the depths of the human soul. It is not the place and there is no commitment or knowledge on the subject to carry any thesis any port.The faith that profess the Borgin, in general, is a utilitarian faith: agreed to deal with the embites of the day, the hardness of the field, the Pilgrim feeling that another world can probably better exist. The only truly believes is the fool, the enlightened one, the voracious reader all transmutes it in obedience blind to the word. Dreyer films as if it were a theatrical representation: in very few occasions, I remember a camera is comfortably seated spectators. It is theatrical film without another obstacle to the dialogue fluid all the characters. This camera is, however, also roams the strict limits of a room when in the room what is relevant for the development of, on the other hand, very little (argumentativamente) plot. There is a scene in which the doctor and Johannes were ensarzan in a theological discussion acaloradoa. One requires that the faith is the salvation of the world and the doctor, burdened by his militant secularism, scientific, argues that the world is saved by the political action and critical materialism. All that well pespuntado by the movement of the camera, makes us to get involved in an absolute way in the thinking of every Boxer in this mystical combat.The viewer of this film is aware that this film is beyond any hierarchy: that more than film role is attending a willing moral revelation as if it were a movie, a reasoned and logical concatenated frame. Who has placed the film as a way of life should see Ordet at least once in life. This chronicler not asserts that each viewer get invaded by the subtlety of its purpose. There will be who see the numen and there will be who, having opposite, not perceived. And after all, I reason, faith is that. It is believed or not believed. The film is that: you're inside or only entertains you. The word, the word became flesh lucid, Vertigo of ideas.Another aspect to consider is the beauty of the scenes that happen outside the walls: the wind shaking the corn, modestísima choreography of clouds... Those details face the mental nature of the film (religion, redemption, meat, Salvation, the miracle that we know that you will get at any time) and the secret order of the universe, that does not require chants, prayers, or moral digressions to excite.It is necessary to insist on the halo of pure feeling that exhaled throughout the film. Dreyer is drunk of life. Ordet is an absolute monument to cinema with capital letters, a milestone, a real tribute to the moral nature of man above their deviations from their sins and their erratic stay in the world.Addenda: Ordet is an extreme film in many ways. Or is considered a work of art, it is my opinion, or a pain in the ass, a joke, an intolerable excess. If it is not, as always happens, you can not comment, so their opinion, look it up, give the great pleasure of sailing in this burial.</body>
</review>
