<review author="Caty" title="Cadena Perpétua" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a pity that perhaps not will take none of the Oscars which was nominated (although already know how these awards), but his great reception among the public was perhaps the greatest reward that could be.</summary>
	<body>I remember that when I first saw "Perpetual chain" some years ago in a pass at dawn by La2, occurred, between the movie and me, one of these "arrows" that notes nothing more see the first images on the screen. And made me a lump in my throat at the end, when network and Andy at the end are. Since then, every time you passed the film on television, leaving what had in hands and gave me to see her.Finally, her I bought on DVD. Some days ago, I went back to take a look to write this article with some property and again began to feel the old knot often accompanied me when I had the opportunity to sit in front of her. With a screenplay based on a story by Stephen King, imprisonment of director Frank Darabont, really can be considered one of the great Decade of the 90.Andrew produciones Dufresne(Tim_Robbins) would not have much to highlight if what we saw on the street. Very correct, incorruptible to a great extent, is the Executive of a large bank.A common face, a common life. Run the 1940s. The fact is that the existence of this person gives a twist completely when he discovers that is deceived by his wife with a golf player. It is drunk. He comes to think of killing her. With the gun in hand, trembling, I thought if doing so or no.pero did not do so. Meanwhile, the same night someone murdered his wife and her lover leaving a lot of evidence that pointed to Andy. "Sentenced to two life sentences, he was taken to prison, where their dreams were locked under seven keys among violent prisoners and abusive guards.""Perpetual chain" could be seen as a film about a friendship, how Andy is in its partner network (Morgan Freeman) all the nobility and confidence that, in an environment so hostile seems impossible to imagine. But the truth is that the true leitmotif of the film is the feeling of hope. On how dreams persist living and intense for decades and decades, even in circumstances under which, the hopelessness and disappointment they would dent in anyone.At a time of the footage, one of the inmates more elderly, Brooks, finally receives his conditional. What should be very gratifying for the old librarian just transforming into shouts and tears. "After 50 years here, these walls is everything that the known", I would say network. And that was what was happening. The world outside, for the old Brooks had been transformed into a monster that devoured himself. The had already become accustomed to the jail. That was their world. Those walls were their freedom. Those prisoners were true friends. And that fear of living out of Shawshank prison make that Brooks would prefer to flee otherwise: hanging from a rope in her room rented nothing more going out into the street. But Andy didn't so not conformed. Even after two decades based on suffering the worst physical abusos-tanto as psychological - to which a human being can be subjected, the still kept the flame burning. "Beware, the hope is dangerous here inside" network warned. But Andy not heard. And hopeful continued. He didn't want great luxuries, only a simple life, a beach in Mexico, a ship old to navigate and earn enough to subsistir.y a beer in the Sun, exactly as that day on the roofs of the prison. Or like when Andy sneaks into the garita of the guard to put them through the speakers an album with "The marriage of Figaro" prisoners (I have no idea of what the hell sang those two italianas.y the truth is that I do not know it, good things don't need understand them.) I guess they were singing about something so beautiful that I could not express themselves with words, and precistamente is why made you the heart throb. I assure you that those voices you rising higher and further that no one living somewhere so gray could dream. was like a beautiful bird had entered our monotone cage and would have dissolved those muros.y for a brief moment until the last man in the prison felt libre.claro the warden that didn't like anything. (Andy he fell two weeks in the hole by that Act) and the same applies to hope: no matter how many beatings you receive, how much you humillen.ella, the hope is always there, guiding you and making you go ahead. And for men like Andrew Dufresne, hope never disappears.What most draws the attention of this production is the script, which is very well developed and worked, emphasising the harsh reality of who is behind the walls of a prison and has to survive knowing that it does not have nor the most remote possibility of going out into the street and above it is innocent. It presents all the situations that can occur in a jail, from discussions between prisoners until the corruption in officials and administrators. One of the strong points of its history is also the way in which the prison is reflected in such way that is a world quite apart from abroad, with values that do not have to be equal to our own, to free citizens. As for the characters, their dialogues are excellently prepared. While Andy demonstrates that hope that we talked about above, network assumes the role of the man who is there to comfort him and to show the reality where he lives, is more realistic, more resigned with his destino.y to the end just ilusionando with Andy, starring in an encounter that leaves completely without words at the end of the projection.The conclusion I got from this film is that we can imprison a person, to his body, but never can we imprison your mind, your spirit. It is a pity that perhaps not will take none of the Oscars which was nominated (although already know how these awards), but his great reception among the public was perhaps the greatest reward that could be. In 1966 Andrew Dufresne ran away from Shawshank prison. The only thing found was his inmate clothing stained clay, a tablet of SOAP and old hammer of gems practically spent so much use. I remember that I had thought that a man would take 600 years to dig a tunnel in the wall with him. The old Andy did in less than twenty. Andy loved to geology, I guess that you fit with his meticulous nature.For him, the time passed slowly, as in the Glacial era. Geology is the study of pressure and time and in fact, that's all we need: pressure and time, that and a big poster.As I said earlier, in jail a man makes almost anything to keep your mind occupied, the favorite pastime of Andy was to take pieces of that wall to the courtyard, handful to handful. The night of his escape, Andy did what was commanded: left the warden shoes like two mirrors. The guards, nor were evangelicals either, honestly, how often you look at the shoes wear another man?. Andy reached freedom dragging for 500 yards in a pipe full of crap that stank as I cannot or imaginar.o may not want to imagine me what. 500 yards, the length of five fields of football, almost half milla.a the next morning, more or less when Raquel Welch revealed her little secret, a man that no one had seen before entered the National Bank of Mainehitherto not existed only on paper. He wore his documentation in rule and his signing coincided with men they had front. "That morning Andy went through nearly a dozen banks, in total left the city with more than 370 thousand dollars of the money had been shutting warden Norton with an imaginary identity: their"compensation"by the age of 19".</body>
</review>
