<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Juegos secretos" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Secret games is a failed dissection of the American media society.</summary>
	<body>There are some situations in life that produce us a curious sensation of something already lived experience of déjà vu, as if we were protagonists of a flashback, for using cinematic language. The presence of games secrets in the 79th Edition of the Oscars is one of those situations, since that five years ago, the previous work of Todd Field, in the room, also had a presence at the annual awards of the Academia.En games secrets, Todd Field adpata the novel by Tom Perrotta, which has also participated in the script. The calm and tranquillity of a residential neighborhood is truncated when Ronnie j. McGorvery (Jackie Earle Haley), a pedophile fresh out of prison. Some residents concerned about children, create a Committee whose objective is staying alert monitor to Ronni, and try to throw him in the neighbourhood. Meanwhile, routine life of Sarah Pierce (Kate Winslet) gives a turn when she meets Brad Adamson (Patrick Wilson). Todd Field presents us with a story that explores the hidden side of the lives that take place in a peaceful residential neighborhood American lives full of lies, deception and broken dreams. The initial proposal of the film, despite a disastrous form of voice-over narration captivates the viewer with a very attractive first half hour. However, little by little the plot is goes weakening, without take too much to break down completely. The script, where there is not a hint of originality, which weakens ostensibly, lapses and quickly produces a great narrative abyss, which collapses the attention and interest of the Viewer. For its part, the characters are flat, mere caricatures, without motivation or ability to evolution. The slow pace prints Todd Field history and the duration of the tape are the elements that give the lace to games secrets. b &gt; only interpretations and some unhealthy curiosity and somewhat masochistic keep the public in his armchair. Kate Winslet done a brilliant job, as we are accustomed of great restraint and sobriety, interpretation which has earned his fifth nomination to the Oscar with only 31 years old. For its part, Jackie Earle Haley makes human character, which already is commendable and worthy of applause. Patrick Wilson performs a correct interpretation, while a Jennifer Connelly, as usual, there is no who is created.Secret games is a failed dissection of American media society full of well-worn situations and common places. Todd Field again disappoint five years later, proving unable to live up to expectations. As then, the unique appeal of the film are interpretations of its actors.</body>
</review>
