<review author="Marta" title="María Antonieta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>At first the film promises, but ends up being very "pop" wrapper with little content.</summary>
	<body>I note that I am not one of those people who love to Sofia Coppola and all that it does. "Lost in Translation", although Nice aesthetically, it seems simploncilla, and history find it me very irritating with a tipa suffering for their holidays paid in Tokyo and much messing of American-in-Japan on the curious are Asians and how bad that speak English. "The Virgin suicides" yes I liked, but clear, the film adapts with great fidelity the beautiful novel by Jeffrey Eugenides, so it does not count. In general, I think that the Coppola is very overrated and it works in what works, largely thanks to being the daughter of who is. On the other hand, they may not like those movies that play with current elements in contexts or environments of other times, and I think "Romeo+Julieta" and "Moulin Rouge", Baz Luhrmann, more as a failed experiment than as anything other. Having said all that, I suppose it is not surprising to say that I went to see "Marie Antoinette" without waiting for nothing more than a display of modernita which might be its Director. And, to be honest, at first I thought that I had made a mistake. At first, the thing promised, and while it is true that details as music or hairstyles to layers are not too stringent - or pretend to be him-, was not something that called the attention unduly or is annoying. At the beginning, clear. It is then completely hand and begins the "anything goes", with dances showing the soundtrack of way too obvious or own advertising scenes. There who about to appear some Converse will find very funny. I guess it is, but it is also certainly representative of what the film: long "pop" wrapper and little content. And, to make matters worse, during long time. Because that is another: "Marie Antoinette" goes through long "phases". The phase in which nothing matters more than her virginity and his enmity with the mistress of the King, the stage music, cakes and colorful, the bucolic phase "sheep and garden", and so until the end - precipitadísimo, by the way-. Jumping from one thing to another without any coherent, even purely formal connection. Finally, that despite its careful image, this reinterpretation of the story of the famous Queen I didn't. In fact, I think it is the worst thing that has made the Director. But I have already noticed that I am not one of those people who worship Sofia Coppola?</body>
</review>
