<review author="F. José Lorite" title="La Novia Cadaver" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Life and death are never so particularly represented as to when this Tim Burton, giving a ludicrous treatment, thus criticizing the current society.</summary>
	<body>Return to a world apart, the world of Tim Burton where he directs with Mike Johnson the new installment of this own universe, where the dead are not both and the living do not appear to be so.Tim Burton continued with its aforementioned own universe, in the line of nightmare before Christmas, now recreating an old Russian legend, that fits perfectly in that style obsessive seeking refined forms and impossible within the characteristic atmosphere of grim and ghostly, we already showed in works such as Bitelchus or Eduardo hands scissors, but away from the colorism of some of his latest works such as Big Fish and Charlie and the factory of Chocolate.Para recreation of this Russian legend Burton uses a technique as previously used as stop-motion, for the creation of the characters and the story has served a great team of animators include two Catalan brothers, the brothers Grangel which have achieved that his creations seem significantly to its dubbers, include Johnny Deep voice that puts Victor Van DortHelena Bonham Carter, which gives voice to the bride corpse, and Emily Watson to Victoria Everglot, giving life to their respective characters.In this legend, Victor Van Dort, rich family but without cache and Victoria Everglot aristocrats ruined family, two young men belonging to the Victorian era are going to marry without being known before, is a marriage for convenience although quickly emerged the spark between the two, in the trial of the wedding Victor is not able to pronounce their votes so dead of fear runs and practicing for a scary forest fits the ring in an old branch turns out to be the finger of a defunct, dead on the day of her wedding, dragged as well to the world of the dead, making his fiancée wait desolate in the world of the living.Life and death are never so particularly represented as to when this Tim Burton, giving a ludicrous treatment, thus criticizing the current society. In this new film proposed us two worlds, the world of the living and the world of the dead. The world of the living distilled hypocrisy, conventions and interests which causes a sad society off and without any color, while the world of the dead is more simple, giving importance to the feelings of its inhabitants looking for his happiness, causing a world of colorful, fun spontaneous and sincere, proof of this is the warmth with which receive new guests. Intelligent use of the music and the songs included in the film, having the exact time and without getting tired, are into perspective.Splendid film that you catch with all its tenderness and spontaneity, making you feel participate the travel of its protagonists towards his love, providing exquisite touches of love and nostalgia that hechizan in his fabulous staging.</body>
</review>
