<review author="Jorge" title="Cache Escondido" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The videos are "the gaze of the other", the "other" us spy and frightens us</summary>
	<body>Rare film for us Argentines, that we do not have on hand so the problems of racial discrimination as some European countries but does not seem to casual to appear today, after the conflict in the French suburbs. In this way, the film can be interpreted as an allegory. Placing us: what are the videos? What role play and what they can represent for this family? The videos are "the gaze of the other". The "other" us spy and frightens us, we do not know from where and what he sees or what he saw.The fear arises from guilt of the protagonist and his wife, in the allegory is the white, wealthy and bourgeois, society front to the "other", to the marginalized of African origin living in the suburbs. The first indication gives it almost Street fight with the young black rider in terms of delivering a beating to the protagonist, who after insults and bluster, opt to avoid the lawsuit with a request for forgiveness by the wife. The second clue is the distrust of the white boy to his mother. There are several others. Note all developing a suffocating atmosphere, which is why is not, as it is not the "other" which filmed, but that is always present and his presence is felt. The white family does not want to have the "other"; her distracted from their chores of your life which you are entitled, he intimidated, but the State, the police, can not help to remove it off porque.el "Other" he hasn't done anything. There is no reason for the police to intervene. If there is an aggressor, it is the protagonist. Drawings remind the child conflict between the white and the Algerian, where there was a perdidoso and a winner. Who loses is the Algerian, son of those who came to post-war Europe to work on the reconstruction and remained there as kelpers, as second-class citizens. This generation was lost, had no education for economic integration and the result is clear to see in the small, squalid Department Majid, in contrast to the cold and comfortable housing in the white family. Majid grew up to his son without resentment or oblivion but could not survive the depression of its marginalized generation that saw progress, comfort and culture? from the outside. His death becomes effective in front of his child executioner. His blood is mixed, is confused with the Rooster which earned him expulsion of the House of culture and progress. The Rooster? the French Rooster announcing tomorrow, progress and advancement. dies degollado like Majid, whose parents were killed in the Seine by whites during the conflict with Algeria. There was no progress, there was no integration for them, only death; gallo did not sing for them. Does the final scene shows the children of actors out of the school, talking? That could solve the enigma of the videos and can be a new Rooster that sings for both, always and when they go together to the school; always let the other be another one another alien, faced, but that recognizes it as equal part of a society still indebted.</body>
</review>
