<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El resplandor" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the best films of Kubrick, but it was always considered minor works. It is also the best adaptation of a Stephen King novel. And it is the best performance of a Jack Nicholson almost always outstanding. Is it needed most?</summary>
	<body>Well we all shine onLike the moon and the stars and the sunWell we all shine onEvryone come on (Instant Karma John Lennon) A start: A yellow car along a road that skirts a lake between mountains taken from above: so starts the shining (The shining, taken from Lennon's song), but the director not was in Oregon filming that scene: he delegated decision-making Douglas Milsowe and the expertise of his daughter, who oversaw the location of foreign film.Jack Torrance is a writer in search of a novel, an alcoholic writer, married to a prudish and father of a son of a paranormal outstanding sensitivity. Will they hire to do the maintenance of the Overlook, a luxury hotel in the Rocky closes season low by snow. In five months of isolation, prefigures Jack, you can write her novel and do a simple job. Grady, the former security guard, they inform, became crazy: he killed his wife and their daughters to hack and then committed suicide. Life in the hotel leads to Jack becomes crazy and make Grady during the last footage of the film.Everything else: Danny, the son of Jack, walking the aisles with his tricycle. Richard Donner accused Kubrick of plagiarizing him that a child with a tricycle appeared in his successful "The prophecy".Room 237: Danny was invited by two twins to play with them forever. We have seen a lift who vomits a ton of blood.A spectral barman serves Jack a whisky in a kind of party at The Gold Room, the huge Hall of the Overlook. The hotel, except for the Torrance, we know that is empty. Room 237 again: Jack is there a nude young woman in a tub: to kiss her turns into an old pustule and sores.The ballroom of the Overlook are crowded of people: Jack suffers an accident, a waiter poured you a drink over the clothing. Animated chat service serves so that we know that the waiter is Grady, the previous guard, which killed his wife and daughters to battering, although the Grady we see does not remember to be such. "I'm sorry dissent." The watchman is you. You have always been the watchman. I remember it well. I've always been here ", says Jack while he assesses it.""The typewriter:" do Although one will rise early, it won? t dawn sooner "or what amounts to the same thing." "Not for much early Sunrise earlier". Kubrick, detalloso until the obsession, was personally responsible for that in each country the typewriter most a text according to the popular phraseology. The phrase is repeated until the naúsea.Jack gets bastard: Wendy, his wife, tries to escape when he sees a little already played Jack. She locks him up in a closet and take awhile. Jack, with the help of a reasonably nice Grady escapes: brandishes an axe (the most famous axe in the history of the cinema) and breaks the door of the room where Wendy takes refuge. Loose there the famous: "Here's Jaaaaaaaack", which has its legend, of course. Apparently the phrase was improvised by a willful Nicholson and although Kubrick you pleased, made repeated 157 times. Now we don't know, at this point, if the bastard is Jack or Stanley. Jack kills Halloran, the former chef of the Overlook, who has come to the hotel by telepathy linking him to Danny.Jack, the axe, the snow and Danny, fleeing: the technical work of Kubrick is an amazing exercise of brute steadycam by the labyrinth of snow or the corridors of the hotel. A ghost with the wounded head tells to Jack Torrance, already completely gone: "do A nice party, truth Jack Nicholson is here in her wild gestures sauce, inebriated himself as seldom seen.??"The final photo: Kubrick, in the hands of Grady, teaches us the photo that closed or open questions. We see Torrance in The gold room in the dance of July 4, 1921. Grady it seems he was right with everything what you told in the service.Inventory of curiosities: all the interiors of the film are real. A rumor: the initial takes of Kubrick with car debris tuck mountains were used by Ridley Scott for the escape of Dekker with the replicant in Blade Runner.Es the Kubrick film, along with Barry Lindón, where there are more repetitions of scenes. Jack Nicholson clashed repeatedly with Kubrick by this abuse. The narrow-minded of Shelley Duvall was continually battered by the director to get her a more natural, in his words, "State of stress or fear or bad grapes".Kubrick cared especially the soundtrack of the film as it was always his habit: parade Ligeti, Bartok, Penderecki, Beryl...or the Orchestra of Ray Noble in the songs of jazz to salpimentan any part of the film.Dubbing: lumpy and splendid voice of Rafael Taibo covers Halloran, the chef. Neither the Forque Veronica that doubles or doubles of Jack Nicholson Wendy contented to the Spanish public, although choice (very curious thing, really) was carried out by the own King Kubrick.Stephen was not satisfied of the work of Kubrick. Yes, on the contrary, he was enthusiastic about a miniseries filmed by his friend Mike Garris. In the novel of King, the hotel arde. Kubrick saw him laughable. A vulgarity.Conclusion: the best 1980s horror film. One of the best of all time. Only by the great madness of Nicholson worth all of it. King was deservedly honored in Carrie and Misery. This is the most successful, which contributes to his love for leaving filming his works more solidly.</body>
</review>
