<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Pulse" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>American horror film Japanese-style on a virús which seeks to steal the life of human beings to thus get one of their own. Much fear does not give, but the idea can leave you thinking awhile.</summary>
	<body>I'm going to venture me with this movie, given that all indications are that it is a remake of another Japanese who had no great fame in the West and a clever Director has decided to bring her here. Aesthetics and the theme is 100% Japanese, with those bad white face that you suck the blood. By the way, has who copied whom? The bad characters is equal to the Dementors from Harry Potter.La film is about a group of kids, of those bodies ten, with extensive knowledge of computer science. Total, one of them, who knows more is attacked by a nosequé makes that it will be putting purple until appears his girlfriend and this commits suicide. And the thing continues, with the TV warning of a new virus that is transmitted by the computer, the palm and even toasters. And coming to the end is not God, that this should be a criticism of the society in which we live, where lost humanism of frias relations towards personal and impersonal relationships of the computer. Or I know I know, I learned well.Nothing, this is a hell. They say it is a film of fear, but gives three scares predecidos coming from a Chan-Chan that takes away the fear. Well, I have to admit that if I am in the first scene I shit there same, but since the seat did not happen from a mere "sustito Uy". The plot is curious, with a virus that travels by computers and that goes out to steal the life has no human beings. So, until I would even say I have a Matrix touch. The actors are very well see, but do not understand how they do not go naked unnecessary or similar. Actors are not very much, I do not vibrate, of course.In short, film america of terror to the Japanese style on a virús which seeks to steal the life of human beings for this way to get one of their own. Much fear does not give, but the idea can leave you thinking awhile.</body>
</review>
