<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La gran evasión" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential film war semi, which shows greater leakage of prisoners which took place during the second world war. Dynamic, intriguing, tense, emotional, personal, with thousands of small stories that have made it one of the best films of all time.</summary>
	<body>If I have not seen this movie 20 times I have not seen any time, and this has been the first that I've finally seen the opening scene. Not be why, but that entry into the concentration camp had never passed through my retina. Also this time I I have heard that it is based on a real event, with which the hairs as usual hooks have become hairs as beams of skyscrapers. That wonderful film.The film is about a modern concentration camp during World War II. It fall all military prisoners who have been captured and recaptured many times, i.e., experetos in fugues. According to the philosophy of the Chief in command, they have gotten all the apples rotten in a basket. So the prisoners decide, guided by a natural leader, make more flight that was never made, to achieve that Nazi troops lose time searching for them, instead of fighting on the front.This film is of the few of the second world war which does not show cruelties and horrors of war and concentration camps. Shows a friendly face of the war, with some very innocent nazis who rub the absolute candor. On the other hand, the allies are astute and intelligent mostly, with a great sense of honor and duty. Perhaps too much Candida vision which gives, but certainly a tremendous film. A terrific cast, with a real story that puts the willies and calls the epic, manages to keep the tension for almost three hours, something not easy to do.In short, essential film war semi, which shows greater leakage of prisoners which took place during the second world war. Dynamic, intriguing, tense, emotional, personal, with thousands of small stories that have made it one of the best films of all time.</body>
</review>
