<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Preparation and development are the work of a good magician of the cinema which, unfortunately, has failed to finish the trick.</summary>
	<body>"Every great magic trick consists in three acts." The first is called the promise: the magician shows something ordinary, but as you might expect, so probably not.The second act is called the turn. The wizard makes the ordinary something do something extraordinary. Now however, although look the secret, so you will not find.This is why there is a third act called the prestige. This is the part of the twists and unexpected changes, in which life hangs in a thread, and somewhat surprising look that you've never seen before "in this sentence, which is repeated several times, summarizes much of the philosophy of"The final trick (the Prestige)", the latest film by Christopher Nolan, interesting Pearl"Batman Begins"or"Memento"director." Therein, the writers (Nolan and his brother Jonathan) we are talking directly to us viewers, letting us know what is going to happen; the whole movie regarded as a magic trick.To build a film mystery it must be very careful with solving it well, and even more, if you spend the entire film commenting that the end will be the milk and you have to be very attentive ("are you watching closely?" repeated endlessly). My biggest problem with the film is that, finally, the resolution find it me unsatisfactory. Both roll to ultimately get the top hat (Yes, has left me a joke) a resolution so glib, find it me rather disappointing.But there are also aspects that I like, and many, starting with the performances of the cast. Hugh Jackman, actor that grows slowly and will still give us many joys, knows to show us all the weaknesses, doubts and transformations of his character. Christian Bale, an experimentadísimo actor despite his youth, is exhibited in his role of obsessed by magic. Michael Caine already cannot be said nothing that has not been said before; It is a large screen which although it leaves little pleasure to see it. In brief interventions can score to Scarlett Johansson, coming out for what could have hired to any other, and a David Bowie that brings an air of aristocratic, lunatic and mysterious to a character that is you could have gotten more juice.The atmosphere is really successful, both by the excellent art direction able to put us at the time, by a photograph that oscillates between the realist and magic with great naturalness. Not by chance, these are only two nominations for the film at the Oscars. In this way, between the careful production, great performances, a story with claw and that capacity that Nolan catch the Viewer, is passed a very entertaining while.This is one of those movies that worth see more than once to appreciate all the small details that are scattered throughout the script (attention to the parallels between what happens you to one and another protagonist). A script that makes us go changing point of view, alternately identifying with the character of Bale and Jackman in this spiral of hatred and admiration in which the two characters become entangled.This moral ambiguity is disturbing and appealing but the problem is that the Viewer to not identify is finally with anyone, can break away a bit of the plot. Plot is complicating it skillfully plot twist in plot twist, until that is damaged with some alleged surprises are not such because us them have been launching face of rather crude form during the last third of the film. Why consider five minutes late, those in which we were going to leave open-mouthed, as most disappointing movie. The own Nolan says it in the script: once the trick is known one feels disappointed. For this reason, many times it is better to suggest that show.My feeling out of the cinema was empty, something akin to a coitus interruptus (I guess). And it is that preparation and development are the work of a good magician of the cinema, able to create an entertainment of first order with fascinating moments. But Nolan, unfortunately, has not been able to finish the trick.</body>
</review>
