<review author="Iñigo" title="El Espejo (Zerkalo)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The memory as a trip to the posterity.</summary>
	<body>Ingmar Bergman on Andrei Tarkovsky: "my first discovery of Tarkovsky was like a miracle." Suddenly I was next to the door of access to an enclosure that I had always wanted enter, but whose key never had been given to me, and that Tarkovsky was moving freely and confidently. I felt encouraged, stimulated: someone had expressed what I've always wanted to say, without knowing how. Tarkovsky is for me the most important. "It has created a new language, which is the essence of the film, because it presents life as a reflection, life as a dream". In fact, of the above is "Zerkalo". Dream, poetic reflection, loved, evoked, a past that belongs to the director himself, but is also ours. Yesterday that merges with the contemporary, to build tomorrow, the most universal future. "The mirror" is the work with more autobiographical load of Tarkovsky, but not why it cannot be sealed, waterproof. Very personal, with exclusive elements of his memories, that form bubbles which transported by air, fire and water consumed in the course of his awakening, not he ceases to be a portrait we can recognize ourselves. "Zerkalo", as its title indicates, is the mirror in which we all look. It is the narration of a past meets present future and happen to be the essence of the nature of our human condition. It is necessary to travel to autoreconocernos, transcribing our entity, reach the point in which we become crystal clear water and are able to encourage us to our reflection. Recurring theme throughout the work of Tarkovsky. There is no narrative based on a classic storyline in "Zerkalo". There is no chronological or, therefore, logical order. Not matter (or comes to mind) to explore the real value and meaning of the film. The story itself is broken to form a cycle full of oneiric elements, memories, isolations, scraps of a reality experienced by one and represented for all. Tarkovsky gives the more metaphysical sense, risest, bombastic in his filmography to her recurring phrase of "Sculpting in time". Create forms, figures, sometimes transparent, you sometimes muddy (like water flowing from our life), to decorate in our interior. "The mirror" is not a complex movie. We turn her into complex. Evidenced by an introduction for quite a few incoherent, diffuse and whose explanation has nothing to do with the set of the film. But, as the director himself says, if we look at our interior the answer is much simpler than that of what appears. This scene, absolutely still the final path of the work, this path in search of our sincerity, our deeper truth, which will make us find the freedom lost, hidden in our pain. It pursues the reflex, excavated and eventually found in the form of a stammering young healing hypnosis. Recovery of spontaneous speech as faithful analogy of the encounter of ourselves, of our condition cercenada by a draconian regime that doesn't let us act as, in essence and, of course, since our birth, should act. The fourth film of the Russian director was about to take him to jail, by the inclusion of ambiguous images which served as form and refuge to a criticism which eventually confront him with the authorities. All this in a Communist dictatorship of the u. r. S. S. by then impossible to rebut, unless you'd like your life to run serious danger. The film, obviously censored, had a very complicated and delayed initial release, and was only screened in minority and very reserved places. Before damn, today work of cult. Much more than that: work of art, cultural heritage of a Russia as outlined in the world. In these difficult times, therefore, had to find ways, through metaphors, subtle images, intelligence Escapist, to escape the obvious, not show, do so unaffordable for obtuse minds. Only open minds, in search of continuous growth, could understand its magnitude and adapt it to their lives and their cultural environment. That gave the film sense Supreme, universal, which was precisely the maximum of Tarkovsky. Censorship, as we all well know, enhances the imagination. Without it, as many claim with sentiment ironic and slighted, the cinema will never be the same. And it does not fail the reason analyzing the thesis from the creative point of view. And also being aware of the situation, in the case that concerns us of the work, the disease is always point of inflection (or home) to start to rethink matters transcendental, vital, that we escape over our previous existence for various reasons. To the limit of our lives, on the brink of death (item in common with Bergman, but treated in both in a very uneven manner) we begin to understand, or at least tried. Thus, Alexei (alter-ego of the own Andrei), in the course of his evil, is transformed into someone very aimed to reflect. It does look to his past to his mistakes, his path, the way identify with him to, at the same time, identify us us. We are part of those memories, to constitute our own. It is as if you tour time which ghost, observing, learning, taking for himself, inserting in lives outside to feel the suffering that seizes them, their thoughts and feelings (which are also, on many occasions, his own, those of his childhood) before a becoming which seems painful, either because of a war coming, for the recovery of lost love, or for redemption against the cause of damage to which it is not known how pardon. Alexei, the character, is all. We are all him. Belongs (mos) to his memory. It is an inseparable set if we want to find us and understand. Much of memories (dreams) concerning his childhood, it will become live on the way that can invoke them, is sometimes active character of the same, sometimes remains hidden, only his word (hence the predominance of spiritual over physical for Tarkovsky), not his person. It may be some relatively unrelated memories, viewing only, others hard, brittle, scary, but many are his past, pending covering wound, pardons waiting to occur. No doubt, reminiscences to his innocence and, at the same time, joined her womb (remains to historic film remember the impressive dreamlike sequence of levitation). Thus, "Zerkalo", cycles and spaces merge crazy way to note that, quite simply, the time "does not exist". There are universal feelings, times of them are unnecessary. Perfect example of this would be the bird that Alexei houses in his hand, transferring its cultural past to a future that esperanza, longs for story telling. Certainly has moments where is impossible to discern past, present or future, because they are unique to the director, only he associates. But to us we should not matter, the message is universal, global. We can insert an experience anyone, our, our habitat. The film passes through stops the lyrical and beautiful, to dark and scary (for past not complete or apprehended, which is like an abyss that generates fear, but not to the use, helpings, but real fear terror), ranging from by mysterious, exciting or delightful. We are not guided by the surface, which in appearance is purely cryptic, incomprehensible. Otherwise, we will only see disjointed sequences in time and space, not knowing to distinguish without are in present, past or future, if we who are there, if they are the same characters or if they have or stop having continuity. Nothing makes sense. But that, nothing matters. Effectively, can be complex insofar as memory, expressed images, are not ours (are of the own Tarkovsky, his own experiences). If not we are pleased to take them as their own, apply them to our lives, there is no mirror that look. There will be no way to go. Even so, here the memory not acts simply as a generator of memories, as component ajado (as it alters and abused in the majority of films), but as a method to mend us, to take her skills and apply them to our learning, our spiritual growth. That same memory footprint of the road to take, will disappear when we place ourselves on the path, which must be only visited by us. Hence emanates the historic flat final sequence, forming a long travelling (Tarkovsky House brand) which runs the nature, the vision toward the same as Union with the human being, making him immortal, achieving a littered with plenty of beauty and splendor. The report cited as a generator of Union of all ages, children, mother, grandmother (played by the director's own mother). All together in the freedom that nature has given us, free of splits, contemplating their gleam to the rhythm of the forklift, masterful, sublime, spiritual music of Bach. A final anthological, immediate to the divine, that nothing of what it name makes real justice. Hope naive? Eternal question of whether happiness lies in the memory or the oblivion of the same. That is already point of reflection itself and non-transferable. Memory leads, but then it will be a background for a glimpse at the Union of generations that have been a reflection of each other (a divorce that is repeated, a pardon do not know how to offer: more sacrifice in the work of the genius). Now we alone have our way. Nature is our true mother, according to Tarkovsky, is reflected to perfection with the above. A vital and recurring theme in his filmography: "We are part of the force that goes from the stone to the water". Certainly, everything dies and comes to an end, but through the mother and its essence, thanks to it, if you are looking inside, will remain live forever for our eyes. For when one wants to realize what you are trying to, comes the colossal final of "The mirror", reaches the zenith of the journey to regain it again. And yet understand it at all, tears sprout cheeks. It is not urgent dry them. Urges not guess it entirely. Truly seminal is has not cried our person, our physical portion. It is the spirit which has shed tears. Because, for the first time in his biography, he has played with the fingers. Because, to provide an inexplicable lyricism to the footage, Arseni Tarkovsky, father poet Andrei, he recites own verses, a few poems full of Précieuses, pace of reverie, passion and essence. Because the last step is not only one of the best in the story that the film meets. It extends far beyond the celluloid, of culture, of everything we know in life. We do not have more to thank Andrei Tarkovsky do a unfathomable play, never achieved a scale and style. A work for all time. We therefore are not only before a masterpiece: we are faced with a timeless work of art, superb, exciting. An ode to the existence, a poem to life. As these stories in which the mere voyeur, aseptic spectator becomes a part essential of them: from birth to death, since the Genesis until the consummation. As a sonata intones in autumn twilight of the leaves, and monitors trees out to the uterus pushes. As in a Crystal feels the pulse of the rivers, bleeding of SAP and wonder at the open hole of the Tempest. As the whisper that escapes the stairs, dressed in ecstasy that merges with the wet lilac, and brings us far, to his dominions, on the other side of the mirror. </body>
</review>
