<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Los amigos de Peter" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The friends of Peter are our own, that part of us that we leave the path, but to which we go when we want to. The film is a canticle, above all, to friendship, to the need for friends to make bearable the racking at times insorpotable of life. And Peter knows well.</summary>
	<body>In the friends of Peter there are very favorable circumstances so that the impression of viewing is excellent and lasts long enough so that the film will be remembered with a special affection. The first is a dazzling cast: Kenneth Brannagh, directed, Emma Thompson and his wife then the always efficient Stephen Fry, recently seen in children of men, which are three of the best British actors of his generation. Then there is the beautiful script by Martin Bergman, Rita Rudner and the own Brannagh, that scales between comedy to the Woody Allen (ten friends meet after ten years in the House of one of them, the such Peter, Stephen Fry) and acidic, sentimental, mocking, more overload to the drama look to the Woody Allen also (ten friends not only tell war stories and make jokes about vaginitis of the daughter of the President but that they put the) (fingers in the mouth and scratched beyond where the itching then mutates in damage).The film benefits from the State of grace of the cast, but also the relentless evidence that feelings and confessions that emerge at this meeting in house of Peter (and its luctuosa pressing conclusion) are affordable to any sensitive heart, intimately plaited to his own life experience.Does not require the friends of Peter Motley machinery of other films of Brannagh, so friend bizarre Shakespearean verb and complex narrative structures as in the more crude in the winter or the Frankenstein by Mary Shelley. To the way in which Love boat, here holiday at sea, she opened her barrage loves of Caribbean cruise, small orgies of random frivolona, Brannagh film also discovers a showcase appetizing, predictable, is true, but sincere, archetypes, you are configuring the concatenation of revelations, confessions and disappointments that bedevil Peter to confess in the end, what grips truly its heart and everyone knows / we all know what's the role.Brannagh renounces his Lair to the vitamin text of epithets and rimbombancias to offer a Honourable entertainment which, on occasions, could well be confused (and that is a loa) with an episode of BBC television, but see welcome placidly shocked by the wealth of a few disaffected and sane, sincere, characters goes to life, lucid and nearby.</body>
</review>
