<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Matinee" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hybrid between the science fiction of the 1960s, pobretón and pathetic, film and drama on adolescents. A naïve film, funny, advisable to always, which gives a very accurate view of an era.</summary>
	<body>Matinee must be taken very seriously, even if take frivolous ways and his style is a bet radioactive blatant by the film pulp of 1950s and 1960s where Americans slept with the fear to be abducted or to tap manara water that become them capitalist beetles. The seriousness of Matinee lies in its context: the usual films such dressing is prolific serie B scurfy and shabby-looking, low budget and beat fantasy that abounded during the cold war in the us as decompressor cultural war tension and noise shocking of bombs, not falling, aimed at all sides.Shudders thinking that the fiction of Dante is seasoned with everyday terrors extracted from that reality convulsed by the dispute between Russians and Americans, and the mob of countries attached to one side or the other to torpedeaban stability with small interested civil wars. The cold war was the threat to escombrar the world and Lawrence Moosley, a prodigious John Goodman, is the wizard of deception, the genius big fairs of people who mislead families buy their concoction, which is movie popcorn, off film of any claim of durability, as Dante's own cinema and this film. We have thus film within the film, a film that talks about the films from a time where Bruce Banner, the hero of Marvel, the Green Hulk affected by radiation in a military trial, was the icon of a blurry future. Mant, the film Moosley advertised superbly on Matinee talks about all this: Atomic ants and perverse, dream on the Moon and rays of working men that much open eyes when they sit in a movie theater to leave that the magic, the lie, falsehood, deceit, withdraw them from the barbarism of the world for two hours.They are the morning now lost for the sake of the new youth, historical then you aversions technology that they appeal to individualism, social segregacionismo and some elitist exclusivism. Dante, who was the first cartoonist and later editor for Roger Corman, who learned that they could make good film at low cost, he has a style casual, generous in winks to the television series and in children and adolescents, rico 13th–15th in that with his mentor Spielberg, although this is more bombastic in the message, guignolesco, grandiose and refined.Matinee is a disguised burlesque satire of a society agitated horse between the nuclear scare (Bay of pigs, the Cuban missiles, the Soviets on the beaches of California as a Supreme threat) and the healing of the wounds of World War II. And the film splendidly helps nothing traumatized in excess. What makes Woosley is what Dante, in the background, aims, although they may be other times and threats and fears are also others and other costumes. Dante is an inspired worker who has entrusted entertain the troops while arming the barricades: entertain is distract, move, suggest, inspire, teach and, in any case, seek the joy that steal us the teletypes.Matinee is a very wise costumbrista portrait of the "cold" America seasoned with the salt of more crude humor (which is seen in the film in black and white of Woosley) and other humor, corrosive this time, hard, although not hurtful, it explains the pathology of a people entrenched in wonder about the future.During the development of the story, it is possible to smell a Viet Nam in budding and discover that teenagers doing the session have no bloody clue what is communism and if that ideology can disassemble the american way of life that his parents have built with blood, sweat, bars and many stars.</body>
</review>
