<review author="Berto" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good news is printing after a first viewing. Aesthetic quality immerses us in the oppressive atmosphere of the art of Miller. Clouds, crepuscular light, dusty land, strong contrasts of light and full-size textures in the close-up.</summary>
	<body>Myth or reality? The history seen through the magnifying glass of the centuries? Little is known with certainty about the battle of Thermopylae, but one thing is certain: breathes epic on all four sides. Frank Miller spent years preparing his graphic story about the legendary Spartan epic against the Persian army of Xerxes and released one of his most famous books. Years later, we arrived in the form of film for enjoyment of all lovers of action cinema. 300 Spartan soldiers under the command of their King Leonidas stood up to one million Persians who, under the direction of the fearsome Xerxes invaded everything in its path back in the 5th century BC If the figures are or are not, if the Spartans were called by Athens or win them alone, if servants were or were to heart discovered? Removes you all these prejudices and dilemmas upon entering the cinema. The story here in libraries, only there is honour, blood, bravery, war and death. And Warner Bros., hand in hand with Zack Snyder, her presents to the eye in all its Majesty and visual impact.Courtesy of Warner Bros.. Entertainment Spain and the invaluable collaboration of www.muchocine.net, which we greatly appreciate the attention from these lines, had the privilege of attending the first screening of the "300" in Spain, to be released to the public on March 23. The projection was in original version, to be still in phase of dubbing.Good news is printing after a first viewing. Aesthetic quality immerses us in the oppressive atmosphere of the art of Miller. Clouds, crepuscular light, dusty land, strong contrasts of light and full-size textures in the close-up (bronze helmets and shields, fabric layers, red as the blood that splatters in what is, perhaps, the most literal reference to the comic) help us identify ourselves, for pure sensory proximity. Those who have the privilege of seeing her in the Imax version, I imagine that they will understand perfectly what I say. The plot, easily understandable, we also focused on the story told, let us not forget that it is as simple as the determination of a few soldiers on a mission with a unique and inevitable destination. And the script is right to not complicate it unnecessarily. On the one hand, the Warriors fight as heroes. They only do that, but they do like the best. On the other hand, citizenship of Sparta debate the future of their society under threat in the rear. Although it is true that the plot developed in the own Sparta gives credibility to the fact of the departure of only 300 men to confront an army as the Persian, in the development of the film it becomes in its ballast, in this kind of "intermediate" that leave rest to the warriors and lengthen the footage until the hour and fifty minutesapproximately, it seems something politically correct today, but that would not necessarily stifle the creativity of a work. Can be left here in the air a question: when are studies dare to make films of an hour? When we dare to ask them? I don't mean this to be long, much less. On the contrary, seem to pass flying the nearly two hours. But the pace of the film suffers. The game fast camera? slow motion is masterful and works very well in battles or the fabulous girl of the Oracle, but not in the script, which suffers stepping when the body asks for more. And already at the end, arises for me the great failure of the production: references that remind us, much more than what should to stay in simple references to Troy and, above all, Gladiator. A certain lack of originality, which Yes had shown throughout the film, that leaves us a little bitterness in the mouth. Something that was easily avoidable. I will not, however, remove merit to what is the great centre of gravity of the film. The scenes of extreme heroism impossible battles, are a spectacle rarely seen in the film. A great choreography that reaches its peak in the first Persian Horde that attacks against the Spartans and how are rejected and annihilated. The last stretch of the scene unfolds like a majestic and sublime ballet in a magnificent travelling of purely Greek profile. Soberbio.en which refers to the cast, I think a great success of the casting (although I do not know if bound by budget, since it had to carry the digital post-production almost whole piece) the exclusive choice of good actors in supporting roles, without stars, that that gives realism and credibility to the characters. It just overlooking our mind Faramir, son of the Seneschal of Góndor. Do in this way, the viewer focuses much more on the history and avoid what it happened in Sin City, a close reference to mention: that one is amused to find the features of Frodo in the villain in white glasses?Complies with Gerard Butler as King Leonidas, in a sober role, allowing either more fanfare than their blunt phrases, harangues and that Yes, a few glances of hatred to Xerxes that taladrarían their own Hoplite helmet. What it looks, and much, is body, like all fellow sufferers. Are the girls enjoyed with Brad Pitt in Troy here to dream a few weeks? [As an anecdote of the original version, it is curious that a Spartan king you escape from time to time some Scottish acentillo].On the other side, reigning over a sadistic plagued Persian army of monsters, mercenaries and slaves, is Emperor Xerxes, played by a Rodrigo Santoro who would recognize or his own mother, since this is the change of image to which has been subjected to this role. Owner of a disturbing harem, exercises of God on Earth, aided by its imposing supernatural figure. In this sense, one of the most colorful details of the film is all Persian imagery, based on segmented earrings, chains of gold, masks and their distorted voices to appear more serious, cavernous. This last seems to me a very good touch.Lena Headey is beautiful as Queen Gorgo, but he plays starring the bland part of the film. Next to it, is very convincing Dominic West as bad malísimo. As for the soundtrack, was one of the great unknowns surrounding the premiere after seeing the spectacular trailer with "Just like you imagined", Nine Inch Nails. They have finally opted for a classical composition of Tyler Bates (Typ. Snyder), who also drink other great soundtracks war, as Gladiator (again, especially in the voices) or La Delgada red line, who is approaching in moments of the first half of the tape. However, the moments more accomplished and forceful, much more chords for my taste with the images, are those where used more sugarcane rock. And that is, from my point of view, where the film is also guilty of narrow-minded. Another act of courage would have given to Trent Reznor, or someone similar, the possibility of creating a complete soundtrack that nothing would be reappointing the historical character of the film.It is true that to be based on a comic of such magnitude, nonetheless be a magnificent previously published storyboard for the film, was much constrict the freedoms of adaptation, but a greater balance in the plot or, even, focusing only on the battle would have given much more strength to the film. Her they acusarían long video clip, of distorting the Miller comic? It is possible, but I would have run the risk of doing something more daring and not stay with this regustillo to Gladiator that accompanies you in the last 15 minutes of film. Regustillo I also think that it was avoidable still adjusting to the comic.In short, and from my personal point of view, the film lacks courage where you left over craft and technique. Sometimes it is better to err on the side of avant-garde than of imitator of Ridley Scott (there are things that go beyond the "inspired by"). And the sediment that Zack Snyder is the of having lost a great opportunity. Eye that does not the of having made a bad film, which are two different things. For who go to the movies without wanting to see Citizen Kane, the result is more than notable.Do not miss, you will enjoy greatly. A film for the agenda of this spring.</body>
</review>
