<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="María Antonieta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sofia Coppola makes his last work an object of worship for certain snobs, with some virtues (in addition to the aforementioned soundtrack, must also be applauded show a different point of view); but with notable defects.</summary>
	<body>The fact that Sofia Coppola is the daughter of someone so important in the cinema of the last century, has probably helped her to put a dent in the world of cinema. But it is also true that much of the blame has herself: her first film, 'the Virgin suicides', he was already somewhat controversial, but liked it. However, was ' Lost in translation' the film that made him make the leap to fame: good script great Bill Murray.Pero with 'Marie Antoinette' wanted you give a very peculiar touch to your movies. Characteristic, no doubt. Different, original.aburrido. Groundbreaking, controversial. ñoño. Bland Atrevido.Pero. Coppola wanted to make his personal vision on the life of the Queen, but with a dash of 3 pages and an almost non-existent plot can be little to do. Well, be content to his faithful seguidores.pero few.The last film by Sofia Coppola shows us the more personal side of the French sovereign: arrival to Palace, their problems in bed with her husband, Louis XVI; their love tryst with Dukes extranjeros.su fans to the game. Everything quite differently from that film we are accustomed: original, yes but sleepy over not being able to. I understand that you wanted to give his 'vision', but by the way has been left a little attention to the interest of the Viewer.The performances are more justitas: a correct Kirsten Dunst brings pretty face and little else. The rest of side are little known (thanks) and have a not very complex role. However, the most talked about point since the submission of the film at Cannes, is the subject of its soundtrack. And tell verdad.es best. Music modern, striking with the classicism of the time, but quite grateful.And is that little more can be said: Sofia Coppola makes his last work an object of worship for certain snobs, with some virtues (in addition to the aforementioned soundtrack, must also be applauded show a different point of view); but with notable defects: I'm still waiting realized me that actually tell me more of what I saw.</body>
</review>
