<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Syriana" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Infumable intensive workshop of international geopolitics made with undeniable and talented cinematographic forms, but burdened by excessive handling of situations, characters and sub-plots which eventually come crashing what could have been a colorful building.</summary>
	<body>Syriana is a meritorious puzzle whose Assembly governed the destinies of the world or, put another way, Syriana is a practical compendium of end geopolitics, a smart look to the powers in the shadow. Dante is no longer, nor is this love that he put as the engine of the world. "The love that moves the Sun and the stars". Or how to read the already infamous ido Hilario Camacho who sang that the weight of the world is love. Where before Dante or Camacho, each with his ways, and according to the time which played them live and die, is now an Arab Prince, perhaps instructed in Cambridge, sybaritic sins Westerners, although fierce bastion of his popular idiosyncrasy. And the weight of the world (now) is the oil and its accelerated mob of amazed that some reserved of luxury in a hotel of many stars govern our destinies and organized the placement of the tiles on the Board.Syriana is also a spectacular paper on the complex structures of the financial discourse of the world, but is not an excellent film. Nor is it good. Passes an enforced mediocrity, a territory in the limbo between the wild documentalism of Michael Moore in vein or plausible fiction of John Le Carré... Her McLean slight indications that whole plot is caught by excessive clamps. Drag insurmountable obstacles. The choreography of the international bureaucracy displayed law firms of a surprising shrewdness, conspiracies within the offices of the State, financial analysts with formidable influences, Arab Princes with magic lamps under the shoes of thousand dollars and Taliban terror, terrorists always, ignorant and jubilant votive offerings of their cause, which tends to always coincide with our nightmares.This mortar qualified important people builds a Community House and under that roof is the reader is who writes this. There we love and cry, smile and sing. The problem is that the intelligence of Stephen Gaghan, director and screenwriter of this interesting (although I have already said that failed) film obliges the spectator idle, not versed in all chromatic keys policy and their basements, a continuous (and tired) exercise of complicity and the plot, twisting, generous scenarios and ideas, disables all too often our attention spanwhich is surpassed by a torrential flood and sophisticated small frame that, assembled later, they seek a great plot or La Gran plot, the puzzle visionary, apocalyptic, the shadows of the world map.Syriana needed a booklet to explain the spaces blank in our brain. Also needs a large dose of patience: the necessary to circumvent these gaps, the apparently deslavazados pieces, the whole fabric of this global paranoia. To overcome these inconveniences, the film flows with another pace, which Gaghan gives: giddy, agilísimo, contaminated the adrenaline of these times of religious fundamentalism, moral relativism (as much to the Holy Father in Rome) and stock market fever.Barnes, George Clooney convicente, who was more than twenty pounds in a month and was left to grow a harrowing beard, leaves his witty gesture common to be the CIA agent sent to the Near East to assassinate an heir of an oil emirate that is being suspiciously advised, eyes yankees by an ambitious financial analyst (Matt Damon). "The greater the US addiction is foreign oil cheap," says Gaghan, author also of a script very loosely based on the book of memoirs of an American agent in the Middle, Robert Baer.El influence peddling in these high areas that we do not know can not imagine that Jean Claude Van Damme gives to arguments like: everything should be so thick, of a thicket dense and organic. And is this density which lastra to the film where it should: the dubious dream of science political fiction films, genre not abundant titles, but with his Legion of faithful that come on screen its thoughts on the issues here irrelevant or treated, are not few, little is it refine the ear and we pay all the attention we know to what has been said in these two hours and little dirt and black gold.The characters are accidental parts of the argument: there is a dedication in creating them close but rather the opposite: there is no empathy, are mercenaries, definitively irrecoverable people we seem to live in the society of everyday. It is acceptable praise its ideological distancing: its asepsis, his indifference almost. What it shows, and that only at the middle end we understand, it does not require a linking of the Narrator. The event are "bigger than life" as they say American critics of the show business. As this chronicler of the film currently lacking still two or three hervores history and four or five tablespoons of geopolitics international to catch all the subtleties of the script which, frankly, overwhelms, intimidates, leaves the Viewer (as he writes in particular) out of wave, selfless by any deep and relevant thinking that can querér us strain. And I have no doubt that they exist. And large. I do not get to both.Or I'll make no intensive workshop to see brief or leave it for when my mind is less troubled by the lack of free time. That of all there is.Addenda: Curiosities / Frases1.-Syriana is the name to refer to a hypothetical new scenario in East Medio.2.-George Clooney: "There is no intention in the film portraying Muslims as bad". Not as good tampoco.3-Matt Damon: "No one can say that it is proárabe or antiárabe". Not anti-American. (The movie) speaks for itself. "It does not give an answer." Nor does the right questions or for many and we were asphyxiated by both sign question mark. 4.-Stephen Gaghan: "To make the film, spoke with spies, smugglers of weapons, oil, political, intermediaries, members of terrorist, real houses." An agent of the CIA helped me, wanted to that I will understand, that it catch well. "It was a professional liar, but I believe that it has helped me to capture the essence". As he talked with a single character and turned out to be, at the time, spy, tanker, politician, dealer, Member of a Royal House...5.-Syriana was filmed in five languages and four contienentes.6-cast is numnerosísimo: more than one hundred characters of which nearly seventy have dialogue. 7.-Clooney, Heartthrob Hollywood here gray and efficient as an agent of the CIA mercenary, consented to the fattening and the wild population of the beard, but not shave, as I wanted to Gaghan, his head. There are no requirements of the script which can with some divos self-esteem.</body>
</review>
