<review author="David" title="Tirante el blanco" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The only good thing is what dominates this director: nude scenes</summary>
	<body>Last night went to the cinema to see the movie of strained the white (Tirant the Blanc) of Vicente Aranda. I had to go to the Yelmo Cineplex cinemas, therefore in the Abaco not was, so I went to the competition lol. Truth I expected much more of that movie, only with the beginning already left me with bad taste in the mouth, as the only good thing is always that dominates this director: the scenes of nudity.A start with anticipation for the film and a decor that noticed that it was decorated, pure and hard, little care that aspect. later battles them, bad, very bad. I expected more action on them and only saw carnage of horses (blood rain) and four espadazos that seemed school teach you when to cross swords and give mandobles. Very terrible truth, little well-kept battles.The more characteristic, see Rafael Amargo as great Turkish Chief, the truth is that when I saw him, he had a good resemblance, but only fit it in that gave me that you marked some dance as a great dancer that is.Special mention to Victoria Abril, well she online of his roles, teaches everything, starts with a recital of mat for our strained and later the breasts and to end up naked fully permissible doubt is its strong .esas scenes exploits them as nadie.ya is public encasillada.el knows and says it.Conclusion say there is a scene of the film I was marked. to not reveal the film will tell you not details but know is known to be something erotic. the scene where all help Tirant the Blanc to "sex" (that I think is the word that defines that scene) prevented their legs are broken, brought in camilla, turned...carried the Princess Carmesina, in missionary position with a maid, acting mamporrera and all pushing the Tirantlo towards inside and out so that you can desvirgar to the sweet Carmesina full of lust. do not give more details of why you reach this limit, because it only much of the film and although something is mala.bueno honestly, pretty bad, you laugh situations, some very shocking and hilarious.</body>
</review>
