<review author="Luis Zueco" title="Paris je t'aime" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>As sings Edith Piaf?Does Paris sera toujours Paris, plus belle ville du monde?. This and much more is what expresses this film. Undoubtedly one of the most eagerly awaited, desired and hopeful films of the beginning of 2007.</summary>
	<body>As sings Edith Piaf, "Paris sera toujours Paris, plus belle ville du monde". This and much more is what expresses this film. Certainly one of the more expected, desired and hopeful films of the beginning of the 2007.Quien does not know Paris will be able to admire its essence, here what makes different Paris. Who knows here has a unique opportunity to get away from tourist guides and delving into the bowels of the city, in those corners that fill the books and stories, lost in its streets, dine in some hidden bistrôt, lost in some small gallery of art, in a travelling position and live the city as it is, not as we they want to sell. And who loves the cinema will be able to feel that it is still possible to sit in an armchair, cry, laugh and ultimately feel, with a great movie made of 18 short stories.A days walking in Paris heard as a Spanish tourist asked his companion why her call the city of light? with grey that is. Madam, called thus not by the light that it receives from the Sun, but because it is the city itself which enlightens all those who are in it. Paris radiates light by all its corners, and this film is a clear example of this.Directors: Joel Coen, Ethan Coen, Isabel Coixet, Alfonso Cuaron, Christopher Doyle. Wes Craven, Gus Van Sant, Tom Tykwer, Alexander Payne and Walter Sayles. And now a few actors: Natalie Portman, Steve Buscemi, Elijah Wood, Nick Nolte, Willem Dafoe, Bob Hoskins, Ben Gazarra, Gena Rowlands and Maggie Gyllenhaal.Actores: Bruno Podalydès, Leïla Bekhti, Cyril Descours, Marianne Faithfull, Elias McConnell, Gaspard Ulliel, Julie Bataille, Steve Buscemi, Axel measure Frankie Pain, Catalina Sandino Moreno, Barbet Schroeder, Li Xin, Sergio Castellitto, Emilie Ohana, Miranda Richardson, Leonor Watling, Juliette BinocheMartin Combes, Willem Dafoe, Hippolyte Girardot, Yolande Moreau, Paul Putner, Sara Martins, Nick Nolte, Ludivine Sagnier, Lionel Dray, Maggie Gyllenhaal, Joana Preiss, Seydou Boro, Aïssa Maïga, Fanny Ardant, Bob Hoskins, Wes Craven, Olga Kurylenko, Elijah Wood, Emily Mortimer, Alexander Payne, Rufus Sewell, Melchior Beslon, Natalie Portman, Gérard Depardieu, Ben Gazzara, Gena Rowlands, Margo Martindale, Florence Muller</body>
</review>
