<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Juegos secretos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Deepens, giving in the wound with clinical precision, this indispensable child nature that is common to us and puts us face insecurities, whims or flight to stagger our existence.</summary>
	<body>In addition to to discover the great interpretive talent of Tom Wilkinson, room helped me to keep track of a director capable of scavenging feelings with the precision of a surgeon. Despite its appearance of TV, that tape, first feature of Todd Field, laid the foundations for his cinematographic virtues as a filmmaker: a model work in the direction of actors and the calm pace of a cinema that unravels, the more detail, the different folds of his characters. In secret games (inappropriate translation of the original Little children), the strengths of its predecessor are still intact, and even improved, but also suffers from some of the shortcomings of that. As his preference for certain characters, best outlined against others who tend to be portrayed with brush and throwing of stereotypes. Or the rather hasty use of the tempting resource close stories crossed with a tragic ending.Nevertheless, Little Children is an interesting movie that assumes the difficult challenge of telling, not indoctrinate or include moralina, how live several families of class middle/high in the typical American urbanization. Focused his narrative on the summer Idyll live Brad Adamson (Patrick Wilson) and Sarah Pierce (magnificent Kate Winslet) behind their respective partners: Kathy Adamson (Jennifer Connelly) and Richard Pierce (Gregg Edelman). Without justifying with romantic hampered corny or censor the adulterous relationship, it is raised as the result of a child boredom or a naive search for happiness born of this constant dissatisfaction with common life between our societies.The voiceover of the story, from the character of Winslet, describes his tired towards her husband or her daughter, who described as capricious and selfish without realizing the status of girl child from that. Thus, when in her life erupts a unexpected breath of fresh air after his relationship with Brad, believes feel steeped in a pure and crystalline, happiness in the Antipodes of his grey and routine life. And Brad thinks of something. He is not unhappy in his role as master of House or as a primary responsibility for the upbringing of her son, but he isn't happy in his continuing to discuss these domestic obligations and family pressure to approve the review that he remains until graduating in law. Feel as stripped of their teenage years have assumed responsibilities from an early age.Another character, whose history is to baste the set is pedophile Ronald James McGorvey (Jackie Earle Haley magnificent despite being badly bent). Although he is aware of their pathological attraction to children, you cannot overcome its condition of patient or with the support of his mother, the only person that feels loved. And even less in a neighborhood where is monitored and pursued until exhaustion by parents frightened by the threats to his sons Ronald (excellent scene of the pool, with included nod to runs to the Spielberg shark generated among bathers). The story of Ronald comes paired with the of the retired police Larry Hedges (Noah Emmerich), a man with a marriage failed, lost after his expulsion from the police force by a serious mistake that made still in service, and other characters from the film, needy of affection and recognition of a big kid who feels marginalised.In the end, Little children overlaps with some of the pointed hits points more loose as an irregular rhythm by time and use abusive, almost adjacent to the self-explanatory note, of the voiceover. But yes deepens, giving the nail with clinical precision, this indispensable child nature on us is common and puts us face insecurities, whims or flight that stagger our existence, but also of those who are considered by strings, sensible and weighted people. So that, on more than one occasion, let us and we behave as a few big kids than adults that we aparentamos be.</body>
</review>
