<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Manuale D'Amore 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perfect example of failed and unnecessary sequel. Those who enjoyed and mondaron of laughter with the first Manuale d'amore, the best recommendation we can do them is staying farther away possible of its sequel.</summary>
	<body>In this life in which appear the originality and innovation in the arts to sin, increasingly tends to find simpler ways, going to theoretically safe. In the film, that becomes remakes, remakes or adaptations, and an endless list of sequels, prequels, spin-off. etc. Producers, in their quest for greater benefits with the least amount of possible risks, try to continue exploiting the goose that lays the golden eggs, but what happens when not of more than itself?Manuale d'amore has been one of the cooler comedies and originals that have been made in recent years, not only in Italy or Europe, and it became a success. Its main virtue was that classics, with four chapters which analysed that mystery called love recovering the spirit of Italian comedies of episodes. Less than two years later, Giovanni Veronesi offers four new episodes, without apparent relationship between itself, except for the connection of a radio program. In honor of the truth, Manuale d'amore 2 is a perfect example of failed and completely unnecessary sequel. This continuation lacks the grace and originality of its predecessor, and its various episodes become empty and boring to an extent that clears the tedium. Humor is scarce on the tape, and soon there is not the elegance and finesse of the original, but is crude, crossing the line of bad taste on several occasions. Veronesi is a serious mistake, and is to leave on several occasions the comedy to one side and try to tell the story from a nearest to tear drama point of view to something else. This garrafal bug note in the first episode, but especially in the third, the most unfortunate of all saying is step. Only the actors put some light into the abyss Manuale D'Amore 2, notably Carlo Verdone, not in vain is considered by many as the heir of the great Alberto Sordi. Those who enjoyed and mondaron of laughter with the first Manuale d'amore, the best recommendation we can do them is staying farther away possible of its sequel. This continuation is a comedy without grace, coarse and dull, by so strongly recommend saving the entry, and enjoy the pleasant taste that left the original.</body>
</review>
