<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Klimt" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ill-fated (from new) do biopics of height. This is a chaotic list of naked women, colors and several hallucinations. Will syphilis of the painter or the artistic director drunkenness?</summary>
	<body>Klimt is a dispassionate visit the recent history of art: an amateur trip, no sign of sustainability in the memory, the mind of obsessed of the color, refined eroticism of nymphs surrounded by flowers and gold. There is almost nothing memorable in this colorful telefilm that reaches the screens with the claim of John Malkovich, credible, although too lost in a character also excessive. Raoul Ruiz establishes a very original game of lenses: invoice a strange, captivating, concise film in his involuntary brilliance, but leaves an impression so ethereal as the limbs of these paintings of oniric and flambé of dreams.It presupposes an interest in the character resulting in a concern for what the character represents: eroticism, fugal sanity, the presence of important people in the troubled beginning of century (Melies, for example). Academicism, orthodoxy and the formal correction that fleeing Klimt is significantly reflected in the absence of orthodoxy and of formal correction of this film desatenderá many hopes and open, no doubt, other, growing desire to know more about the Austrian painter because this biopic is poor and information rich (rich desgradaciadamente) in flourishes in love with its noted biographer. Ill advised, Ruiz is a forced intellectuality that is intended to (and get half) recreate a period in the history of 20th century transcendent and relevant social and artistic aspects.Some incontinence in the use of the female nude could prompt is an erotic movie with pretensions of properly documented biopic, but no showcasing or commitment in merely sensual scenes or a time translation or explicitation of the reasons of a genius.Syphilis which ravaged wisdom of this painter has also desastrado the film pulse of a director in possession of a valid, compelling material to lift a tribute to art, that the film is scarce. Malkovich isn't good actor that we know: as if understood that this is not the film that will be remembered.I went in search of magnificence and left embadurnado of tedium. I was, in terms of lives of painters, with crazy red hair or surviving Picasso, that without being nothing out of this world, explained with restraint and interest the life of the artist from Malaga with an apotheosis Anthony Hopkins. Malkovich, alien to this world of Belle Epoque transmutada in grey palette of emotions mutilated, survives, such as Picasso, but no more. addenda: and, as if they were Japanese models, women care shaving the pubis that nothing corresponds to those times. (but, come on, this is a very personal appreciation).</body>
</review>
