<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Funny Games" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Transgressive, uncomfortable, necessary, inadmissible, terrifying, intelligent... Let's find more adjectives and put them here. In any case, convulsive film as life. If were you born pa' Hammer, the sky will fall nails...</summary>
	<body>The entire film is already summarized in its first minutes: a bourgeois couple with a son directs with his Range Rover to his house on a lake. They crawl a sailboat of obscene proportions. The entertainment is to go guessing, joyful, appetite, what pieces of Opera are playing on the cd player. Suddenly classical music stops sound and the soundtrack of the film overwhelms with an insistent steamroller of hard industrial rock, noise rested on dubious melodic bases.The rest is an uneasy thriller whose consistency lies in the moral implications and the social justification for a pair of psychopaths that address the placid aburguesada life of a family with the inescapable task kill them without that in any circumstances of the film we are informed about the nature of the crime or the consequences of its implementation. To that effect, Funny games is provocative and is delicately, without hardly strictly cinematographic resources, places trodden by other films, but here they are ampulosamente carried a brutal, though never end us millstone no scene because carry entail an explicit violent component: here not be pornographic and truculenta gore of other champions of the provocation as the Tarantino's Pulp Fiction and Reservoir dogs or pseudointelectual Oliver Stone's Natural born killers. Haneke obvious gloating: settles in lengthy, static levels almost, of characters stranded in the darkness of the immorality (yuppies who assail the House and running their always absurd plan) and characters pitifully anchored in the incomprehension and helplessness of not knowing the object of the game that have been pushed.The episode of the Opera mutated into metal noise is the reference: there is, although I read that Haneke didn't have clear at all, the storyline of the film: how life is based on very fragile foundations and how random (what if not) can vary accommodative deserved leisure of these bourgeois lovers of the bel canto to unmitigated tragedy. Without solution to escape.What tape plasma with some eloquence is not the reason for these bastards who use violence as a game, a fun game, as the title says. Kubrick made a Clockwork Orange with a very clear idea of what intended this apparent advocacy of violence. The novel's title already principiaba a solid departure from any frivolous idea of violence. Droogs and nadsat distressed the streets in search of fun as these Brats of Funny games. There is even a tribute to the film in this: Alex (Malcolm McDowell) is foul-mouthed, lively, cultured and refined, and has an adlátere lerdo, fofo and primitive, its "fractured". As is the case here. The two characters are built with identical mimbres psychological if any psychology can be used for reasoning the behavior of such a rabble. Haneke deconstructs the grammar of the thriller with psychopath and prisoner that we know that he will die before the opening credits: does so by removing all signs of erotic free: the woman is forced to undress but there is never more enseñada skin than is necessary. Nor merciless in the deaths that are produced: aseptically, portrays them almost without a commitment to denounce them. The last one, which seems an accident of the weather that the tragic loss of a human being is significant.The hostage-takers or murderers or the morons yuppies (matter) also play with the spectator, which is a piece in the plot: what they mean in the game, they force you to determine a position or reason the logic of what is happening with them. There is even a scene in which the film autorebobina: what seems to a happy ending, or at least, the way to this happy ending occurs is violently censored by the murderer. When his friend is escopeteado, nervously search the TV remote control to back what has just happened (we see how the tape goes back actually) and delete this discomfort (which his friend dies). This aggressive and uncomfortable tape promises is a transgressive show like few others: exquisite education of the assailants is going aditamentazo his schizoid behavior, its criminal impulse. It hurts thinking a mind awake and cultured enough as to ask eggs please and excuse for view misbehaved then be able to shoot a child or burst a future with this appalling ease.Cannot escape this cloudy observation that the world is evil and anyone in it are fagocitamos the same weak promises that perhaps someday will be better of being catalogued as the unbearable film that dwells in our collection of films to the waiting that a friend eager to thrill ask us some nightly entertainment. Talking exclusively about film, Funny games is not film: it is a kind of experiment based on the techniques of cinema, but it escapes from this conceptual category when Haneke contradicts any logical sense of narration and stays two minutes standing in a frame, which might well appear a dialog box. I felt desasistido, alien suddenly to everything he had seen before. I wanted (and did so vehemently) to rewind the tape to the front. I regretted not to have a remote control (do the picture do??) in order to move forward a few minutes and lose sight of the level fixed, blowout, infuriating, tedious, abusive, of a man with his leg shattered in a Chair or a woman near the corpse of his son, who have been killed, but we have not seen.In very concise words, must be eager to have a bad time to be caught up in Funny games. Event that such desire exist or that one does not have no bloody idea of what's the matter (thing which happened to me), must be apencar then with the bad time. Know carry the rest of the day. Sleep in loose leg after seeing her without nightmares dark on the evil and the bad milk of many, some of which are just hopeless and unfortunately close to our placid life.Haneke seems to fly to Hollywood to do a remake of its Funny there games with stars on celluloid (Tim Roth and Naomi Watts). I do not know completely if I have seen a movie good or bad. Do not fit here qualifications, hierarchies, subjugation to a scale that sometimes is not reliable. It must be wary of everything here. We must swallow saliva. We must close our eyes. Or open them much. Or not to think. Or think of all blow and at a very fast speed.What mundo.addenda: have not read (now go) critique of Funny games in cinema of this noble and valuable website of friend Victor. We could, what reasons there are for otherwise, make a special "Funny Games". Or not?</body>
</review>
