<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Azuloscurocasinegro" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is one of those movies that make people who hates? Spanish film will have to be shut up</summary>
	<body>Last week I could see dark blue almost black, and the truth is that I saw twice by different circumstances. The first of these was last Tuesday of April 11, which I as anyone, went through box office and when I was doing some shopping, I saw a missed call. Upon entering the room, the cinema manager told me that I had called, which is next Friday was going to come Daniel Sánchez Arévalo to present the film with its subsequent Symposium, and so soon. Then on Tuesday I saw for the first time and I loved it. Later I will put my criticism.On Friday I went to go I loved again, Daniel came to present it later disappearing back to appear halfway through film and sit in a row. I was very curious because I had read the post or news (as want you to call) that he had written on his page, detailed as the other day I had gotten at a meeting of a neighborhood cinema to return to view and observe the spectators. Do so that there I was, watching the observer than as well says, - I am that goes to the movies with popcorn and coke? that of course he accompanied viewing.Subsequently held a symposium in which Daniel commented on various aspects of his film and on the current film scene. It is funny and at the same time "sad" that programmes such as Buenafuente and others, lacking this director and some of their players to talk about the film by the fact of not being "famous". Because as stressed the Sánchez Arévalo, the public of these programs is quite akin to that has dark blue almost black, which is why there is a range of almost two million viewers which could be interested and come to see the film, but of course, do not appear in these programs so that opportunity is lost.Well then I'll put the criticism, but first of all, and although I have nothing to do, thank Daniel that he spearheaded to Santander for submission. There are many people who know the figure of Daniel Sánchez Arévalo, but before this opera prima already we had encandilado with other small jewels: his shorts. Dark blue almost black takes the characters of physics II, although by no means forgotten situations and aspects that made him grow as a director, so it includes parts of the world he created in his previous works: Express, Gol, prophylaxis and the guilt of the Mountaineer.This is one of those movies that make people who "hates" Spanish film will have to be shut, or at least you can say that you don't like but not typical that is shit, because this opera prima is nearly masterful.Daniel as a good writer that is, has been able to dosage and make that dark blue almost black us encandile and make us laugh and cry with a few characters human and very close. Characters that we can find in any city or even our closest circles. Urban stories that give the possibility to prove that film there more than explosions and assaults, and allowing the actors enjoy with characters that are going to grow and explore several records.From a sensational Quim Gutiérrez through Marta Etura, Raúl Arévalo, Manuel Morón, Antonio de la Torre, Ana Wagener to Héctor Colomé. No doubt a spectacular cast, that although a lot of people it seems unknown, now start you to be familiar.There are many people who say if a movie is good or bad according to what have found them, in part is logical, but also have that appreciation must be meet and pay attention to many other aspects that form the product just to see.Based on all this, dark blue almost black, is confirmed as a good film, although I dare qualified excellent (one of the best of the year, and that we are in April) that the people vibrates with the film, do not believe that no one be indifferent and who isn't immersed with the characters and their experiences there is. In addition to that, already at a technical level, the direction of the "Rookie" Arévalo is very sensible. Planning, use of the camera, their limited movements, of escuadres them you, the music, the art direction, casting, ultimately to everything that must be borne in mind that the House does not fall, is taken afloat and in what way. The truth is that if with his next movie call or raise the level achieved with this, we have a director that can give much to the Spanish film and the seventh art in general.</body>
</review>
