<review author="Nobody's perfect" title="Tristram Shandy" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Winterbottom uses as an excuse the adaptation of the novel Laurence Sterne to stop telling a story of the film within the film, which offers a parodic vision without detract from the credibility.</summary>
	<body>Who go to the cinema to see an adaptation of the famous (more in England than in our country) and funny novel of nine volumes the life and opinions of Tristram Shandy, will be a disappointment. The film is not, at least in the content, a faithful translation to the screen of the book? very difficult objective by its peculiar character, everything is said. However, yes we can affirm that Witerbottom has grasped and reflected, in a way, the essence of this text of the 18th. As you already did literary work in its time, the cinematographic supposed parody and experimentation of conventional narrative structures.The film starts telling the story of the book, until you reach a second part in which the action moves to the own set of filming of the movie. It is then when we hear "cut!" and live assist the ins and outs of a real film: rivalry between stakeholders, funding problems, romances between the template, script changes? The English director leaves the film and opens us a door to his shooting, printing to the scenes a sense of ironic humor that arouses laughter in the audience.In both parts of the film is Steve Coogan who leads the cast. The actor carries with nearly the entire weight of the film, great in its double role of Tristram Shandy and self-centered and competitive actor that gives life in the shooting. Coogan co-starring with Rob Brydon - both had worked with Winterbottom in 24th hour party - some scenes of rivalry that not can soar to the category of mourning, if anything ridiculous duel, precisely because of this spoof character. As ridiculous and hilarious are many of the reflected, although entirely realistic scenes.Winterbottom, whose heterogeneous filmography so far varies between the mainstream and the underground shows with this production his more independent facet. Tristram Shandy is an author who film without being round, nor the first to address the topic of the film within the film (have done before an end made in Hollywood, the game of Hollywoodo or Ed Wood, only to mention some recent) provides quite a few great moments of humor. Crazy humor, as the reality itself, which on this occasion is that of a shooting.</body>
</review>
