<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El Motorista Fantasma (Ghost Rider)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You're empachado both visual trick computer generated and have found no hint of epic or emotion on a tape which, precisely, should offer both qualities in abundance.</summary>
	<body>The cyclic premiere of a film based on a comic book superhero he remains very profitable film, but such overabundance may be harmful by repetition of diagrams and narrative styles in each new installment. Possibly the cause of the adaptations are increasingly routine is at the origin of these projects, almost all as the beginning of a sequel that bring considerable commercial revenues. With each coming-out of a hero of vignettes is anxious to constitute a franchise. And thus these deliveries on the origin of the characters tend to copy each other in their structures and contents. Do we start with the character without their superpowers, we explain the trauma? should it have? which you are awarded the same, and then the story follows the predictable course of a hero ajustice their antagonists and fights evil.The Ghost Rider continues to imply this script and for his argument, has chosen to take ideas from the recent comics of this character, developed in urban environments, and discard (less a shy nod of the film) the first? and better? comic recreated in solitary and arid deserts. Throughout the game that this character could be offered by the ambivalence that occurs between the rider Acrobat Johnny Blaze and the evil entity that takes over, a Mefistófeles sicario is going to fret by incompetence of the screenwriter or the business need of creating a film to audiences of all ages; bet without hesitation to this adaptaciones-molde to respond more to this last cause.From the choice of the cast already it warns a whiff little bold in this new 'mainstream-comiquero'. Nicolas Cage, who lost the ass for sink the teeth to a superhero again last thread and with a junkie's own gestures. Peter Fonda, lost in the rush of 'tv-movies' American returns to the Hollywood universe to make Mefistófeles. The rebel son of American Beauty, Wes Bentley, who also walked a tad gone, makes wrong as the son of the devil. And the voluptuous Eva Mendes (a woman to remove the hiccups) obediently assumes the Protocol role of beautiful girlfriend of the hero of yore.Thus, at the end you're empachado both visual trick computer generated and have found no hint of epic or emotion on a tape which, precisely, should offer both qualities in abundance. That's the 'cine-cómic' me starting to bore.</body>
</review>
