<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Manuale D'Amore 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The first was a success and therefore repeated the formula with a title corrected and increased or, better said, stretched and ligerito.</summary>
	<body>Already the first installment of this tontón Decalogue of audiovisual self-help for "love of love" seemed to us a substitute helpings, entertaining but ultimately, mix of certain curious winks and many not so much by appellants.What is the novelty and the tape was fresh by surprising his mount and correct spinning of his argument. Also thanks to solvent and actors well known in Italy as Jasmine Trinca (the best of youth), but with little impact media outside the country. Experience makes us ready and shows the work of marketing, including sharing Elsa Pataky and the great Monica Bellucci. Avowed my predilection for the actress, I embarked on the task of making them see it lost in the passage of a craft creation to production in series and long.The factory of churros does this title which engarza some pearls? few, the truth - with cheap jewelry. The result is a necklace something kitsch that you you can put one, twice maybe, but already. They threaten to edit the damn manual updates, and we warned, it will no longer result in the desired effect. Here already costs Giovanni Veronesi, director and one of the three writers who write a couple of sympathetic, but not much more interesting stories than the other two, picked a little tweezers to fill the Turkey.Now, however, there is no doubt that this Manuale d'amore 2 will be a success, in the same way that it was the first, not only in the Italian box office but their international sales and awards? aspired to a few David Di Donatello. With a view to the promotion and sales, Barcelona is the framework where part of two of the stories.Falling in love, motherhood, less conventional marriage and extreme love. These are loopholes of love treated friendly although lacking strict cinematic interest, that for example is missing rhythm in their two latest stories. Now, if we see the film as an object of amusement, go see this fresco on los lances and the enchantments of love, will not repent, provided that it does not end with the feeling of that abuse their trust.</body>
</review>
