<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Pulse" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Repeats the same patterns of most horror films from United States: atmosphere of mystery, pretty girls who die later than his fellow - more ugly than them-, raids and little more.</summary>
	<body>Wes Craven, become factory, us back surplus story with repetitive elements in the classic titles of terror with and for young people.He repeated on the idea that the dead are among us, more of what some believe, and are no more savvy cabe in what regards to the use of new technologies. These beings of ultratumba already know tricks and we, as viewers, also, although at times, and that is the miracle of the film on the big screen, does not need that we create that tell us to spend a bit cramped in the armchair and I must admit it, entertaining. This is the only virtue of a title that repeats the same patterns of most horror films from United States: atmosphere of mystery, pretty girls who die later than his fellow - more ugly than them-, raids and little more.If you take it as something original? and believe me that it is difficult-, hooked his approach and his design to some extent surprised to go from the typical succession of deaths up to the panoramic view of an apocalyptic present. Criticism to our contemporary way of life is not subtle, but quite the contrary, but we already know that the excesses lead to nothing: footage wears a nervousness and an aesthetic that it just proving to be tired.Wes Craven, forgiveness, filmmaker Jim Sonzero is not modernized but that anchor in formulas that give good results. At the end everything becomes a new review of what have done others - and many of them better. The kitchenettes of terror adapts the action that takes place in the Japanese Kairo, of 2001, and garnished the story with usual young University born in the country of opportunities and typical of his productions scares, whether in the form of dreams or through cybernetic solutions quite catastrophic.</body>
</review>
