<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Bosque de sombras" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite being an explicit homage to classics of the genre, it's sometimes interesting to a filmmaker to cook a dish with the same ingredients and using the same recipe.</summary>
	<body>Newcomer Koldo Serra always made it clear that he wanted to make a film about solitary confinement which just fueling confrontation: the couple, between different social classes and cultures. The starting point, although recurrent, can be attractive. In fact during the footage we cannot remain immobile, expectantly to what is going to happen, deceptively abstraídos.A pity so much tension go to hell with a poorly resolved story that we of course not desvelaremos. Moreover, not the pen we esgrimiremos to unmount the work. We could do because flanks that attack has this directorial debut, although in view of the wide sleeve that gives so many stupid, stereotypical and absurd productions, here go to defense of the indefensible for a reason: is a modeling of film that is likely to improve.It tries to innovate, turning the established patterns. There is the fact that will fall good as flies, the main actors are those that look less at the end and be enabled psychological substrate to certain characters to be analyzed by a therapist specializing in family. Despite all the efforts it doesn't work as a product, perhaps to mix so many aspects and then not dissect well along a linear storyline, with few unexpected excitement peaks.Supernatural stories, with mysteries or by more fearless killers found in the forests of North Spain the best setting. But the scenario does not help much when there is more action than content and maintain many open doors, is why we feel a bit cheated. Does not the roster of stars, which also makes up a substantial interpretive material wasted in a journey to us seems irregular and poor.Even so we ensure that we must follow suit to Serra. Anyone have bought him the opinion nor nor the undersigned has gone mad: this creator in the making promises though his debut is not at all bright; It does so by risk, although it is wrong. It is not comparable but at times his creature reminded me to the luxurious who can kill a child?, Narciso Ibáñez Serrador, where the harassed became executioners and us was not strange.</body>
</review>
