<review author="Caruco" title="Juegos secretos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Todd Field maintains its ground intact, but very estimable and putting in scene at least three major issues, linking them between if and involving their characters in them.</summary>
	<body>Three (are they supposed) respectable mothers and housewives in a park seen in the distance and, if it is necessary, with a prismatic, the sexual object of his desires, a burly and attractive father who comes to the place with his son. Although its presence to the peat and excited, they will never cross the barrier of decency to even engage in four words with him.Another character, an expolicia frustrated by a mistake of the past (Gregg Edelman), also notes to a wrongfully with a history of pedophilia (Jackie Earle Haley). But he does it with no intention; with the self-imposed mission to make note that it is monitored, and even pour lapidary painted in his garden or threaten you personally if you feel it is appropriate. Yes that feels (socially) legimitizado to cross the barrier with that strange even to violate their personal space.From one extreme to another, so that us is allowed and what not; who we are and what they would like to be and to have, the second film of Todd Field moves. A portrait so cold as conclusive of the day to day of a typical urbanization American, the beings that inhabit, anomalies, desires and frustaciones.And makes taking a pulse that oscillates between the Sam Mendes of "American beauty" and the best Todd Solondz, stopping at the most bizarre behaviour of his creatures. Splashing in addition his story with humor so estóico as sharp, by unexpected, it resembles the Wes Anderson.Madame Bovary guiña you to Spielberg.Entre as much reference, Todd Field maintains its intact ground: eyes, silences, empty or found complicity; also of respectable beings who dare, forced or not, to cross the line of the inappropriateness or directly as punishable moral or legal action.And makes it doing a not perfect film: lengthened in your footage, with a narrator in unnecessary off, sometimes leading its proposal to average gas. But very estimable and putting in scene at least three major issues, linking them between if and involving their characters in them.The first is: the pursuit of happiness is an act of rebellion, subversion, against the rules, and may also cause pain to beloved or nearby persons. This is for Sarah Pierce (Kate Winslet), a mother and mistress of House, as a modern Madame Bovary, discover the delights of adultery to fill the gap of a marriage and a husband that already only shares roof and daughter.It is for the disoriented Brad Adamson (Patrick Wilson), trapped in a State of children unable to devote his time to work on something that not fancy you, permanent, and relegated to the shade of his beautiful wife (Jennifer Connelly), which takes the pants, and the money, at home.And it is also for Ronald (Jackie Earle Haley), another adult in a mind not so child already and Yes sickly, spoiled by his understanding mother (excellent Phyllis Somerville), living in own jail for its uncontrollable sexual deviation, paedophilia, and retained by the bars of a community that feels threatened by the presence of this predator of children. It includes a sequence with an excruciating nod to the daily Spielberg.Sublevaciones "shark".Second issue: our defects, defects and limitations allow us being the person we would really like? Until that point we are guilty of not having achieved what we believe we deserve? Thus suffer their characters, included the expolicia or the child molester.Experiences, the circumstances, the destination, the others influence, but it also springs to mind the fable of the Scorpion and the frog, where the nature of each is important even if it means to sink us in our misery.For example, a secondary character, Sheila, played by Jane Adams (which seems just out of the "Happiness" of Todd Solondz), wanders briefly for a couple of scenes. And it does coincide with the quote blind, through an announcement of the press, with the child molester Ronald. After that he invite her kindly, and within the warm brightness of a restaurant, to "share something sweet", we turn to night and a car outside. There, Sheila feel not the "sweetness" of a dessert, but also the inevitable and bitter "sting" of his short-lived couple.The happiness that is haye while we are installed in that comfort, stripped of responsibilities, which offers children, time in which where everything seems to be possible. "With what leads us to the third issue: childhood, not always successful ability to ripen, and the inexorable passage of time.""Secret games" opens with images of porcelain figures reminiscent of the children, the old and what us clings to the past; and with flat details of watches with their sounds and needle marking the transcruso of seconds, minutes, years?. Later, there will be a (vain) Act to destroy these as ornamental as symbolic objects. There will also be some more uprising attempt, but in the end (almost) everything will continue as.</body>
</review>
