<review author="Mala Besta" title="El Motorista Fantasma (Ghost Rider)" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The screenplay, in addition to the original character, trample trampling himself. The characters are all incredibly bad. The protagonist has intellect and dialogues of a border.</summary>
	<body>"Ghost Rider: the rider phantom" is the last product set in the Marvel Universe who comes to our screens. Starring Nicholas Cage, a big fan of the comics, it seems that even has "helped" with the hyphen. Such is his love of comics which one of his sons has named it Kal - the (the original name of Superman). If it has been able to commit such cruelty with a poor child, imagine what you can do with a film.In short, the film tells the story of Johnny Blaze (Nicolas Cage), a stunt rider to save his father from certain death makes a pact with the Devil (Peter Fonda). In exchange for salvation, Blaze becomes a minion of Satan, whose job is to collect the souls the Lord below requires. Motorcycle. When appears in scene a powerful contract manuscript by the sale of thousand souls, they both Mefistófeles and his son Blackheart (Wes Bentley) want, Blaze has manage to save the file, kick ass bad guys and bind to Roxanne (Eva Mendes), and all this while fall you is the wig. Because they hear, Nicholas Cage has a wig that it seems have smeared you the bald in brea and forced him to run a barber shop. Awful. The director and screenwriter is Mark Steven Johnson, that those who follow the genre of superheroes will recall as the perpetrator of "Daredevil". Here again to make your own. Any hint of interest beyond the special effects of the Ghost Rider character may have, has gone down the toilet. The original story unfolded largely around a man who had sold his soul to the devil but that was forgiveness before God with true love, an issue which has given rise to great classics of literature as "Faust" or to some extent "Don Juan", here becomes a ridiculous fights ring. But what is expected of a man that has been said about his character: "a demonic vengeful hero, a sort of Orpheus or Faust". Define Orpheus as a demonic vengeful hero comes to be equal to say that the chicken Caponata is a bird of prey, more or less.The screenplay, in addition to the original character, trample trampling himself. The characters are all incredibly bad. The protagonist has intellect and own a border dialogues; Eva Mendes is limited to teach the neckline and put silly face. Satan seems a teleshopping presenter and has less authority than a urban guard. Blackheart, the fearsome antagonist from hell, is so threatening as a man with a very bad hangover. Furthermore, none of them seems to have some clear motivations, or at least the film does not bother to show them. For what. The case is to get many motorcycles.The development of history is very irregular. It take long to start, after a long presentation of characters that is useless, because while it raises the basic relationships between them, it passes through high details insignificant as why Satanás chose Johnny Blaze, or what he has done, or what. Of course, all this will clarify later, when a character explain it word of mouth. The real antagonist appears well past the three quarters of an hour, and everything ends by solve quick running, when more or less all the protagonists are turn a corner.At the visual level, "Ghost Rider" is a real horror. The greater creation of the film, the rider is appalling, and has proportions more than resemble the Ghost Rider, they make it look biker Microcefálico. The special effects are quite poor. Not technically, but in its design. All the demons, spirits and ghosts that swarm out there seem to have been taken from other films, and nothing surprises at any time, except Nicholas Cage.Miren hopefully this page always little cage. We hope that us it just hurts see it on screen. But in "Ghost Rider" us agrace with what is, without a doubt, his worst performance to date. It is absolutely ridiculous. The two characters are taciturn and solitary rider and a demon that face has a skull covered in flames, and Cage gets that both have the same expressiveness: that of a lighter. His body language is that of Elvis in his worst era, and above it seems that he does very well the subject of aging, what motivates ridiculous levels in which teaches its powerful musculature, hides one of the sides of her face (which to me gives me that it has gone through the operating room, very poorly), takes a horrible makeup, or directly put an average in front of the camera.His co-stars do what they can. Eva Mendes has a ridiculous character, the quintessence of the vase female character that laughs thanks to the protagonist and which has to be saved. Peter Fonda, who has seen you and who sees you. And there is also Sam Elliot, who makes about always: cowboy who spits on the ground.Finally, a boring film, worthy successor to "Daredevil" in the career of its director. Recommended for those who have put their scooter Metra-Kit.</body>
</review>
