<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="El hombre del tiempo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Curious and interesting, movie will not reach around the world, as it was the case with?To purpose of Schimdt? and?Strange coincidences?</summary>
	<body>Gore Vervinski dares to this drama tragicomic after having passed the terror with The Ring (the signal), the adventure with Pirates of the Caribbean and the road movie with The Mexican. The interesting thing about this new proposal is that you it's a rather unusual film. Fails to convince at all, but it makes us think about many aspects of life. Nicolas Cage is a man who has much success in his work but his life is not very accomplished. You have problems with people, strangers that pull him food when they see him on the street, and the most important: with his family. Michael Caine plays his father (which is already an incentive) with which has a good, although complex relationship. Then are his sons, his ex-wife and the boyfriend. David Spritz (Nicolas Cage) is a local television time man, who can sign for one of the national channels, with the consequent increase in salary and luxuries that this entails. Up there either, but on the other hand is an apathetic, angry man, metepatas, a character that just dropping you well and that you feel compassion in many moments by inept that becomes. But not everything is bad in it, what happens that they will often twist situations. Tries to help his daughter, offering it different hobbies which she rejects altogether, for example. Archery. This hobby will become balm for all your problems and help you relate a little better with people, as it tends to be very angry with anyone who recognizes him and asked how will be the climate. It also tries to get back with his ex-wife but not he achieves success with their strategies. Vervinski also offers us the positive and negative of being a popular face side. So hard that it is the school when you're little and you amoldas not to the usual stereotypes, as it is the case with the daughter of Cage; and as well as the confidence and the actions to be done by our family. In short "The man of the time" is a curious and interesting, film will not reach around the world, as it was the case with "A propósito de Schimdt" and "Strange coincidences".</body>
</review>
