<review author="Mala Besta" title="Juegos secretos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We think that we have been of the few that have not had a religious experience during viewing, and we have not seen God at the bottom of the cardboard of popcorn, we shall confine ourselves to say that it is quite boring.</summary>
	<body>"Secret games" is one (again) "sour look to the typical American family", "a harrowing and nothing complacent look to the daily hell of matrimonial relations", "a modern Fable" or the last work of the "new cinema neoindependiente USA". Me I have not invented it. All of this is said in there, in the press specialized. We think that we have been of the few that have not had a religious experience during viewing, and we have not seen God at the bottom of the cardboard of popcorn, we shall confine ourselves to say that it is quite boring.Illegitimate daughter of "Crash" and "American beauty", the film of Todd Field x-ray the life of a quiet and typical American residential neighborhood, those that at this stage all already know that they are full of psychopaths, unhappy, dissatisfied housewives, onanistas, procaces girls and ice cream cart. In this case, the story focuses on lathe to two parents now already not to say parents; A parent is Brad (Patrick Wilson), a young man without a job, married to the wealthy Kathy (Jennifer Connelly), a quite castrante wife. (B) parent is Sarah (Kate Winslet), young and educated woman who has married Richard (Gregg Edelman), a husband who should be castrated. Both are walking to their kids, and taking into account the vital boredom where they live, is what needs to happen. Background there is also a pederast just reintegrate, Ronnie (Jackie Earle Haley), and a somewhat radical police and intransigent but which ultimately is good, Larry (Noah Emerich). Typical of one of these neighborhoods.Although both parents clearly are the protagonists, each of the characters has its own history, which fully develops throughout the entire film. This helps a lot to it lasts for more than two hours, so anything about going to the cinema with piles, say what you say the announcement of that cream. All frames are quite waterproof and are United because the director wishes to place one of the protagonists always on screen. With which the movie lacks practically structure, jumping from person to person and from place to place without end. What Todd Field allows certain luxuries, as shooting a football game, although relatively integrated into the story, giving a still more heterogeneous finish the set.But all this is not truly annoying. Even the dull tone pedantuelo and throughout the film, with scenes gafapasta visually very gimmicky and requiring the characters make pirouettes by the frame to place as God sends, or the fact that everybody walk around quoting Flauberto or Tolstoy. Worse and unbearable is the insidious voiceover that Todd Field like the Viewer. Anytime there is a man telling us in the background, with all kinds of detail, what they feel each of the characters that appear on screen. Awful. still, "Secret games" has managed three nominations to the Academy Awards, one for his screenplay and two more for his cast, as it is normally the case in these films comes to be the most notable. Kate Winslet, who get naked and with little makeup, and that always gives idea of it gives everything for art is most thankful role. Moreover, it is a fairly conventional performance, however he has managed a nomination the best protagonist.Jackie Earle Haley has the same but for supporting actor for his portrayal of a pederast that same thing could have been ludópata, drug addict, Kleptomaniac or journalist of the heart. Although his performance probably is the best of the film, the character is not too well drawn. But that certainly is a pederast, who always rate very high on this new neocine.The male protagonist, Patrick Wilson, said in an interview, a time ago, one of its goals for the new year was in films that didn't undress. Again will be.Both husband and wife, Jennifer Connelly and Gregg Edelman, are simply appear, and for her to show off body, by contrast with Kate Winslet, which is what Todd Field, that it would be looking, seeks to make us overlook the attractive entering meats and little women.In short, a pretentious and boring film, that nominations will be resolved as will begin to fall into oblivion. Recommended for people who live in neighborhoods bad, so they know there is nothing worse than being upper-middle class.</body>
</review>
