<review author="Mario" title="El Motorista Fantasma (Ghost Rider)" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The taste of Coca-Cola Zero is unbearable: Nicolas Cage finje be a biker smoking non drinking alcohol but candy does? and he is addicted to the documentaries of monkeys.</summary>
	<body>Is true that some film makers follow a whiff to stale of which it is difficult to detach. In his day, Daredevil following a style at the very least questionable, with the cuernecitos leaping across the rooftops between ridiculous dialogues and pop hits / rock totally notable. Mark Steven Johnson began to drop those bad effluents, and the feeling that you were going to accompany throughout his career was very strong.Yesterday was premiered in cinemas around the world Ghost Rider. Mark is put hands to work again, and the result is neither more nor less than what was expected. As in the adventures of the man without fear, we have a bland movie like few, marked with digital effects television and very dynamic (not consistent) arguably. However some details lowered the pretensions of its predecessor, as the villains, led by Black Heart, which sadly resemble the frustrated Elektra.En malutos this time, Jonhy Blaze is a circus artist who makes a pact with the Devil (by mistake, first stupidity) and that, later, the same Mefistófeles kidding coarsely. Peter Fonda plays the worst Satan I remember, decorated with very bad special effects, but without a blade of charisma.The taste of Coca-Cola Zero is unbearable: Nicolas Cage finje be a biker smoking non drinking alcohol but candy does? and he is addicted to the documentaries of monkeys. Eva Mendes plays an improbably confusing girlfriend that her boyfriend her burning head. Is the eternal sidekick not for jokes? In short, aguachirri.The soundtrack is disregarded, when everything seemed to indicate that the items rokeros and metal attached to the perfection with the character; We no longer crush with passengers the MTV hits, but that one of the topics interpreted it Ozzy nor solve the mess.The action sequences are a good plomazo and in half of the roll you are already watching the clock. Perhaps the only thing noticeable is the characterization of the own rider and the intro which tells the story of the Ghost Rider (personally also highlight the extraordinary chupa of leather, which no longer anyone who finds, at least at a modest price).These movies so bad would only need a dose of sinvergüencería and bizarrismo to be sympathetic. However, in the new times of CGI and qualification for children under thirteen, the series bé dead, not causing anything other than yawns.It is a pity all this, when years ago we entered the cinemas to see things like Robocop with our children face, and however we are here? I still did not I loaded to anyone with the ICU I keep at home.Conclude, if you are going to see the Ghost Rider because you know what awaits you: sugar, absurdez and quite boredom overdose? and but that is to say my companion.</body>
</review>
