<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Toro salvaje" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Possibly the best film of boxing in the history of film, with a spectacular Robert de Niro in the role of Jake the Motta. It has unleashed in me a deep sense of revulsion, but that is the cinema, to the senses is wake up from either way.</summary>
	<body>Not long ago I read in a magazine the classification of the best films of the history, all in line with the últma delivery of Rocky (which by the way the original did not appear in the list). In the first place was Toro Salvaje, a classic of those that every human being must see, and as I am a more humane, being in an outburst of spending, a pack of Scorsese my medium Zucchini wants to return for any movie you liked I bought at the Fnac.The film tells the life of Boxer Jake La Motta, from its beginnings until his retirement and later life. Shows a violent character, excessively violent, misógeno, blunt and Díez. His boxing is the best, and quickly rises in rank until it reaches a moment that no Boxer wants to deal with it, but not get the championship belt that never accepted aid from anyone. This joins its worsening relationship with his brother and his wife.I have to admit that the film I did not like, given that these so violent films, palpable and real violence, get me bad body. The treatment that gives Jake women me crispa and the boxing scenes are too explicit. Someone will say, and you see why a boxing movie? Man, that a classic is a classic and the boxing movies I usually like, but in this there is cruelty. Moreover, it is an impressive peliculón, with a great De Niro (who had to clog up many kilos during the filming to adapt to his character). The atmosphere is great, and secondary actors I like, given that they are very expressive quality that has been lost in modern cinema. By the way, there a nod (or as the viewer wants to see) with the law of silence, in the time that is talking to the mirror as if was his brother. This is modelled to the scene of the car from the movie Marlon Brando.Resumiendo, possibly the best film of boxing in the history of the cinema, with a spectacular Robert de Niro in the role of Jake the Motta. It has unleashed in me a deep sense of revulsion, but that is the cinema, to the senses is wake up from either way.I'm with Rocky.Besitos.P.D: the key scene of the combat against Janiro is brutal.</body>
</review>
