<review author="Victoruco" title="V de Vendetta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Too much policy, I would have removed social burden and would have given him more action</summary>
	<body>N, is not about me the movie (because, I understand it either, but seems to be that I am not the only one that starts with V?). Finally, is the case that you I wanted to watch this movie? Be written by the WachoVscky brothers her supports, that they were the creators of the Matrix phenomenon. And the truth is that it is entertaining, but fails to be as its predecessor.The story is very complex, and there are times when both name and both turn you get to lose a little? It is very well threaded, and at the end you see the puzzle fits surprising and correctly, but I still think it is too convoluted? Do besides that he gets into complicated issues? does in my view it is too political, I you would have removed a bit of burden? social? to give a little more than action.The subject is a "terrorist" according to the Government, fighter for the freedom of the people, he said. It is based on a comic book, it is true, but it is a delicate subject? because justify violence is an issue that cannot be treated lightly? But well, rely on what is the film itself.The interpretations are very successful, well, the protagonist has it easier? because not is you never sees the face? is it a famous actor? We will have been always the same person who was under the mask? It will be done casting for that role? Does testing them it mask?. We therefore resolve doubts: V is neither more nor less than Hugo WeaVing, agent Smith. Yes, the evil Matrix! Do now think for me: he will always been? Anyway, that never will know?Natalie Portman spectacular, tremendous? what great actress? When the see me remember this piece of film called "Leon (the Professional)", probably my favorite movie? Natalie was great small and still is now. Thus, it is an entertaining movie, it will not become a mass phenomenon, but you well spend in the cinema. Then to enter into debate and seek more feet to the cat, now they will be others</body>
</review>
