<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Babel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This newly lighted 21st century epic. Generous gift for future generations to illustrate the desquiciamiento of this society now. Emotional gift for those who live here and find this terrible mirror of our differences and our similarities...</summary>
	<body>Babel is a beautiful exercise in research on solitary confinement. Moving, and emotional, at times bombastic this third film of González Iñarritu complete what the author called "the trilogy of pain" with loves dogs and 21 grams. The brittle narrative of his argument emphasizes the also fragmentary nature of the human condition: good and evil do not exist as sistematizable nomenclature, everything is moldable and melts arbitrated by subtle and sometimes intangible threads. An event that happened in the past can inevitably influence the future. A fortuitous gesture (the gift of a Winchester that a Japanese tourist makes a Moroccan Guide) may condition one huge range of other facts, also incidental, years later. This butterfly effect takes in Babel huge dramatic dimensions, based on universal and developed firmly, without tenderness, splendidly lunchs feelings about a sincere speech that speaks, among many other things, pain and fugal happiness (the marriage going to Morocco to see if there, being alone, they are) or the unlikely concatenation of coincidences that can upset our placid life and our upholstered environment.For all this, González Iñarritu mounts three films in one: is not anything new since loves dogs or 21 grams also developed this narrative technique with different results. Morocco, Japan and the border of Mexico and the United States are the scenarios to put the pieces of this racial, cross-cultural, globalized and babélico crossword ending seize our ability of amazement to leave us mystified by the lightness of being, as I said Kundera, and the bombastic pageantry of random.All the characters of Babel are marked by an error: Moroccan children and the tragic shooting, the Mexican maid that does not take parental authorization to remove us children, girl Japanese sordomuda who has not passed its isolation and the loss of his mother, the American marriage which aims to revive their love in the grey a postcard of the Atlas.Este film has no expiration date: is entrenched in some imperfect virtues, but emotional. It is true that González Iñarritu is already pursuing with this narrative model too anchored in a formal pattern and linguistically surpassed, but we are still feeling an itching, a fresh outburst in the perfect images to this Mexican artist who knows just get into the neon of Tokyo that drag their greedy camera on the trails of dust of the Maghreb. In its says, some elongated episode (the wedding in Mexico) or excessive time which puts the Japanese girl, whose contest (where relevant) does not mark the tone of the events on which the film is based. This does not harm the overall impression: that we are witnessing a masterful piece orchestrated with craft and feeling and that explicit, evil that in spite of us, the barbaric of the world, their disenchantment... In a necessary aside, I note the pleasant feeling of reduction in cache that have been offered divos as Brad Pitt Cate Blanchett to take charge of their characters or do an honest and free from glamour to which we are accustomed. Támden González Iñárritu-Arriaga, director and script writer, seems to have agreed a separation. As it should be. The combined dolor-emoción - tragedy is already sufficiently exploited.Only by the very methodical process of assembling the film chapter in the history of cinema with independence that is being nourished by both award and is there already deserves bound (then you have to correct or enhance the post) to lie (Eastwood, Scorsese) heavyweights in the Oscars to come.</body>
</review>
