<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite its flaws, letters from Iwo Jima is still a very good film in which Clint Eastwood returns to prove that it knows to shoot as few filmmakers today.</summary>
	<body>While preparing flags of our fathers, American vision of the battle of Iwo Jima, Clint Eastwood met the existence of a book containing letters from Japanese soldiers of the garrison of Iwo Jima wrote to their families. Then, Eastwood decided to make a second film that received the Japanese vision of one of the bloodiest clashes of the second Mundial.Contar war a same historical fact, more a battle, from two different perspectives is not something new in the cinema, for example as it was done in this great war tape which is Tora, Tora, Tora!. Letters from Iwo Jima promised to fill the gaps of flags of our fathers, and will undoubtedly fill them for those not very smart viewers in historical matters. The story focuses on general Kuribayashi (Ken Watanabe), Commander of troops on Iwo Jima, with a private soldier, Saigo (Kazunari Ninomiya), you only want to survive and return home. The first part of the film focuses on the run-up to the battle, in the feelings of the characters, and the discrepancies between the controls. These minutes do not have the strength that one might expect of a tape of Eastwood, but as soon as the battle begins, the story gains intensity and drama. The atmosphere they create tunnels is oppressive and rarefied, further conveying the suffering of the characters. However, there are several details that squeak, ending not fit very well in history. One of them is the sequence with the captured American soldier. In addition, the flashbacks end not function, that instead of giving more packaging as a whole, they have the opposite effect. In the war scenes tape deteriorates slightly, these scenes are stuck with shoehorn between scenes of flags of our fathers. The picture almost in black and white of Tom Stern again absolutely masterful. For its part, the performances are good, stressing especially that of Kazunari Ninomiya.A despite their failures, letters from Iwo Jima remains a very good film in which Clint Eastwood returns to prove that it knows to shoot as few filmmakers today. And any excuse is good to get into a film and enjoy the work of the last great classic Hollywood</body>
</review>
