<review author="Berto" title="Noche en el museo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Typical infantil-familiar film of Christmas, a little awkward-parent, which will have to win the affection of his son showing you that it is responsible and hardworking.</summary>
	<body>We at beginning of year and we have already the first megataquillazo with us. Night at the Museum, here in Spain had relatively large success of public, nor can be compared with the smash hit that has taken in the US, where its collection has exceeded $ 200 million, making it the first big Blockbuster of the year. I must also say that there it premiered in full Christmas holidays, what the boost definitely, and do not understand how Spain and the rest of sites not her they premiered also on those dates, because almost of insurance fund-raising would be even twice which they have achieved. Let us not deceive ourselves, night at the Museum is a child movie, with all the topicazos children and aimed at a public which is not demanding and conforms to (almost) anything. Runs the roost Shawn Levy, a director has behind him, attentive to the impressive curriculum: honeymooners, twelve at home and finally the unclassifiable horror which is the Pink Panther. It is clear that once would have to accept with some movie that interested minimally to the public, and is on this occasion that he has achieved. With such tremendous box office already has secured a second part of the film (totally unnecessary), besides the fact that his name is associated with large projects that previously had blocked, as it is neither more nor less than the address (although I'm hoping that it is going to destroy) an adaptation of Flash to the big screen (my God!).In the film that we are discussing, is the typical infantil-familiar film of Christmas, a little awkward-parent, which will have to win the affection of his son showing you that it is responsible and worker coming to work at the Museum of yore, which by a curse what at the Museum comes to life at night. By in the Middle, some bad middling, try to dock the Museum, but well, I not tell more because if the movie cannot lose the already little grace which of Yes account.The script, as the map of the world before the discovery of America by Columbus, without any surprise, with a superesperadísimo finish, but that the smaller the House is going to love, is what this film stands out in a few more than efficient special effects. So, during the footage, we will find ourselves hovering around in the corridors of the Museum from a Tyranosaurus Rex, until lions and monkeys, passing by a figure of Easter Island and even Genghis Khan quite come to least, the truth.The absolute protagonist, Ben Stiller, actor bad ever there, but do not know how manages to always join in some box office pitch like this before us. His performance in the same tone that always, same face, many exaggerated grimaces, and nothing more. I believe that we will never see this picking up an Oscar. accompany Stiller Carla Gugino, the only thing salvageable from the film, and although plays a fairly small, it correct as it is his tone in all his performances. Also appear there, Mickey Rooney and Dick Van Dyke, seems to me more like homage to with something else, but hey, even with Stiller showing be a lot better than him as actors, even at their age.Two others who did not lose the mess are Robin Williams, portraying a cardboard Teddy Roosevelt, and as it could not be less, the almost official boyfriend of Stiller, Owen Wilson, passing it big making cowboy in the West, without little interpretation highlight.Ultimately, an entertaining film that will love to the mas peques (little'uns) of the House and to all those who still retain the child being inside, but horrorizara to the rest of the people that can go despistada thinking that he is going to see something more than what you can see in the trailer.</body>
</review>
