<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Venus" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is not, however, a pastelón sentimentaloide and tear - as I have said that to me personally, the subject I raises - is a skillful comedy-drama with excellent moments of humor.</summary>
	<body>Venus is one of those movies that voluntarily never had gone to see the film. Everyone has weaknesses and I, fled all film that includes a child, dogs or lawn as protagonists. So, they have been excluded from my retina or have flooded me her films as: Elsa y Fred, life is beautiful, Cinema Paradiso, champion? This film enters the category of my alienista vetoes and from frame one entered me a grief that is still me.Peter or? Toole plays an old glory of the interpretation that, currently, endures the monkey of the foci with the wrinkles of his voice and his roles of dying or dying semi leather. Not him it has have been difficult to get into this character that twenty years ago that this actor of perfect diction and porting of gentleman not played a player.The case is that Lawrence of Arabia is not the typical endearing man, is a sort of green old cynic who, with the bull given by age, it is an insolent and still flirts with girls descocadas. In the recent news of his life, crosses a twentysomething and between them begins a relationship in which the veteran is more a Pygmalion than Benny Hill. The film is not, however, a pastelón sentimentaloide and tear - as I have said that to me personally, the subject I raises - is a skillful comedy-drama with excellent moments of humor provided above all by the encounters with the generation of the protagonist fellow - Richard Griffiths and Leslie Philips - with a very bright hyphen of the architect of my beautiful laundrette or Intimidad.En tone of derisiondo, are drawn in the footage the misery of old age: loneliness, physical limitations, go saying goodbye to friends? and something very important that says the protagonist:?I'm dying and I still don't know? A highly recommended reflection about the parallels between adolescence and old age that speaks of what fuímos, we are or will be someday. (snif)PD: the Lord or? Toole owes me five litres of liquid, because I almost deshidrato me years ago also seeing the man of La Mancha.</body>
</review>
