<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Destino final 3" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If second parts were never good, because third already or I am telling you</summary>
	<body>Curiosity made me get close to see the new film by James Wong, who had already directed the first part of this series, and that because say it that I liked. On this occasion I cannot say the same, if second parts were never good, because third already or I tell you. You could already guess that the movie would not be no masterpiece, but it is that the catastrophe and the ordeal that was going to be put up all the footage could see already from the beginning. If something characterized the saga is by its starting time in which occurs the tragedy that will later be a feeling of the protagonist so vary the course of death. In "Final destination 3" takes place in a park of attractions, specifically in a giant roller coaster, but the truth is that neither using a medium so enabling Wong achieves that us between Vertigo, or fear or tension go in a vehicle so fast and so much anguish creates in many people.The script is predictable, with dialogues really simple, fall is more vulgar and stereotypes with some sequence that really ashamed. If we already start from this basis it is difficult that you can do something worthy, so acting level you can imagine how it will be. I have to say that the star Mary Elizabeth Winstead (Sky High, The Ring 2) is saved from burning, than seen apparently is not. The funniest are the deaths of the protagonists, that make the film to regain a little interest lost in these ramblings about who will be the next to die and these interpretations that make some pictures released in the amusement park and serving them as a prevention guide. Most regrettable and worrying is that it is having good fundraising and to achieve a product so bad there behind a large group of professionals. "Final destination 3" returns to place low hours to fantasy film and horror, in terms of quality that remakes and absurd films at the box office it is surviving. The truth is that recommend this film would be very bad milk, but if I have to do, the fiercest public will be those teenagers who enjoy entertainment with lazy exercise and seeking predictable situations, children's dialogues, see a pair of tits and a little blood.</body>
</review>
