<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Clint Eastwood is a brave, honest, skillful and generously creative director but here it has squandered an excellent material to the not calibrate well a bland cast and a heavy mounting.</summary>
	<body>In the 98 Spanish Spain hurt: Clint Eastwood, in its own way, it hurts their country, and puts it in a politically heterodox way. The historical model supplied heroes, pride and honor is here modified. Flags of our fathers tacked a simple but hard nut to crack, plot which is not vindica the glory or advocates of the homeland they are called into question the reasoning that move a people to forge their myths and to lift, sometimes heroes beyond where there are only people struggling for ideals or, as they say in the filmby save or save those who have close.Though Iwo Jima today is the sign that indicates the beginning of the end of the fascisms, the film rescue what has not been or has been sesgadamente and contradicts (in an open and even blatant) textbook of school which has occupied for 60 years the desks in the United States of America Warhol wrote that there was no deeper than the surface itself. This is what Eastwood and his screenwriter Haggis (Crash, the last Bond) set: on the surface, the icon and his ancestral to Captivate and seduce and how this icon (the legendary image of the flag of bars and stars in the Suribachi mountain on the Japanese island of Iwo Jima) hides a sham.Photo of Joe Rosenthal, who died recently, burns in the hands of the people: the soldiers were others and explain themselves, the heroes are the wounded and the dead and those who were not limited to be commanded labour that needed all the help in the world because the mast that improvised weighed much, but the propaganda machine of precise heroes war and the Government of (first) Roosevelt and Truman (later) requires champions of the epic, soldiers complicit in the deception (which nailed the flag were others, and are no longer) willing to not disassemble the farce and motivate the American people to loosen the Pocket in war bonds. Truman asked 14 billion dollars in the period of two months: raised 27,000, which amounted to nearly half of the State budget in a year.Flags of our fathers is not a war epic, although images of field spare no showmanship and the director not be amedre to show the barbarism of war with gruesomeness several and little colorful details. Nor is it a film of patriotic style because the pattern to the use of good and bad that it fascinates all blind flags worshippers is not articulated. I remember now a joke of the broken in the country who came to say that all the flags of the world are manufactured in Hong Kong.Eastwood deconstructs the archetype of the hero: lowers it power tool to cajole the citizens and give them encouragement and legends in equal parts to the end that folklore was reconstituted and new generations have idolsicons and merchandising varied for the altar of dreams.The film excels in stress the importance of the tour three rubber-stamp Sham heroes do to raise money for the Government. Politicians are the real heroes of this plot: more Sibylline impostors, who not preparing the body on the battlefield, but draw the incendiary profiles of the martyr: cause that, at the end, in all the wars, on all sides, always benefits to them, whom they did not lift a finger and not shoot a bullet.In the absence of seeing letters from Iwo Jima, the vision of the conflict from the Japanese side, Eastwood returns to desmostrar is an author model, intelligent, committed to the film as a vehicle for emotions and responsibilities, independent and very personal.The film is not outstanding because there is an excess of flashbacks that bedevil the narrative thread and determine certain laziness to follow the history, that malea when it indiga in excess in the everyday life of evil called Heroes on their return home. Sobran final minutes and there is a (justifiable, in any case, but painful) excess of battlefield minutaje.The wretchedness of the false hero is emphasized with this return to everyday life: there is the Indian soldier that emboldens (drunk) with some policemen because not serve you at a bar because of his race, but then a whole Stadium will wait to see how staged the pin of the flag in a spectacular exercise in artifice invariably Yankee. The curious brand Spielberg-Eastwood production ensures quality cinema. This does not call into doubt, but here the master has not turned on the diana of excellence as we have lately accustomed: confined to tell us a story noble, necessary, difficult to chew on the skin of an American, but little nuanced if one is outside and attends this bombastic show of farces, hombres-anuncio and showy hymns for the return of the boys home.</body>
</review>
