<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Las mantenidas sin sueños" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Analysis to the argentina of family conflict. Feminist film with an acid, corrosive, likeable spike occasionally, which speaks of the hardship of a convalescent Argentine society of corralitos and political miseries.</summary>
	<body>Projections of parents not always coagulate on the horizon of the children. This is the phrase that gives birth to this puzzling Opera prima Vera Fogwill, Director and Argentine actress which reserves the title role of the film, Florence, is an ex-drogadicta that malvive in a destitute assumed a very mature daughter from game to game, trying to rescue her from the dark place where they think it is. The social background of the film questions the integrity of the family, his ancestral vocation of nucleus of society and the traditional concept of women as absolute axis of its maintenance, but here the mother occupies the role of daughter (by his desasimiento and its abandonment) and the daughter takes the powerful role of responsible and archetypal mother. The decline of the film, its voluntary escoramiento to the loss of moral values which must be a mother, is very successful. Treatment almost indie of the script stands for two wonderful actresses and an accomplice at all times (Los Babasónicos) music.Feminist film with an acid, corrosive, likeable spike occasionally, which speaks of the hardship of a convalescent Argentine society of corralitos and political miseries that have buffeted the future of a country huge, visionary, creatively rico and with an admirable spirit.The film premiered (triunfalemente) in 2005 than in Argentina. Come here now preceded an accumulation of awards (best film at the Festival in Milan, best film for the public at the Festival of Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, best film at the Festival Latino in Los Angeles and presented as best film for the famous Golden Globe). This list of winners (excessive, perhaps) attests to the fighting spirit of the film and its interest more than perceive their essential vocation of intergenerational drama or, if you like, of conflict mother-daughter.</body>
</review>
