<review author="Ricard Marcet" title="Los paraguas de Cherburgo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Scenes such as the sad farewell of lovers, and an ending very close to our reality, will recall us that, despite achieved maturity by its Viewer and the film, the screen can follow overwhelmed with emotion.</summary>
	<body>After an elegant camera movement, the privileged spectator looks the becoming of people down the street from a Zenithal perspective. It begins to rain on the cobblestones that fill the screen as if it were a brick wall. The credits of the movie are projected on the wall. Pedestrians, covered entirely by their colored umbrellas, glide among the names of those responsible for the film as if they were obstacles. Thus, to the beat of the music of Michel Legrand, typography and walking umbrella dance together forgetting their different nature.With this choreographic game, in my opinion, representative of what will be the subsequent footage begins the umbrellas of Cherbourg, film that Jacques Demy lead the Golden Palm of Cannes in 1964. Geneviève is an attractive young woman who lives with her mother and to help in the shop of umbrellas that have. You will know a Guy, a kind-hearted and handsome mechanic, and immediately they love. While Madame Emery, the mother of Geneviève, does not approve the relationship by the youth of his daughter and the poverty of Guy, which separates the couple will be military service: he will be allocated two years to Algeria and may not return to see. Pregnant of her beloved, but without hearing from you, Geneviève bow to his mother's wishes and marry Roland Cassard, a rich salesman of jewels. Some time later, Guy will return to the city.Judging from the plot of the film, which already was told us more than once, we might think that we are faced with a melodramatic musical anyone; However, it will not take to realise that we are faced with an unusual film. After the opening credits commented, we will be surprised by a few characters who speak singing. Nor spectacular numbers inserted by force or musical moments, motivated by the plot; in the film Cherbourg of Demy, in which the real landscapes submit the saturated colors of the decorations of the musical genre, singing is the natural form of expression of the characters that inhabit it.The concern invades the spectator: we are faced with the sublimation of the constants of the genre? To a tribute? Perplexed with the recital which does not cease and the choreography perfect camera and commissioning scene, we can not get question about why such technical feat. A classic and predictable structure crystallized in three episodes that betray the framework of enunciation, as well as a few stereotypical characters arriving even in gold on his own condition (Madame Emery: Solo dies of love in the movies!), induce us to ask ourselves the linguistic nature of what we are seeing, and to understand the innovative contract offered by Jacques Demy: The director chooses to cut with the shackles that enslaves the worn-out film musical theatrical tradition, leaving aside the cabaretero number and becoming the constants of the genus codes that govern the world of the film, which determine its nature. Thus, hand of Demy, the musical ceases to be a combination of elements of diverse origin to become a way of narrating essentially cinematic.Is true that the earlier conclusion is the result of a reflection after viewing of the film, however, we can confirm the aware the viewer's position during the screening of the film. Only through their willingness to participate in the game raised by Demy, we can explain his involvement in a world that wanted so airtight. The spectator gets rid of his cuirass voluntarily and is shown vulnerable, allowing, thus, that at first get you to seem laughable, touches him deeply. Scenes such as the sad farewell of lovers, and an ending very close to our reality, will recall us that, despite achieved maturity by its Viewer and the film, the screen can follow overwhelmed with emotion.</body>
</review>
