<review author="Ricard Marcet" title="Glen or Glenda?" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The blindness of the director by a company repudiated by the establishment, his honesty perpetuated in a film incomprehensible, are able to deeply touch the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>The film "Ed Wood" (1994), Tim Burton would give the final push to the process of revaluation of the work of the filmmaker known popularly as the worst director in the history of the cinema. Reviled by the time in which he lived, Ed Wood, controversial filmmaker ever there, has become the greatest exponent of what today we know as culture trash (ambiguous nature concept). An approach to "do Glen or Glenda?", his opera prima, it will allow us to clarify, insofar as possible, the value of this unique director.A mysterious old man played by Bega Lugosi, actor who played Dracula in the celebrated version of Tod Browning (Dracula, 1931) and Ed Wood is responsible for rescuing from oblivion, introduces us to the film from a couch in the middle of a small and strangely decorated laboratory. Take to accomplish a steamy experiment, after Lugosi turned into a sort of demiurge, directly address the Viewer to make way for the narration of the facts: in the city, a regalia is has suicide. The police which is responsible for the case, surprised before the status of the deceased, will ask explanations to a psychiatrist. This, will illustrate you on transvestism and transsexualism with two stories which occupy the rest of the footage. The first, significantly more developed, will be the story of the tormented Glen (alter-ego of Wood and performed by the same), who does not dare to confess to Barbara, who is promised, his condition of regalia. The second will briefly tell the life of Alan, who will see fulfilled their dreams to undergo a sex change operation.Theatrical realism to portray the daily pictures of the life of Glen, as for example the scene in which looks at the TV wearing clothes of her sister, will be close to the institutional video through the overlap of the pseudoscientific discourse of the psychiatrist. This medical point of view that keeps us away from the protagonist with which, in principle, we must identify, entroncará with the oneiric treatment receives the omniscient character played by Lugosi. The spectator, accustomed to a narrative made in favour of its privileged location, attends stunned a confusing and unbridled grammar whose surrealism, as well as the torment of Glen, is on the rise: grotesque metaphors (see the stampede of bison) and other extravagant images will result in a long sleep in which escenificarán, reminding us of the infinitesimal production budget, the ghosts that torture the mind of the protagonist. Sex, fetishism, desire, violence, remorse. Finally will come through a situation which, because of its more than obvious symbolism, is laughable: Glenda, alter ego female of our character, can not save Barbara a fallen trunk that imprisons him, the virile Glen will really get it. After resolving the nightmare, dare to explain the problem to his beloved and, by love, will accept it.Someone could think of Ed Wood, for his willingness to vehicular intimate discourse through a peculiar narrative (as cross-dressing affected him of lifetime), as a fearless precursor of cinematic modernity. However, his unconscious denial of tradition that precedes, seems to make him in a single case, a rarity in the history of cinema. Their willingness to do conventional film hits of face to face with a rare personality that seems to have not integrated the established mode of representation. The result: a film that (re) invents the film unintentionally, that he seems delirious in the eyes of all those we have been educated under a certain narrative canon. The conviction with which uses its effects of fair barraca, the innocence of metaphors, the interpretation of itself, narrative obfuscating. This displaces the interest of the Viewer, making the figure of Ed Wood film the real protagonist of the film. His blindness by a company repudiated by the establishment, his honesty perpetuated in a film incomprehensible, are able to deeply touch the Viewer. This seems to have happened with Tim Burton who, far from falling into the current worship to the freak, heir of the old show of monsters, has slum wood becoming the hero misunderstood one of his best films. Us might seem contradictory that the celebrated director of "Edward Scissorhands" (Edward Scissorhands, 1990), accommodating in their own brand of manufacture as author, celebrates a filmmaker as Ed Wood. But if something can say after seeing Glen or Glenda? It is the conviction with which works in his work against not leave us indifferent.</body>
</review>
