<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Días de cine" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not by a film we will massacre the Spanish film. We do not with others that also deliver such garbage. Spanish film is raising head, but then comes a title in this manner and her clench...</summary>
	<body>Model of minimalist, short or diminished or reduced to four critical ideas primary and three secondary beneficial the same idea: the film is bad.It takes lifetime el bueno de Antonio Gasset with his great days of film now do a film with the same title and above, is bad with greed. It has nothing that deserves to be considered good: gets carried away by the film scurfy, simple to the naïve and Brutus as a kick in the noble parts us has been accompanying for a long time, and that still (occasionally) emerges.It is bad, because it has been said: very bad without benefits that slow the opinion. Trembles so terrible: will be liked in previous films (days of football, the other side of the bed and company) and here wanted to loop the loop, in the end, discuss squaring of the tomato and the encouragement of the statues.So this is going to become a critique, in a review of a spectator pleased or furious, more so than in a warning: do not go, do not lose time in the cinema with a crude history like this. Take out their children for a walk through the parks. Stay with friends and divaguen on the goodness of the Bus policy. Establish a strong Covenant with his common sense not to let go by advertising and perpetrate such nonsense again. And if film of what they earn, if it truly is that, I have a tasty bunch of fleshy grapes made frames. Now I think of Apocalypto, I do not know if it still resists in billboard. Or Kubrick's Lolita, with this nínfula of ambiguous meats and eager to be perverted by a Professor of Germanic literatures. I say.Not by a film we will massacre the Spanish film. We do not with others that also deliver such garbage. Spanish film is raising head, but then comes a title in this manner and bends her... Oh, and how...</body>
</review>
