<review author="Iñigo" title="Pulse" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Computer viruses that extend, ghostly appearances, a future in danger: a pulse to the patience of the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>Yet another tape of terror influenced by Asian elements that comes to the Billboard of our country, and once again makes it from the place where born stars with dreams and move in starry dreams."While they continue to generate benefits, as they currently do, they will continue giving sense the phrase labeled on the front of the rabbit of Duracell.""Pulse" is another clear example that terror is doomed to become extinct in its truest sense. Demeaning you within this genus because it is not known in what place it exactly. Perhaps suspense, full of tension macedonia perhaps. But anything horror, none of embarrassment.Already leave no space nor to startle, simuladamente warned in advance and with intention of annoying recidivism.It will not be a server which contradicts the film before us comes to distract an empty evening, but as obvious suspicion, the spectator in search of film (not mere pastime) immense, or being more lenient, cinema as artistic medium, will not find any Philo here.Is more. If us invades an evening with accumulated tasks, with some prior irritation or we are obliged to pay your entrance fee, surely will launch all kinds of insults (and not without reason) against the mother that shone Jim Sonzero.Dice the adage that patience is the mother of all sciences, and we are not going to be in all the human and spiritual peace that fills us with, which rectify your message. Breathing deeply all acquires best dyes.Because we are all perfectly warned that "Pulse" is not just another movie to fill the pockets of some while (without shame, of course) are deshabitando others. Come on, the Act of life itself.This remake in the form of by-product (no one has said that the original nor is, despite the fact that the intentions of the two are very different) baby everything a bit, and at the end, obviously grab a staggering cogorza. A SIP of "Resident Evil", one of "28 days after", another "Silent Hill" and, not to be left with so little, several long drinks of all Eastern tapes occurring to us: "The Ring", "Missed call", etc. And that many of those listed, in turn, were clones of other already lit.Perhaps with "The curse" the thing had its spark, but at this point, no longer surprise ghostly appearances, girls whose mothers are unaware of the concept of cleaning to do their filthy nightshirts (okay, here what we see are fuzzy and blinking spectra, I recognise his great step towards the singular), the trickle of faucets, lonely bathrooms, preceded increases in volume coups, ghostly cameras, mobile phones that leave no sound: very easy, all topics accumulated over the last decade in this kind of movies. Pretend to be surprised so non-obviousness more than a clumsy and ridiculous presuntuosidad.We could, without major setbacks, work as editors in his team, we know better than the director himself when he brincará a cat, will leave a shadow or a cry will hit the neighbor.And for more inri, looms true message moralistic/critic towards a society in which computers, piracy and technology advancing at a terrifying rate, and can generate insurmountable conflicts. Who the hell is the writer? Indeed: the ineffable Wes Craven appears in the path of the credits.Clear that Yes. Nor need the fatalistic, desert, chaotic end that characterizes films such as some of those listed at the beginning of the text.But there are days in which one rises benevolent, and rather than generate a simple and direct explanation that defined the film as a monumental trash (fruit of the suffered loss of time), is dedicated to search its favourable points. Probably in "Pulse" there will be None if you look at film, but without meditate more, I apuntaros two: its clear character of hollow entertainment and dark, perhaps apocalyptic atmosphere but always achieved and consistent with the intention of the film.Nothing to mention. No one is lost nothing, so let's stop give rise to platitudes. For that is "Pulse".The rest, each Viewer is perfectly aware of what you're buying and what you sell. Everything leads us to film today's trade: some work, others rush to the pragmatic. Some win, others lose. But, who has said that this is the game that all play?</body>
</review>
