<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Delicatessen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Poetic blend of perverse comics and modern fairy tale, film noir and romantic pastiche. 13 rue barnacle carried the film by David Lynch</summary>
	<body>Opera prima Jean-Pierre Jeunet, then recognized by other works of more impact media (Amelie), but minor film depth, Delicatessen is a love story between cannibals. Already warns the playful character, naive almost, of the film in their delusional titles of credits. Then the story is classic in recent European cinema, as orphan films of this type (here have to Guillermo Fesser that invoiced El milagro de p. Tinto and the adventures of Mortadelo and Filemón to tow this foundational Delicatessen). There has been a kind of cataclysm nuclear or something similar and we are on the outskirts of Paris. Rises a cochambroso building in which lives a curious and consensual community. The butcher who runs the business of the low is killing them and gives by chicken or cow that continues to be human flesh. All consenting the Muskat because there is need to eat and no one believes that he is going to touch him in disgrace come next. The arrival to the building of a circus performer in search of his boss disrupt routine and forcing all tenants to rethink the food chain. The artist falls in love with the daughter of the butcher, which represents just the opposite than his father, partly because she is a vegetarian.Not I revealed anything relevant with this mild synopsis (I not being friend never writing details of the argument because this site or me I no place gutting what not should know), but I bosquets the surreal narrative machinery of Jeunet.La comedy of the film relies on broad humor so crude as cash strokes. Shantytowns of the scenes (which is, by far, the fundamental appeal of the film) love so much that we are for a few days (and with all the films that in those days we can see) infected the plastic extravagance of a genuine and perverse artist who knows if old reader of any French edition of our immortal Ibáñez Percebe 13 Rue. The building seems, eaten by the mist, populated ghost gothic castle. Or is that its inhabitants are not actually?The truculence of his proposal is lightened with the love story and the humanity of the clown, but weighs more Expressionism, the distortion of light, some hypnotic ability to reconcile reality and fantasy, logic and disorder in a handful of excellent images.Jeunet jumped to the U.S. to shoot an Alien: the wonders were in France. The author did not fly: could not write their imaginary particular symbolic. Here he exploits in every corner of the House, in the gestures of the characters.Delicatessen is apocalyptic, eschatological, beautiful cinema in his rust, mixing poetry of perverse comics and modern fairy tale, film noir and romantic pastiche.I saw her in its premiere, large room, and it fascinated me. The review, online television, generous, but little always, not I was disappointed nearly twenty years later. I most appreciated the lavish and delicious music (which are unexpected as saws or piers objects creaking) I have been able to slow the Vertigo of the action, look behind and stop playback when I wanted to. Privileges of home theater, says a friend.Jeunet and Caro, his other buddy in the whitefish, separated shortly thereafter. If there is a fantastic film, using the most legitimate and language of this adjective, it's Delicatessen. If they have not seen, look. Do what you can sit two hours and stop polluting this wonderful insanity. The film ends with an excellent visual apotheosis: the building, contaminated by the ridiculous and tragic epic of its occupants, comes abajo.addenda: so exquisite photography of the film is the work of Darius Khondji, who would then work with David Fincher on the uneasy Se7en. addenda 2: upon the death of an old, his daughter is sorry for not having been able to dismiss it. The husband, cooler, resolved by saying that they are still in time.</body>
</review>
