<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Azuloscurocasinegro" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Daniel gets to mark his style, because he is faithful to its principles, its past as a short film maker, his philosophy of director</summary>
	<body>After little more than two weeks, a film as "dark blue almost black", that comes brand new in style with three Biznagas at the festival of Málaga, can not see in any of the two multiplexes of San Cugat del Valles, and already only is projected at four cinemas in the city of Barcelona, reflects perfectly the situation of our national cinema.I wonder, with despair, the luck that you bring to these other Spanish were not rewarded or not even released works in Málaga. The film does not reach the public and dies, inevitably, without an engaged and effective industry protected legally, independent and with a real power of distribution. This disaster, this clear and permanent crisis of Spanish cinema, has nothing to do, as much that so want us to sell, with the problems of piracy on the Internet. It is Internet, precisely and in this case, from where is being achieved, in large part, create a well-deserved word of mouth about this movie that is prompting many people to go to the cinema.Although, in fact, I never intend to be objective, I would be also impossible to be writing about this opera prima by Daniel Sánchez Arévalo. In my case, I know Daniel shorts and also know that to him. The film, however, enjoy if one is made, no doubt, to the great public. That is why the greatest concern of Daniel is that his first feature goes unnoticed for the vast majority. We speak does too in Salamanca, Daniel was safe, quiet, knowing that it has managed to create an honest and quality piece. That it has fulfilled more than their own expectations as director, intelligent author effective and intuitive and sensitive Viewer. But it is precisely why, Daniel is not shown outside at all to the almost black dark blue picture of our cinema.The plot of the film begins where ends one of his latest short films, his Super and acclaimed "Fisica II". Rescues the characters here to draw a simple story, but emotional and portrayed with astonishing dexterity. Skill in the visual, to mark a style, but without empachar. To narrate the visual language and separate the characters when they need it, join them when they should be together, to suggest and recreate with small symbolisms and winks. Skill in a mise en scene right and some sober and real performances with entertaining and intelligent dialogues. Because we know that make people laugh in dramatic situations is never an easy task.Another deadly Pirouette is the achieve mix social realism with the commercial genre. Know the topic social lightening just enough drama and not leaving already so trite and reviled style camera in hand, keeping the decision to leave the camera on the tripod or the dolly. And in addition, Daniel manages to mark his style, because he is faithful to its principles, its past as a short film maker, his philosophy of director who believes in the great importance of the screenplay and the acting direction. Who creates from the respect and humility and knows and manages to convey to the viewer their own enthusiasm for history that recreates. And that, is already more than half step to paradise.And as there is also some but in the film, to say that obvious academicism of the author, and the undeniable faith in dramatic structures, in the formulas of genre and script rules, take away from the story space for the surprise. History is always quite predictable. In addition, to keep the pulse so much and so successful Pirouette, some moments end up show is also unlikely and little credible. However, is everything so pampered and told with so much respect, sensitivity and enthusiasm, this hinders not for nothing a brilliant and talented opera prima you know good cinema and managed challenge.Finish pointing only two things, on the one hand to predict the obvious, a hopeful future for Daniel Sánchez Arévalo, and on the other, make you a very clear message: will not regret. Go see her!</body>
</review>
