<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Ases calientes" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do is that?Hot ACEs? It is not more than a Grand Guignol grace without any sense. A collection of bizarre characters that not hesitate to massacre each other without the slightest consideration or modesty.</summary>
	<body>You have to fuck, man. A few months ago I rented "Narc" and I was shocked by a film crushing, harsh and Spartan to the core. An empty film of any artifice in which Ray Liotta, pulling to obese, was superb. A film about friendship, love, loyalty and betrayal that, with a few doses of violence very tight to what it was, was at the fair, with the appropriate pace speed.That is why, when I saw that it was premiered this "Hot ACEs", written and directed by the same Joe Carnahan's "Narc", me Terry hands. And when I read that the thing was mafia and organized crime. because almost levité that one has weakness, confesa, and notorious for that genre.And yet, what a disappointment most brutal and tremendous! It is that "Hot Ases" is nothing more than a Grand Guignol grace without any sense. A collection of bizarre characters that did not hesitate to slaughter each other without the slightest consideration or modesty, without that at any time we come to understand the reasons and, what is worse, us irrespective of a damn. It is the shadow of too elongated Tarantino? Perhaps. But "Hot ACEs", rather, connects with lysergic dementia of the worst Oliver Stone, of monsters as "Alexander" or "Ex officio assassins". Aesthetics of violence seeking to overlook the graciosa and that is pathetic; he tries to impress and just bored.Shots here, tattoos there, gadgets by now. pseudo-místico-intellectuals parliaments delivered by characters supposedly rolled I and such regrettable cartoon pictures such as the three brothers psychopaths.Dear Joe: what happened in your head between the formal restraint and emotion without limits "Narc" and this "Hot ACEs" bobada? Suffered a stroke and still you do not recuperaste? You have a bad trip with an expired tripi? How you convenciste good Liotta, the less interesting Andy Garcia or the alternativillo of Ben Affleck so join this cluster of nonsense?Male, do you see because according to the magazines in the industry, you'll be that roll the next adaptation for the screen of a James Ellroy novel: "White Jazz". And look, if this "Hot ACEs" slapstick is you can apologize because we are all entitled to spend a cold streak or to get us drunk one night and ridicule; not playing with Ellroy. So, friend Joe, be very careful there outside.</body>
</review>
