<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El tercer hombre" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great film of intrigue in the streets of a Vienna another thrown down by the second world war. One of the best films in the history of cinema, which continues to surprise with its intelligent and well spun argument. Highly recommended.</summary>
	<body>I think I'm going more than a steady pace. Anything of a physical impairment, given that every day I am more visible in that plane, neither of these trifles. What tells me that I get most is that I am starting to make collections of Sunday newspapers. Yes, I confess, I'm doing the collection of classic film that gives every Sunday newspaper that that clamp your pages. And at a good price, hear. By the way, the synopsis highlights until the last frame, so not leais.The film is about an American who travels to Vienna after World War II, when the city was divided into five parts, one per each occupying power and the last international. He travels to see an old friend, but get there discover who has died under mysterious circumstances. Total, that as he is a writer of novels of the West, believes that it is trained to investigate the alleged murder by your account so it faces to the army to do so.I loved this movie, and that films of Fame then I fail to kill. The setting is simply great, with that Vienna was genuinely quite crumbling. Very good actors, of those I like to me, with very marked gestures (especially the Duke or count, not remember well). The very remarkable script begins soft, with a kind of pirado that look to his dead friend, but grows until the final climax that exalts the film. Also, gives a little history lesson, that's always good. By the way, get Orson Welles in a very good role.In short, great film of intrigue in the streets of a Vienna another thrown down by the second world war. One of the best films in the history of cinema, which continues to surprise with its intelligent and well spun argument. Highly recommended.</body>
</review>
