<review author="Luis Zueco" title="Klimt" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sad waste of money, effort and above all to a character, so special, so different than the inept that made this attempt to film.</summary>
	<body>This film to which followed the track since the end of last year when you had to be released, has been one of the biggest cinematographic disappointments of recent years. With a history like the life of Klimt, not needed nor invent delusions, hallucinations, or extravagant attitudes. It often happens that reality surpasses fiction, and in this case a figure so suggestive as of Klimt has devoured both director and actor who gives life, John Malkovich, who already thinks only his personal showcasing.With a scenario as the capital of the Empire earlier this century, with the first world war, with the universal exhibition in Paris and the artists there, with the movement of the Austrian secession, with Shiele and Klimt. With the sensuality of his art, the beauty of its allegories, with its unique style, with all of this. Why? Why does it take invent so many other things? Focus on things without importance with the sole intention to impress the spectator, which actually ends what is bored of so much mediocrity, while trying to see background of works by Klimt. Try to follow the film is impossible, because there is no such film, only a suction of scenes without any thread than one, only John Malkovic, never giving the size. In addition to be able to admire some of his works, and the continuous parade of naked women, little more there interesting in this film. And now I understand its delay and the fact that only project in two rooms of Madrid.Lamentable waste of money, effort and above all to a character, so special, so different than the inept that made this attempt to film. A missed opportunity to make a great movie. In addition it had been very well received in Madrid after two recent exhibitions there of his work in the capital and the Juan March Foundation in the Mapfre Foundation.</body>
</review>
