<review author="Dragon negro" title="El Motorista Fantasma (Ghost Rider)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With this Ghost Rider, Johnson makes it clear that, as much as you like superheroes, that does not mean that you know to make good movies about them.</summary>
	<body>Director Mark Steven Johnson likes making superhero films has been demonstrated, began with Daredevil in the direction, in a film that wasn't no wonder but saved from the burning through a few details. He had no so lucky with his screenplay of Electra and Rob Bowman perpetrated a real hodgepodge of film. Now, with this Ghost Rider, Johnson, who writes and directs, makes it clear that, as much as you like superheroes, that does not mean that you know to make good movies about them.We start with a full script of topics with the typical story of the superhero, as he gets his powers, the story of impossible love, trauma of the protagonist, learning skills, fighting with the bad guys, etc. Okay it is what it is and it cannot be much more, but at least if that can make good fact and provide details, talks and motivations that make the plot flowing, coherent and distinct, which in this case there is, moreover, there are scenes of ridiculous and meaningless, others stuck with shoehorn and some sonrojantes phrases. Then have a Nicolas Cage is as an actor of penalty and get a pathetic performance making palurdo sometimes and ridiculous chulito other. We continue with one of the points that should have been the Fort of the film and not just convincing, are the special effects. The blazing skull should have been more terrifying, dirty and dark, we give more fear in short and seem more real, although it must be admitted that the fire made effect. Then there is a little developed and some spectacular action scenes saving only some scene of the rider on his bike.A shame a character that could have given much game with a different approach, just been wasted in a film with so little substance is expect that not to give the opportunity to Johnson shooting a sequel, that this man is devoted to something else and stop already martirizar with films of superheroes are not equal.</body>
</review>
