<review author="Florinda Chic" title="El último rey de Escocia" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film by Kevin MacDonald is very entertaining, surround, shocking and even at one point has a harrowing twist in the line of the Midnight Express. With all this needless to say, that I recommend it strongly.</summary>
	<body>The last King of Scotland comes to join these particular memories of Africa that Hollywood is making in order to sell popcorn and step, denouncing abuses faced by the continent's Western society: the constant gardener, blood diamond and Hotel Rwanda.Sin however, this story is distancing itself from the others. In all the films mentioned above, there is a more or less seasoned hero who at one point or another of the film becomes aware Savior of mankind. The last King of Scotland, is not only a monstrous work interpretive Whitaker, also is the story of a Faust sold his soul to the devil for little more than solid mulatas, swimming pool and bottles of Dom Perignon. The seller is a Scottish doctor - who plays lost adrenalítico, James McAvoy - no sign of heroism and irreproachable conduct, ultimately, one of our. This character we see him desvirgar his innocence as he falls into the clutches of the erotic power of that purchase, Idi Amin, and see you the overnight become his physician, psychoanalyst, Director and above all jester.The figure of the tyrant dictator mad, megalomaniac and child and mental horny buddy, I can not think another actor who could have done better than Whitaker. And even to the surprise of his fans, get the Agent Scully, i.e. Gillian Anderson, which I recently saw also splendid and poking fun at herself in Tristram Shandy, the last of Winterbottom.La film by Kevin MacDonald is very entertaining, envelope, shocking and even at one point has a harrowing twist in the line of the Midnight Express. With all this needless to say, that I recommend it strongly, because although you have never heard talk of Idi Amin, and you import a radish African dictatorships, the history is not at all distant and is a magnificent film.</body>
</review>
