<review author="Taliesin" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite the fact that it fails to bore, the film is set with an irregular rhythm that does not help the form of flashbacks that has chosen to tell the tale, which occasionally confuses and subtracts freshness to the action.</summary>
	<body>Flags of our fathers is a film set in the second world war, whose plot focuses on the landing and subsequent decision-making of an island to the South of Japan: Iwo Jima. Until here everything is little novel, so its director Clint Eastwood has decided to focus the camera away from the field of battle war and closer to the political and social field. But what makes it unique is that you along with other pelícucla, letters from Iwo Jima, it will form a team that will have the same fact from different perspectives: flags of our fathers will make it from the American point of view and letters from Iwo Jima will from the Japanese side. Eastwood continues for much of the footage in which canónes to war movies refers. It all starts with a group of young soldiers embark on a mission of great importance for the development of the war and little by little we will be featuring the characters, and see that each of them has a different motivation for the shoes be playing for his country. The war is shown with the objective harshness that already used Spielberg in saving soldier Ryan that, however well that yet in flags of our fathers, is still the best military landing in the history of the cinema. The rest of the field of battle scenes stand out for their sobriety, and focuses on that at times seems that Americans not faced the Japanese, but rather went to hunt animals. I guess this yawn more surprise in the Viewer when he discovers that the Japanese also have father, mother and even feelings. But the strong part is the showing us Eastwood when the plot focuses on United States, away from battlefield, where shows us the shame and lies of the war. On Iwo Jima as blood and death, in the White House are symbols that allow to sell the war to the citizens. Tell us how a photograph of a few marines by placing a flag can become a metaphor for the victory, no matter how many lives have been lost in the effort or few lies has to tell. And how truly powerful message is that you are falsehoods are worth for Iwo Jima, Viet Nam, or the nearest long Iraq. Despite the fact that it fails to bore, the film is set with an irregular rhythm that does not help the form of flashbacks that has chosen to tell the tale, which occasionally confuses and subtracts freshness to the action. Another but must be put is that not noted by the direction of actors, who are at the service of the overview, so in general are something flat and reach the Viewer. Despite these black dots, flags of our fathers is an interesting production with anti-war vocation which gives me the impression that will gain much see letters from Iwo Jima, with which the whole picture will be completed. I liked: the sobriety, a far cry from the war film of action, of the scenes of fighting. I did not like: the characters are somewhat flat, so no I got involved with them at any time. Curiosities: The Japanese Government not allowed filming scenes of fighting in the island of Iwo Jima, so filming beach scenes had that you done in Iceland, whose beaches also have black sand due to volcanic activity. Recommended audience: tough film, both in its form and in background. You need a slow digestion, so it is not recommended for those seeking a light dish.</body>
</review>
