<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El último rey de Escocia" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The last King of Scotland is a very necessary film, which serves to remind us of the atrocities of the past, and that helps to become aware of the atrocities still committed in Africa.</summary>
	<body>In recent years the film tends increasingly to seek entertainment pure and simple, empty and simplistic films capable of despair to any movie buff boasts of being. But at the same time that happens this phenomenon, occurs another completely opposite, is the increase in films of historical and social complaint, most of them of European production, as the sinking, Sophie Scholl, and now, the last King of Escocia.Kevin MacDonald, renowned documentary filmmaker, is responsible for bringing to the screen to one of the most bloody dictators of the last quarter of the 20th century: the Ugandan Idi Amin Dada, responsible for ethnic cleansing that caused more than 300,000 people dead. The story focuses on a young doctor, Nicholas Garrigan (James McAvoy), arriving in Uganda to have fun and help the population. After an accident, Dr. Garrigan will know to Idi Amin Dada (Forest Whitaker), and will soon be submerged in his particular universe. Macdonald faced a similar challenge with great aplomb, and proves to be the height of the history that has denounced. The Scottish filmmaker leaves aside the rumor mill that has surrounded himself to Amin, offering a sharp portrait without concessions of a cruel, vengeful, eccentric and unstable tyrant. There will be who gets the hands to the head by the fact that the film humanizes the genocidal, but that no one be misleading: humanize a historical figure is not nor much less justify their acts, but it reminds us all that a human being was responsible for such barbaric. The solid screenplay by Peter Morgan and Jeremy Brock is an excellent starting point for a film of great intensity, with some magnificent scenes, such as the first appearance of Forest Whitaker on screen. And the time comes please stand and applaud an actorazo as Whitaker, who made a memorable and outstanding, interpretation that no doubt will go down in the annals of the history of the cinema. His work is so impressive that it overshadows altogether to the rest of the actors, while some, like James McAvoy also made very good performances.The last King of Scotland is a very necessary film, which serves to remind us of the atrocities of the past, and that helps to become aware of the atrocities still committed in Africa. And leaving aside their background, is essential only to see the extraordinary work of Forest Whitaker, until now unknown by the general public, but one of the best actors of the current film scene.</body>
</review>
