<review author="Pablo" title="Plan oculto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will delight those who enjoy with the unexpected twists</summary>
	<body>It is surprising to see the capacity of astonishment that causes people to simplicity. The controversial vision of Spike Lee takes advantage of a simple plot used to bathe some of his characters with such socio-cultural prejudices that both likes and badly embedded in his later works. The truth is that the movie has a very successful style and a history somewhat predictable but with details which baffle the viewer stunning him and making him ignore the most obvious and logical things which are actually those that provide the solution to the problem.Personally robbery films attracted me much, for what he really enjoyed this, what I liked most was without a doubt the role played by Clive Owen, a sort of robin hood modern, relaxed and unperturbed practically throughout the film and showing a pride in his speeches that I understand that became unbearable for some, but for myIt was an ideal antagonist. A master.A brilliant sequence of credits will show us step by step as a painting truck going picking up a number of individuals whom dressed in industrial monkeys make a bank called Manhattan Trust control. The forces of order not slow to make her relevant appearance, led by a Denzel Washington somewhat arrogant and vain but turn rogue and aged in the body making it to symbolize an old dog that could not reach the American dream on the right track and that use this conflict as via to satisfy his ambition. the dilemma is if the hara in a legal and judicious manner or if sucumbira to the so-called attempt to corruption. On the other hand we have an icy manipulator named Madeline White (Jodie Foster) to seek to safeguard the interests hidden in a box of the Bank the founder of this site. Objectives of this woman are not entirely clear, it is a sort of solucionadora problems for senior and wealthy officials of the city. (a kind of Sr.Lobo). Given this percale, the viewer feels a strange situation, don't know who put party. Initially none of them directly sympathizes with the Viewer, creating an interesting spiral of sub-plots and intrigue that will delight those who enjoy with unexpected twists.Throughout the film you can see some small criticisms with which they disagree. The truth is that the conversation between the black child and Clive Owen speaks for itself, or which Denzel Washington has maintained with the polícia that encañonan. Even so do not see them appropriate for the type of film that is hidden Plan. Anyway is logical that Spike Lee try to leave their mark and so increase the controversy to promote their new work. A work, which from my point of view do without such details to become a prominent place in the thrillers of these last five years.</body>
</review>
