<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Venus" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Peter or?Toole gives life in a masterful way that hardened cynic who is Maurice, filling the screen with each appearance, doing every gesture and every look a real lesson in interpretation.</summary>
	<body>Do four years ago, Peter O.?Toole, one of the best British actors of all time, received his first Oscar, the honorific. And in his speech he said that he still wanted to win a statuette for best actor. Do many laughed at the comment, taking it as part of English humor, but this year Peter O.?Toole returned to being nominated, and remember that there has already been a case in which an actor has won an Oscar after receiving the honorific, Paul Newman.Maurice (Peter or?)(Toole) and Ian (Leslie Phillips) are old friends and semijubilados actors in second row. Its comfortable routine and his morning talks at a café are interrupted by the arrival of Jessie (Jodie Whitaker), the great-granddaughter of Ian. Jessie takes not crazy to his great-uncle, but Maurice will engage a very particular relationship with her, which will exercise as a guide and mentor. Venus is one of those movies that it seems that only they can do well the English, that combines tenderness, fine irony and some touches of melodrama. A combination that could easily fall on a tear, and sentimental story that Roger Michell however manages to avoid. The film is based on a solid script with a few well built characters, with two distinct parts, the most ironic first, and a second more bittersweet. Venus reaches have some brilliant moments of fine British humor, but when the irony becomes sweet and sour, the history lapses significantly. Despite being almost as backdrop, the film pays a deep, heartfelt and very necessary tribute to the big players already retired and unfortunately, almost forgotten. Peter or?Toole gives life in a masterful way that hardened cynic who is Maurice, filling the screen with each appearance, doing every gesture and every look a real lesson in interpretation. Leslie Phillips, Richard Griffiths and Vanessa Redgrave are perfectly their roles, while Jodie Whitaker is not only able to endure the type opposite to Peter or?Toole, but get that their work shine, always in the shadow of such giant of the performance.Venus is a beloved film, seen with a pleasant smile from start to finish despite the bitter taste of the endgame. And more than anything, have the immense pleasure to see Peter O.?Toole with a character is a luxury that is priceless.</body>
</review>
