<review author="Javier Saz" title="The host" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Joon - ho Bong returns to mix genres with his characteristic humor, and create a monster very very enjoyable but somewhat unbalanced in its second half.</summary>
	<body>Thanks to MuchoCine.net see a morning pass "The Host" (?)(Do Gwoemul?, 2006) from Joon-ho Bong with very high expectations after his excellent "Memories of Murder" (2003), unusual mixture of detective story, comedy and sociological portrait. Here change the environment of the police for the monster-movies. If in "Memories of Murder" the result was notable and original (although I see some downturn in his long second Act) in "The Host" part find me too irregular. I will explain.The film begins with a great sequence of twenty minutes (excluding the flashback of do scientists?), the first act of the story, surpassing the achievements of any monster-movie self-respecting (except the "Them!", (1954, Gordon Douglas)). But under the guise of monster movie Bong Joon-ho is dedicated to your personal look about the characters and their environment. A ruthless and hilarious look. Do comedy, drama, action and complaint? This personal way of narrating works it in the first half of the film, but after a crucial event in the middle of the film, the balance between comedy and drama are descompensa and unnecessarily lengthens the plot (perhaps Pantry you twenty minutes of their two hours), and although in the outcome he dates the flight, let me a bittersweet taste in relation to the first hour of film.The presence of the monster is really purely circumstantial (monster movie) and it serves to Joon - ho Bong to show us the way (change) run through the characters after the key at the end of the first act event, the search undertaken is hampered by the environment in which they live. Joon-ho Bong ridiculed and denounced to the estates of his country, to health care, the Government, the army, the media and American interventionism.Visually brilliant, his narration is more visual verbal (the best gags are Visual) and achieves very plastic images (as his already recurring overhead slowed down with rain), albeit sometimes somewhat repetitive.Joon - ho Bong returns to mix genres with his characteristic humor, and create a monster very very enjoyable but somewhat unbalanced in its second half. (3 +)</body>
</review>
