<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Bosque de sombras" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The deep Euskadi of 1970s forests are the claustrophobic scenario of a western outlaws Patxis and outsiders Smith. A good Spanish movie that while it is not round, is more than decent.</summary>
	<body>A student outdone, that is what occurs to me say Koldo Serra and his forest of shadows. Taking into account that it is his directorial debut, I give an eight. If outside her third film, would be left with a 5.5 and my evaluation would read something like: Serra manages the climate, but not the climax. But on the other hand, this is a movie and not a test as they seem to believe some media, and is a good Spanish movie that while it is not round, is more than decent.The deep Euskadi of 1970s forests are the claustrophobic scenario of a western outlaws Patxis and outsiders Smith. Two British couples come to spend a few days relaxing in this environment, but obviously that nothing. From the beginning it starts to smell the toasted and the locals will not receive these guiris to the Bienvenido Mr. Marshall. However, Serra wallows in atmosphere that if we had not seen previously trailer or picture, we think that it will not happen anything in the footage.For me too obvious homages of film buff, who just saturating. Serra Pekinpah straw dogs you should like and has left record well, as well as other western classics. Not be so I blame, it has done so Soderbergh in the good German and all felt them great.The actors are superb, starting with Gary Oldman - 10 for Koldo to recover for the independent film - makes no shade no in this forest to the magnificent Lluís Homar. The art direction is brilliant and the only bug that I see as a whole is already commented of the argument, which as a dish countryman Arzac, promises a lot when they have it, but if you ask... It is half empty and full of superfluous ornaments.PS: Recovery this premiere of last Friday because I have already given the rod with the highlights of this week: the last King of Scotland and Inland Empire. Good weekend and on Monday? Oscars!</body>
</review>
