<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El Motorista Fantasma (Ghost Rider)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another one of the Marvel factory on a motorist that night Burns by a deal he made with Belcebú. It is not even the worst gender, sinvergüeza Daredevil, nor the best, see Spider-man, X-men or the controversial Hellboy. Total, to take the time and see a bit of special effects.</summary>
	<body>I guess all that I read you are waiting for a fierce criticism on this film. Well no, also do not understand many behaviors of that style. Let's see if I can explain, all movies can not be rated by the same standard, i.e., a porn movie is valued by lustrous members and bodies of scandal, not by his script. Similarly, if a comedy does not make me laugh, but has a perfect Assembly, the film is bad to not cover its comic goal. As with the films of pass passes bullet to frame the same or at least similar.The film is about a kid who does stunts with his father on the bike. One day discovers that his father has a fatal disease of need, so pacta with the devil that this remove you the disease. By this agreement, this becomes a sort of Mefistóteles sicario, as so many were before. Becomes the Ghost Rider, modern version of the Ghost Rider. One was basically going to horse and another motorcycle.Well, because another one of superheroes. The script harmful, as it was expected, with a motorist tormented that he tries to kill at all costs and that the devil avoids. A love that cannot be achieved by that these gentlemen have to be lonely (things of contracts). And a curse that does not know well as remove. Very typical. The special effects are very good, with emphasis on the stage of the skyscraper that is superb. And all becomes quite boring, with a few very flojitos dialogues, and with little action, which is the most important thing. These films have to have more fights and less metaphysical rolls of what suffers. Burning skull seems an advertisement for Hemoal rather than a movie of a guy.In short, another one from the factory on a motorist that night Burns by a treatment that, Marvel did with Belcebú. It is not even the worst gender, sinvergüeza Daredevil, nor the best, see Spider-man, X-men or the controversial Hellboy. Total, to take the time and see a bit of especiales.¿Y effects how not usa helmet that boy?Besitos.P.D: I have to write the phrase peak of the film. It says the bad malísimo, with all the solemnity that the situation calls for "my name is Legion, for we are many". Hahaha, brilliant.</body>
</review>
