<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="The Queen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Its critical impact is perhaps somewhat exaggerated, but there is no denying that Frears manages to take full advantage of a history which, in principle, did not seem to offer as many possibilities.</summary>
	<body>"The Queen" is a film which, a priori, because of its subject matter, not attracted me particularly. As it is managed by someone as competent and reliable as Stephen Frears, with one very interesting cast and is supported by some critical success and public I finally decided to see it.The film tells how were the days before and after the death of Lady Di and how affected to the Queen and the Government of his country. As some of my friends will recall, I had the "luck" to live these days in England itself (what memories!) and I assure you that the reaction of the people was amazing.Those moments of overreaction are well reflected in the film, seen always from the point of view of rulers and, especially, the sovereign that, coming from a culture of stoic suffering, not it was to understand what was happening to her around. To add realism, the file images are perfectly integrated into the action and used with restraint, always with a narrative purpose.Stephen Frears is a director of the good, that there is no doubt. But, in addition, it is a very intelligent director who, usually not only obtain some good performances from his actors, but rather you know support them when he has to do. This is one of those cases.It is true that the script is good, focuses on the essentials without neglecting details and brilliantly examines the psychology and the inner world of the main characters, focusing more, as it is expected, in the Queen. But if the choice of actors and the interpretation of these would have been wrong, the project had been shipwrecked big.Everyone, from James Cromwell (Prince Phillip, husband of the Queen) to Alex Jennings (Prince Charles), passing by Michael Sheen (Tony Blair) made some great performances and conform to their characters of perfect form (flame attention how move some actors, tracing impressively to its original).But above all highlights the imposing figure of Helen Mirren, which is not that he interpreted to Queen Elizabeth II, is that it becomes it. His eyes and his gestures transmitted throughout the interior of that woman fight and make it in the center of the film and most memorable of the same. Attention, for example, to the scene of the deer.Despite that and the elegant direction of Frears, tape peca of certain coldness and intranscedencia (someone cares the British Royal family?). I am friend of the coldness nothing because the pirates and smugglers of Moonfleet are passionate people, but I must admit that, in this case, is justified by the subject.Its critical impact is perhaps somewhat exaggerated, but there is no denying that Frears manages to take full advantage of a history which, in principle, did not seem to offer as many possibilities.Moonfleet.es rating: 7 out of 10.</body>
</review>
