<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Juegos secretos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>His descending tone, their expectations failed, not recognize, in the end, as the good movie that is is attractive in its approach and very well done... Memorable scenes along with flat resolutions lowered the final print...</summary>
	<body>The emotional turbulence of the placid and bourgeois residential neighborhoods of the United States have occupied numerous films. All digging in the same pathologies: apathetic marriages who seek air in new adventures, are sexual hidden bass facades respectable, adolescents who at an adult age calcada their parents...It abounds in this narrative material rico, but stays halfway by the half-heartedness of its conclusions. All that in a glorious first half hour points to heights significant dramatic then becomes exciting and instructive exercise of containment, where thin models described mere clichés, to forms of the more trite stereotype.Before that happens, before that we unplug the interest, there is a prodigious album frustrations and fears, of characters victimized by the routine who live at a distance happiness and never dare to address the risk to give a bit of life to its disenchanted days.The newly freed paedophile who returns to his neighborhood and does not hide its deviation, departures housewives that rest on the bench in the park with an eye on their children and a handsome dad entertain them the other, the unbalanced ex whose job is to harass the pervert and, above all, the love story of intervenor of Brad (Patrick Wilson) and Sarah (Kate Winslet) to which refers the inconvenient Spanish title (in English, we found a more conformity) (to the plot of Little Children), which takes a lot of this excessive footage, but just turned into an abusive (although well photographed) carnal fray hidden from the children.Sarah is not the Emma Bovary believed: her aura of inevitability is different and their ways of housewife frustrated by a non-existent marriage (there is not a single scene in which both occur as such unless the husband is caught with the panties in his face doing digital onanism) also differ from the character of Flaubert.Brad is a loserpending content his wife and now finally get his title of lawyer and spilled by his role as father responsible and pigeonholed in the routine that, in the eyes of society which lives, it is up to his wife.Secret games delivered moments of exquisite film, well filmed, beautifully built and very beautiful invoice. The scene in which the pedophile enters the pool is, apart from an indisimulado shark Spielberg tribute, a magnificent detail of what Todd Field wants to count, and that he already noted in the overvalued in the room, the hypocrisy of the community, which defenestra the neighbor for the sake of safeguarding their State of life and morality that carried about when what they are witnessing is an exhibition they of sins that laceran. Ultimately, Field even dares to draw the profile of pedophile in a more humane way (great actor Jackie Earle Haley) to put on the table the labyrinth of emotions of those who assume the right to prosecute others. Very revealing is, at this level of things, the scene in which the Group of housewives who love literature houses sit down to discuss Madame Bovary when we know (perhaps knows all) that Sarah is Emma and who are evaluating is herself.The movie suffers by the little finesse when it comes to drawing the conjugal portrait of two marriages: there is a clear vision of what they are experiencing. The slight drops of information we are given are not enough. Field is not the seasoned director that I would like the film to explain much with the minimum elements. However, it not fragmenting that now already announced as a voice to listen to in the American cinema.These sleepwalkers characters that roam a neighborhood of green porches and plácido well-being, say little maturity so that you can deposit on his shoulders the difficult task of educating their children. None cares about that.In the end, a series of calamities that now is not necessary to disclose lead to all addressing his Vertigo, its inertia to throw away because they want to aspire to be more happy or expressed more conveniently, to find happiness anywhere else because in the living have not found a life.A voice in off impostada and false uncomfortable too, but not Field abused. The problems of Hispanic dubbing made that we imagine Kevin Costner behind the voice. I promised, at that time, wherever possible, return to that custom mine see original movies with their subtitles, but that's another story.A tone more indie than the top American Beauty (whose screenplay was much more than Yes), secret games is a great proposal to go to the movies, but not to leave as a castanets or to promise us to see her again after a while prudencial.addenda: went to see the room nothing more complete these secret games. It has similar features, but the intentions are others. The first film of Todd Field is more raw, less lightness in the imprint of the characters. Recommended both and, luckily, huge easy to find in any video club room.</body>
</review>
