<review author="Iñigo" title="Inland empire" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>David Lynch is bringing to the true David Lynch: the new film has spawned.</summary>
	<body>Are not few those who say that David Lynch is you cannot only against a project: it desatará the box of Thunder, will do what your mind and your intuition dictate you, the universe itself will become a chaos where the slightest piece order will become a threat, Anatomy-spatial logic will be removed from the dictionarya new concept of cinema will emerge even.That is, neither more nor less, what has made the genius of Montana. It shattered completely celluloid, considered according to him "a dinosaur" slow and heavy, and it has reinvented itself all entered judgment creating a new stage (necessary and future) "film".Digital freedom that both worships the prolific filmmaker notes, and in what way, "INLAND Empire". Their personal traits, their non-transferable items, everything what characterized the Lynch film seen here transported to its maximum expression. Ago, for the first time, he really wants to do.Even more. Exceeds all limits of expressions. He becomes the classifiable (which was already little part of his film) unclassifiable. Born the metacine, the film within the film, movies in the movies. The film is life, life is cinema. And it arrives the moment in which it is impossible to discern which is which.Therefore, this new movie will largely increase (if possible) the gap between the followers/analytical Lynch film and those who do not understand their behaviour or despise him: those who see in his recent work an anthological joke or an obvious insertion in the world of hard drugs.Now, that gap is insurmountable. It unsettles or wonder. This is the end.But never him has gone head to the good of Lynch, and not intended to take the hair. Maybe the only thing that makes is parody of itself. And, in the same way, it embeds many details that serve as a reference to his previous film. Gives the impression that farewell something, probably your 35 mm, to make way for a new life: the digital life. An era which starts very unevenly, even with hope, joy, or messing.There are allusions, as I have said, to "Road lost", to "Mulholland Drive", to "Twin Peaks", even moments necessarily deepen as "Darkened Room" or "Rabbits".It is go much further than "Mulholland Drive", introduce himself, through an enormous Laura Dern, on Hollywood Boulevard to terrify him, breaking with their reality and their fears.Through narrow, dark, oppressive corridors (remember extensively to the "Lost Highway"), the search for oneself will be undertaken. The actress in search of the person. The person looking for the actress. And without knowing how or when, both will be merged being impossible to return to reality or identify her.There are certain issues that seem to recall to the "Videodrome" by Cronenberg, but here all those details will be swallowed up by the universe of Lynch, understanding the mystery better than the same Hitchcock brought beyond the border between good and evil, between madness and sanity: between fiction and the substantivity.Without influencing the script (or relativity of the same), what makes here Lynch is kill the film, kill an era in which there is no complicity between director and spectator, between dream and life, between mystery and Rapture, between death and rebirth.Arises what was once, what should have resurfaced some time ago. The path to the real meaning of the big screen.You can sit, overwhelm you, stop the heart with the brutal tension, try to find the mystery and sense, vanish you, let you carry, interpret, let him do, cry, illusion you, break you, terrorize you. You can look at that huge screen and see you reflected, discover the new life within life, know that the protagonist are only you and that salvation will be subject only to you.It is, in fact, what happens to the film. Everything depends on us, that we are not mere Guinea Pigs subject to laughter easy, waiting in the purgatory of the fable, discreet hideaway of the infierno.¿Ser or not to be? Have or not have? Blasfemias.David Lynch, ignoring those who branded the work as complex madness, gives a new meaning (lost to the "INLAND EMPIRE") to film. It gives life to the film. He sacrifices himself with a knife in the stomach, so it forcibly vomits to engender the seventh modern (and ancient) art.David Lynch, the only genius in life, creates the first latent in our big screen masterpiece: its artistic peak.</body>
</review>
