<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Paris je t'aime" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Beautiful postcards are confused with leaflets without value in the mailbox of the film memory. They are the consequences of meeting a challenge so attractive as heterogeneous.</summary>
	<body>Beautiful postcards are confused with leaflets without value in the mailbox of the film memory. They are the consequences of meeting a challenge so attractive as heterogeneous.The challenge, surpassed by far was to bring together two dozen filmmakers and convince them that each one had to shoot a short story? 5 minutes?, with Paris as the background. The theme was free, it was enough to have relationship with love in any of its forms: desire, passion, selfishness, loss, memory, etc. A contribution to further glorify if the most romantic city in the world, with permission of Venecia.Por should be what we see, those responsible for whether the pearls were short, and that the collective work reaches the 120 minutes. In this drawer find everything from elaborate stories, such as those who sign the Cohen brothers unsurpassed Steve Buscemi - and Tom Tyker - Natalie Portman again in State of grace - until some that another joke camouflaged as cinematic experiment. The end result is more than acceptable and even with the most tasteless episodes managed to entertain us. To stay with good taste after taste all the candies of the Pack? I already say that some aftertaste is us antojará stranger than others-, not go into issues of marketing and originality, because this city, like New York, has inspired this type of containers. An example with sequel is seen Paris by. premiered in 1964 and more than one you will remember to 40 filmmakers involved in Lumière and company, although the link is different.When you leave the film will pass through his mind the faces of Juliette Binoche, Elijah Wood, Nick Nolte, Sergio Castellito, Fanny Ardant, Maggie Gyllenhaal. Also for those of others to which we have no name, such as the occasional tourist who writes an essay on the Paris that has been. Memory is selective, and only some pieces, survive to oblivion as the epilogue of Alexander Payne, loaded with irony, Isabel Coixet, Fable fall better or worse, but it is an excellent storyteller, and the signed by Walter Salles, the more moving parts.By the way, that the "pieces" not him carried error: is not a puzzle because there is to eat the coconut, just enjoy, muddle of scents contained in small jars.</body>
</review>
