<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="3º colder" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting exercise posed from a minimalist approach, the choice about what is most important, love or be loved.</summary>
	<body>Interesting exercise posed from a minimalist approach, the choice about what is most important, love or be loved.Until the action progresses we feel a bit lost and one, which has already experienced it, recommended that be swayed. Only thus you will enjoy to the maximum of this curious and attractive display of intimate film.Almost everything is disconcerting: its inception, on a lonely Beach in the Basque country, grasping a possible ending or a home, but far from seem a predictable story this German film is presented as a peculiar composition for several reasons: do not get many Germanic productions, has signs of sociological experiment to introduce an element strange (but not both) in a "quiet" routine and gestures and urban landscapes prevail in a reality of few words.If I had to search similarities with other titles we recurriríamos the consequences of love Italian and Uruguayan Whisky, although more for the atmosphere than by sentimental polygons that form. Got something that is President and conveys a sense that invites you to think in the lucky star and they are sea, undressed the Iberian accent and colder, in particular "3 degrees less", making case of his translation into Castilian.One of its greatest wealth - and has many that we will leave you to discover - can be found in performers, able to sustain eyes in close-up: the camera seems to extract the deepest feelings. The ground where operate does not seem hostile but strange, which dispenses with unnecessary; for example look at the city that seems deserted and exclusive for the puppet outlined and manipulated by the still unreleased film in our country.Be honest and seeing the devouring desire of the Billboard, the future of tape is cold as its title. A pity, because that is made with feeling, containment and correction, qualities that overlook too many filmmakers to reinforce in the halls, obviously with the unconditional support of the public.</body>
</review>
