<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>?Little Miss Sunshine? It is a very well-intentioned film as caramel, friendly style, absolutely revolutionary. Conservative? A little, Yes. But I like the aroma of deep, although alternative America and a both freak like that?Can sideways?, for example.</summary>
	<body>Reading the Ideal of this morning, eve of the Oscar ceremony, a lapidary phrase came to define perfectly to this picture that takes months and months in poster: "The Oscar is big".A truth as a castle. This intimate and friendly "Little Miss Sunshine", yet tender and kind, is not comparable to movies as solvents and scope, "Babel" or "Infiltrators". It is a nice and tender, funny at times and melancholy film on other occasions, but is not, even remotely, this masterpiece, this great movie that must pass to posterity as winner of Oscar Recapitulemos. In a lost village in the United States.UU. a somewhat dysfunctional family must embark on a journey to California time trial to involve the Benjamin in a pathetic child beauty pageant. And there are, in a filthy van, failed father convinced that success can be achieved through a manual of self-help of his invention, the hippie grandfather, drug addict and more vast than panties of esparto, lucid and realistic mother, frustrated intellectual and suicidal uncle and the teenager in permanent rebellion against everything and everyone. And, of course, the girl, ugly and gordita, but with personality and desparpajo. The film tells the relationships between them, you tense sometimes, loving others. And raises a caramel criticism against the tyranny imposed by society towards the thinness and beauty, by ratifying the politically correct speech that beauty is inside and that the really important thing, is to feel good with yourself, ignoring the canons of beauty defended by magazines, fashion, cinema and television.With a Marxist end, the style of the anarchic and surrealists brothers, that leaves you with a pleasant smile on the lips, "Little Miss Sunshine" is a film as well-intentioned as caramel, friendly style, absolutely revolutionary. Conservative? A little, Yes. But I like the aroma of deep, although alternative America and a both geek, as that "between glasses", for example. A movie that we assume will not win the Oscar, but sees with pleasure and sympathy. Neither more nor less.</body>
</review>
