<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Wicker man" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Scruffy version of a classic that I do not know: has the (huge) merit of making me want to see the old. It will be a gem. This weakens for many minutes, but in the end, weighing pros and cons, we give an acceptable opinion.</summary>
	<body>The wicker man is housed in the modern flood of remakes billed some irrefutable classic beside or on the nostalgia of an icon of the series B. After viewing, ranging from the intrigue to the disbelief in a few minutes, have entered me a huge desire to dig on some store shelves stocked the original work, English, from 1973, filmed by Robin Hardin.Esta second release confirms the idea that, on occasions, we should leave things as they are exceeding all the efforts of these people (Nicholas Cage)(dull as usual, involved included producer) focuses on this curious scribe and other kind readers take the old film and her devoremos to see what went wrong Neil Labute, cultural agitator in this telefilm luxury and erstwhile director of really interesting tapes as chasing Betty and in the company of men.A policeman traumatized by the death of a mother and daughter on the road while he has been able to avoid it suffers a huge depression which is suddenly released when he receives a letter from a former girlfriend who asks that he go to a coastal island in the Pacific (Summerslide) to look for his daughter, who then turns out to be bothIt has disappeared. The island is a community that lives under a Matriarchy magical, subject to a number of laws unrelated to the civilized logic of the police. Pagan rituals and a very precise hierarchy of religious type confuse the police until the final outcome, which has an interest and we are not going to gut canallamente here.The downside of The Wicker man is that the end is predictable from the first minutes. Still feel admiration for that kind of films which entangled the argument to the point that one feels at the end idiot by having not seen before, say. Everything is clear, even if there is an unpublished point (mild, predictable one also for sharper than my own minds) that raises the overall impression a few points. Very meritorious (artistic and evocative of worlds that the movie still looking for them, curiously, not recreating) the location of foreign (an island in the Bay of Vancouver near the border with the United States.)UU. ) and the photography of Paul Sarossy.El role of Ellen Burstyn (the supposed Queen Bee of the community) is laughable as it also is the final scene in which everything starts again, although we (viewers already posts a day of intrigue and the perverse machinery of these mystical Amazon) already know where it leads and with what untapped modes.</body>
</review>
