<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Más extraño que la ficción" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The essence of his mastery lies in an original argument transmitted through a good script, and something that makes it even more worthwhile, is not based on any novel.</summary>
	<body>I know that it was released more than one month ago but due to a series of job changes, already I can not go to press releases for which, as any mortal, I should put me in the conventional cinema, while I organize my time, so I saw this film a month after its premiere and, frankly, seemed so extraordinary to me it would be difficult not to mention him.The essence of his mastery lies in an original argument transmitted through a good script, and something that makes it even more worthwhile, is not based on any novel. It is why I am not going to reel off the magic of history and, moreover, I recommend not to see the trailer. Directly, arriesguensen and go to the movies.Not to Sin from selfish, let me give some clues, rattled with "The Truman show"?, they enjoyed with "forget me!"? If the answer is Yes, and they have not seen yet, "Stranger than fiction", run because, as it is often the case in many cinemas, good thing not always last long (in Madrid only a room that expose, the rest go you know). Anyway, we will always the legal vacuum when the bad distribution prevents us pay for what we buy (you will tell me, that after several weeks looking for the CD soundtrack without any result, I saw forced to type on my computer and voilà! morphed appeared?)I only stay to make one point, do you know what I liked the movie? Something very simple: the protagonist is realized that he was alive, and then became a hero. I would like to try to explain that feeling to different grey midgets that have passed my lifetime (companions of work, ex-boyfriend, acquaintances?) but it would be impossible, and you know why? Because most are zombies and want to remain so; they prefer to have a mediocre life but smoothly. That is why that give you the congratulations to all the Harold Crick who have the courage to say what they feel, goes for them.</body>
</review>
