<review author="Vsancha" title="Bosque de sombras" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting exercise film whose greatest sin is obvious references to which does not stand in the comparison of a script full of shadows.</summary>
	<body>The interesting thing about the film in Spain industry comes mostly from the world of the short, where you can find interesting, original and risky, works thanks largely to the same format. Mismamente tonight two of them fighting for the Oscar and would not be unreasonable tomorrow see open the news one of them lifting the coveted statuette. They are several authors who have made the leap to the film and with good results, already saw him last year with Sánchez Arévalo and his Azuloscurocasinegro one of the most acclaimed national films by criticism and the public. And soon we will have the much-anticipated works of Nacho Vigalondo; "The Cronocrimenes". Recently it has come to us, with quite some delay in distribution, "Bosque de sombras", opera prima of an SUV in the world of the film, Koldo Serra and was presented at the previous festival of San Sebastian. it is perceived from the outset, this is a tape full of filmic influences, smells like cinema of the 1970s and moves away from the prototype of cinema that is lately. From the opening credits to the "Grupo Salvaje" until their development much reminiscent of films such as "Deliverance" or "Straw dogs", influences that the author always has recognized, until his band sound with the great Leonard Cohen.Resulta rather than surprising to see an actor of the stature and experience of Gary Oldman in a draft of a first-time unknown to the general publichis performance as well as sharing the whole is more than correct and they do that their roles are credible. The direction of Koldo laudable and exemplary narrative pulse. Very good photography, but his big problem is history itself, the "leitmotiv" that moves the characters themselves (some of them poorly developed) and that they trigger the exaggerated maelstrom of violence doesn't work, is lost easily and hard you to find due to the approach of situations too forced. The outcome of the film is quite failed because it reaches a point that doesn't know how to give the final thrust.Koldo Serra was clear what I wanted to do in his first feature film, wanted to translate his cinematic influences in this tale of incommunicado detention and violence entitled "Forest of shadows" where there are too many shadows in a widely dispersed script. We welcome various proposals in the Spanish film and is first and foremost a film entertaining and recommended but failed in its definition. What if it becomes clear after seeing her is that we have a filmmaker with a future for a while.</body>
</review>
