<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Inland empire" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A history of Soviet rabbits in a world without ratings. Someone understand me? Here is the deep substrate of this problem.</summary>
	<body>Inland empire is a bluff, a sidereal fly in an ashtray of foam, a beautiful psychedelic fish drowned in a juice of amphetamines, a superlative adjective in a text without possible outcome, a song by Philip Glass (of the most thick and unaffordable) in a reventona Tavern of retirees. Inland empire is David Lynch in its purest form. Recently I wrote here a little text on the things of the Lynch friend when it is proud of its creativity and dares to go, naked, hair, the secrets of the art. At this point, I do not know if the journey has been satisfactory. In my case, thinking only in my rejoicing as a spectator, has not been any recommended trip. And that this good man has made me spend pleasant moments, júbilos much height with some of his films. Here too there are a (necessarily brief) comment to his Blue velvet, but this Inland empire is something else: something of a slower chewing and a confusion of more systematic because when Lynch decided to confuse us there is no doubt that is going to get it. Off, we fail to elucidate reasons which includes only his reason.I have no desire to disrupt alien curiosity as well that I am not going to gutting the argument. Nor do I have the certainty that could. I don't know in what state of trance narrative to be to matching the appropriate verbs, with fair adjectives that life a synthesis, a synopsis or as you want to say.His generous footage gives for wanting to leave or want to last one hour, according to the spirit. We were then in that this film is a challenge to our patience or a gift for our Kinky masochism. I have read comments on the net that give complete information (place, designed, exquisitely notarized) on the film and others that, fortunately, allied with my disappointment or my perplexity.Inland empire (will and finalized) deserves equal revisionado. As some Dreyer's or the more robust and staff Cronenberg films. Scarcely matter to leave Laura Dern (that are thirty women in one or not is no woman and everything is a poetic twisting of our mind-blowing mind) or my very dear (except in Eragon and some another trip to the watered-down film of primary school pupils) Jeremy Irons.Lo I have very clear is the tremendous game facing the boring blogger Lynch (today with rings by the time sensationalism of the Oscars) or responsible for movie buff who wants toto despite the inconveniences, give always and everywhere a message clear, sharp, decodeable.I I am abstaining: I arrobo the legitimacy of not to speak. That you think others. Or this is an opinion: the unique, perhaps. Everything else is an exercise tightrope of sins not cleaned, women on the verge of an attack of Lynch, rather.I promise that I will see it shortly with a less contaminated mentality. If it is possible. And write (as God or Billy Wilder mandan) another entry in my page, another review on this every day more complete page of cinema in the network. For the benefit of inventory movie buff. The world is strange.</body>
</review>
