<review author="Mala Besta" title="El grito 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A mechanical scares movie, recommended to all those who have already seen and liked.</summary>
	<body>The villains in horror movies and much scare have always had a brand, an object, a sound that makes them distinctive, and announces his presence when it suits. Freddy had his glove of long nails, dragged by the most annoying places: blackboards, crystals, the guts of Johnny Depp. Jason had his hockey and Leatherface mask another mask more in keeping with its name. "The bad"Scream 2"to frighten their victims appears that he grabs a bottle of soda, because his appearances are announced with a sound that I swear that me reminds me a burp of terrifying have no much, less, clear, that he has eaten in a Mexican."The cry 2 "belongs to one of the last great franchises in the world of cinema. Great because it appears to extend without end. So in short, and without adding books, comics and other derivatives paper that cleaned, there are out there, two Japanese films, "The curse" and "The curse 2" which in turn have their American versions, "The scream" and, by the same director of the original, but without sharing more than the characters and rancid special effects. And for 2008, the third part of the American branch of the saga, which "Scream 2" threatens to an end (that I might add, rather than an end seems a trailer). All deliveries more or less share the lightness of the history, and this is not less. Of course, that in this case, rather than lengthen it to base of repeating over and over again, the same scares get fill the 100 minutes multiplied by three.The film details the lives of Karen (Sarah Michelle Gellar) and her sister Aubrey (Amber Tamblyn), who has gone to fetch her to Japan after the terrifying events of the first part. On the other hand we have Allison (Arielle Kebbel), Miyuki (Misako Uno) and Vanessa (Teresa Palmer) that do not have anything else better to do that go the House cursed to spend the time and finally specifics to Trish (Jennifer Beals), that thirty seconds of projection you a.6 a sartenazo in the head to her husband (Christopher Cousins) and then eats some fried eggs. Obviously, all frames are related among themselves and with the previous installments, as we shown hastily at the end, with a thousand cuts, flashback, flashforward, Flash Gordon and others. The rest of the time are quite waterproof among themselves, and could well have turned into three manageable chapters of a series, rather than a film that is made longer to the viewer that the characters; Finally and after half of them died at half footage.Each of these chapters is arguably quite poor, with characters who more than anything else are there so that the viewer has something to entertain between scares. In addition, perhaps the saturation of similar films, but "Scream 2" has moments that seem completely copied from "Ringu", or similar. The largest contribution of this installment to the series appears to be that it deepens something in the origin of the curse that feeds all the films, incidentally, is like an episode of "MacGuiver" or "The A team"; We all know what will make the characters and how going to end all, the only question is how and when encerrarán them at a hardware store.Visually it maintains the style of the series; While the years pass and increasing the budget, is still that the fearsome vengeful Ghost is the son of director in pajamas, while it is true that it has moments desasosegantes, they lose a little in the large number of intentions to scare coup Orchestra and screeching noise, that end up tired.The interpretations are quite routine, inherent in this type of film. Lot of career, far cry, much hiperventilarse. Highlights about the other Matthew Knight, who plays the son of Jennifer Beals, and that day make a biopic of Gary Oldman could well interpret it.Finally, a mechanical film scares, recommended for all those already they have seen and liked him.</body>
</review>
