<review author="Mala Besta" title="Voces en la noche" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Somewhat flojilla but compensates with its duration, which is appreciated at a time in which even ads spend two hours. Recommended for listeners of?Talk to mention?</summary>
	<body>Seems to be an axiom in the world of cinema that says that all the films in which Robin Williams comes out with a beard are good, and all that comes without beard are "The Bicentennial Man". In "Voices in the night" Williams leads two-day beard.The film tells a simple story. A radio announcer homosexual, Gabriel (Robin Williams), whose programme reads his own stories, receive the daily manuscript of a boy of fourteen, Pete (Rory Culkin), which details the sexual abuse that has suffered during his childhood. His social assistant and new mother adoptive Donna (Toni Collette) is recommended as therapy, and Gabriel is so impressed by the book a telephone friendship that engage. But one day the boyfriend of the announcer begins to suspect that Donna and Pete may be the same person, so Gabriel begins the investigation. The succinct script, with very few characters and barely the hour and a half, is in general quite care. While dressing thriller, mona stays, and except for very specific moments there is never a sense of restlessness or suspense about the fate of the protagonist. That Yes, manages to always maintain the interest until you reach the end, which is a little disappointing, mainly because it's not too inconclusive, and given that the film not looks much cry by a sequel, is not well understood which is the objective of an open end.Is true that the movie is based on a real event, and I guess that it is why he pretend to be faithful to the same, but it is film, not a news. If Michael Moore do what pleases with reality, I do not know why Patrick Stettner not could have taken a license or two to give a little more than packing to the last minutes of "Voices in the night".The visual style of the film is much appreciated. A very upscale scenes and a pretty well-kept compositions, especially in treatment of light it regards. So much that as the minutes go through and the plot is picking up some slightly darker dyes, so also does the lighting, and there comes a time when it seems that all levels are illuminated by a match. Sometimes it is suggestive and others, simply do not see a cucumber.The weight of the film falls almost altogether on Robin Williams and Toni Collette. Williams meets to perfection; far from "Patch Addams", its interpretation is quite restrained and also the character is quite adequate, with that air of fragility and these kilillos has caught with a detoxification cure. Toni Collette, on the other hand, despite not being a bad actress, has a character too complex, and that also have given a somewhat ridiculous teeth, what removed you enough realism to their interpretation. Sandra Oh is also passed by the film, but nor is long or paints much either.Finally, a somewhat flojilla movie but it compensates with its duration, which is appreciated at a time in which to ads spend two hours. Recommended for listeners of "Loose talk".</body>
</review>
