<review author="Plissken" title="Inland empire" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Once again, among the joke and the feeling of seeing something unique. Hate the Lynch film because strives too not tell me nothing and irritate me. I admire the artist Lynch because it is able to take me three hours reacting against his work.</summary>
	<body>Background: 'The Elephant Man', 'Blue Velvet', 'Twin Peaks' and 'Wild heart' I loved, 'Mulholland Drive' me outraged. A couple of years later, I reconcilié with his film thanks to overdose: 'Eraserhead' and 'Lost Highway' at a stroke. David Lynch I like Nice, but I do not share his relationship with the Viewer. It entered the projection of 'Inland Empire' ready, once again, to be challenged and defeated.What he believed would be: Nikki Grace is an actress in decadence that gets a role in a film with Devon, a young actor with a reputation of womanizer. Just at the beginning of the trials, they discover that they have embarked on the remake of a damn movie, especially for its protagonists. Nikki begins a search for his own identity through a threatening oneiric maze.What in the end told me: schizophrenic filmmakers, sitcoms of rabbits, whores and a circus Internet theatre and full of Poles will compete out of favor with the audience of the century XXl. alien to the fight, Lynch descojona of all of us in its "Inland Empire" which gives its name to the film. Or there is this or nothing, which in the case is the same.David Lynch demonstrates, once again, be more "mainstream" filmmaker and best challenges the intelligence (and patience) of the Viewer. Three hours of continuous chaos, a spiral of climax that are happening, one after another, from approximately the film 20 minute. Until that time, Lynch develops do narration? that it only serves to give an overview and some peace of mind to turn investors. Later, and supported in his new toy, digital video, the Missoula returns to his subjects, his obsessions, and again, more than ever to strive in annihilating all possible narrative. It exempt from the need to "tell"?Inland Empire? It is able to fascinate with the strength of a glorious Laura Dern in the proximity that the video gives to this new nightmare, with the overwhelming power of the masterful use of sound and music. Is Lynch in its freer and less film since, perhaps?Eraserhead?.And out there, is precisely where the viewer can find their particular exit to atmospheric terror of?Does Inland Empire?: Lynch, in the background, does not want anything, just evoke feelings, moods. Have you on the edge of the seat. He has perhaps never wanted to have much (unless paid you for it). Yes, is very aware of its almost mythical dimension, and this is able to laugh himself, of his filmography to the full and the spectator, critical included. If you survive to his almost insufferable Hermeticism, 'Inland Empire' is very entertaining, and even fun.Do short, Lynch requires all your attention, your intelligence and your patience for? have a bad time. Later, the lights are lit, and you're next to someone that is familiar to you, and you wonder to yourself about what you've lived (in silence, no one knowing that you've understood nothing), and what you've lived can not be measured in numbers, stars, or anything like, decide to keep you quiet and not say anything until you get home and look in the network the interpretations of others to the that you've lived. At least, you are not alone in your confusion. Once again, among the joke and the feeling of seeing something unique.Hate the Lynch film because strives too not tell me nothing and irritate me. I admire the artist Lynch because it is able to take me three hours reacting against his work, chills or clean laugh. A 2 for the film, a 8 for the work. I do not know if I explain: go to see her and believes.</body>
</review>
