<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Juegos secretos" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Inspire in that they inspire, Todd Field has a unique, special movie, cuativadora, sensitive and atrapadora.</summary>
	<body>I love this kind of movies that seem to be one thing and end up becoming another, wholly or partially different. With Little Children (or secret games, if the preferéis) is exactly the same. The promotion made about the movie was excellent hand, but on the other hand, empty, as it only seemed to address an issue: the love triangle. Although fortunately the bestial Todd Field film is much more than that: it is a choral, intimate, strange, frightening and exciting film.What stands out most is the wonderful script, based on the novel by Tom Perrota and written by this same and director. Perhaps the only thing that takes away points in favor (very few) is already directed by Sam Mendes-American Beauty in which, rather than inspire, takes note of it, without copying it at any time, clear. But there is also another thought, is that secret games as a reference (at times) to the novel by Cheever, Madame Bovary (which was mentioned during one of the best parts of the movie). Inspire in that they inspire, Todd Field has a unique, special movie, cuativadora, sensitive and atrapadora. One of the most interesting resources of the script is that magnetic and quasi perfect voice-over, which leads to the film until they almost disappeared, so that we see with our eyes, the fatal outbreak of an outcome, which will soon be "helped" by this mysterious voice. So I have to congratulate his writers for work impeccable, worthy of veterans, although Field is not.If the secret games script is wonderful, we would say that the direction close to perfection. Yes, it seems that me is going on with the movie, but it is what to me has seemed: practically, a masterpiece. Minimalist and overwhelming at the same time, the direction of Todd Field manages to catch us with an incredible force up let us facts powder once completed the film. Not only that, but the splendid and original montage accompanies the film to be precise, exact. It has, the movie, a couple or three of really impressive sequences, as the swimming pool, the park or the aforementioned discussion on the novel Madame Bovary. It is precisely these scenes which enrich the film and make it be perfectionist, unique. As I said earlier, this is a choral film, in which, apart from a love triangle (narrated with an incredible pulse), appear stories of a pedophile (the best of all of them, no doubt) and a retired policeman who hides a terrible past. These three interesting stories of inhabitants of a neighborhood of medium class of Massachusetts combine unexpectedly reaching a child conclusion (in the good sense, although only entendedor if the film has been) where more than one life collides in extravagant way.There was not, at least for me, best title to Little Children to this movie. As you come to understand during the footage, adults behave like their own children, or of a child way and without much sense (tuned to the scene of the station with Patrick Wilson). SPOLIER LIGHT! This moral to reach to fully understand one time ends the film, when the protagonists reject their dreams and ambitions to return with what they have more security (their children, in this case). And behold, probably one of the best quotes of the film (the daughter of Winslet's intentándo soothe his mother, what should be the other way around). END OF THE SPOLIER.Interpretations of secret games could be a synonym of prodigious. Perhaps this film with best performances from Crash, which I find some similarities (SPOLIER!!!!) (Emmerich helping Haley or Dillon helping Newton), the cast is absolutely credible, sensational, close. Although, in all of them, would highlight the immense Kate Winslet, the best role of her career, which seems more a girl that not an adult; Jackie Earle Haley, an interpretation that is outstanding, perfect, terrifying and painful. Perhaps the best role of the film, since it had been never before treated a pederast with such depth; Noah Emmerich, where especially shines in the denouement of the film; Phyllis Somerville as the mother of the paedophile, in a tremendously appealing role, because very few times had been the family of a child molester in a film, and the truth is that it is arguably tragic. They highlight not so much, interpretations of Patrick Wilson and Jennifer Connelly are also great, but perhaps do not reach the perfection of the other roles are somewhat more empty.In short, he claimed that secret games rubs the master being one of the best films of the year early. Some may have another detail that is a both failed, as the speed and excessive hectic that is used in the outcome, but this is just to mention something "bad". I did not see in the room (the previous and first film of Todd Field), but there is no doubt that, having seen this wonder, me the I think rent at least. An absolutely incredible film.</body>
</review>
