<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Eastwood has specialized in the death of a masterfully touching, exciting, thoughtful way, so raw as poetically realistic and mature. Thanks, Clint, for continue giving birth masterpieces.</summary>
	<body>My brother asked me if, to see and enjoy "Letters from Iwo Jima", it is necessary to have previously seen "Flags of our fathers" given that, as it is known and notorious, Clint Eastwood has shot two different, both films inspired by the same facts.And the answer is that not. To enjoy that piece of masterpiece undisputed, lucid and exciting (to not sentimental) that is "Letters from Iwo Jima" is not necessary to have seen the previous, but is highly recommended to see the two as both are feedback one to the other, complement each other, they speak to each other, something of what discussed in another article.On this occasion, to tell the Japanese point of view on events in Iwo Jima, Eastwood Yes has filmed a strict and canonically war film with the particularity that, for once, the "good guys" are those Japanese who often were the bad guys. I entrecomillo about "good" because, as in every war movie self-respecting, the border between the hero and the villain must be tenuous enough as so things do not end in a pamphlet.And in that sense, the last film of Eastwood continues to be exemplary. Starring Ken Watanabe in State of grace, that manages to breathe your character all the grandeur, melancholy, decision and abatement that it requires, "Letters from Iwo Jima" shows, fears, hopes, fears, the flatulence, the cagaleras, laughter and tears that prevent a handful of young soldiers who, simplythey have done a bitch calling rows. Although it is by comparing with the already referential "Saving private Ryan", a film if foster kinship this "letters from Iwo Jima" is with the terrible "paths of glory" by Stanley Kubrick, with whom he has many points in common, above all, when it comes to denounce the injustice, the foolish and the mental closure of both military with the uploaded gallons of the bib to the blunt.Eastwood tells of a society, rigid and hierarchical, which faded shouting Banzai! to possibly not return to reappear anymore. Speaks of ideals of the samurai, of temperance, resignation to misfortune, of heroism, the Picardie cowardice. and through the characters of general Kuribayashi and his junior Olympic rider, speaks of the absurdity of a struggle facing people who were once friends, colleagues and supporters. Two sequences are especially foresight in this sense: that of the delivery to Kuribayashi a colt by some American servicemen that pay you homage before returning to Japan, told in flash back and, of course, of the Charter of the American soldier that is read aloud by one of the Japanese.With these cards, just like that with M$ B or without forgiveness, Eastwood has specialized in the death of a masterfully touching, exciting, thoughtful way, so raw as poetically realistic and mature. Thanks, Clint, for continue giving birth masterpieces.</body>
</review>
