<review author="Javier Saz" title="Inland empire" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>By the time a succession of images with sound not I had stuck in such a way to a seat, although during many moments I could not decipher the meaning of what he saw, the sensations and feelings were alive and intense.</summary>
	<body>On "Inland Empire" (2006) by David Lynch, first say that by the time that a sequence of images with sound not I had stuck in such a way to an armchair, although during many moments I could not decipher the meaning of what he saw, the sensations and feelings were alive and intense. I ardo in desire to see to make light in some shadows again, I am not able to do a story about the film by unfathomable and hermetic is on first viewing. "This would rather be sketches on the first time I saw"Inland Empire".""Inland Empire" is a film a contracorriente, far removed from the narrative convenional, cares more about creating sensations with the use of the image and the sound that tell us narrativamente a story (though ultimately her count). It could enter into the discussion if the film is a narrative means of expression or - as in this case - is an artistic medium that view (and cover) you philias and phobias, discussion in which I will not go for not seeing the sense.When I see a movie I want to convey me things, whether ideas or sensations, and if he does so through his plot, the putting in scene or for their performances lacks importance. And "Inland Empire" has transmitted me more things that much of the current Billboard, it conveys me fear, terror, insecurity, suspense, unreality, magic, film and art.There seems to be three narrative lines, that of actress Nikki Grace (Laura Dern), the character Susan Blue (Laura Dern) and the Polish history on which they are based, the three "stories" intersect, overlap, are doubles, are confused and converge, with a bold result and at times confusing. It may be the film more radical and sealed in forms and contents of Lynch, twinned with his debut in "Surrealist head".Lynch, after his nomination to the Oscar Award for best director at Cannes for "Mullholland Drive", is in a position to do what he wants and we are perhaps to his total work, although I can rush me.Lynch may be the current director best party brings to the sound as a narrative device. Mix of the video art, avant-garde and resources of both film narrative, visual as soundly. "Lost Highway" and "Mulholland Drive" appear to be simple sketches of this "Inland Empire".Film markedly sensitive, complex and full of autoreferencias is one of the movies that more afraid I have been seeing them, the nightmare of folly. Happily in the cinema there are still unexplored by cross roads, and this is a good example. (4) The note is also a stub. (4/4 +)</body>
</review>
