<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It seems that Eastwood learns from their mistakes and while in "flags..." the flashback came to bore the Viewer, here are counted righteous and fairly concise, and help to understand the character in question which has been.</summary>
	<body>I have always heard say that of "To adjudicate a lawsuit must listen to the 2 parties", seems that Eastwood applies this rule, and after "Flags of our fathers" now shows us the Japanese with this "letters from Iwo Jima" perspective, where with a careful monochrome photography (only highlights the Red of blood and the flag of the rising sun.)in this unusual film, released worldwide in V.O.S, and with one budget of even smaller than"flags" where advantage, not just decorated, but also some plans already filmed beforehand, is the reunion of Eastwood with the cinema of author, where one delves into the courage, courage and obedience of the Japanese soldier.On the other hand, inexpressiveness of many Japanese actors, found me little more than surprising, especially in the Eastern cinema, the "whole" are the faces of the protagonists, usually very expressive, here, the vast majority, except the great Ken Watannabe, suffer from this fact, and show the same expression whether rien, as if suffering.The band sound, simplistic, but effective, I was a masterful, already offer that we were one of the best scores of 2007, where with just a few chords, show few, to tell the truth, the poetic, the divine, and inhumanity (a war so is, for good or for evil.) of a military struggle.The plans with camera on his shoulder, in the most raw scenes of the battle, contribute, as it provided in "Flags." an almost documentary aspect, that is beginning to be "House brand", for the director; on the other hand, thank you less Gore that on the previous tape, showing only just enough to not traumatize us too.Perhaps, another of the negative parts of the tape is its excessive slowness, burdening in some moments the same too, and it is to these 144 min. projection become brutally heavy, especially at the end of the tape.It seems that Eastwood learns from their mistakes and while in"flags" the flashback came to bore the Viewer, here are counted, fair and fairly concise, and help to understand the character in question which has been.If I have to highlight a plane of all that I have seen, I prefer the latter, Mount Suribachi and the beach, to the rhythm of the soundtrack of the same, beautiful and sweet at the same time, showing the lives that were lost in that small piece of land.</body>
</review>
