<review author="Jose Contreras" title="La vida de los otros" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I know very well that the Stasi violated the privacy of the Germans, and I know that the mafia vendettas are perverse. But do not want a director between judging with his Catechism of values. I want a director that I penetrated in these Hells mojigatas uncensored.</summary>
	<body>Take for example the godfather. Any director of middling in charge of that history would have sentenced to Corelone, viewers learn to be good children, or that we will not conferred to him, the Director with the mafia. Coppola dares with the morlaco, is identified with the mafia until the end. It is one of the greats. Not because you choose chords beautiful on the soundtrack or place the camera on a place more chuli than others. It does not help anything continue reviewing the technical specifications of the Godfather hanging praise, we are not going to find the explanation that makes it so tremendous.This step gives Coppola is which does not give the German film. Hirschbiegel made a film about Hitler for the sole purpose of not understanding Hitler, Henckel von Donnersmarck analyzes a plot of the stasi with the sole intention of which we do not understand what I felt a stasi agent.An expert in espionage of the eastern Germany receives commissioned to monitor a theatre author and her lover. After click throughout the House the spy discovers that two victims of the system are in the background and that the Minister himself abused his power to obtain the favors of the woman. From that moment you change your attitude and collaborates with them.The problem is that since then the character ceases to have meaning. The character faces against the regime that keeps and the own work done, which sounds very good for a viewer today, but does not tell us anything about what happened in the Germany then. If the public were Catholic, the director would have filled the protagonist of crucifixes. It is somewhat quick to win over the audience. But lack the audacity that more than enough in the godfather. I know very well that the Stasi violated the privacy of the Germans, and I know that the mafia vendettas are perverse. But do not want a director between judging with his Catechism of values. I want a director that I penetrated in these Hells mojigatas uncensored.I liked the setting, this eastern Germany tristísima with wallpaper and worn sofas. The beginning is sublime. The protagonist explains his methods to a class to listen to an example of as becomes an interrogation and stays electrizada, as well as the public.</body>
</review>
