<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La vida abismal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Vacuous and relamido I contrived that not enough to entertain, although I get an interest in seeing how everything ends, it is something. The abyss was in the armchair.</summary>
	<body>Ventura Pons has seemed always a literary director and not because it is left to ruin a film by an excess of spoken prose but imagine there was a novel under the film and, in the majority of cases (I think now of Quim Monzó, a prodigious writer), a good novel. Not this is unfortunately the case. Pons pulls a work of Ferran Torrent which has crápulas of night the initiation of a young man in the environments. Then there are whores, people rogue and evil live. Or maybe this is the life and the rest are fringes, appendices, fillings. The virginal young opens this perverse catechism and squeezes it with willingness to learn in a short time what life given in years. This is the experience. Abysmal life disappointed by one more inconvenient mise en scene, which is not credible, that warns chapucera for more than the argument dazzles in loose scenes (perhaps the principle). I have not seen Oscar Jaenada making shrimp, but here he's troubled, confused, despistado, depressed, as the song of Hilario Camacho. He looks not taste and character is as wishing that the film ends. Chinese (so called) is back much, but the actor that gets us on screen not explicit: stays in an impertinent gestures and a face with intentions, although deadpan.Characters living to the limit not fill a movie by far that has what one means that there will be telling the story that we suspect we're going to have, but all agree to precarity when asked what passion (sickly if you want when items that recount are large and require big words or a desire to also great not ruin everything for not taking care of details). Comes now to the memory the (pathetic) scene of the Declaration of love with the French girl. If they put a trailer and give those scenes, does one film?Ventura Pons made the why of things (1993) and Anita noi loses the train (2000). Look for the gentle reader in some video store any one of them or both and you will see that there are ex officio and ways. The first love. Here there is no enchantment, nowhere near.</body>
</review>
