<review author="Taliesin" title="La vida de los otros" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The great stories are hidden in small acts of some men who discover that reality dislike.</summary>
	<body>True fans to the big screen already some time ago that they discovered that European cinema has a lot to offer, and between all signed productions in the old continent, the German films demonstrate the maturity of a cinema that is usually well above average productions. Goodbye Lenin, the Edukators or the lives of others are some samples. Which we are discussing today has won many international awards (among which is the best European film) and is not for nothing. The lives of others puts us in East Berlin at the beginning of the 1980s, when the police for the security of the State, the Stasi, kept an iron grip on what they did, they said and almost to what thought citizens.The protagonists are two men sentenced to not be found never face to face: on the one hand Georg Dreyman, a prestigious writer, pressed and favored by the party, not just write what you really want; by the other Gerd Wiesler, one of the best men of the Stasi: thorough, rigorous and seemingly devoid of any trait of humanity. But then happens something that breaks the delicate balance and cause Dreyman decides to break his silence, while Wiesler will begin to question their own convictions. The trio is completed with Christa-Maria Sieland, actress and couple of the writer which is partly trigger for change in both.The film also serves as a portrait of what was life in East Berlin harassed by the Stasi, to investigate practically any citizen to submit the minimum suspicions for activities considered illegal. From open correspondence and filling of tapping the homes of the investigated, through illegal detentions followed by endless interrogations. The pace is thriller, although there are touches of drama and even humor. Both the photography and soundtrack (in charge of Gabriel Yared) are exceptional and the interpretations of the actors only be described as magnificent. Stresses especially that of Ulrich Mühe in his role of the Stasi officer, which is a character who requires a sober work and built through small gestures.In summary, the lives of others is required viewing for those who enjoy the film, as he masterfully presents a story that mixes different elements in the end offers a very emotional film and left good feelings in the Viewer. Essential.</body>
</review>
