<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="V de Vendetta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Poorly lit, without rhythm, pretentious, with a few pathetic dialogues, failed, full of cliches, boring and even shameful in many moments</summary>
	<body>With both comics fan and both Geek Superhero in the network, I much fear that this criticism I sent to hell for non-moderns and the anti-cools. But friends, I can't help but write that "V for Vendetta" to my seemed "truly a mierdetta" Yes, me I have not read the comic of Allan Moore, I hardly spent the "Mortadelos and filemones", "Spiderman", "Superlopez" and "Jabato", but no matter. I went to the cinema and tried to entertain me without instruction manual.What I found was an uncle pedantic, escaped from gatherings of Garci, disguised as a Fox and a mask. A film pretentious, poorly lit, without rhythm, with a few pathetic dialogues, failed, full of cliches, boring and even shameful in many moments.As action movie, am disappointed. Too little chicha and anything novel. (The lovers of films about authoritarian futures with a good accióncoreografiada "Matrix" style, I recommend "Equilibrium".)As a superhero movie, anda closer "Catwoman", "Daredevil" or "Scooby-Doo", that of "Superman", "Darkman", "The Raven", "Batman" or company. Special effects do not feature at all. The camera work and the Mise en scene is little more than regularcita, flooded flat media and short, with machines of smoke on the side working without rest and offering general whiff to study. As I said before, you cannot find a look original or novel, despite having sent to paint everything what appears in grey and black screen. "Sin City", bet much more boldly, for instance just to the other side.As for the music. buff. even I prefer before the musical call techno of "Blade".The actors, well, inform that Natalie Portman is also very good with such shaved hair and Sidney Oconnor. John Hurt is always very angry and a TV and others, basically, passing out there. The love story is stuck at the end all, of obliquely and is not believe nor the screenwriter, director, nor the Wachowski brothers in the production.History is an assortment of intentions, a pastiche from "beauty and the beast", "The Fox", "the Phantom of the opera", "The fight club", "The count of Monte Cristo", any of the numerous existing and less original on authoritarian future productions, and "Bamby". Come on, silly.Everything is predictable, languid and almibarado. Everything is so incredibly absurd, so unlikely and so inexpensive boring, some scenes are up comic without trying it. As the shameful escenita hesprecióoooon and all those other numerous flashbacks which catapulted us shame others, without any mercy, levels in which we discovered, suddenly, in the film pressing strong, very strong teeth. And where on top, so they give us everything ridiculously masticadito. Or as all those scenes where the visual prima always on common sense and reason, and where Moreover, if it cannot explain already nothing else then because not matter.Moments such as where there is to believe so, without more, that that gentleman, disguised by obligation, and in search and capture in a militaristic, dictatorial and police state, manages to manufacture 300,000 masks and layers, and, in addition, send also to each particular House, every Office and den of England alone, without removing the mask and without that caught it. Or having to watch as our fellow countryman entertains forming a figurine that draws its logo V-shaped with the help of 10,000 piececitas of Domino (that told them), to only then topple remain alone, in the best style "dominoday", and for his unique jamaipanese enjoyment. And so everything, one after another, gentlemen. And Yes, already is that black guy is supposedly a hero, and there is always a certain amount of fantasmada in these films, but here, many times these acts have also a weight specific to the central plot. It causes neither more nor less than a revolution, and I only would like to sell me the move more intelligently and Curran. (As in the "Club de Lucha", since you mentioned it before) But no, here there are only unexplained attacks without dead, in the style of precious Fireworks illuminating the balconies and under the music of Tchaikovsky. Just have at our disposal a cúmulode images and inconsistent actions and tramas fotocopiadas.¿Y as sold all this then? Well, because we add an attack in London and to be precisely on the subway, then talk a little pseudo-philosophically on the symbolism of overthrow representative buildings, four phrases more supposedly witty and style "the ideals are bulletproof," a little obliquely and another little bit of germ warfare, avian flu and then already everything is supposedly fashionable and also, we have to favour all a mass of incrédulosque believe and will defend this project as a modern, bold and innovative. In short, a complete disappointment of film. No wonder nothing to the two brothers of Matrix have decided, at the last minute, spongers is better his second Assistant. Can anything be done even worse than the aftermath of Matrix? Yes, friends, you can. Of course you can.</body>
</review>
