<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El buen alemán" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With the good German, Soderbergh paid cult to film noir par excellence, of the classic Hollywood studios.</summary>
	<body>Steven Soderbergh is a type of film that seems to have come out of the classic Hollywood by a tunnel of the time, not because of his style of leadership, or the stories that account, not even for his films itself. But for their ability to jump into the void with different and risky, projects of improvisation. Any current film is capable of making a film as Traffic, then Ocean? s Eleven, from there turn to an independent tape as Full Frontal, a futuristic thriller as Solaris? and thus a list longest ever. Only for this reason, all his work, until the more unlucky ones, have this so attractive aroma, and unfortunately so rare, classic cinema, cinema of truth.With the good German, Soderbergh paid cult to film noir par excellence, of the classic Hollywood studios, from which have emerged some of the greatest masterpieces of the history of cinema. Jacob Geismar (George Clooney), war correspondent, travels to Berlin to cover the momentous Summit in Potsdam which will decide the future of Europe and the world for the next half-century. Returning to the city in which he lived before the war, he reencontrará with his longtime girlfriend, Lena Brandt (Cate Blanchett), to discover that it hides an important secret, and that his driver, Tully (Tobey Maguire), is helping her. Based on the novel by Joseph Kanon, Steven Soderbergh recreates the atmosphere lived in post-war Berlin with great credibility and realism. A city marked by an increasingly more tense and unstable balance of power, in which each power seeks his own spoils of war, while the entire country faces trial winners and humanity. With that background, Paul Attanasio signed a solid script which is mixed with ability to intrigue, the political situation, and even romance. The script is a tribute to film noir, with a few good characters that appear to be taken from any classic 1950s: a hero, hard and lonely, that a resounding but contained George Clooney gives great uncertainty, as well as provide a variety of emotions, and la femme fatale, role that endorses a splendid and disturbing Cate Blanchett, in the style of Marlene Dietrich. Of the technical work, emphasizes that fantastic picture in black and white, as well as Assembly, both of the own Soderbergh, and the music by Thomas Newman. All these elements give the tape a greater aroma to classic movies, which is commendable and worthy of applause. Good German has numerous references to films such as the third man, and especially to Casablanca from the poster to the final scene, winks that can be seen as tributes or blatant copies, that item leave it in the view of the Viewer.The good German, in addition to being one of the most attractive proposals of the Billboard, serves to be reconciled with the commercial téoricamente of Hollywood cinema. It is also a fantastic excuse to enjoy with the great film noir titles.</body>
</review>
