<review author="Lady Winter" title="El buen alemán" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A plot of intrigues and passions without too much mystery and quite predictable that, despite everything, it is entertaining.</summary>
	<body>Steven Soderbergh is back with the good German, a failed homage to Casablanca. At this point in the film do something different in the film is virtually impossible. Casablanca was already shot, more than 60 years ago, and there is only one, as there is only a Borgart or an Ingrid Bergman. Try to compare the charismatic George Clooney with the nerve of Bogart may have a pass. But what is unforgivable is trying to make us believe that Cate Blanchett (Lady of ice) can have a shred of class, beauty and talent of the Bergman. Is true that Blanche comes as the character of cold German ring to the finger. Because this coldness in performance is precisely what characterized you (demonstrated in other movies like Babel or various of the rings). But his deadpan face does not transmit sensations or feelings, and therefore not fit for according to what roles. Despite all levels placed strategically so that the viewer wait to hear from one moment to another piano by Sam, the movie is not bad and may come to be regarded even innovative, by being shot to the old-fashioned. Ironic, isn't it?The good German is nothing more than a history of war, in which four vertices of a same square fight over succeed. Three men who love one woman, that handles them all to his own liking. Tobey Maguire is draws the meshes of the man Spider to become an American soldier that considers itself superior to all and is nothing more than a pardillo. Blanche is a German Jew from a dark past that must resort to prostitution during the war to be able to succeed after the disappearance of her husband, a skull privileged for the numbers to which both sides want in their power. And, finally, George Clooney, an American journalist who already shared bed with the girl in the movie before the war and returns to a bombing Berlin to make known to the world the signing of the peace that will mean the end of the second world war. A plot of intrigues and passions without too much mystery and quite predictable that, despite everything, it is entertaining. The best is, without doubt, Clooney, to which black and white I feel pretty good and makes him forget about his longtime role of mature interesting that served to launch to stardom. But Berlin stands out on all possible actions. A city coming down of which everyone wants to escape. The atmosphere is perfect and the way of filming to give more realism to the story requires a round of applause. Resource insert images taken from the documentary technique give this history of victims of war of a greater drama, although without being tear. This is perhaps the most unforgivable mistake, which there is no identification with any of the characters, as all seem too distant in time and space.</body>
</review>
