<review author="Lady Winter" title="The host" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An interesting and innovative Bong leads with good pulse and approach best eye cinematógrafico, that hooks quickly and offers, in addition to a good time, much think about what.</summary>
	<body>Imagínen a good morning a gruesome monster emerge from the sewers of the city and begins to Prime with our neighbours. "Nothing new under the Sun"? We think? "now come the special forces of the army, or a calloused and heroic police officer, or a giant robot that will save the day". That have become accustomed us the action and horror films. But here's the boy prodigy of the Korean film, Bong Joon-ho - who already offered his depressing vision of terror in the held Memories of Murder - to ask ourselves: is really that what would happen? When the golpée disaster: who will be really there to protect us?Gang - du Park is a loser with few lights that works at the snack bar of his father at the Bank of the River Han, in where the inhabitants of Seoul enjoyed a pleasant summer day. Both are visited by Hyun-seo, the teenage daughter of Gang-du: he wants it with madness, but his work as a father "and head of the family" leaves much to be desired, despite his attempts to please her as the save every penny to win to buy a mobile generation. While Gang-Du is the service, the weekenders warn a strange form hanging from one of the bridges; moments later, a monstrous creature has emerged from the river and campa to rampant hunting down the panicking bystanders. Gang-du, desperate, can see only as the beast drags Hyun-Seo with them.It is surprising how the film deals with the theme of the monster: parodying her and chopping it from the first moment. The transition between the knowledge of fondly manners family Park and the irruption of the monster is so abrupt that cause, in a first moment, disbelief. Against all the precepts of the suspense, the monster is shown in its entirety from the outset. To design it seem to have attended before biological criteria that the dread: the monster is simply an antropófaga whale with legs, nothing terrifying jaw of the Tyrannosaurus or the babeantes jaws of the Alien. The quality of the animation underscores that impression of watching something too real as to enter the game from the movie monsters. In the first minutes of the film, all topics (including the heroic American soldier) will come down.The film will continue in a bittersweet tone, mixture of tragedy and comedy. The reunion of the brothers of Gang-Du (a licensed alcoholic unemployed with revolutionary past and a sharpshooter of arc fails to pass the bronze) before the supposed funeral altar of Hyun-Seo is paradigmatic: four relatives are twisted pain on the floor while they hit each other and the flashes of the journalists riddled you. The family Park is maintained by the Government in quarantine while authorities alarmed about a virus allegedly transmitted by the monster. However, a call from Hyun-Seo will make them know that she is alive, captive in the lair in which the creature stored their prey. In the face of general indifference, the family Park must join overcome his own frustrations, sacrifice everything to deal with both the monster and greed and hypocrisy of a society that leaves a montage directed from the highest level to manipulate. An interesting and innovative Bong leads with good pulse and approach best eye cinematógrafico, that hooks quickly and offers, in addition to a good time, much think about what.</body>
</review>
