<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La ciencia del sueño" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Splendid exercise of visual juggling, surrealism to GLUGs, film made to the delight of who is already tired of seeing movies made to be understood, streamlined, compartmentalized, hierarchical, stalling...</summary>
	<body>Tosk script that Hollywood cinema is born from a model necessarily dependent on proven formulas of success and popular support and commercial encounters proposals like this. The science of sleep is the mental turmoil by Michael Gondry, its overwhelming importance as modern surrealist author. It can not be understood otherwise lacks completely of interest use the traditional narrative machinery when what is intended (and in my view gets) is explicit mechanisms of sleep, the capacity of the fantasy to drive the destiny of the world.Not needed by both Gondry a stanchion script, a fictionalized script. A team in tune will simply with his hallucination and a roster of actors, without overact, resized the usual records to deliver a dramaturgy sober in their schizophrenia, clean in dismay.In this sense, Gael García Bernal creates a credible, sharp character (and is already difficult), accessible in the Vertigo of this society entrenched in a continuous feeling of shock, imbalance of unforeseen hostility. Stephane not discerning the real of the fabulado: how one assembles in the other without visible fracture. Its creative richness is the overwhelming iconography of the film: released weight Kauffman Gondry (being John Malkovich, forget about me, which was stubbornly screenwriter), is allowed to check a disconcerting, unique, film deshilachada by sections, convincing always in the sense that meets the expectations that contracts.It was one the impression (I I had during most of the footage) that the film is definitely this: a consensual sham, a stop polluting, a continuous weakening of resistance that we build the fantasy dream (illusion) not do shake the solid architecture of the real world, the only one we have objectively.The science of sleep contains beautiful images, inventory impossible objects that populate the feverish imagination of a subject whose pleasures dispensary provisions of an infinite and disturbed world of lies. It is the lie, its pre-eminence in tautologously perverse universe, which lifts the film, which structure and desestructura a script capricious (if any), go and great, enduring work of a director who has a unique smell to it politically not already incorrect, but monstrous.When one comes out of the cinema and see cars or shop Windows full of garments real and tangible, useful, valid, is amazed to not go by their eyelets ants hulled or that the display of the desktop of our loft does not break down in elementary beams of light containing winged horses and arrows of blue cellophane paper. Breeding ground suitable for fans of Freud, the film blinded (jubilosamente) to not provide handles valid for separating the precarious reality (the Office, the boredom, the routine) and the colourful cartoon of dreams, the oneiric fundamental component that builds this gem of creativity that will endure, not I put in doubt, to become a small classic. It cloying and it hastía, it is accepted: is inevitable. The protein argument cannot be sustained without there decays, lagoons, parentheses in interest. Our own attention ability falters when it is overexposed to a tralla so eye-catching and forceful portentous visual gags, everyday objects transformed into Visual poems, in the psyche of a haunted metaphors.An addition or a recommendation: we must find the original version and flee from the plague of any folded Edition, even though our dubbers are, incidentally of forced step, always professional and compelling. The protagonist speaks French, English and uses the Spanish, their mother tongue (Mexican is) to verbalize their dreams.No wait a waste of humor: this is not what he wants French Gondry. The science of sleep is a very adult reflection in child, playful tone at times, on human communication. Just what not to forget about me, his previous film (in English Eternal sunshine of the spotless mind) what espoleaba where the reflection was not the imagination (the dream, more properly) but the memory, his catharsis, its revered good repute as a primary resource to sustain the balance of our rationality.Have you, gentle reader, his horse from cardboard, your time machine, her reality show inserted into vein. All that: amplified, made major exercise of deliberate creation.Never before, never before in a long time, a film I has raised so much joy. Or in other words has long experience of cultural style (say a book, an album, a film) not let me so transposed, so listing the happiness and, at the time, so sheltered in sadness that the argument given, cryptic, smooth, leisurely: that is very difficult to talk about feelings, that our bodies communicate very well in the sensual, in bed, physically, but that every day, in leaps terrifyingly, us will hiding in the individualdad recelando of the other, opening gaps then complicated close to separate ours from alien, lived in fantaseado, accessible from the metaforizado.Stephane obrero, the sad composer of calendars, is the perfect image of alienation. The shortage of branchings of the circumstances surrounding the character are not free: in dreams have its most ferocious defence. Go to the movies, have fun in the armchair, although they come out (like me) absurd intoxicated. I wonder (is a question which I leave open) what shall this man, so promising, so cool in theirs, with a conventional plot, with a wearable history, with a sobreentendible thread, without jumps in time, without comeduras of coconut without cardboard horses.</body>
</review>
