<review author="Bloody Will" title="The host" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story that engages the public and has genuine brilliant moments, whilst, as in almost all film monsters, tends towards the end to fatigue.</summary>
	<body>I do not know what will have the Asian movies that, starting from a premise that any other industry to become a blockbuster bazófico without a script (not look to the West), manage to tell a story that engages the public and has genuine brilliant moments, whilst, as in almost all film monsters, tends towards the end to fatigue.Maybe The host is that you'll not find before more than overused genus of large bicharracos. There is no chunky heroes, or with good coefficients intellectual and much less essential requirement of contract. Who confronts the monster is a family commanded by an old man and followed by a failed arch Sharpshooter, a bum, and a fool of auction. All with the Mission of rescuing the smallest of the clan, and all with an absolute incompetence to carry out that purpose, which makes the movie a success.Park Hee-bong (Byun Hee-bong), has a small put food on the River have Seoul, and strip for a family of two children, a daughter and her little granddaughter. Gang-du (Song Gang-ho) a real immature 40 tacos, Nam-il (Park Hae-il), a hysterical unemployed, Nam-joo (Bae Du-na) Sharpshooter of arc Olympic and Hyun-seo, daughter of Gang-du. When an enormous mutant amphibian out of the river and caught one of them, the rest will come to the rescue but not passing all possible calamities.First, the very first appearance of the Gwoemul, which I believe should be its name since it is the original title of the film. It is one of the most impressive sequences of recent years. Rather than spend 10 minutes, and during the following 20 Monster sweeps with the park where is the snack-bar of the protagonist. This is something radically opposed to everything we have seen so far, where it does not appear the beast learns until that we have 1 hour of footage. In addition, nothing to envy to the American CGI. The lack of control of the animal slaughtering to anyone who crosses on its way makes you to skip literally seat, and the end of the attack, simply an apotheosis. Only by this already worth seeing her.From that moment already let more aside to the "bug" to focus on the efforts of the family to recover one of its members, and not lost one iota of interest in the film. After a harrowing image in the sports centre of the affected population, becomes an escape from the Hospital that recalls the most gamberras comedies. Sometimes comedy, at times drama, show that it is not necessary to have the breath of the monster constantly in the neck to make the story interesting.In addition, I like to think that in this type of movies not everything has to end so richly. Let's be honest, if we are behind an amphibian of nearly 10 meters, something will happen, and there will be consequences. The film explores the nuance of reality in the meantime terror.Now, everything has his but. To my gives me the feeling that spare you a quarter of an hour or at least not extend too much the end. Everything happens so fast at the beginning which seems to be delayed and relantizarse towards the last quarter hour, as if one has to drive the film in 2 hours at all costs.The Host is a real rarity in the world of celluloid: film entertaining in the genre of monsters. There other cases (shark), but abound so much mess and joke that this movie is all a shock to my belief that Mathew Broderick and Godzilla marked a before and after in the horror film.</body>
</review>
