<review author="Andrés" title="Stoned" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A script quite light with phrases such as 'the problem of the happiness is boring'</summary>
	<body>I know this is first time a fiction film recreates the Rolling Stones with this since we have reason enough to want to see it, is not it?. "Stoned" (2005) from Stephen Woolley tries to tell the "real" story of the death of Brian Jones, the founder of the band was found dead at the bottom of your pool. At first everyone thought that it was a faux leg of Jones, who spent all day drugged, but Frank Thorogood, a type who worked at his home, confessed "on his deathbed" having him killed. This is the version which takes the film.The thing sounded interesting but is a difficult challenge. To begin we have to as well known as the Stones, as characters, stars and a major episode in the mythology of the rock: the death of Jones. I.e., the public's expectations are high and I think that many feel that they have tried them to sell cat by liebre.¿Que we have here? A film about rock stars. They are so like each other! First we ask ourselves who will be sufficiently similar to so-and-so to interpret it? After: the difficult beginnings, great opportunity, the fans, drugs (essential and nearly protagonists), loss of control, decadence, Salvation or death. The End.Si well "Stoned" is not a film about the Rolling Stones, but Jones, are recreated some facts with other members of the band. Thus we can see the actors who interpret to Mick Jagger and Keith Richards, both with low profile and very few lines, but you can not ask more (would have been worse, I think). The action is concentrated in the months prior to the death of Jones, his dismissal of the band and the quick collapse of drugs and in the pool.To animate the story director spices up his film with beautiful people, naked bulk, musical sequences, showy travel of LSD, i.e. all the paraphernalia of the 60s, to at least entertain the eye and ear. A script quite light with phrases such as "the problem of the happiness is boring", so try to summarize the philosophy of Jones, and some touches of documentary (newspaper, filming of the time cuts) and so you go to report something and then not you come to surprise and can answer with certainty to the question: who killed Brian Jones?</body>
</review>
