<review author="Torbe" title="Apocalypto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>El bueno de Mel Gibson has just made a movie that reminds me to other movies such as Rambo, or Predator, when the dam becomes Hunter, mud, water, traps, the jungle. Even resembles a little straw dogs.</summary>
	<body>El bueno de Mel Gibson has just made a movie that reminds me to other movies such as Rambo, or Predator, when the dam becomes Hunter, mud, water, traps, the jungle. Even a little resembles Paja.El dogs problem I see in this kind of movies is the historical rigour. Gone are the days in which the teachers we they placed a movie so the students learn things. That's thing already of the documentaries from the history channel, because in the movies we see each attack against the terrible history.And this movie is not going to be less.For those who you have seen the movie, is not how a few Aztecs pick up prisoners for their sacrifices to a quiet Mayan village, and as weapon of God because he escapes one. The movie is exciting and super entertaining from beginning to end, and I recommend it strongly. Few movies are done so today in day, the truth. With that realism and that pace. The movie makes us what we have always been, some warriors and hunters who gave laps through the jungle killing bugs. Thousands of years have been so, and I think that the movie, like because us back to our origins.It is one thing that catches my attention much think this movie that he never won an oscar. There is no dedicated stars, nor the language is English. (they speak in Basque language all the time, or a dialect of this). I like the Mel has passed all and gone to a movie different, colorful and hyper-realist, because you think everything that happens.The problem is when internet is consulted and is researched a little about the history of these peoples, one realizes the cultural trampling and the desproposito that it has been this movie. Here I spent some of the things that squeak in the movie: - the architecture of the city is a mix between Petén and Puuc, both with 200 years of difference.-at the arrival of the Spaniards, the Mayan cities were completely abandoned, however in the movie it appears full and in construction-experimental archaeology investigations have shown that the sharpened Obsidian has the ability to easily cut slashes of flesh and blood, however in the movie just leave bruises. non-lethal-in some scenes the mercenarions use Macuahuitlis, the weapon of the Aztec Legion by excellence, the Mayans used Spears and axes-many weapons are reduced to a stone tied to a stick - most of the characters in the movie used bone ornaments directly embedded in the face. Although worked bone, there is no evidence arqueologica that was used on the face.-priests have pheasant (fasianus colchicus) feathers in the plume. The pheasant is a species of China and it was imported much later to Mexico around the 17TH century-the Mayan civilization is to date, an agricultural society. The existence of a jacket community without milpas is simply unrealistic.Do these are some of the things that are wrong in the movie and the debate is opened because it is lawful to undertake these historical irregularities? A movie is the vision of a creator, therefore, can change things to suit? Who knows andeNo me what I could believe, but there is, in one of the frames of the movie the guy has crept to the character of the popular books where's Wally? That if the cachondeo father.If we start with these stories, already I I'm imagining as will be the movies Morrow, all full of subpeliculas in the own movies. Messages, jets and a thousand things more into hidden frames. Times change, and the film more.One last appreciation more: massacres in the sacrifices. I rescued a comment poured into the putalocura Forum: "the movie portrayed the Mayans almost as genocidal, sacrificing and throwing the remains to tutiplen." The truth is that this level of only sacrificial genocide reached it the Aztecs in their "flower wars", when the Empire needed to constantly new victims to satisfy their gods. "The Maya sacrificed people, it is true, but not those industrial levels."There are many theories about the extinction of the Mayans. Disappeared from the Earth or they were annihilated by the Aztecs before? No one knows, what is known is that ate human flesh, in fact, almost any ancient civilization is saved from having eaten human flesh.And the sacrifices, if, is made. It was the way they had for power between the hierarchs, unfortunately at the expense of human lives.Talk about this me tiraria days, I think it is best to see the movie without more, have fun and not give too much importance to all these historical errors.PS.If Mel Gibson in his movie invents things, I also would like to do in my articles, so I said that in this movie they speak euskera haha.</body>
</review>
