<review author="Noa" title="The host" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We have an entretenidísima movie that works as a great drama freak or a revision of the genus of science fiction with new and attractive ingredients. Highly recommended and enjoyable. Not you the Miss.</summary>
	<body>This is a great movie with family dysfunctional, clumsy and losing dearly, and above, Monster and Monster!. I went to the cinema completely clean of synopsis, trailers, reviews and comments (was only aware of the good reception in Sitges and boom box office in Korea) so I did not expect anything, except for a few comparisons suspiciously wrong by the Distributor on the poster: after?Shark? and?Alien? does it arrive?The Host?. Nothing further from the truth. The film of Bong Joon-Ho (Chronicle of a serial killer) is another story, it is a very interesting genres milkshake: action, science fiction, with giant monster, drama, HUMOR, political satire, and even autoparodia also. The same director has stated that he has also tributes to Godzilla or the Loch Ness monster, and has sought inspiration in the running of the bulls of San Fermin. Oh, Yes, as you read.The film starts with an introduction totally expendable, but already makes us suspect the black (or yellow) humor to distil 'The Host' (beyond 'Gwoemul') "." We are on offer, we can only sit comfortably and enjoy. Below and without further delay, we see the rush initial, located in Seoul, the presentation in society of "the thing" and its consequences, focusing on a very peculiar family. From there the tragedy, the horny tone and tension occur hand in hand in this South Korean film.I would like to tell you of the mutant monster, a cross between crocodile, dinosaur and giant squid. An authentic enjoyed special effects and sound effects (essential to see her in a movie theater, dear friends of the animals of burden.) a joy of creature that moves with speed, elegance and jumping of hangovers. Thank you see most of the time in full light of day and why not let be integrated. It's a bug of luxury!As I said before, the film plays almost all the time with humor and drama, and is that the laughter of the four people that we were in the cinema rumbled in the room of beside, bizarre humor called. With the exception of a sequence which made me frown a good bit of embarrassment (time ground and weeping). Anyway it is not diverted from the tone of the film, and we have in mind is an East movie, with all that that entails.The flat acting is impeccable, the protagonists are sensationally well defined, well advanced and well interpreted, especially a memorable Song Kang-Ho that is my idol now. In short, an entretenidísima film, which works as a great drama freak or a review of the science fiction genre with new (why not original) and attractive ingredients. Highly recommended and enjoyable. Not you the Miss.</body>
</review>
