<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Magnolia" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Risky and sensible, slightly hackneyed, although outstanding in its resolution, Magnolia is a runaway Colt who knows where it is going, a spectacular punch in the nose of the American accommodated, urban, gentrified (unknowingly) and afflicted, like many, of loneliness, boredom, of pure incommunicado.</summary>
	<body>Magnolia is a dazzling alembic of stories that referred to Short Cuts even though it does not coincide with this acid vision, although happy with which van knotting all levels. The Paul Thomas Anderson film escarba in narrative constructions of greater complexity. It is a film of a huge brazenness, which gives a forcefulness unmitigated conclusions. The viewer who attends this controlled blasting of the foundations of the society does not leave the film reeling, but costs then return to everyday life. The short stories, the arrogant plans and the vital adventures of fundamentally tormented characters of the degree of torment that crushes them in a grey, morally reprehensible when not perverse life we only know they bullen head.Continuing Biblical references (not only literature but iconography as the testimonial rain of frogs) report that Anderson thinks out loud about the faith and how the shadows of Utopia celan a sediment of ideological dandruff. Chance determines the life that we know, but what has this director overfunded is that random has also its epic, his field of battle and his absurd map of shadows. This is how we see all the characters of the celebrity that portrays the great script of Anderson's own: desasidos of hope, wrecked, sadly doomed to not encourage any hope, but even in this negative position, in that firm and severe deconstruction, Anderson sought to humanize his creatures.The wonderful end, which must not be gutting in these lines, weapon of a disconcerting naturalism, which knocks down all the ideas that we had been aprovisionando for three hours before at a stroke. In them, unmistakably, they told us specific events, tiny stories (nine, actually) that happen at the same time in a valley of California. Coral in the mode in which filming Robert Altman (is no longer among the living), Magnolia slightly decomposes the drama too hence towards insanity. Julianne Moore as a young wife of an old dying man (Jason Robards, brilliant) is passed part of his performance screaming, longer, obcecada in feeding his spiritual blunder with pills. There Anderson loses the North, but is an excuse because the narrative material is enormous and is not easy (not me so imagine) fill the gaps that the stories are abandoning (and there are certainly some and of them one search in particular, the reader, visible and uncomfortable).Tom Cruise does not leave much, but fills more than in many films where it occupies the entire screen for all the minutes. Earned him a Golden globe this meritorious performance as well as the nomination for best supporting actor in the Oscars. And it is one of my recent favorite actors, Philip Seymour Hoffman, that makes an absolutely nuclear role in the film, the host of a television program into a crisis of identity and values.Not be amedren by its excessive footage: consumed with greed, he chews on occasions. Film served with cleanliness. Far-fetched, spoiled in their excesses, but useful film to bear the weight of so much film adocenada, impregnated of predictability which usually occupy the billboards of our vices.</body>
</review>
