<review author="Jesus Lens" title="La vida de los otros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When finished the projection of?The life of others?, in a movie theater filled with unusually for a German film, became one of those special and unique silences which predict a 30metre standing ovation.</summary>
	<body>When he had completed the screening of "The lives of others", in an unusually full cinema for a German film, became one of those special and unique silences which predict a 30metre ovation, in which all had participated willingly and relax. someone that would break the fire have there been.Said it Sacai, nothing more appear uncredited: "is one of those movies that you just want to applaud". Effectively. "The huge and long peliculón Florian Henckel von Donnersmarck (Flo onwards) not only happens in a whisper but that you indeed, reconciles with the good things of life.""The lives of others" is an immersive, Lung free, in the reality of a Germany of the East very close in time. When we hear talk of films about the cold war, Checkpoint Charlie and the iron curtain, we are accustomed to being in ByN, that tell exciting stories of spies, harassment and non-stop action. But the reality of the Socialist Germany in the nearby 1980s presents as much less glamorous and more menacing and gloomy in the film of Flo.Una Word, a concept plan about all the protagonists: blacklist. We are between the intellectual forefront of German Theatre modernity. And arise the suspicions. Is it possible that Georg Dreyman, one of the great cultural icons of German socialism is so good, so pure and so loyal to the regime as it appears? The mediocre, to Ascend, use a very effective technique: sow doubts and spreading shit on all those around him, in a way that the foul layer of fog that contribute to to its around can disguise their own inability and its odor. And that is what makes one of the capitostes of the Stasi, the dreaded secret police German: put under surveillance to Dreyman. Let's see what happens.And so, the relationship between the security guard, Captain Gerd Wiesler, an official expert; and the guarded and his girlfriend, a famous actress, begins to be more contradictory. And changing. And ambivalent. And again contradictory. And fascinating. And beautiful. And tragic. And many other things and feelings generated by the viewing of a fantastic and hypnotic film that speaks to us of a past time, but who is there to the other side of the remains of a wall. And in the minds of many, many people.Indeed, the film of Flo has much to do with that other, equally fascinating film by Francis Ford Coppola: "The conversation". Both are formally austere, but a draught and a transcendence that show the film without being boring, can be much more than a hobby or an entertainment for kids. A fascinating film thesis, which suggest can be done without plúmbeos speeches. Without launch viscera against the Viewer, you can get this not blinking for two hours and a half. Without free pyrotechnics you can get shock of neurons in a few spectators who, when offered quality film products, respond and come to see them. Come from where you come.</body>
</review>
