<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Cabalgar en solitario" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Modest, simple, Western of stylistic resources apparently minor. Western hero traumatized, although stoic in its primary role, heroic almost. A masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>Ride solo, very faithful translation of the original Ride lonesome, it is a western sober invoices, without embellishment, subordinate to the narration of a story and oblivious to any other aesthetic consideration. This helps the professionalism of a director underrated, absent in the usual lists of Directors of posh that when occasionally populate the industry magazines or Web pages. Budd Boetticher was a master of westerns, where he made a dozen of great films. Most of them with Randolph Scott. Scott plays a bounty hunter carried a prisoner before the law. A couple of very curious Bill outlaws addressed it in the road with the Pilgrim idea of stealing the goods. Flat Boetticher camera generals (which he was also a bullfighter, behold the also more than curious data) amplify the idea of the hero solo, mythical, convinced that his loneliness is the best in the world and that their mission does not need another company to his horse. We are dealing with a very original western, which has gone down in history (to mine also, secondary and jubilosamente) due to its neutral colour appearance of the West film little West, to put it in some way. Characters have a new dramatic content and the story, impetuous, spurs them way so accurate that it seems that we are witnessing the first western, a genre virginal and primary.The movie buff will recall with special pleasure more than notable flat end mounted crane in which Ben (Randolph Scott) finally gives settlement to his revenge (his dead wife) or the scene in which an Indian arrow has an impact on the body of a driver of proceedings. Maps showing the efficiency of an extremely meticulous, artisan director in the sense of manufacture a work narrativamente portentosa, precise, able to feed the interest of the Viewer from very few ingredients.Film classic or perhaps classic in one sense of the term because there are other western of greater nombradía. This is rugged and masculine, significantly spiced by some touches of humor very welcome and, above all, honest in the proof of the worth of a genus that ultimately was dying as the 20th century was maturing and the Viewer (the American and which is not) believed to have views all films of the West when the genus is infinite and has the potential to huge expand its unquestionable pre-eminence in the history of the Film.</body>
</review>
