<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Paris je t'aime" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A varied film made with taste and sensitivity (or bad taste, for the great in everything else, less here, Christopher Doyle) and with some superb performances.</summary>
	<body>Are beautiful, charming, sad, poignant? And what you can expect from these directors? Well, a varied film made with taste and sensitivity (or bad taste, for the great in everything else, less here, Christopher Doyle) and with some superb performances. Highlight names, both directors and actors, such as Coen, Binnoche, Coixet, Payne, Portman, Nolte, Rowlands, Suwa, Gazzara, Coixet, Salles, Tykwer, Schmitz (perhaps his short is the best along with the Depardieau and Payne), Castellito, Chomet (fucking mimes!), Sandino Moreno, etc. Although their respective shorts have fascinated me, there are others that have disappointed me somewhat, such as those of Alfonso Cuarón, that despite being a simple short, it has its charms, not just take the trick, and Olivier Assayas, that could be explained much more with the story of Maggie Gylenhaal. These two I have appointed is not that they are bad, but that simply do not have drawn me the attention especially. But there is, in "Paris, je t? aime", the worst film I have seen in my life: of Christopher Doyle, an incredibly pathetic Barbet Schroeder and a storyline that sorry. Moreover, there are stories that do not say fu or fa, but do not bother (Conversely, enrich intelligently the film), as the of LaGravanese (with Bob Hoskins and Fanny Ardant), Gus Van Sant (to me, personally, thought me, his short, pretty tough, although many people in the film you loved), Wes Creaven (another controversial)(, but certainly a formidable performances, both Mortimer, Sewell and Paye (Alexander) - as Oscar Wilde!-), Bruno Podalydès (the first and friendly short), Vicenzo Natali (original, Yes, but lacks strength, lacks it the spark Coen) and Gurinder Chadha (Yes, it is nice, but a tad typical).In conjutno, the film presents a formidable Assembly (without the names of the directors before the start of each short!) and a structure ordered by most original neighborhoods. The music is beautiful (tuned to the song at the end!). Well, as you can see, to criticize this movie needed nominate performers and directors, because but we left with little. I recommend it to all those who you want to see something new, original, intelligent, varied, irregular (although very little), beautiful and sad.Small masterpieces are those of Joel and Ethan Coen, Tom Twyker, Alexander Payne, Gerard Dépardieau and Oliver Schmitz. Good shorts and more than kind belong to Isabel Coixet, Walter Salles and Daniela Thomas, Sylvain Chomet, and Nobuhiro Suwa. The shorts that complement the film include Gurinder Chadha, Wes Craven, Alfonso Cuarón, Gus Van Sant, Richard LaGravense, Bruno Podalydès and Vincenzo Natali. The shorts that, definitely, sobran: Porte de Choisy (of the unforgivable Christopher Doyle) and Quartier des enfants rouges (of Olivier Assayas).By the way, don't miss the end where several of the shorts intersect with the song La même histoire de Fund. How big are all!</body>
</review>
