<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El hombre de Laramie" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Western Shakespearean inspiration, emotional review of the ancient idea of revenge. A masterpiece of the western and one of the best performances of a secondary of luxury, Donald Crisp.</summary>
	<body>Anthony Mann westerns are epic in the manner in which are the Budd Boetticher. Both dominate the film script and generate suggestive imagery: the rider slightly drawn in an eerie landscape, the hero fatally marked by the overwhelming weight of the inevitable tragedy. The man from Laramie anticipates the western Clint Eastwood, who is the last director concerned dignify the genre. The argument refers to Anthology Film Noir where a man decides to investigate the reasons for it that does not require research: who sold weapons that some Indians bought to finish killing his brother. This story of revenge is not new: change the characters, sets, the score, but the plot cela the same traditions, the not mutated, pure essence where men are always pioneers and gracefully fighting injustices, which tend to be landowners who take outside lands that you paste your livestock or restless ira chieftains not consenting to a stranger passing through his plot. This is what makes James Stewart, who suffers an excessive punishment, an unnecessary humiliation. It is then when decided to put themselves at the service of Kate (Cathy O'Donnell) faced with the "waggoman" that atosiga.There the love affair, which is resolved in a unconventional way. Nor violence typical of the western, Mann stylized until reduced to a dry, minimal, concise and forceful expression we miss at fault. It engolosina not show evil, but all the escenas-clave are bathed in a rich sense of violence as the only viable solution.Filmed with a still balbucente cinemascope, the man from Laramie is a perfect example of film where the landscape is one protagonist, perhaps one more binding and decisive that the apparent and real. A masterpiece of the western and one of the best performances of a secondary of luxury, Donald Crisp.</body>
</review>
