<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is one of the most profound and poetic about the never seen war analyses. Although more than a war film is a film of heart, with deep wounds and a very wise moral background.</summary>
	<body>As well as letters from Iwo Jima Japanese speak Japanese and not in English, although it is an American film director Clint Eastwood also speak another language: your own. We all know that the director has a classic, perfectionist, rather minimalist style. It is the Eastwood style, which is little like with many other directors. Her last and acclaimed film, responsible for colcuir the diptych on the battle of Iwo Jima during World War II, is called letters from Iwo Jima, and we could say that her best film is after that another masterpiece titled Million Dollar Baby. I have not seen the first part of aforementioned Diptych, the more irregular, according to critics, flags of our fathers, but I assure you that I do not think it takes to having seen to see the second. Moreover, I think that it is better to start with the good and continue with what it is not so much, but perhaps I'm wrong, and the penultimate film of Eastwood is a wonder, as some say. Well, better stop compare and go to the grain.Paul Haggis and IRIS Yamahsita are responsible for the screenplay for the film in question. One could expect less Crash director and screenwriter of Million Dollar Baby, but if only her had written it, I guess that letters from Iwo Jima had not so many references to Japanese cinema. And here is when you notice the presence of Yamahsita in the more intimate scenes (can not lose you the sequence of collective suicide) or more characteristic of Japanese culture. Thus, the combination of each of the writers makes this a film with one of the scripts more solid seen in years, absolutely credible, well coordinated, tailored.But as you know, a good screenplay must be very well directed so that the result is a masterpiece, leaving band performances. And there is our Clint, able to get better at the same time that get older (great, by the way). It is incredible to think that a man starts acting in spaghetti-westerns of more mediocre and end up winning more than one Oscar and performing several masterpieces. Therefore more credible is this fact, which happens to Mr Clint Eastwood, which adapted the script from Yamahsita and Haggis with extreme sensitivity and makes him a real prodigy named letters from Iwo Jima. With the solid script, the address is one of the strengths of the film, carried out with absolute mastery and genuine respect. It is, the film of Eastwood, the closest thing to the intimacy itself, to the personality of the victim and the winner (I am not referring to the Japanese and American, respectively, but all the soldiers in general), and not of the good and the bad. In short, say that the director has made his second more intimate, personal, poetic, human work and above all with respect, even if do not stop you filming on the island of Iwo Jima, which I find reasonable, as much as one come with good intentions. There are many scenes for these 141 minutes that are hopelessly recordables. Will to not seem heavy, only name a couple or three, perhaps, which found me most brilliant. The first could be when the Japanese pick up an American soldier named Sam to kill him. But as they see that it is too wrong, they decide, instead of ending his life, trying to save him. Like this, predictably, it does not happen, one of the Japanese soldiers found in the uniform of Sam a letter from his mother. It read aloud, so that his companions hear, inevitably, feel weak and strong and take courage and fear at the same time. And, precisely, the sentence that concludes the letter is repeated later by one of the Japanese to encourage loved ones. The second best scene would be, for me, of the flash-back the general (played by a wonderful Ken Watanabe) recalls during a part of the film, showing with a few American politicians that give away you a weapon for his entire career. When he returns home by car, feels an enormous loneliness, however much that awards have conceived you by his honor. This is, probably, one of the scenes with the best phrase that had been in a movie. And Lastly, noting the courage and solitude, remains highlight the honour, which Eastwood chooses to use it, main and not only, in the last scene of the film, the most tremendous, the most terrible thing that has seen for the footage. Once general Tadamichi Kuribayashi (Watanabe) is about to die facing some American soldiers, which just beat the Japanese in the island, it looks like Saigo (a splendid Kazunari Ninomiya, in the photo below) comes with the blade that just bury all cards belonging to your Triathlon by one of the mountains. When he arrives next to the general, it tells you bury. And once you do, more norte-americanos soldiers arrive in order to snatch Saigo, which terrifies to see that one of them takes the weapon was the general wearing always (from the scene mentioned above). Here is when it shows absolute mastery with which Eastwood has approached the film, leaving, as the flat end, one of the beaches of the beautiful island of Iwo Jima. Ladies and gentlemen, we are once and for all, before an absolute masterpiece, made to measure, made with honour and courage, made with innate sensitivity and talent. Clint Eastwood wheel her second best film, after Million Dollar Baby, with a poetic, slow, beautiful and sometimes noisy rhythm. And, in conclusion, it would say that letters from Iwo Jima is such wonder since it is imperfect-which makes it even more personal. This is one of the most profound and poetic about the never seen war analyses. Although more than a war film is a film of heart, with deep wounds and a very wise moral background.</body>
</review>
