<review author="Alejandro Salmerón" title="Mi noche con Maud" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Difficult film, visually little attractive and with a great script that compensates</summary>
	<body>Rohmer reveals a heterodox and highly personal style of film-making with their arts where, perhaps the way it is not much, but the background of his stories are a contribution to the seventh art; especially this film, the most prominent in his career. The film begins with two key elements, predestination and free choice of the person arising on basis of mathematics undecipherable conversation between protagonist and secondary instances of syllogisms. Once put the chips on the Board only is enjoy the crux of the story which is the pinnacle of the same, where we will be witnesses of a struggle for the strong defence of values; who the enemy Maud, a beautiful woman with much expertise, will try to subvert them in a night trap's friend Jean-Louis will prepare. As it was for me "The godfather", really exemplary values of life are learned of Rohmer. Another remarkable nuance is that in this story no good nor bad, anyone who is to judge how to act in the individual; making it a more realistic film, which opens even more the sea of uncertainties and doubts which is undergoing the protagonist and the viewer that by adopting that approach everything becomes more grey.The film is made in the key of comedy and would really be attractive as such if the view I not turned in a couple of fairly obvious details, such as the end, which has a reflective twist (fairly brief, by the way) that reveals the background of latent melodrama, which leaves you a bit cold at the end of the film; the other "but" are sets of lighting which seem to be a bit made "hair", i.e. If one is accustomed to see comedies may appreciate the light tends to play a sweet paper to wrap the film an aura sweetened product which really this great work lacks, not to say that it is the antithesis. This last may sound to connotations but sometimes a factor compensates the other, as it is the case. However it can be deduced that the lighting looks for other purposes.In conclusion and as a recommendation or not, just say it's a difficult film, visually little attractive (not for photography, eye, but also by its lighting) and with a great script that I think that it offsets totalitariamente Jean-Louis Trintignant and especially Françoise Fabian makes collection of elegance and intelligence in this film. A work focused on a more purist audience on the topic, in short.</body>
</review>
