<review author="Mario" title="The host" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite being advertised as such, comparing it directly on the posters with Alien or shark, the truth is that the experience of The host far than they were those movies of the 1970s.</summary>
	<body>A new production of the distant South Korea rang with force at the last festival of Sitges. Bong Joon-Ho, responsible for the outstanding Memories of murder (which I've not yet seen) presented on this occasion what could appear to be a monster-movie of life. Despite being advertised as such, comparing it directly on the posters with Alien or shark, the truth is that the experience of The host far than they were those movies of the 1970s.The differences between the Eastern approach and Hollywood, to which we are obviously more used, are obvious. The pace of the film, as in almost all citations with slanted eyes film, is at least strange: I wouldn't say that slow, at least if we adhere to the idea that we have of this concept in these parts, it is not dynamic and fast-paced as he recited the poster, comparing it with those two masterpieces. The host has a Cadence paused and anomalous, quite hard to describe but easily identifiable for any follower of the film in that area. This long creature appears very soon in full light of the Sun, forgetting the possible dramatic tension focused on the own Monster and sliding the development in other directions, clear symptom of what we find.The sense of humor that handles is difficult to follow, and laughter that sounded in the room were probably due to ridiculous that we are certain comedic situations.These factors, along with some other more, made that the film I became hopelessly boring at times, without be able to avoid me feel alien to the way of telling a story that has been proposed.However, apart from the absence of embellishment and the amazement that generate characters, is no less true that the real shots of the film and its real interest are not exactly going out there. Social criticism and the direct attack on American policy are, without any doubt, the real objectives of the director. As was the case in Godzilla, Joon-Ho used the pretext of a monster mutagenic to wield a political satire and complaint to the brave.The simile with the war of Iraq or the anti-terrorist pre-emptive strikes are very clear: A military base of the USA pour chemicals into a river, which later will cause a disaster in the form of mutant fish. The scenes are reminiscent of the CIA training people like Bin Laden or the initial support for Saddam, planting the River with waste for later harvest monsters.Years later, with the vermin in full swing punishing the natives, some absurd sign makes them deduce that there is a virus dangerous for the international community to weapons of mass destruction? Concerning this passage is absolutely brilliant the sequence in which an American military doctor finds evidence of the virus in the behavior of the protagonist. Finally the USA involved in the country riding a chicken that will eventually take that solve the same civilians who suffer the consequences. The final apology of the President are fully revealing.This message, together with the presentation of one family any together, despite their differences, face adversity, distance to this film of the like and, in my opinion, get that some own, perhaps, of the immense distance intercultural barriers exceed.Members of the family, desquiciados and out all idealità, but defending despite everything, and without knowing it, values of honesty and greatness (Homer Simpson model) as well as the surprising end anti-Hollywood, manage to make forget, somehow, not too adventurous staging and artistic conception. Therefore, I choose finally rated the movie positively.</body>
</review>
