<review author="Jose Contreras" title="The host" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The nonsense of Korean cinema at risk like us for the simple reason that aren't the nonsense of American cinema. I prefer not rushing to hang trophies everytime I see two Lords of slanted eyes comiéndo an instant soup with chopsticks by the fact that here use spoon.</summary>
	<body>The nonsense of Korean cinema at risk like us for the simple reason that aren't the nonsense of American cinema. I prefer not rushing to hang trophies everytime I see two Lords of slanted eyes comiéndo an instant soup with chopsticks by the fact that here use spoon.The protagonist, which I will call the protagonist because nobody is able to remember a Korean name, is a really pathetic loser. Dyed blond, with a paltry job treats post, slept all day, takes care of a daughter who serves as mother to such loser. It is a type of hero that can work in the East because it is modeled the stereotypes of any film of karate in series B. To my bothers me by the crude imitation of the Western rebel and because perhaps in our cinema connected with the loser but never with the clown. To do antics, here the hero always has to a friend.More strange food and traffic signals are family relations. The protagonist loses his daughter at the hands of the beast and the two brothers are so gorrazos. You do not know if the native Viewer perceives the scene as comical or dramatic, but feels an urgent need for that move to another topic. The monster not devour the girl, la guarda in your pantry. The father knows that she is alive, but isn't the more anxious to rescue her, the three brothers unite their skills as well as three pokemon. New fraternal elections that would not make a Western creator.Koreans remember his dictatorial past like the Spaniards, yearn the barricades. One of the brothers prepared molotov cocktails while the taxi driver reminds him that they already have democracy. The evil of the beast holds political charges of thick stroke. The monstrosity is the fault of the army who manipulates chemicals at an American base. The surgeon who wants to prove that the monster carries a virus against all evidence is American estrávico. The father launches the search for his daughter when he hears his voice on the phone, which starts a point of emotion. But a police official refuses to take it seriously and stops him by Nutter, which is halfway between the Kafkaesque Chronicle and the sainete. I never know when a Korean is kidding and when going seriously.The beast is an infographic acceptable image. The computer used was not of last generation, either lacked some megs of RAM, but it is the least. At the beginning it chases people like an attraction of fair. We started to take it seriously when you eat their victims. The girl locked up in a nook of the Lair has the option of sit and wait or risk to seek a way out. When the girl plays the type out the show begins. It is what little is left of the seal of the director of "Memories of murder". That and a couple of intimate scenes that do not stick to the plot. It can make you great enthusiasm we sneak them, but it should not do so. Looking for another argument for them, either or is repressed a bit.</body>
</review>
