<review author="Florinda Chic" title="El buen alemán" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Clooney and Blanchett were they criticized no chemistry between them. More than a chemistry problem, I see it more a matter of overacting in both.</summary>
	<body>The career of Soderbergh is one of the most unequal of the current film. Do do Oscarizado by Traffic and sold to the? mainstream? with the infinite consequences of Ocean and their thieves, now presents the good German, an exercise of self-satisfaction that serves to pay tribute to the film he likes: fatal women and man hieratic engaged in devious stories of spies. The director puts us in a Berlin military post in which nobody seems to have a future and most attempts to erase its past. To this bleak picture comes a journalist - Clooney - in search of a great article and old love?Cate Blanchett-. A murder and all the spy film clichés make up a fairly diffuse argument of which is likely to be lost if it is not very attentive to the screen. Clooney and Blanchett were they criticized no chemistry between them. More than a chemistry problem, I see it more a matter of overacting in both. However, the couple does what it can with some dialogue impossible, topical and manichaeans. Obviously is a calque of the interpretations of the hard Bogart or the fragile Ingrid Bergman but moved to 2007 and a few faces so contemporary, Squeak.The most positive aspect of the film is impressive photography in black and white. Soderbergh has shot with the methods of the 1940s, using a single camera and lenses of that decade, resulting in an enveloping atmosphere and an aesthetic worthy of the productions that pays tribute. As cool as the war that came years later was the host of this film in the last Berlinale. Nor the Americans have supported her at box office and like this there so unforgiving, it was ignored completely in the recent edition of the Academy Awards. He competed for the statuette to the best Original Soundtrack which ultimately went to Gustavo Santaolalla - Babel-.</body>
</review>
