<review author="Yul B." title="Un puente hacia Terabithia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Close your eyes and open mind. Very important phrase you have to keep in mind when watching this movie.</summary>
	<body>?Close your eyes and open mind?. Very important phrase you have to keep in mind when watching this movie. Use the protagonists of this story for imagine, with amazing reality, the fantastic world of Terabithia, and truth, seems a Council for the Viewer.It is clear that to enjoy this film should be open fully to what tells us its director Gabor Csupo, by the grace of the author of the inspirational bestseller, Katherine Paterson.Es key will not remain with the easy, not leave you carry only by the visual part of the invention, they go beyond, i.e. that you profundicéis in storytellingthus to be able to capture the messages of friendship, humility, nobility, resignation or fortitude that launches us the tape during the 95 minutes that lasts.Anyway should be clear two things before going to see it: first, that we are talking about a film told by children and for children, in which the adult characters are only present to give realistic and unimaginative, counterpoint to the story. Do do yet the film is both enjoyed by kids of a certain age, I would say that starting from 8 years, for elders with the mind? open channel?. And, second, is not an overflowing film special effects with filler text. It is precisely the opposite: it is a daily story with abundant calling attention, whose small footage of fantastic elements are represented by the righteous and necessary FX. So that fans of special effects that you had intended to go to the cinema to see this film, animated by a few trailers that I consider to be misleading, and a promotion based on the advertising phrase? of the producers of the Chronicles of Narnia?, abstain from doing so because the roll will not out there.Do do with all this into your mental hard drive, the movie you seem entertaining, sometimes charming, although at the end pensaréis that it has lacked a couple of boiling points to be considered as a product Disney with possibilities of becoming in a? classic?, now called this company, in their DVD editions, old successful revenue and its new blockbuster pelotazos.Do I already told you that he had read somewhere that American critics had compared this film with?The Laberinto del Fauno? that both mixed fantasy and reality. As the saying comparisons are odious, and in this case are more patents, because the approach of?A bridge to Terabithia? do is much more white, innocent and sweet than the award-winning story of Bull here are two imaginative children with a beautiful and enigmatic forest by means, and its capacity of invention is much more? light?. It is true that living a mediocre reality and that their fears are reflected in each of the characters and elements from the environment of his fantasy world, which are owners, but the circumstances in which they live Jessie and Leslie are not as harsh as the Ofelia.Vamos than the story is different. It is a film that you will remember your childhood days, and you will feel on many occasions identified with the two protagonists of the story, who are the undisputed stars of the film.Do to Josh Hutcherson had already seen him in?Zathura, an adventure spice?, smaller and pointed out ways with his interpretation of the typical older brother nasty and capricious that many have had. Do here makes a convincing role of child discriminated against by their class, a great timidity behind his successful drawings, and by circumstances of fate is his soul mate, female version called Leslie, who plays Robb.A AnnaSophia Robb AnnaSophia we saw in?Charlie and the chocolate factory? as the screeching masticadora Violet gum, and now more crecidita, even prettier, and with a striking resemblance to Keira Knightley, makes as convincing as the teammate role: a bizarre student whose personality and overflowing imagination drag Jessie to the world of Terabithia. The connection between both actors/characters is ideal.Do there is almost always a? but? in this criticism, and for me there are several. I do count: certain moments of the plot are a tad long, to the point of seem unnecessary. Few others are unconnected, which also makes them seem unnecessary.The same applies to an important fact of the film quite sad, I can not reveal; I personally it felt out of place, justifiable only to cover the dramatic fee of the product, and draw the viewer the easy tear.And finally, one of the persecutions in the forest seems to be made hastily in the FX, which, at the level demanded today the public is a negative point.After all, the balance that is removed is positive. As minimum has been a film that covers the basic need of all film lover Viewer: have a fun time. And this dear friends is lately becoming a virtue which is in short supply.</body>
</review>
