<review author="Taliesin" title="El buen alemán" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With the good German, Soderbergh plays to shoot as fifty years ago and, although interesting, is closer to the experiment to the masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>Just need to compare the good German with Casablanca posters for ententer the Declaration of intent by Steven Soderbergh could not be clearer. The good German is film noir, black white, and with many of the Archetypes of the genre. Again the second world war and the reunion of two lovers. Again a plot full of conspirators and Crusader interests. Again the murders and sex with the look. But, nevertheless, this is not Casablanca. The film takes us to the Berlin defeated in 1945, the Potsdam Conference to be held. Captain Jacob Geismer (Clooney) comes as a journalist, and the violent death of an American soldier will take you to get into more trouble than thought. Soon you will find with Lena Brandt (Cate Blanchett), who was her lover in Berlin a few years ago. Not desvelaré much more of the plot, but if you say that you have other meeting points with the classic starring Bogart, including the final scene at the airport. And this can be both an advantage and a disadvantage. The advantage is the classic aftertaste that keeps the tape and reinforced by a great work of photography and a meticulous post-production. The disadvantage is that the attempt of tribute lastra both characters and script, so that the viewer has just realizing the trap and can discover where did address both.In the section of the interpretation, in addition to the histrionic character of Tobey Maguire (aka Spider-man), is remarkable of the protagonists. Clooney quite well, as always, but not just give the character the character you need and Blanchett with a beauty cold closer to Marlene Dietrich to Bergman. By the way the scenes of no-sexo star perhaps be the best of the film.Ultimately, the good German is an entertaining film, although it is ballast at times by the rigour that Soderbergh has self-imposed to be faithful to the film you want to honor. To highlight the protagonist couple and the care that has been the setting, both artistic and technical levels. For this reason, although it is not one of the best works of the director, today it is the best in billboard. Interesting.</body>
</review>
