<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Crash" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A portrait deliciously well set deep sensations of confronted feelings of realities crudely exposed</summary>
	<body>Only an accident, a whim of fate, a shock, perhaps the two cars in a city like los Angeles, where one without an engine with wheels is hardly anyone, is today able to make personal universes of every citizen. Violence is only capable of savvy a city of undead. Crash is a choral film where several stories intersect, following the pattern of "Grand Canyon", "Magnolia", "Vidas cruzadas" or "loves dogs". In this case, all the stories are good measures and collide pointing to the same place, in a portrait delightfully set deep sensations of confronted feelings of realities crudely exposed. A sincere and disturbing portrait on a city characterized by chaotic mixing of ethnic groups, racism, fear and lack of principles. A superb portrait on the agonizing loneliness of these solitary souls and prisoners of a dysfunctional society, violent, armed to the teeth, sadly dehumanization and in which all happen to be victims. But Crash also speaks of the intolerance and the loss of innocence. How there is room, however, for hope, for the magic, and as survives even the possibility us, freedom to always the worst or give the best as human beings. Also reminds us that the man is a very complex being that sinks in an impersonal and hostile society. Where victims of the confusion, the good are also becoming or discover as bad and the bad guys at the same time, as good. Where the moral line and the ethics of the current American society seem to be deleting dangerous and inevitably as the stroke of a chalk in the rain. And at the same time, is this a portrait of modern societies around the world.Paul Hagiis, who came to know for writing the script of "The million dollar baby", here performs a low budget film without that technically you notice at any time in the footage, full of intelligence and emotion. With a casting that works, some superb performances, a round and perfectly structured script, a successful look, a very successful and consistent atmosphere and a well-managed pace, which maintains the required tension and gives us glorious moments. A breath of air for the so predictable and boring Oscars and a pleasant surprise that demonstrates once again that, from Hollywood, in the meantime Boulder and much mud, still continue to arrive some pearls of the seventh art.</body>
</review>
