<review author="Caruco" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>May it lack of exceptional originality, or maybe that you like more or less, but it is a gift for the good lover of cinema.</summary>
	<body>"Letters from Iwo Jima" has its own entity, it is autonomous. But it is inevitable to see as the reverse, or the complement, "Flags of our fathers", the diptych that Clint Eastwood has done so many eager energy, despite his 76 years.Now, this invisible enemy, these almost-Martians who emerged from the underground with their weapons, or appeared in the middle of the night to jump over their victims in "Flags of our fathers", materialize and become flesh and blood, and also alma. Becoming in addition the contrast of these photogenic heroes that raised a flag in the Suribachi.Unos mount, Americans, used as icons of mass to raise funds for the war coffers. The other, heroes anonymous, whose last letters even reach their recipients.And together, the two movies, compose a recovery of the historical memory. Eastwood, during the massive presentation in "Letters from Iwo Jima" Japan, it seemed outrageous that the majority of young repudiation completely what has happened on the island of Iwo Jima in the World War II, where more than 20,000 compatriots lost their lives.We are all human beings.But above all, and was not to expect less, it is a story full of humanity. It highlights what should prevail is the individual above the absurdity of the war (or not so absurd to those who benefit economic, political or strategic), even if it is rational over the concept of the collective of "patria".It is clear that, for someone who poses his eyes in the Empire of the rising sun, the gaze of Eastwood is a Westerner. Although support in the indent of a Japanese Rookie, Iris Yamashita, the end and Cape, is a Connecticut Yankee in the Japanese Court who dares talk about characters and concepts far removed from his mind and world.However, his perspective is appropriate because, ultimately, what tells us is exactly the same. A Baker of Osaka or Tokyo, is what you want to translate Eastwood, just like one of Oklahoma or Kentucky; and all feel their fears, all have left behind something or simply all struggle to prevent their "homeland", or the future of their children, from falling into the hands of foreign barbarians.It is the battle of human beings with the same feelings of doubt and fear, with the family, wives, children and that life they had and who was forced to leave. In one of those details that are more significant than they appear to the naked eye, even the protagonist, general Kuribayashi (Ken Watanabe), professional, worship and tight, almost apologizes in one of his letters to his wife for the fact of having left outstanding, so everyday things how to fix the floor of the kitchen.The true triumph.Eastwood gives his vision of the Japanese perspective more intimate, and away from the parallel Assembly, between the front and the media circus that underwent the American heroes return to the United States.UU. The music of Michael Stevens and his son Kyle Eastwood, is as minimalist as effective, and appeals directly to the sensitivity. And the monocromatismo of photography, adapted to the coldness of this volcanic rock which is Iwo Jima, gives the film a more virtuous.It is also extraordinary, elegant, balanced and charismatic, the interpretation of Ken Watanabe, and Tsuyoshi Ihara, as Baron Nishi, and Olympic "hero" in riding.It may the content of "Letters from Iwo Jima" lack of an exceptional originality, or maybe you like more or less, but it is a gift for the good lover of cinema. And, like Mel Gibson in "Apocalypto", to highlight the courage of its author in this effort so that copies are exhibited worldwide in original version subtitled. This will make that they dramatically reduced sales of popcorn and entries in the multiplex; but the film, and in a way no less splendid, win.</body>
</review>
