<review author="Caruco" title="La vida de los otros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sequences, characters and images impressive, always emerging of honesty, sobriety and passion contained in the proposal.</summary>
	<body>The always watchful eyes, ears sharpened to the fullest, the face of impenetrable emotions. Captain Gerd Wiesler (Ulrich Mühe) is one of the best agents of the 'Stasi', the secret police of the former German Democratic Republic. It has the foolproof method, precise questions and the time required to ensure that any suspicion of treason or dissent to the nation, if guilty, end confessing or chasing his friends.In this Germany of the East prior to the fall of the Berlin wall, all citizens are suspect and the spirit of Orwell is resurrected to become the coveted dream of mechanisms and the desire of a Government which wants to have everything under control, and its residents well guarded. With this nod, the debuting of thirty years, Florian Henckel von Donnersmarck begins his narration precisely in 1984, in a GDR which seems rather anchored in a decade earlier, the seventies, and definitely aposentada Summit in the work of Orwell. there, Wiesler, you alias HGW XX/7, it is a neat and effective official with his work, and one of the best among the more than 170 thousand agents of the Stasi who came to be. An expert in infiltrating his nose and ears in others lives, redecorate the houses with hidden cables and microphones, and doing the word privacy may not make sense.Under suspicion.But, in another of the great successes of the Henckel film, for better or for worse, these agents of the security of the State we are presented as mere professionals or bureaucrats, simply, making his work, without resorting to the easy to show violent topic or maníqueos.And, like them, or as the citizens of the GDR, the infallible Wiesler also has the factor human, full of errors, weaknesses and feelings. Like the artist who should monitor, George Dreyman (Sebastian Koch), an author of theatre who, by work and commissioned by the interested party Minister of shift (Thomas Thieme), becomes another potentially subversive "intellectual" and under surveillance.Dreyman, and have it in insurance, is guilty at least of two offences: for that revuelvan you the bowels in a State where the talent is pursued, and having as it loving an actress so desired, as anxious, Christina-Maria Sieland (Martina Gedeck).Talent without repression.The man who knew too much, or the need to take sides. Listen to too can sink neighbor, or perhaps also make us understand better. Wiesler as Dreyman, as this magnificent film, characters made retained feelings and about to emerge. The work of its performers, and the secondary, is perfect, as the of a prodigious Martina Gedeck ("elementary particles"), presence and so irresistible voluptiosidad as fragile and dangerous.There are also scripts and images impressive, always emerging of honesty, sobriety and passion contained the proposal as that look of surprise Weisler to check, although hundreds of times, has witnessed an informing which filled his soul from disappointment.Even you can see in these acronyms of "HGW XX/7" a nod to another Welles, Herbert George Welles, author of this "War of the worlds", in whose status as invaders and invaded, escudriñados of the virus which can lead to the collapse of a system, are the characters and elements from "The lives of others". In any case, reasons ample there is to make it one of the best films of recent years.</body>
</review>
