<review author="Caruco" title="El último rey de Escocia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An estimable, and film made only $ 6 million.</summary>
	<body>Fiction or deception as a means to get closer to a reality, as the same film. Giles Foden's novel, which was based on "The last King of Scotland", introduces us to a newly licensed Scottish physician become the man of confidence of one of the most atrocious dictators in Africa, Idi Amin, among others, is it especially that honorary title of monarch.A dramatic appeal, like others, properly rigged, or adapted, showing the film by Kevin Macdonald, but they correspond to what happened and they serve to deflect our gaze towards another sad page of history in the black continent.In the case of the protagonist, the young man unconscious and sure if same, Nicholas Garrigan (James McAvoy), is inspired by several Western doctors who had contact with the Ugandan leader. "And it is embodied in a Forest Whitaker in State of grace, which provides its gaze, restless, playful and menacing, and its large presence, Idi Amin, the man who regió, based on fear and blood, the fate of Uganda from 1971 to 1979.""Black power" incident.A dictator cultivated the arts of war by the same British, sexually insatiable and charming, able to seduce both his people and the international press, but also a megalomano forward to change the world and, above all, a be distrustful and paranoid that would lead to torture and kill roundly. Its victims include more than 300,000 Ugandans, including soldiers to its own service.Is in a way "adapted" to the story, or closest to what happened, can eventually disappear one of the Ministers of Idi Amin (in reality, one even put land of through, exiling, fearing); the Asian minority were expelled (in a dedisión applauded by most Ugandan, but which would adversely affect trade, given the mood of these); accused the representative of "Cannibal" (and this black legend has contributed the fact that kept the severed heads of some enemies in the refrigerator); his petulance and bravado to the face, or send letters, to powerful (as to the Oedipal mother Patria British) heads of State; or which appeared one of the wives of Idi Amin dismembered.And the young doctor Nicholas Garrigan manifests itself as an extension of the rest of Western, unrelated to this harsh reality, and blinded in the comfort, luxuries, gifts and entertainment.Actors and actorazos.Formally, one of the best technical aspects of the film is a lightness, mounting, and photography that reflects very well the texture of the 1970s. A work in which he sure has had to see that previous career of MacDonald as a documentary filmmaker, and came to earning him an Oscar for best documentary in 1999 for "One day in September", on the attack of Palestinians against Jewish athletes in 1972, in Munich.En images that capture both the exotic fascination as madness, moves a James McAvoy perfect as Dr. Garrigan, but eclipsed in screen everytime appears the charismatic and frightening Idi Amin/Forest Whitacker, sometimes as a child in search of affection and understanding, others as an unbalanced capable of the worst. Do even shines a Gillian Anderson in his brief escenes, and does so with a change of? look? little remember their times of "X-files".And it highlights in a film that is not either be round or extraordinary, sinó rather irregular, illustrative and willful, and with some dramatic touch to what "A man called horse" doubtful; but an estimable film, made with only $ 6 million.</body>
</review>
