<review author="Caruco" title="La ciencia del sueño" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Four steps are perhaps the distance that separates us from the happiness dreamed the real, of our inner world outside, the genius to autism and the incompresión.</summary>
	<body>This is the type of movies that make me happy. So they have staff, and so they can get to surprise me. The tandem of Michel Gondry with the revered screenwriter Charlie Kaufman had given a product so special as "Forget me". But the French has now taken a necessary step, the spared Kaufman (hope that not defintivamente), to dive within their own universe.Perform a work, only faced with danger, with all its strengths and weaknesses, in which give rein to his status of artist, sole author, without the shadow of Kaufman, and to see that was capable.And behold, Gondry staged representation of two worlds, almost parallel. Not at all because they often intersect or touch. On occasions to learn how to coexist, in others to follow doomed to be separated. One is at the level of physical, imperfect but recognizable and easy to share; the other is more abstract, intangible, perfect but only in the imagination of oneself. Reality and fantasy.So far, so close.In the case of "The science of sleep", both worlds could join only giving four steps, exactly which are a door to another between neighbours in the same landing.Perhaps the distance that separates us from the happiness dreamed the real, of our inner world outside, the genius to autism and the incompresión. But there are four tour steps that can also be insurmountable. One of the dangers of detain too in our wonderful and utopian fantasies.It would be formidable to have the elegance and socanerría of a Cary Grant or Sean Connery. Or resemble the rebel without a cause born to live quickly and intensely, and die young but free, as the Laszlo Kovaks of Jean Paul Belmondo in "at the end of the escape"; become the cynical and hard, and sensitive, Philip Marlowe who played Humphrey Bogart in, for example, "the big sleep"; the honest, endearing and popular Ransom Stoddard of the James Stewart of "The man who shot Liberty Vallance"; even in el salvador Neo Keanu Reeves in "Matrix".Marijuana Gondry.Pero not. Then comes an individual of the ilk of Stéphane (a splendid Gael García Bernal), who invented his world; "does a fictional television show, horses of cardboard, impossible time machines, cotton clouds and buildings constructed with the? stop motion" of the more traditional animation. And a guy with a fair dose of stupidity, creativity and romanticism, which appears, settled there, either in Paris or in the big or small screen, and steals the heart, at the time that feeds our illusion.A Stéphane confronted with the reality of a grey work and the lot which must be swift, with a co-worker in a State of permanent zeal that revitalises your hormones, Guy (Alain Chabet); and with a neighbor, Stéphanie (Charlotte Gainsbourg), which could be the link to the "normal" world. With it, there so much win!, or both that lose!.I saw "The science of sleep" will be already more than four months in the last film festival in Sitges. Among the spectators who swarmed the aged film El Retiro, and an audience, perhaps too delivered, not stopped laughing and celebrate this invention by Gondry. Then, it was not a particular fan of his work. But in one of those rare and magical times, I also felt in communion with all of them.As Kaufman, or that crazy point to the Spike Jonze, will I need more doses of Gondry.</body>
</review>
