<review author="Caruco" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ideal for a quick consumption and, incidentally, to remove some awareness, between Dove and Dove.</summary>
	<body>Years ago that film left this idyllic view of Africa, well mystery and mysticism, and of a fascinating continent with large open spaces and landscapes filled with exoticism and dangers. It was the Africa adventurous and romantic from the seventies and eighties, was giving way to another type of treatment: the complaint and the drama of its inhabitants.A couple of seasons ago we had a good dose of the atrocities that were committed in interminable civil wars, "Hotel Rwanda"; and last year was "The constant gardener" which made us open our eyes on another made wild and criminal: the using its people as guinea pigs for large pharmaceutical industries. But, as already they managed to say the characters of one and another film, what happens to Africa and Africans, does not care (almost) anyone.One of the politicians that appear in "Blood diamond" also exposes the principle as: "the sad history of Africa is that whenever you find something of value its inhabitants suffer and die in misery." This has happened with ivory, with the gaucho, gold and oil. "And now with diamonds". And the use of slaves for decades, I might add.Child exploitation.On 1 December 2000, the general Assembly of the United Nations unanimously adopted a resolution to try to curb the trade in the dimantes in gross called "conflict zones", especially those from Angola and Sierra Leone. Rebel groups the Government used them to finance their bloody revolution.And that counting the plight of thousands of children used both as slaves in very long working hours extracting precious stones, such as children recruited as soldiers of the militia. In this regard, one of the best and most recent cries of denunciation from the world of entertainment has been the excellent song "Diamonds from Sierra Leone", no less brilliant rapper Kanye West (do and that begins with a? do sample? from the song by Shirley Bassey for the "diamonds are forever", in the 1971 James Bond).And this is also the best in the movie Edward Zwick, this attempt of complaint, and combine adventure and commitment by resorting to a format of blockbuster Hollywood whose list of actors is headed by two stars of the calibre of Leonardo DiCaprio and Jennifer Connelly, to try to reach the widest possible audience. Another issue is if the film Ray to the same height. 'Fast-food' reassuring.Zwick Orchestra a plot of codidias on a huge pink diamond found Solomon Vandy (Djimon Hounsou), a native who only want to meet again to his wife and children which was separate; and the unexpected Alliance that you will find in a white, Danny Archer (DiCaprio), born also in Sierra Leone, and a mercenary in appearance without scruples, who only cares that precious stone in question, but that it will be taking party along his journey with Solomon, and the encounter with a beautiful journalist (Jennifer Connelly), who tries to expose the tragedy of this people.Brainwashing, Liberation slogans and drugs, even obliged to test the blood of the son of Solomon and the objective of rescuing him from the clutches of the revolutionaries, becomes the main axis of awareness and denunciation, together with consumer interests to help explode and sink over that country.But the film develops routinely, with dialogue full of clichés, with characters so one-dimensional as the same reporter, or villains that appear. A strenuous footage and a quality Bill, but still the most anodyne patterns of the more well-trodden entertainment you both want to be committed and reassuring. It is shocking, but nice; with its moments of drama well calculated, distancing themselves from the true protagonists of the tragedy, and ideal for a quick consumption and, incidentally, removing some awareness, between Dove and Dove.</body>
</review>
