<review author="Ana" title="La ciencia del sueño" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The science of sleep has a very personal magic, does not resemble any other thing. It seduces with its peculiarities are not perfect and his experiments of a rather emotional narrative.</summary>
	<body>Texture of dreams made from things of every day with peculiarities, such as the material of the boxes for eggs or the cardboard toilet paper tube. The science of sleep this made of rare, but real things of every day. Michel Gondry has great sensitivity to find these fantastic things and then to interweave them in a narrative that goes between the real and the dream without making much difference. When is a dream and when life itself seems nightmare?The past two films by Gondry made them from the hand of screenwriter Charlie Kaufman (Being John Malkovich), who always tends to these mind games between twist realidad-ficción. Still in the science of sleep displays many items that they have in common, but the ingenuity of Gondry is more organic than the Kaufman and even arguably less mathematically cold. In the narrative of this film not everything is perfectly clear, nor clearly necessary, but it works.Gael García Bernal in the title role that their dreams are presented as if outside his own TV show, Stephan TV still thus, neither dreams nor reality come to be what he would like. This film is must much interpretation of Bernal maintained between panegyrics and calm, without becoming stay short at one end or the other. Stephan comes France Mexico for work that got him his mother which is supposedly creative but in reality is basic and very boring. His French is not very reliable so it oscillates between the English to be understood, and the Spanish for a moment of true desperation. Adding to the general confusion and the peculiar texture of the film.The science of sleep has a very personal magic, does not resemble any other thing. It seduces with its peculiarities are not perfect and his experiments of a good emotional narrativamás. A joyful tragedy which is quite an experience for the senses.</body>
</review>
