<review author="Nobody's perfect" title="Teresa, el cuerpo de Cristo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ray Loriga gets back behind the camera after ten years to give us a correct portrait of our more usual mystique. Portrait not excited and either adds nothing new.</summary>
	<body>Teresa, the body of Christ brings nothing new beyond show us a few bleeding sores more and carnal interpretation (and not both for the Episcopal Conference has been the cry in the sky? and never better said - as has done it) of love, here of the nun Teresa towards a God incarnated in the body of a Cristo-mancebo passion. Warning: who go with intention of seeing flesh, little goes to see - if anything Intuit - Paz Vega. Even so, the story of the adventures of this atypical nun of cradle, since enter as arrogant novice until he founded her own convent under the "old"rule is not tedious, even is entertaining at times. Moreover, Loriga tells us that Teresa de Cepeda y Ahumada was a woman in love with until the death of God, intelligent, rebel and campaigner, party, had visions and Bill. While it is true that this last is more surprising, these are all things that we already knew of the portrayed. Is missing, on the other hand, his facet as literary creator? which the director goes tiptoe-not in vain the work of Santa Teresa is considered Summit within the lyric of the Siglo de Oro Spanish.The pistol from my brother had been so far the only foray into the world of cinema by the author Ray Loriga as director. As the other (as writer), however, has written the screenplays for the seventh day (Carlos Saura) and absent (Daniel Calparsoro), and participated in meat Trémula (Pedro Almodóvar). In this production of Vicente Gómez also exercises the functions of writer: written by himself, he takes you to the screen. Note, however, that transfer of the text to the image the masterful help of cinematographer José Luis Alcaine, as well as the art of costume designer Eiko Ishioka, winner of an Oscar for Dracula, and support in the music of Ángel Illarramendi. Perhaps all these elements that get that this film will not be in mediocre, but not raised, only for this reason, in the category of "a good movie". As photography is concerned, the indiscriminate succession of pictorial compositions of pre-Raphaelite Court can lead to boredom to the Viewer. Abusive succession of pictures, adequate to see in an art gallery, not so much perhaps in a cinema.Paz Vega as Santa Teresa is contained. The role requires. But he notices. We are witnessing a contained interpretation Yes, forcibly contained. The guess little comfortable in the skin of the Mystic. The rest of actors complete the cast of the movie, master most. Side more or less usual our film as Álvaro de Luna, José Luís Gómez or Manuel Morón. They note that they have craft and art. The part of secondary female get worse stop: Geraldine Chaplin and Leonor Watling, each making Geraldine Chaplin and Leonor Watling, respectively.As a CODA, not I refuse to mention two sentences in the film refer to the own Santa Teresa: "Endemoniada not, but all engolfada of God", said by herself, and "is ascent of prayer", commented by the always magisterial Eusebio Poncela (what a shame that her role is so short).</body>
</review>
