<review author="Rafa Martín" title="The host" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Relatively recommended, and with some other genuine fright and good suspense, although it seems rather a mere excuse to criticize, criticize and criticize.</summary>
	<body>Her have been sold as a horror movie, but this film no way to sell it. Part homage to Alien, part social commentary, part environmental discourse, part comedy, The Host is one of those movies that aims to be more than what it really is (a film with bug, for God's sake) and that takes all the prizes in all the festivals because the filmmaker is called Smith, or Pérez, but Bong Joon-Ho, author of the fucking great Memories of Murder, by what this film really worth that is entertaining and has momentazo but isn't bad, has been elevated to the category of resurrection of the genus (without knowing that it has already taken place and is called The Descent).Total, the thing starts when a doctor (American) tells his lackey (South Korean) cast forty gallons of formaldehyde into the River have. Five minutes later, in the middle of a quiet park and in full light of day, appears the bug in question: a trout with legs and teeth as my arm of long dedicated to make picadillo a halfway and carried the other to his hideout in the sewers. Among the abducted is the infant daughter of Park Kang-Du, a young newsagent who has the misfortune of being stupid and rescue from the clutches of the monster girl is not (the side which makes when he realizes is priceless). Together with his family that included his father, owner of the business, its Executive brother and sister champion of archery, rush to the hunting of the bug to a brutal pace for an hour and a half. Then the movie realizes it is pigeonholing, and as this is very bad, check the hand brake, what pisses us off living.Do because even more or less that hour and a half goes like silk, with sequences very entertaining as the flight of the family of the hospital where quarantined, and dominated by the humor? eccentric? and that both like Mondosonoro, for example, carried his characters a liar to wafers in half of a funeral for the victims. In Memories Of Murder humor works by making a parody the futility of the security forces. Here is to make grace to make. And that do not see as it distracts. Obviously The Host has ambitions, and today the height of the film with claims is to attack American politics, what seems very well provided that you do not a film with bug. If're going you to do, do it as do the Japanese with this metaphor of the Hiroshima bomb which is Godzilla, not to a diabolical scientist (Paul Lazar, the cross-eyed entomologist of the silence of the Lambs) that lacks only two horns, the Trident and the tail.So just after a splendid scene of hunting (family, stuck, waiting for the bug in a cabin), the thing for fifteen minutes or thing, where is tells us that the only way to act is to use Agent Orange (especially despicable chemical weapon) to put an end to the bug. And there are demonstrations of ecologists, and social criticism, and more pana to United States (that being there in Seoul as fifty years, what makes you be logical for the South Korean Viewer, not for me, I want a movie with bug).The case is that The Host is very well directed (what levels is removed, the very mamón). Trout with legs sing much, but is to be welcomed that the director does not play with the shadows, with light or with the blows of effect. The monster causes fear because we do not know what it is capable, we know that can resist, nor we know how you can end up with him, not because we do not see. Boon shows more than suggests, but is so skillful that it gets through the obstacle without any problems. As actors, to highlight the protagonist, Song Kang Ho, very correct in his role of alelao and the girl who plays his daughter and that is carrying the weight of the suspense of the film (his attempt to escape from the monster, which at that time is asleep, is the second great scene of the film). Of the others, because it's always. So meet. is there. Like many by its depth, and for his attempt to deal with a multitude of issues. But when I go with the "horror movie" chip put in my head, I prefer more direct things, and I would have apetecido more something pure and simple gender. In any case, relatively recommended, and with some other genuine fright and good suspense, although it seems rather a mere excuse to criticize, criticize and criticize. Americans know, I thing, you know. They are bad. Leave them in peace. And give me more I bug.</body>
</review>
