<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Invisibles" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bardem, away from the ephemeral flashes and vacuum couché, has produced a film to give voice and image to victims of conflicts forgotten or neglected by the media of communication.</summary>
	<body>Javier Bardem does not conform to the photo of rigor in the refugee camps rigged in ways of Colonel Tapiocca or holding a bowl to a dying on the Bank of the ganges, not. Bardem, away from the ephemeral flashes and vacuum couché, has produced a film to give voice and image to victims of conflicts forgotten or neglected by the media of communication.In doing so he has worked with Médecins sans Frontières and has convinced five filmmakers to make two separate short films about ignored problems of the third world: Wim Wenders, Isabel Coixet, Javier Corcuera, Mariano Barroso and Fernando León Aranoa.El result is invisible, a film documentary that far from being film of evasion, is cinema of invasion - of consciousness. Isabel Coixet has focused on Chagas disease - caused by a parasite that causes mortality in Bolivia. Javier Corcuera still trying some underprivileged in Colombia trip to recover their land seized by armed groups. Mariano Barroso shows us the paradox between health and money that occurs with a very profitable drug to cure sleeping sickness and all business marketed as inhibitor of the growth of hair.Wim Wenders shows the heartbreaking testimonies of Congolese women who have been raped by militias and guerrillas of the country and Fernando León de Aranoa try to shine in the eyes of children who sleep in shelters in Uganda fearing to be recruited in the night and be converted to paper soldiers.With exposed, nobody will eat some popcorn seeing this work, shocking where there them and very far from pseudo conscience assaults more Hollywood as blood diamond, the constant gardener or Babel. The latter seek also swell their coffers and here there is no famous actors or special effects, or romance, or chance. It is raw and hard reality. Bardem, who could well have been dedicated to designing men's fragrance, allocated profits from the film to Médecins sans Frontières. For that reason, alone worth this binge of injustice that feel like a slap.</body>
</review>
