<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Teresa, el cuerpo de Cristo" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It started with the band's controversial film of the season, and however stays in a portrait meapilas that well could have been made forty years ago, with censorship in full swing.</summary>
	<body>We have met with the Church kind reader. And after this small tribute to Miguel de Cervantes, there is to say that if it is difficult to make a film about religious subjects today without offending anyone, so too speak of it without hurting any kind of sensibility. For more centuries that have past by more theoretically evolved to be the human being, there are certain topics that will always cause controversy, and religion, whatever, is one of them. And if a it tape religious put you a title so striking and provocative as Teresa: the body of Christ, already have served a good serving of controversy, which will mean a greater expectation from the audience at the same time.Ten years after his first film, Ray Loriga returns the address to show us from a theoretical new point of view to Santa Teresa de Jesús, a key figure in the history of the Catholic Church. Loriga intended to bring the viewer a character well known to all, both books of history and previous films, with a fresh and new vision, away to Saint Theresa of pure mysticism and showing his human and carnal side. However, Teresa: the body of Christ moves away from the commercial and initial intention of Loriga, offering insight into blessed and prudish character; rather than portraying a woman with lights and shadows, and their struggle, the filmmaker conducts a purely hagiographic portrait. Also it must be said that one of the keys of the step to the posterity of Santa Teresa was his literary work, and such work appears on the tape in a disgraceful background. The script, part of which the own verses of Santa Teresa, make it up (in a surreptitious manner) is flat and devoid of feeling. The direction of Loriga is lousy, slow until exhaustion, and lacking any notion of what the film rhythm, which happily contributes its nefarious installation. Ray Loriga cares more than the visual aspect of his work that the story itself, and that happens invoice from the opening sequence. There are a number of scenes, the daydreams of Santa Teresa, in which the tape stripe as ludicrous. The only positive aspects of so ineffable title are costume design and photography of José Luis Alcaine, really merit taking into account the desire of its director to make colorful pictures in motion. Best of the tape, is certainly the interpretation contained of Paz Vega, showing all her natural acting ability with a brutal change of registration and sober.Teresa: The body of Christ started with the band's controversial film of the season, and however stays in a portrait meapilas that well could have been made forty years ago, with censorship in full swing. Perhaps some critics should form a secret Inquisition, in which we would act moved to preserve the good name of the film, leading to works such as this to his well-deserved fate: the purifying fire.</body>
</review>
