<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>These defectillos, not as large as it may seem for my comment, do not prevent the viewer passes two entretenidísimas hours of pure cinematic spectacle in which will be without a doubt one of the most remembered films of this year.</summary>
	<body>It's one of the films most awaited by fans around the world and I could not miss the opportunity of seeing her three weeks in advance, mercy to the invitation sent by Warner Bros. Spain and muchocine.netLa excitement was palpable in the room and was not for less: "300" is based on a prestigious comic of the less prestigious no Frank Miller and is directed by Zack Snyder, whose first film, "Dawn of the dead", was a great cover letter.For many, the story is well known but still I rhubarb unveil too. We are in the year 480 BC and the huge Persian army led by Xerxes (Rodrigo Santoro) prepares to attack Sparta. With certain political problems that prevent you from bringing together his entire army, the Spartans King Leonidas (Gerard Butler) brings together 300 of his best men and prepares to deal with the Persians in a narrow passage known as Thermopylae. The rest is history, but if you don't know don't you worry because you do not need.If something is raising expectations and is going to give that talk in the film is its visual treatment. I have already heard everything on the subject: if they are cartoons that if everything is computer, if they are painted decorations? My recommendation is that you do not think at all that and simply be carried away by the feast full of force and spectacular images that flood the film. There is no point in any projection in which there is a striking image and little matters if they are generated by computer or not; the result is visually perfect.It is instead what is talking about little other aspects which to me I found outstanding. The sound, for example, is impressive. The storms, the advance of the army of Xerxes or the voices like thunder on the battlefield, echo in the ears as a few times, reaching mingle at some point with the impressive soundtrack of Tyler Bates, that I do not know how it will work without the support of the images, but since then, heard in the film is of the most memorable of recent times.Another aspect that attracts perhaps less attention, as usual in this kind of films, is the interpretation. We must applaud the work of casting because the actors conform to their characters like a glove.Gerard Butler, an actor who always seemed to me that it was missing some strength, put all eggs in one basket and composed a Leonidas very hard and fair at the same time, with an irreproachable honor code (for a Spartan, clear). His voice, his presence, his charisma on screen make us understand that we we have a King who anyone would continue until the same hell. An example of the bottom picture in which the gaze of Butler, only understandable for those who have seen the movie or read the comic, says more than thousand words.Beside it, a Lena Headey beautiful, giving full force of character imaginable in the Queen of Sparta. His character, which would make that a man faced an army only to protect her, stars in the parallel story in Sparta that is sensed but did not on the original comic. This story is very well introduced and has so much interest that is it missing to begin no earlier than it does, because it also serves resting between battles and therefore helps modulate the pace of the film. The rest of the cast meets their roles perfectly but I would like to highlight the imposing presence of Rodrigo Santoro as Xerxes (see photo above). Presence that, in addition to the interpretation of the actor, is achieved in two ways. The first is well created that are special effects that make us it appear as a King of more than two metres in height, huge front of Leonidas (already itself high and robust). The second is the tremendous physical transformation of the actor, a guaperas of truth, which hardly recognizes with makeup and digital retouching.But no it has seemed a perfect movie so I will mention the defectillos that I see that they are more feelings than to objective factors. And my feeling is that, in certain moments, the film is too excessive and causes a certain saturation of stimuli in the Viewer.On the other hand, in my opinion what the tape is maremoto lacks of pure emotion. We are witnessing the battles with completely clouded by the visual feast your senses, but that prevents us from thrill us or us to really worry about the evolution of these battles or its protagonists. Speaking of battles, I think that it would have nothing happened if one of them had been trimmed slightly in the editing room.But these defectillos, not as large as it may seem for my comment, do not prevent the viewer passes two entretenidísimas hours of pure cinematic spectacle in which will be without a doubt one of the most remembered films of this year and that shows that Zack Snyder is called to become one of the most important principles of century conductors.</body>
</review>
