<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Bosque de sombras" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do me the favor run billboards of movie theaters in your city to look for her to go to see her. Opera prima a renowned short film maker such as Koldo Serra, already deserves if entry to discover it in the film.</summary>
	<body>First of all, if they have not seen yet, do me the favor run billboards of movie theaters in your city to look for her to go to see her. Opera prima a renowned short film maker such as Koldo Serra, already deserves if entry to discover it in the film, which is the ideal place for the objective enjoyment of a work like this. Comparisons did not escape anyone, that is the reality, and in addition seeks originality in a desperate and anxious industry under this vomiting of remakes, sequels and prequels American. But by this same is remarkable an original proposal such as the raised here. As remarkable is, without doubt, a mise en scene enveloped in a successful claustrophobic atmosphere thanks, in large part, to a magnificent and planned work in art direction, recreating lovingly this Northern landscape and the rural environment of the deepest Spain of the 1970s. A virtue is the director himself, to recognize and take some cinematographic intentions clear, specific, inspired and influenced other referents of such magnitude as it is the own Peckinpah. References and comparisons here already invite one to dream of cinema of truth and are welcome. Let's say that the sources, in this case, already support starting the story you want to tell.He has been criticized from some parts the script, and even some of the dialogues or interpretations, but it is true that the demands of the languages involved in the shooting and the plot of the film are notable, and here the problem of having to English actors chapurreando Spanish and Hispanic actors to advocate as best they can with the EnglishIt is that at the end of everything, they end by bending you the movie as well as allowing that some of the actors are dubbed themselves, which almost always ends in something close to the catastrophic. I think the only thing that happens perhaps is, some isolated moments there in some other uncontrolled downturn in the overall pace of the film which can, in turn, leave the viewer out and hinder the final climax. But as yet, the film stays full until the end and will give us also a couple of memorable scenes and a clear sense of sobriety and good job behind the camera. "Forest of shadows" a very decent debut that brings together a great photograph and talent for a story with their own style.</body>
</review>
