<review author="Dragon negro" title="Inland empire" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fear, despair, boredom, curiosity, exhaustion, intensity, frustration, fascination, despair, will leave the film mulling over what you've seen or tried to forget it.</summary>
	<body>Fear, despair, tedio, curiosity, exhaustion, intensity, frustration, fascination, despair, all these feelings and more can/can have during the three hours that lasts the new torment or genius perpetrated by David Lynch.Para start do not case of the official synopsis can be found around the film, little have to do with what you are going to see. The film begins with a girl watching television and crying, a scene ira reappearing over the footage and is one of the keys to unravel this complex film. The next scene is another good example of the film to which we have become accustomed to Lynch, the visit of the new neighbor that gets a dialogue that it will gradually grow in tension and absurd, what promised to be an innocent visit just turning into something really strange, evil and terrifying. From here and during the first hour of film everything seems to be more or less coherent and meaningful, but the entrance through a mysterious door with a strange name marked chalk in an alley will the protagonist to find evil (already prophesied in the scene with the neighbor) and it is here where go backwhere everything starts to become confusing and where the nothing seems to make sense.And it is in Inland Empire around a turning back is back, everything is cyclical, it mingle the yesterday, today and tomorrow without that we know very well which is which, like the real life of the actress and her character in the filming of a movie that is a remake of a cursed film that never saw the light. Lynch plays with the love and sex, and again mix of real life and fiction between the Idyll of the actress and actor, both married in real life and in fiction and whose acts will have serious consequences, as we are already warns.The succession of scenes, in principle without sense, seems to have some consistency in small details, every scene is reference in another and everything seems to be a confusing dream, or nightmare, in which things are mixed and tells us the same over and over again but with different scenario, at various times, but with some similarity. There are guidelines that are repeated during the footage, and when everything seems to come to an end, we again bring back to the beginning of the film and misplaced us once again. New references to the film within the film, reality and fiction fused in the mind of a Hollywood star that comes at the end of the journey of the film really emaciated, a Laura Dern in an interpretation of luxury.There are a thousand details to decipher in Inland Empire, renumbered them all here would be impossible, but I have already given some, the rest will have to find you and put together the pieces to try to give some meaning to the film, if it is that you really get found it, probably will have to see the film twenty times and still be doubts, perhaps only Lynch has in his head the solution or perhaps neither he knows herin any case you will be the film mulling over what you've seen or tried to forget it.</body>
</review>
