<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="The host" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>New reading of the film monsters. Much less good than some vocinglan and acceptable in their mediocrity as adult film. Entertainment has in spades when the creature to the puñeta with their baboserías. Outside there, little meat that cut, none to sell.</summary>
	<body>I'm afraid disagree, for once, with the militant movie fan orthodoxy that ensures the excellence of a film when I only look at more of the same, but in this case (and that is relevant) with that attributable to Korean culture cultural decontamination. I'm afraid disagree because I have not seen much pessimistic criticism and there are more praise than dissent. To The Host attributed excessive virtues when he possesses (is true) only some.Japanese inheritance of post-nuclear monster has powerfully crystallized in the idiosyncrasies of a country of huge Western adhesions, which has a cultural reference next in Hollywood and cela undeniable own identity heritage. In this context, Bong Joon-ho perpetrating the masterstroke of the Millennium Startup: a monster film alien yankee merchandising with enough charms national to enrapture all Korean eager to iconic spree and with much influence Hollywood, of course.Korea of the South is not a shielded territory: it is porous, permeable. This factory of scares scares not in excess: the monster is well explained, is well designed and is surprisingly well dosed, although it appears much more than the aliens and sharks that have nourished the film - with - recent creature. By this or more that are desgranará lines more down, The host are not excited. Do you like? Because no dislike, that is already enough. The family resource is well focused, but poorly written. Do not understand Korean humor or the pseudodramático mass of crocodile tears which the dedicated characters release so that we understand that they are very aggrieved at the loss of the youngest of the family, which is to be the emotional axis on which scales all footage (cumbersome).Containing portentous scenes such as the first time we see the monster on the banks of the River have Seoul, The host then falters by the weight of its own machinery of fiction. Gives equal has trouts positions with regard to chemical weapons or that one understands that the director wanted to sneak us a subtle speech about the dangers of the dictatorships of the welfare state. That is all very well, but the building collapses when we realize that twenty minutes of very good boot have already staged everything you wanted to see. The rest is a silly jokes and abuse tours technologically achieved by the sewage of the city.Political speculation comes alive with sharpness. The monster is the excuse to acogotar the neck of the citizen. It often happens. The protagonist family (excusad to not give names) is portrayed with a verismo Italian style, perhaps detailing too rigorously its reasoning and its psyche. It is not a film of Bergman or Sirk. Its ready director so requires. The host may indicate a jaded American cultural colonialism country moral temperature: physicians are American, the culprit of all the barbarism is American and decisive methods are Americans, i.e. excessive, cinematic, turgid, hollow, baldíso, in the last and obvious instance."kaiju" or Asian cinema to the Godzilla and company owes The host a greening of unpredictable dimensions. If so far West was called to steal scripts of ghosts and amazed, we now have a blockbusteriano Philo, a vein of gold unpublished. I fear the worst. We didn't have enough with the Americans and now we have slanted eyes creatures for trampling on the billboards.Another notable inconvenience is the mixture between horror and comedy film. There are moments in which you do not know if he attends a parody to the Scary movie or the original. The family epic is deslabazada, fraying. Those moments of domestic privacy sins of naïve, arroba one not requested bis comic that makes the whole dash. On the other hand, the scenes with monsters offset this decline of tension. We have criticized many times film supported in the presence of a creature (predator, Alien, jaws, Jurassic Affairs or Mimic) evident shortcomings outstanding one: characters without substance, near argument in the invisible. Therefore now is one that backtrack. What wrong with The host is precisely this: the family thing, the strictly emotional plane. What going you to do.There are changes of registry innecesariso, abrupt. There are dedicated players that not can rank in good or bad because the script are given does not offer sufficient attractiveness as its work esplenda and excited. The question is, after all, fundamental: does lack emotion in a movie of bugs?Not the idea that the film is not bad you must detach from this review. It is not, at all. What is not and must not find three feet to the mutant bugs is an outstanding film or relevant or as one wants to say. It is not new SAP to the fantastique. Nor is there a before and an after in the film monsters. Three minutes from the Nostromo in Alien fill more than twenty of this by the sewerage of Seoul. No despiste thrills avid reader. The scenes that open the film (the Monster's attack on the banks of the river) are absolutely recommended. Is it worth paying for ten minutes?</body>
</review>
