<review author="Puspus" title="The host" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With some brutal beat downs, with a viral subplot that nobody ends up understanding and a finish that is pure delirium...</summary>
	<body>Soon after a decidedly dramatic start "The Host" reveals its Achilles heel: is 100% Korean. And this explains that in their country of origin has raised more than sixty million dollars and Spain, France or United States just get staying in the top ten more than a couple of weeks. The public West, between which logically myself, is not yet ready for Asian cinema. Yes. The Japs movies are cool. The Korean also. And the Chinese, as no. They have disturbing images, they are original, not draw attention. But we will never achieve that they fill us at all, we persuaded. These guys are really very disturbed. Comes to the head "Old Boy", "The curse", "Hero", "Audition", "Kung-Fu-Sion", "Battle Royale". What happens to these people? Is there something in the water who drink again them tarumbas? Are there other bacteria in the sushi that we had not spoken? All the named are tremendously innovative films that revolutionize, one way or another, the thriller, horror, martial arts, suspense, comedy, action. but with which they never connect because, unfortunately, we do not have slanted eyes. "The Host" has magnificent scenes, transgressive humor, characters that you adoptarías and visually is cane. But the Japs are the Japs and not conform to, easily and simply, a monster film. They have to mix the horror and humor, politics and al gore, Spielberg and Lynch. and clear, so get them. With some brutal beat downs, with a viral subplot that nobody ends up understanding and a finish that is pure delirium. What going you to do. These guys are as well. They prefer to complicate the existence of sign masterpieces. Nevertheless, and as the gafapastas we are already almost legion, "The Host" will become collector's item when it comes out on DVD. I would never say that it is a good film (God frees me) but yes I would dare to say that you it's an entertaining rarity that won't leave anyone indifferent. How many films American or national killed by a review as well!</body>
</review>
