<review author="Puspus" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excite not excited and also presents its faults (too much footage, dialogues forced...) but is entertaining and complies with its mission of stretch consciences. Money well spent.</summary>
	<body>A Director as Edward Zwick, common in the movies for the showcasing of the shift guaperas (Brad Pitt in "Legends of the fall", Tom Cruise in "The last samurai", etc.), a server did not expect much. But hoped that, because the frame on the African continent and be about the recruitment of kids and trafficking of precious stones, "Blood diamond" Yes to provide something more than the usual succession of snapshots of di Caprio smiling at dusk. Fortunately it happened and the film, without being perfect, it rises above the average and entertains more than two hours and peak that lasts. The cause must be sought in the script, because it shows worked and is approaching its fragments more escrabosos with the seriousness and respect that they deserve. In this way we encounter scenes such as amputations to machete or the murder of the child, unthinkable in a product of these features, that not never forgets his interest in the box office, but they are there, with his brutal intention of complaint exposed. The music of almost always impeccable-James Newton Howard, the spectacular African landscapes and the worth of Mr Zwick to shoot spectacular scenes of action also provide theirs. And what to say at this stage of an actress as Jennifer Connelly. to me this girl already gives me like you do, which I always think is extraordinary. It does not usually happen the same with model Djimon Housou, usually relegated to empty productions of action/adventure, but here discover as an interpreter loaded with talent. Leonardo di Caprio, curiosities of life, should be the most benefited from the trio, because for something the plot of the film is structured to his around, however, nominations to separate Oscar, me me is the least successful of the three. Simply me so I don't believe in the role of cynical smuggler of diamonds. It is that childish face, this soft fluff that makes up his knob, these golden mechitas. A character so ambiguous and skeptical as that interprets would have needed an older actor, with best saddlebags. I speak of Clive Owen, or Russell Crowe or even our "spanish friend" Viggo Mortensen. If what the academics wished was to relaunch the career of Di Caprio (something that I doubt that the boy needs), there were "Infiltrators" to enjoy an outstanding performance and seamless-just. In this with nominate Housou had enough. In short, things in the film. So, in short, "Diamond of blood" is a good film and with this I am referring to it belongs to that class of movies that like everyone, folks, grandparents and children. Excite not excited and also presents its faults (too much footage, dialogues forced.) but is entertaining and complies with its mission of stretch consciences. Money well spent.</body>
</review>
