<review author="Dover157" title="King Kong" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>King Kong</summary>
	<body>The effort of the director for making this film making in his masterpiece narrowly costs, health, money, and his wife...xD. and is the great Peter both efforts made in the draft that thickened about 25 kilos in a short time, surpassed the initial budget in 200 million dollars and his wife are gossip. Or we have a movie cared for to the smallest detail, with some really impressive visual effects, a pretty good picture and some appropriate actions. And is that this king kong 2005 difference well little of the original of the year 1933 in terms of characters and plot. Some scenes are calcadas to the original thus respecting the previous work and throwing a little land that terrible remake of 1973 with Jesica lange in the role of the diva.So I think that is why thank the director to us beyond shown a film true to the 1933 that although the argument is not very complicated this new version has tried to deepen the relationship between the woman and the beast. To highlight the great work of Naomi wats for transmitting the affection that comes to feel for the APE and the performance of Carl Denham in the role of Jack Black. But I think that above actions this sovretodo special effects, a display of technique and engineering that leaves with the mouth open more than one.To begin this introduction to New York City in the 1920s is simply splendid, and later the island skull, with indigenous peoples, the rugged jungle, huge creatures and the mighty Kong. A very well recreated Gorilla, both modeling and movements (thanks to Andi Serkis). But although as throughout this film sins of several things. The most serious is its duration, because certain scenes from my point of view is the could have saved, because there are scenes such as the of the ship that sobran and make heavier waiting to see the ape. The duration is a burden that has failed to calibrate well Peter and unfortunately will cost dearly.And other negative point is the soundtrack. Here Peter has neglected her more than the Lord of the rings. It is not that it is bad, only expected a soundtrack to the height of the ESDLA. I think even the game has better soundtrack. By the way, the official game of the movie is highly recommended, it shows the hand of the director and that is welcome because it is fairly faithful to the film.In short, I strongly recommend you see this film to the film because seeing her on TV screen is a crime. That you not take back their 3 hours of footage, in the end I left a good taste in mouth.</body>
</review>
