<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="The host" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Well above the spectacular and popcorn maker, The host exorcise effectively the fears and desires of contemporary Korean society, inoculated by the deadly virus from the apathy and despair.</summary>
	<body>Turn off the TV and we eat to taste! The horror genre has given us little but exceptional moments of good political cinema? in my memory are the night of the living dead (Romero, 1968) or the invasion of the Snatchers of bodies (Siegel, 1956), and also the invaluable M, the vampire of Düsseldorf (Lang, 1931)-, even though they could not tune with the sensitivity of the public nothing receptive to link good show with intellectual metaphorat least the enjoyment by staging it will always thank. It is the case of The host, a more than good political movie, and a no less compelling and enjoyable (at times, but what moments!) horror film.As in Chronicle of a serial killer, Joon-Ho (not confused you, please, with John Woo) showed us that he knew combine intelligence with a thriller with intentions cross the pilgrims that adolescent gender issues, to give us a work that exudes a fierce critique of institutional delay and corruption that his country, South Korea without Fireworks. However, while on that occasion Joon-Ho leads his narration to a narrative poetic and bitter, without offering us hope or shelters who grab our mood, The host seems convinced that only from below, from the construction of a real active citizenship, can his country attacking the Leviathan that numbs and convinces her that the best option is to shut up and wait to the (non-existent) virus(by the way) for the delay and defeatism is thin.In this sense, the protagonist portrayed in the movie family becomes as a plural and lucid metaphor on the Korean citizen mood: clumsy father, boyish and almost always asleep; the unemployed Bachelor, idealistic and ashamed of his impoverished family; does sister medalist, acting always afternoon, sentenced to the sad bronze? And the girl, that girl presented by the director as the most capable of biting the beast from within and without browbeat, is the hope of a Korea as numb as his protagonist, so convinced of its uselessness as that father awakened only by the tragedy of seeing his daughter die.As in his previous film, Korean filmmaker gets without subtlety several fingers into the wound on the situation in his country. Only the boot and the closure of this film say it all. An official brought the Allied and envied United States? is the scene in which the medical team is block and simulates effectiveness to see how goes his American counterpart - worthy of Charlie is (us not forget) the trigger for the tragedy, coupled with the feeling of inferiority and the adocenamiento of the Korean citizen. The position of the director with respect to American interventionism is very clear, as is the vision of fragile, corrupt and little professional institutions, who makeup the reality. In this respect, appreciate the causticidad of the scene in which the officer sheathed in his yellow monkey turn on television to inform those affected.The host not can therefore be taken as a horror film to use (American), although scenes such as the attack of the beast in the park or the terrifying spitting of the animal in the sewer well worthy of shark or Alien (this is how we are presented with this movie posters and promotional videos). Well above the spectacular and popcorn maker (which already for just these reasons is a great proposal to enjoy two Sabbath hours), The host effectively exorcise fears and desires of contemporary Korean society, and by extension, as already did it the stylized V for vendetta, of all the countries of Western (and westernized), inoculated by the deadly virus from the apathy and despair. Perhaps the most beautiful of the film is the scene which the father (the entire family) struggles to get out of the bowels of the beast to his daughter. And the rain that wraps everything in Joon-Ho movies, as washing, who soaked, the darkness that surrounds them (does in Eastern iconography water seem to possess this dual role of Messenger of fate? see The ring or Dark water- and restituidora turn of the order). And this priest, approaching the child that her daughter rescued and that he himself shall adopt as its own. And, above all, the iconoclastic and ironic, final worthy of Billy Wilder.</body>
</review>
