<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="La ciencia del sueño" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The science of sleep has put their expectations in the presentation of animated frames that plastificaran the inner world of the character with imagination and optimism, but fails. Rather, it stuns, disconcerting and SAPs.</summary>
	<body>Long live the disruption! This proclaims that judgment the character soñambulista who plays with solvency? but the truth is that to look like alelado it should not be the very Stalislavski - Mexican Gael García Bernal, is not just a fleeting remnant that accompanies this stew of pseudoníricas images that is the science of sleep. No, it is something more, it is a statement of intent by a Michel Gondry released the excellent scripts Charlie Kaufman had attended him so far with one genius that manifest in the master forget about me! and at the bottom and deranged (but with a personal logic) Human nature. And it is that in the science of sleep everything seems disorganized, as a collage pasted randomly through a pastiche of frames mounted without criterion. Do as much who wants to Gondry, nobody ends up believing the more or less imaginative world? thing up I doubt - the duermevelas of the protagonist. Instead, the proposal to set crumble with ease, giving the feeling that one has attended a meeting of naïfs scenes (that's the word: naive), which of course not just sojourns at any port. Perhaps believed the director presenting numerous dislocated images and depicting the emotional world of the young lovers, the viewer would be hallucinating film and waving Palms in the air. Not enough, Gondry, is not enough.Indeed, it is curious that end enjoying more of the woodyalleniano character of the co-worker, a fun Alain Chabat, that of-already at the end of the agonizing film - Odyssey of the troubled Stephane. And it is that you better a goat on a ridge than clouds flying. The science of sleep has put their expectations in the presentation of animated frames that plastificaran the inner world of the character with imagination and optimism, but fails. Rather, it stuns, disconcerting and SAPs.There are moments that lifted the film, but that lasts a blowing. As I have already said, Chabat and his dialogues are gold, as they are silver first daydreams of Gael. The pelotuda and fellow couple geek is sympathetic, serving as a counterpoint to the pragmatic Chabat. Does Charlotte Gainsbourg? to eat at the scene of the party, with this mini sesentera - as if nothing happens between dream and dream of your agilipollao can partner? The rest is cardboard, papier-mâché and cotton. Who expect to return to the universe of forget me! You will feel disappointed. Nowhere near approaching him. It would be like comparing the cut and paste pre-school with a Chagal.</body>
</review>
