<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Bosque de sombras" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In backwoods tension arrives late and no reason to make it credible. In this sense, script failures are fateful, order what could have been a suggestive movie. It will be for the next, Koldo.</summary>
	<body>First feature film of Bilbao Koldo Serra, but not his first experience. In 1993 he made his first short film Sick of you, with WINS at the Valencia Cinema Jove. Followed by night car, Hachar me!, and love of mother (1999) and the Witch (2003), all very juicy's train. With this latest win many awards, among them the Meliés of gold to the best European fantastic film of 2003 short film. Also it has given TV spot (Licor 43, Bizkaia tourism, Galicia Calidade) and video clips (the dream of Morfeo, OBK, Extremoduro, Siniestro Total) as a filmmaker, Assistant of direction, storyboard artist and screenwriter. The boy also provides graphic design, such as writing for film festivals and samples of short films. He has published a comic album titled the beast of the day. Finally, Koldo knows the ex officio, but need many more notches in his revolver.In times of creative dryness, we hope that novice filmmakers take us out of darkness and us deslumbren with his materials operas fresh and desprejuiciadas. It happened with Amenábar or the small of the Trueba and Koldo Serra is presented in the media as a promising rookie which is poised to give us good moments of cinema? indeed, Amenábar also debuted with a thriller, gender greedy but very difficult to boot the attention of the public, perhaps because of the saturation. I have no doubt that Koldo is going in the right direction. Truth is that the technical Bill for backwoods is outstanding, and to newcomer he notices that he does know take the camera where required. And the Guipuzcoan exteriors are magical. But it ceases to count. The casting is deficient? except Oldman and Homar-both or more as it is dubbing (it is painful to hear Aitana!). The actors who interpret the brothers? a rookie Jon Ariño; Andrés Gértrudix, which at times is the more credible; and Kándido Uranga - are comic. Aitana is - besides unrecognizable - tasteless, like Paddy Considine, however much that becomes hard, the tape remains a memo. Only to Virginie Ledoyen? a Natalie Portman to French - are you felt tables, although Koldo wasted it; It would have been great to use it to lift the action, running through the forests of Articuza. Oldman and Homar are tremendous beyond where they are, but the script does not give much more.Koldo takes regarding film two very senior tapes that said drinking its forest of shadows: defence (Boorman, 1972) and (1971 Peckinpah) straw dogs. Does and it is true, they are relating direct, so direct that there are scenes from the script? written by Koldo and a colleague - who survive of the original. Do see if not the scene in which a sexy Virginie Ledoyen wet blouse in a source, leaving see little but plump nipples? as the Susan George in straw - before the contorted jaw dogs that seemed to fool the people? an excellent David Warner in straw dogs, and later in front of all the locals in the bar, and all for the attention of his cowardly hubby. Who has seen straw dogs know what they are talking about. Peckinpah tape tension grows slow but effective, only thing that we do not see in Bosque de sombras. The fact of extending in excess the presentation of characters and their emotional conflicts contributes very much to this. Except the scene initial at the bar, after an hour of movie nothing has happened, and we already are we expecting anything. It is late to hurry the drama which will trigger.No less close to straw dogs, they want to appear the scenes of the attempt of rape or of the appearance of the group before the door of the House. On defense, we find not only similar in the environment chosen and poorly exploited by Koldo to create anxiety in the Viewer, but also in the equally wasted idea that humans are transformed into beasts when survival comes to (defence). In forest of shadows, the environment there is so hostile and yes it looks like from the beginning the defense of Boorman. The presentation of the locals at the bar is ñoña, nursing home. Many sides put the actors, not sorry to go there to spend some fat and acojonante, beyond the teaser we saw on TV. In straw dogs, Peckinpah us coming with stealth, but surely the tragedy through the dispassionate relationship between the writer and his wife, and acts of exhibitionism of it before a group of locals excited to see walk naked to the home through the Windows of the House. In backwoods tension arrives late and no reason to make it credible. In this sense, script failures are fateful, order what could have been a suggestive movie. If Koldo had left him the script to someone more capable or lit, everything would be solved otherwise. A correct picture with dazzling landscapes is not enough to attract the attention of the public towards a genre so hardly copied and how much more surmountable. Still, entertaining, which is always half of what a director should expect of all creation.It will be for the next, Koldo.</body>
</review>
