<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El grito 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pass through box, stop their euros, if they have nothing to do. If they have, do so. Although it does cost more. Money is not the most important thing in life.</summary>
	<body>ITodo is becoming too confusing. One believes that he is in a world and then it is another. It opens a door to the waiting to find a garden and what he sees is a slaughterhouse. Close your eyes and search with the imagination a beach with shells and children playing with the waves and that sees is a forest where campan to their wide elves and witches, perhaps a Catholic fundamentalist or a hooligan with mild artistic inclinations. One film is going to spend a good time and get hurt, enpantanado in almost always dark thoughts about the convenience not to return ever again or use more rigorous selective criteria. It weighs even the possibility of not returning to stepping on a film and leave the eyes on home TV. Hence it is always possible to give to the stop and change the disk. Or put any. Reading is a first-rate entertainment. There are excellent books on the market. I have been a voracious reader and leo still with fury when time allows me to. Ah Charles Dickens. Ah Paul Auster. Ah Borges. Ah Gamoneda. If the book thing not strain, is the music. Take one a cd from the shelf, drops in the favorite armchair and closes his eyes. Bill Evans piano can fill all the expectations of happiness that a human being sought. Or some melodies by Billy Joel. Or the symphonic rock of the Genesis of the first time. If the gentle reader still has doubts about how to occupy their time, you can exit to the street. Not everything is cinema, books and CDs, although that can fill very demanding appetites. There are still friends with those who take awhile and discuss the divine and the human with a good bourbon in a winter terrace. Or simply take a walk, be carried away by the wind while the afternoon deposed its rigors and night looks between the roofs of back home. In the end. Life can be wonderful, as says a television announcer of phonetic bombast and poor patch cords as a pariah in the reception of the Rockefeller Center.Y all this came in connection with the film, I remember.It is that last night I saw the cry 2. And left thoughtful, as the gentle reader warns, fatigando pros and cons, being resolved in my minds (I have one, Yes, Mr) over whether to forget this event or incorporate it into the thick list of awkward moments that are entailed the passage of days. I don't know what to do yet. I do not know how to proceed my almost always straight thinking. The best positions to be honest, is not the thing for both. Infumables jumbles of lower moral caladura and this one has seen (what they want to tell you) has to some incombustible instantly. Or maybe a couple or three. Outside this bonanza, the film is a chestnut of considerable size that is undermining our patience until the eyes begin to bite us and the brain (which is wise, dammit) asks loudly (more crying) abandon the room and paseemos by the avenues, outdoors, watching cars, families going and coming through the parks.My friend j. warns me of these excesses mine: Emilio, take care of yourself. Don't go to fall ill. It is very easy (concluded) start with the cry 2 and then swallow entire Filmography of Andres Pajaros and Fernando Esteso, although had tits to galore.And once got in these conaza of the rising sun then it is very difficult to return to Stanley Kubrick or Alfred Hitchcock, that you both liked. So bad is it? Because I am not clear whether the adjective "bad" is entirely appropriate. It is strange. It is a remake of a sequel. It is a gimmick. It is, agree, a package of popcorn a kilometer in height which is eaten in one sitting and then you have left on an empty stomach, as if nothing had entered.By delve into my fault, I admit that I saw the first and me angry not in excess. This second reached me deeper. The curse of the House has come out of the screen and I traded. I'm inoculated. The virus has invaded my critical capacity. This review will end up being benevolent.IILS Japanese cinema is giving us more and more joy. After the incomensurables Dark Water or Pulse (sober inspiration Japan) has fallen on our screens the cry 2. If still has not come to the film, stop what you are doing. Go. To run. Row seven. Eight also. There is excitement and fear in abundance. Requested that the producers should seek another House soon (the same better you if they change the furniture) and launched for Christmas scream 3. And if three cries do not satisfy their yearning for spectral infants in damn houses, go to the nearest video store and rent the Japanese originals. Or buy them. There will be a pack. Tapes mothers tend to be more raw but no less shocking. How beautiful is the cinema. How happy I am today.</body>
</review>
