<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An expressive film, hard, with a finish that can seem typical, but which is undoubtedly the most appropriate.</summary>
	<body>If one wanted to make a film about the diamond trade in Africa, a deep drama about mankind, about ourselves, of our behaviors, and also had numerous good dose of adventure, what Director would you choose? I, of course, departing from my list to Edward Zwick (the last Samurai) and that the horse-trading Feranando Meirelles, who directed a wonderful film also entitled the gardener complaint. But as we all know, people can change, therefore, Edward Zwick has also changed. The director of the most acclaimed legends of the fall gives us with blood diamond, without being pessimistic, to the contrary, a little smoother than Meirelles in city of God, a true sample of film adventures, armed conflicts and above all, of complaint. And is that three stories apparently here nothing related collide as a bullet in the chest of a kid, so spontaneous and unexpected. From a smuggler (superb DiCaprio) apparent unscrupulous to a fisherman who loses his family (magnificent Hounsou) and comes a "stroke of luck" or a journalist (great Connelly) interested not only in his story, but also in the world that surrounds him. These three stories so distinitas and so similar at the same time they come together, initially, by the main case of self-interest, but as the film progresses, the three arises immediately a relationship that goes beyond the interests and policy. Hence arises the friendship, love and hatred, sometimes.Portray a subject so hard and so difficult is that many directors are unwilling or come to play it, since that, for their own reasons, they dare not. But yes there are a series of daring, that not only are fighting, in a manner somewhat commercial trafficking in diamonds, weapons, whatever, but that they also believe that the public, in a way or another, will be interested in the subject. To me, personally, caught me enormously the already mentioned the constant gardener, a personal adaptation to the novel by Le Carré dealing with the illegal action carried out in Africa with pharmaceutical products. In blood diamond medicines become diamonds, but the message is the same.On the other hand, it is important that a story like this is performed so convincing, realistic and dramatic especially. And for this has Zwick to a trio of actors that you already like to have anyone else. They are Leonardo DiCaprio, in a sensational role (especially at the end) and very convincing. Then there is the grandiose Djimon Hounsou in the role of the fisherman, the core of the story and which brings more drama in everyone, on an exceptional basis, no doubt. And finally, to highlight the great presence of ever best actress Jennifer Connelly (recently seen in secret games), in an emotional and made interpretation very talented.Also note no less excellent music by James Newton Howard, with an incredibly emotional main theme, and photography of Eduardo Serra, with some levels of very nice landscapes and others closest that perfectly express the feelings of the protagonists. There Miss how the action scenes, that are not only action, but they contain a considerable dramatic force (pay attention to DiCaprio and the son of Hounsoun trying to escape from one of the guerrillas) are shot.In short, we have a great movie with several genera dominant, as the adventure, the complaint or the pure and simple drama. Blood diamond, is, an expressive film, hard, with an ending that may seem typical, but which is undoubtedly the most appropriate, and some magnificent performances.</body>
</review>
