<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El ciclo dreyer" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Joke with serious film violet. I wasn't on the work or I learned anything as much as I wanted to. Dreyer, film lover sausage in Franco's dictatorship and the spectators do not deserve this.</summary>
	<body>The declive, this agora leads for the movie buff enjoyment, the hermetic space of geeks of the seventh art as a vocation of life, has in the Millennium Startup little shaft. The Vertigo of time opens up new scenarios for the exchange of fluids in the form of frames, understand me well. The cinephiles is a disease, we know, but now isn't even frowned upon. There are so many rare people loose the world which the passion of an individual to devour film and speak passionately of their devoured matter produces no resentment, I pasmo or revulsion in who, oblivious to these goings, attends his troubled addiction. The cycle Dreyer speaks of geeks film-forums in the 1960s. Carl Theodore Dreyer is flag for the presentation of its protagonists and we already have a movie about movies, a naïve brought texts of palimpsests of cinematografiada reality cannibalism.This hodgepodge of transcendent pretensions produces hilarity, but not because the purpose of the director (Álvaro del Amo) is the grace, the nastiest joke. It is that there are dialogs that can not be heard without embarrassment. By bad. The other solution is the reflexive way, told me my friend j., who walks lately very movie buff. It can happen that the director wanted to whatever does not already give us both characters but archetypes, signs of a reality (1960s, Franco, dark cinemas of fluid verb) necessarily constrictive. I thought up in my admired Tim Burton and his fantastic ironic exercise called Ed Wood. This tape is our patria Ed Wood. This socio-political frieze fails to get bored because the actors (especially the cure) are outstanding. Records pointing them dialogs do not allow that his dramatic delivery can go in other directions. They do what they should: well.What not just enable us to attend with interest to this manual costumbrismo is the excessive artifice of the set. The bombast of the title matches the impostada flood folletinescos, melodramatic, inopportune and humorous dialogues which do not fall almost never. The cinephiles of the Spaniard of the sixties deserved more respect when it comes to pay him a tribute, certainly deserved taking into account (I guess) of the moral strictures of the time.</body>
</review>
