<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Teresa, el cuerpo de Cristo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The poster for the film is misleading and inappropriate, addressed to all those who want to see in the dark meat, accustomed to see peace in all its splendor, has been used pull sexy actress in order to box office, it would be pq knew that they were selling shit story, pity the truth with how great it is the story of Teresa.</summary>
	<body>While I've been filled with excitement to see this film, I found one crappy to add to my list of bodios 2007. As almost everything is horrible in this film I will mention the little good that there are, which is music, clothing and photography.Ironcita puts mode + Despelleje: If what issue was to portray the life of Teresa of Jesus, have been covered with glory, first because missing footage to tell this woman's work, would need dozens of films for this. Second that the script is pathetic and third because the passage in the life of Teresa who has chosen is frankly wrong counted. There is a saying in Madrid film school directors "If you have fucked, molten" and is abusing the fades is an attempt to cover up a loose script. Teresa, the body of Christ, is not loose is non-existent, I have more than 25 fades to black (of output) in the film. With the titles of entry remained "stuck" because they last like 6 minutes, this is unnecessary and also pre-duerme to the Viewer.Even a risk of never give me a role, I have to say to fuck, poorly directed is. terrible.And with all these atrocities the interpretation would not be bright, is linear almost all characters that lack of Fund, the capacity of this film is incredible to look like insnificantes characters with both historical background. So because of this hardly worth talking, we then focus the attention on starring Paz Vega, which have led very badly, the Castilian accent is not achieved, peace is forzadísima in his dialogues, despite the fact that this role not going anything. It is a great character to build in so few mintutos (which on the other hand will make eternal). Peace will most characters of the type "Lucia and sex" (example of what good is well targeting the actresses) or "Spanglish", Teresa you has been great peace, not is whether by the ill-fated direction or that she has failed build correctly this character, but is not really credible and their records are too theatrical. At least not we had to see the feet in the foreground. Although hayq ei say that the profile if it was physical. I have seen better here to Pilar López Ayala.El movie poster is misleading and inappropriate, addressed to all those who want to see in the dark meat, accustomed to see peace in all its splendor, has been used pull sexy actress in order to box office, it would be pq knew that they were selling a shit of history, that pity the truth with how great it is the story of Teresa.</body>
</review>
