<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Diamante de sangre" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another product, this very worthy social denunciation film sifted by suits commercial doneness where not shines neither one nor the other to the desired height. Meritorious roster of actors and great narrative pulse for a tape that will not make history but which is welcome, if it is like a word suitable for the terrible story of blood and hypocrisy tells us.</summary>
	<body>The film always raises a trap: a brief space where the director makes us participate in a tale whose final destination is to distract us, but also consent to ensure us a bit of reflection. Even the most exemplary crappy garnished with some commendable speech. The problem, because what we have written many times, are not the issues. All are filmables. Any argument is worth being brought to the screen. The problem is the way, the purpose, writing. Blood diamonds entertains a lot: there are not almost stops in these two hours of rough portrait of white exploitation of the rich African land. Where the bellows loses fuste is emotion because there are moments in which one feels spectator of an Indiana Jones movie, even though we know that the matter is serious and there is a huge drama in which all are involved as the film shows perfectly under the pyrotechnic Fireworks weapons and persecutions. Edward Zwick portrays violence with ex officio. There are even scenes of astonishing cruelty to be a product made in Hollywood and scheduled to ensure sales and a notable distribution. Zwick risks, but ends up saturate US military adventures in Africa. Despite the sensitivity of the subject, because the argument, in its simplicity, not rummages what should in the vampire look industrial and capitalist society puts on this corner of the world backward and barbaric, theft and dismembered, always waiting for the redemption by way of the escape of those massacred leaves graceful. Leonardo di Caprio, Dijmon Hounsou and Jennifer Connelly are three perfect actors. There is no any hits. They are outstanding. What the script does not complete. Superb Di Caprio in the last section of the film. Blood diamond is an acceptably eye-catching film. It's like a best-seller made film. The film that we are talking about is an impostada hibridacióm of social criticism and sacaperras unequivocally. Everything that WINS by their doneness of NGOs lost it its commercial sweetness that has. I do not know if I stay with the plasticity of the war (excellently filmed) thing or the mediocrity of the social position, giving the target (isn't hard to the aberration of the spot) but not deepens. There is no significance. Everything stays in a disappointing light tone.</body>
</review>
