<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Captivity" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mediocre frame to frame, predictable minute by minute, inconsustancial, neutral in false appearance of novel.</summary>
	<body>Roland Joffe is not promise of quality, but has a pull supported by sober choral performances as The Mission or even the very concise and contained dramatically, despite the excesses that could have been committed, the scarlet letter or the screams of silence.Captivity (captives) takes the new batch of police telefilms to the C.S.I. its formal props. The impostada complexity makes listing of the psychological thriller that aims to its lineup and its advertising to immerse themselves in a blatant (and boring) game of false shadow puppetry where everything is what appears and nothing there is no predictability. The issue is more finely created in the collector (William Wyler, 1965). If one has seen enough movies, there is no surprise, there is no twist that dazzles us, no evidence of that are witnessing something different. It is more of the same, but on another tape. Quote C.S.I., this prodigious number of wonderful arguments, that boast of narrative concision, or unaccountably (both programmed by our private) is denying his film nature and turning it to the range of the televised. Once the film was always something infinitely more attractive than the television. Today there is no such certainties. There is a series of outstanding quality exceeding the attractiveness of the product made to turn multicine checkout. (Go no further) I am now hooked to Heroes, a more than decent review of the filmed comic but without (such as siblings of the big screen) to towering budgets and special effects of flashy (quote Spider-man or the fantastic four or The Hulk).Captivity oozes vulgarity. A vulgarity enthroned by a few characters neutral barely attractive, beyond any shred of empathy. At a time of the tape, gives us just all happens. These disturbed behaviors that plague the Billboard us have already a little tired. Basta Saws. Enough of psychopaths. No more frequented video clips of strain. Always can one find in the dvdcoteca (a word that scares) and pull the silence of the lambs. Now announce a sequel or it is a prequel to the sequel or is a (legitimate) attempt to trace the origins of evil, the primary nature of Dr. Lecter and see if boy, it was already so subtle in its bad milk, so bastard in his poetic bestiality.</body>
</review>
