<review author="Matías Cobo" title="La vida de los otros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A new sample of the enviable health German cinema is showing through various works to uncover, with exemplary self-critical spirit, its recent history.</summary>
	<body>It is difficult to unravel how they operate the gears of empathy. Because, in many cases, it is usually derived from minor details or recondite coincidences. And you can take us so suddenly or penetrate with such depth that, suddenly, our perception of life turn 180 degrees. By similar trance will happen in the lives of others the captain Gerd Wiesler (a splendid Ulrich Mühe), one of the most efficient officers of the Stasi, the secret police of the Communist and former Democratic Republic Alemana.Este police group develops an intense work of espionage suspect especially subject of actions contrary to the pervasive Communist Party and its regimewood borers by a Pleiad of disbelieve and corrupt leaders. Far from having been contaminated by flawed environment, Wiesler continues with its Franciscan devotion to the Stasi. As she demonstrated in exemplary staging, is the interrogator and the 'detector' subversive elements more effective. Neither doubt nor piety, and his loyalty to the party and the Communist ideal is flawless.But his life, as grey as the GDR in the 1980s, will be unpredictably busy while it investigates a prestigious writer (Sebastian Koch) and his girlfriend actress (Martina Gedeck). With them you will be unable to apply the iron manual of the informer as yesteryear and its apparent inhumanity will begin to rid that feels concerned by the investigated outside lives.Thus, the film by Florian Henckel von Donnersmarck gains in interest as it weaves a relationship between researcher and investigated based on subtle complicity. Captain lives, secret and passionately, the ups and downs of the life of its objectives. And at the same time, the viewer attends the decline of a regime mired in their paranoid control of all dissident activity. In a society like this, without freedom to dissent, artists must choose to create the service of the State or live in the frustrating ostracism.In a way, this directorial debut of promising Florian Henckel is situated in the Antipodes of nostalgic revisions, as seen in Good bye Lenin!, sobre the last years of communism in Germany prior to the fall of the wall. But, first and foremost, it is a new sample of the enviable health German cinema is showing through various works to uncover, with exemplary self-critical spirit, its recent history. No doubt, the Rosary of awards that is accumulating that the lives of others is more than justified.</body>
</review>
