<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="The host" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Host is presented to us as an I want to and I can not, at least in the West, and has the slab have we done believing that we were going to enjoy another type of film. I can only recommend the selection of another of the many proposals in the charts.</summary>
	<body>Tricked. It could define me as well once I began to see this film. It is not the first nor will it be the last time that it happens to me. We're a little tired of selling us a product that is not then that will really see.The Host sell as the great new movie monster, following in the footsteps of shark and Alien. In addition "Variety" her qualifies us as the best film with Monster in history. I do not know if the friends of the magazine are some horny, but its marketing campaign and the trailer are doing that people go to see this Korean film.The work of Bong Joon-Ho, is a nonsense that at least here in the West, us (or me) is quite laughable.There are some parts that are saved and are quite well, such as the home and the presentation of the creature creating chaos on the banks of the river and the Park, but after this sequence, the rest of the film is presented as a comedy of the absurd, with characters children and almost coming out of context, that achieve nothing more than amazed viewers wondering that why you have chosen this film to spend two hours of his life. In the adventures of the protagonists and mechanisms of the film, we can find critical to Governments, its mechanisms of manipulation, his experiments etc. Try to show that is fine, but not in this film, or failing in this way, that fails its purpose and only we make even heavier in "The Host".In short, "The Host" it presents as an I want to and I can not, at least in the West, and has the slab have we done believing that we were going to enjoy another type of film.After this, I can only recommend the selection of another of the many proposals in the charts.</body>
</review>
