<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Novia por contrato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not no thing of another Thursday but get entertain</summary>
	<body>Without just seeing the Viewer already knows what you will find: boy that you don't want to leave home, parents hire a young girl, so long be together she falls in love with the typical conflict and happy ending. And it is not them it is gutting the end, ladies and gentlemen, is that you know what happens in "Bride by contract" or don't think so? While one view the film he believes that the movie has already seen, and every scene of the film is known as if memory. Yes, and it is true. But, even so, the film manages to entertain and do have a quite entertaining and fun time to the Viewer, making emerge from the room with a half sonrisilla between the lips. Starring the beautiful star of the hit series "sex in New York" (Sarah Jessica Parker) and with a Mathew Mchonaguy (doubt is written so) repeated once more in the genre of comedy romanticona after the fun "how to lose a guy in 10 days" and whose argument was quite similar to this, or had many similar features. In bride contract tells us an atypical story: that of a young man of 35 living leveraged at home, or as here would, still the boba soup, living thanks to papa and mama and a bed secured in a House also assured. But the parents already can not more, and are tired, so decide to hire the girl with which our protagonist has been dreaming for a long, so that draw you from home and left quiet. Gradually emerges the love between situations of the more disparate and able to do fun drop laughter to the Viewer. As I said, it isn't a movie on another Thursday, and as also had said, it is nothing new, but as often happens with this kind of films, manages to entertain the viewer and make him spend a very pleasant time and gets blown up. The script clear this isn't nothing of another world, with funny situations if, but fairly predictable, and interpretations of both, pretty good for an American film.In short, is not a film to say "often peliculón", but if for fun and forget about the outside in a cinema. Recommended, but only for entertainment, look no nothing more in this film, because we must not.</body>
</review>
