<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El velo pintado" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A nice and discreet, film with Visual and symbolic finds that, while not will go down in the history of the cinema, leaves a good sediment in the Viewer. As one of those wines of confidence. Of the whole life.</summary>
	<body>What rare. Because we don't talk of a blockbuster or a saga type mission impossible III. We talked about a movie time, based on a novel of the very classic and old w. Somerset Maughan. and nothing more. A love story in exotic landscapes and difficult circumstances. "And it is already.""The painted veil" is a film for adults, paradoxically, without sex. A film without childish, monadas, special effects or all the paraphernalia that seems lately drag people to the halls of cinema. And yet with all the predicaments to give a sound slap at the box office, the film is produced by the actors, who are also not Tom Cruise and Julia Roberts, precisamente.¿A what responds so brave and committed attitude? I do not know. But it has merit. "And in view of the crowd that had been in the room last Sunday, bet maybe not exit them badly at all.""The painted veil", precocious and intimate at the same time, are welcomed. There are some interesting things, well directed, the protagonists are credible, photography is fable, the music accompanies. but it becomes long. For my taste, fifteen minutes long. Or twenty. And even so, salts happy film. Well, happy perhaps not. Satisfied. Without sense of loss of time.Personally, I liked some details. For example, the game with the feet and shoes. These shoes of the Watts, splashing in the mud at the beginning, to these neat and white shoes looks after. Shoes Cartesian left next to the bed by the brainy scientist shoes pulled in the passion of the moment by the intervenor vivales, ending with bare feet than. good. We prudently silent.And another very defining moment. Husband and wife chatting about themselves. She will accuse affectionately, during his honeymoon trip to Venice, he spend in explaining how it worked the whole shebang of channels, the conduction of water, etc. She, flippantly, tells him that he would have preferred to stay in Sandwich, playing golf. And it is precisely the frivolity of it, which kills the time making a grinder role, which provides the solution to the ills that plague the Chinese people that have based her husband: carry the water with a Ferris wheel. through a system of canalization. Finally, husband and wife, work together, doing what they best know.And an excellent secondary, of those that serve to explain how the tiny British Isles could dominate half the world: when cholera has made havoc and everyone is dead or has fled, there are colonial, undaunted, agent viewing time: "they sent me to come and here I am." No more doubts, chimeras or questions. A nice and discreet, film with Visual and symbolic finds that, while not will go down in the history of the cinema, leaves a good sediment in the Viewer. As one of those wines of confidence. Of the whole life.</body>
</review>
