<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Invisibles" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Invisible, a true documentary, portrays, with the support of five magnificent directors and a star producer, the current injustice with a realism rarely seen and without any spectacular scene.</summary>
	<body>Or stories of love and corruption, or productions Hollywood with a touch of complaint, nor nor international films where rub injustice in some countries. Invisible, a true documentary, portrays, with the support of five magnificent directors and a star producer, current injustice with a realism rarely seen and without any stage spectacular or anything of the sort. It is not that it is criticizing other movies, all the contrary, I think all of them are very good, but it is that to see this documentary you is the desire to compare them. Anyway, that both Isabel Coixet, Wim Wenders, Fernando León de Aranoa, Mariano Barroso and Javier Corcuera explain, one way or another, the injustice being committed throughout the world with poor people. All of them, produced in an exceptional way by my admiradísimo Javier Bardem, have a raw, realistic and respectful manner several of the lives that are in our world and for some reasons we are unaware of them. These people, the documentary called "invisible", and hence its excellent title. This is a clear homage to all them, a film shot with intelligence and well informed, and above all, very well done. He could not stay with one of the shorts, because they all have their special things. Coixet shows us a reality that exists in Barcelona and many other cities and also the health problems that exist in other countries; Wenders manages to catch the viewer with its so incredibly dursa interviews; Aranoa plunges us into the world of children in Uganda in an exceptional manner; Barroso leans towards the subject of companies pharmaceutical (in a manner nothing similar to the film by Meirelles) and makes us aware of an intelligent way; and finally, Corcuera performs the longest short, perhaps, deeply analyzing the problems in Colombia on IDPs because guerrillas occurring there. Five great, nothing unbalanced short despite being some longer than others, and above all, facts with a conscience, something that today is difficult to find. Although it is perhaps a little weak in the wider sense, since they are all so different, that it may seem excessively risky or personal result. In short, we would have a solid, well narrated documentary and above all, varied mu.</body>
</review>
