<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="El último rey de Escocia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the heart of darkness. While we hope that another future movie amend the flat, I stay with the less histrionic, but much more the quiet American, Philip Noyce adult...</summary>
	<body>Some calling southern Lebanon of biopic? that extended term applied to the genre that recreates (and recreating) in the life of more or less famous characters for the popular imagination - the last King of Scotland, name that we disclose, for those who still have not seen the film, as entirely misguided, although pityingly where. The last King of Scotland scales around the passive (but main) character that plays much soulless unknown James MacAvoy, a Scottish doctor who comes to Uganda? fled the ties of her aristocratic family - willing to help the impoverished people in a bleak hospital (except for the more than obvious attractions of this kind of Lady Chatterley, performed by ex-teniente Scully), and just particular doctor to dictator Idi Amin (a prodigious Whitaker) and privileged witness of their desaguisados.And isn't that why not continue taking one final of having attended a biopic printing. Seems it, but rather because the interpretation of Whitaker overshadows all film matter close to miles away. This actor is that he comes and scares, I I assure you. But even though the defects of casting or script have reappointing the rest, the last King of Scotland raises more as a trip to the interior of the darkness surrounding the terrifying Ugandan dictator, and by extension, to all dictatorial power which, as a black hole, absorbs and devours his baffled Court of Marauders which Saturno. In fact, the film is based on a novel by the British writer Giles Foden and half portrays his experiences and impressions during his long stay in Uganda (lived there from age five).Who does not remember, Idi Amin came to power in 1971 through a coup d ' état against Milton Obote corrupt. He found support from numerous countries and media, which saw in him the hope to become a prosperous country, Uganda and of course away from communism of its predecessor (as worrying for the US Government). But soon revealed that the lamb was a wolf of sharp teeth: was murdering his political enemies and obsessed with persecutory Manias and paranoid visions. The height of the absurd happens when, before the stunned eyes of the international community, the country expelled 50,000 Asians, putting against their neighbours, or offering help in the kidnapping of an Airbus of the airline company Air France by members of the Organization for the liberation of Palestine. It is then when the stories (terrifying all) on their folly they multiply between exiles and carried Amin to exile in Saudi Arabia. He will still die in 2003 without a trial to restore the dignity of civilian victims left by the way.The film outline, through the role of each character, different political positions before the excess of the dictator. From the marriage of doctors wary by experience of any salvapatrias with pretensions of Redeemer, to the pragmatic and skeptical British Ambassador, who criticizes with cynicism the inertia of the people while maintaining their privileged position of neocolonizador; and going through the idealistic but hopeful work of the ill-fated Minister of health, or the suicide need for peace of the doctor of the hospital.But it is in the character of the Scottish where the film could have come out of a mediocrity that places between the varied lot of similar products on the fascination by the luminous fabric that adorns and disguises the power. An excellent interpretation is not enough when the weight of the fabric weighs on the figure of the disciple, (not so unconscious) aspiring teen viewer of false political honesty of Amin. The young and intelligent doctor, Nicholas Garrigan, looms as a child's father, shot out of the oppressive arms of his family (all doctors by inheritance genetic, I guess), to live with uppercase and eat snacks a world unknown and choose randomly, as all the options that are presented during the film. His unconsciousness and superficial way will make you an accomplice of a political regime believed honest and exciting not for deep ideals, but by the inertia of their own need for new sensations. Why is left as soon entice with the treats offered by the dictator, and why nail without shame its bajeras in the exotic bones of one of the concubines, boring by domestic exile to which her husband her subject. It is almost incredible, or at least unlikely, that suddenly he awakens his conscience and realizes the Kennel that has gotten. The script? in which incidentally coparticipa Peter Morgan (lyricist of the wonderful and fresh The Queen) - makes us sneak this awakening the tragic and terrible death of the concubine, accelerating developments towards its unusual and final, only tolerable Hollywood as imperfect metaphor of the consequences of the interventionist policy made in USA.The character that plays Gillian Anderson is presented as well as the other side of the emotional and political currency which could (but was not) choose if it had been in the hospital in the town. In a final scene to see how the character of the Scottish young aims (as if a ghost were) the bus in which the young doctor runs away from a dangerous for anyone who will be foreign Uganda. But it is late. Even late to believe us that end only suitable for bad so-called solidarity film loving blind.While we hope that another future movie amend the flat, I stay with the less histrionic, but much more the quiet American, Philip Noyce adult. And of course with the unique and implacable gardener, of Fernando Meirelles. Incidentally, a recommendable soundtrack.</body>
</review>
