<review author="Florinda Chic" title="El jefe de todo esto" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Enthusiasts of breaking waves, dancing in the dark, Dogville, the idiots, Europe or other good works of the dogma 95 as Mifune, celebration... abstain, this is more expendable. Although if you're a Platypus or Scandinavian, it entusiasmará you.</summary>
	<body>Because although it seems not, given the deep and dramatic load of his filmography, Lars Von Trier has sense of humor, their own. And at the head of this patent, that Yes in its own way has left him: austere and Danish jokes.On this occasion, we moved to an Office in which an unemployed actor is hired to perform the role of a Chief who do not know that is an invention of the true owner to fall sympathetic to his subordinates and they load their anger against the imaginary director of the company in front of employees.Personally not I laughed only. The humor is very local and is told that the Danes start laughing when call you idiots and like me not, then clear, nor smiled. Ignored by almost all of the rest of Europe, it is that Danes between and Icelanders there is a rivalry that comes from 400 years ago when Iceland was under the rule of Denmark, with which these gags nor you take them grace if you're not part involved.However there are some comedic scene that works and of course lengthy dialogues, daylighting and a shooting shooting form called Automavisión. Von Trier released the handheld camera and uses a system that after placing the camera in an artistic point of view are compiled in a program corrections, studied, they are discarded? In short that opens a lot of random posibiliades that controls a computer. The result in my opinion is something syncopated and the image quality of the communion of my nephew.If the intention of the filmmaker is show us that man is a worm for the man when working, much better told this in the Smoking Room, Glengarry Glen Ross or the method.As well as enthusiasts of breaking waves, dancing in the dark, Dogville, the idiots, Europe or other good works of the dogma 95 as Mifune, celebration... abstain, this is more expendable. Although if you're a Platypus or Scandinavian, it entusiasmará you. I do that I have argued with passion these works to those who say that deprive film of artifice is an involution as silly as the choice of some of giving birth without epidural, this time I'll shut up.</body>
</review>
