<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Café irlandés" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Melodrama with humor, naturalistic printing, social portrait, finally, ideas, feelings of overwhelming screenplay film...</summary>
	<body>Costumbrismo holds a type of cinema verité, graceful in its very estimable function to prefigure a story naturalist, colorful and entertaining, nothing twisted, convinced of the eminently narrative essence of its proposal. The inventory of avatars never exceeds the daily life of a spectator invariably involved in a plot almost always close, intimate, raya in the biographical. All we can pass what we see as almost nobody him occur things that live Bruce Willis in their crystal jungles or in the epic adventures of Peter O'Toole in his Arabia.El Lawrence abundant merit of Stephen Frears is to handle the history of Roddy Doyle (author of "The Barrytown", trilogy whose first and rough part was that "The commintments" of the once in first row Alan Parker and with an almost identical to this cast) (Irish coffee) and extract powerful localist load (Dublin, 1980s) and deliver a work universal, easy recognition of empathy immediate, without pandering to the political or sank in the topical, while never supply of truth, truth that scales between the comical and dramatic without listing in excess by any of the two. The gentle reader can rest assured that there are generous of both.Frears was returning home, the BBC, after check in "Hero", a one-act farce to the Capra did glory in Hollywood, but that not worthy the whole of his work. Amidst this British, Frears allows licenses and sutilidades, winks with sarcasm and sweetness or emotion in abundance. Everything is permitted. Unlike the other master of manners (Ken Loach), Frears not overwhelmed, not overwhelms with miserable prints with dark portraits of impoverished society and its social corsets.The impressive performance of Colm Meany as father sorry by the pregnancy of his daughter (and his refusal) to give the name of the father gives the film a very considerable humanity sediment and that gets to this "brat" (The snapper, is the original English title) is entretenidísimo, very well done and film of indelible memory in our movie fan memory. Great chairs can be with few mimbres.</body>
</review>
