<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Bobby" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great movie that could have been round but will be gaining in recognition with the passage of the years.</summary>
	<body>Total and unjustly forgotten at the Oscars this year, "Bobby" isn't much less first movie Emilio Estevez as director, but the truth is that nothing in his previous filmography did portend something similar.On the tape, follow developments of 22 fictional characters at the Ambassador Hotel, the eve of the day that Senator Robert f. Kennedy was assassinated. Obviously, are facing a coral Ribbon that, naturally, the interpretations are basic. If the director could not rely on its cast, the whole cojearía significantly.In this case, fortunately, we are witnessing throughout an interpretative recital of the distribution as a whole. Distribution, I forgot to say it truly spectacular and integrated, among others by Harry Belafonte, Joy Bryant, Nick Cannon, Emilio Estevez, Laurence Fishburne, Heather Graham, Anthony Hopkins, Helen Hunt, Ashton Kutcher, Lindsay Lohan, William H. Macy, Demi Moore, Martin Sheen, Christian Slater, Sharon Stone, Elijah Wood and the own directorOsado is dare to stand out to someone from all of them but I would be me with a wonderful time starring Demi Moore and Sharon Stone in a hairdressing salon. A real delight intepretativa to enjoy over and over again and in which both show what are capable as actresses.Of course, that the other two legs of all choral films (and non-choral, to tell the truth) must be the script and direction. I have no objections of importance to any of the two aspects. The script of the own Emilio Estevez is full of nuances and get fully justify the intervention of all the characters while, for its part, the strong leadership gives the pulse needed to keep us hooked and jump from history in history unless we have the sensation of watching parts of a puzzle. There is no major achievement in the choral film: create an entire uniform from so many different stories.I imagine that in certain sectors ideological Americans not have welcomed the tape and could certainly be accused of overly idealistic. If one ignores the film, Bobby Kennedy would have been the President which, among other things, stop the Viet Nam Guerra and to eliminate social inequalities existing in its country. Ultimately, it was the panacea. It is not that I think that the thing not had gone better with him as President, hardly could have been worse, but this frenzied optimism, in what he had done, it is distilled over the tape I was too innocent.But leaving aside a peccadillo of youth as the innocence, we have a great film that could have been round for more scenes of force, such as the one mentioned above, but will be gaining in recognition with the passage of the years. Moonfleet.es rating: 8.5 out of 10</body>
</review>
