<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Robin y Marian" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Solid film and at the same time emotional envelope the</summary>
	<body>The imagination is not impartial; on the contrary it exercises with rigid dictatorship selected choices, providing pleasure or displeasure without asking permission or even mediate common sense in his blessings. For this reason, our personal memory in the field of cinema feeds a lush and varied cast of films that do not always coincide with what our reason us dictates as interesting, suggestive, and much less as a masterpiece. Why, the film travels with us, riding the frames of non-transferable way for everyone, as mounted one after the other the moments that are building our biography.When I was a kid, I was attending with enthusiasm and expectation the matinees of cinema that was then offered in the district every Saturday. First, the ritual of the supply; They could not miss the popcorn and some other sugary concoction that numb the nerves of the premiere (or increasing them, who knows). However, for our ignorance, all those movies were classic 1930s to 1950s. If anything ever came one of fear or disasters of the then (they ran the setentaimuchos years). And almost everyone in rigorous black and white, which was the color of the film we got used to see.Among these wonderful films I remember vividly one in particular. In it, a smiling and proud Errol Flynn? incorporated in a Frog costume to the Peter Pan - dared to confront the ill with arrogance and irony, while step it took Street to the chati of his adversary, a pavita Olivia de Havilland and that is soft that I guess it made then to my beautiful MOM, but in medieval plan. It was of course the mythical Robin of the forest, by Michael Curtiz (1938). But in the final scene of the duel to the death - stairs up, stairs down - where my nails could become at times a sad stump. All children in the room expected this duel we knew she would and what would be the outcome. Robin Locksey, one; evil usurper of thrones, zero.Forest Robin is optimism and vitality. Even the bad guys seem to smile (for schemed his misdeeds, of course), and swords crossing only to whom it must hurt. For a child, that Manichaean universe was a simple and accurate narrative that was going home happy knowing that was? that's obvious - always on the side of Justice and the protagonist chati, and that he would fight (as Frog Flynn) against all those who dare to encroach upon thrones or steal princesses which they are not entitled. Up himself Don Quixote would be eclipsed before the rush of adventurous adrenaline that condensaban my neurons out of that dark room of cinema.With age, a few bumps which gives the overestimated experience, and some other more adventure film, Robin of the forest remained in my memory as those flowers that one keeps and forgets the books are. When I returned to see her (three, five, I forget how many more), my rush became a conmiserada adult, tender half, asshole half smile. And so far. I guess that with old age recover one that ability to enthuse how easy and Pilgrim, and dream that it rises with the agile and rugged outlaw Robin these steep stairs from which put an end to the bad turn. Until then, are the bad guys who win most of the time this naive viewer who writes to you.For this same reason, a few years ago I discovered a gem that faithfully reflects the way we go through each one with the films that are posing to the bottom of the memory. It is not so well known Robin and Marian, Richard Lester (1976). Front of the jovial and epic nature of the version of Curtiz, this second conforms more to what is today often called as crepuscular, but keeping an exquisite romantic (away from the arrogance of the character played by Errol Flynn nervous saltimbanqui). The plot puts us many years before Robin ended with the injustices that threatened England and restored the legitimate throne of Richard Coeur de lion. Robin is serving his King, which already has a bit of heart and a lot of insatiable chieftain. Castles are not impeccable, the war has not just never and all the Knights are tired of serving his Lord. Luckily (who knows) Ricardo dies and Robin returned to his homeland after twenty years of absence. Everything is very different. Now nothing is left of the five years old, but still a bad (the Sheriff of Nothingham) governed by the lands of Locksey to loose leg. Marion, for its part, has got nun, which is what left a woman by then if he didn't marry you (and Marion already know that only had eyes for his Robin).A hoary and tired Sean Connery notes what has been everything and look for his dear Marion (an aging but splendid Audrey Hepburn), already installed in the monastic life. But the tragedy will again be which one to both characters in a joint venture that will make them live again (and even with more intensity, despite the fatigue and the reluctance) los años felices. The Sheriff of Nothingham, played by Robert Shaw, wants to take England to the clergy, and hence have the mature Hepburn is Abbess. Now you can imagine the rest. Robin and Marian escape back to Sherwood, where they meet a little group of Renegades of the dictatorial policy of the sheriff and are trying to without much resolution undermine its power.But nothing is the same that in times of Errol Flynn, however, life goes on as always - aspera for the honest and prosperous for the undesirable-, is expected that the happyends do not have room in this film. That Yes, they will always be Sherwood, that dream forest where lovers launched an arrow that will take them there never were.There are few endings so bitter and however so beautiful like this in Robin and Marian. If you have not seen the movie, you do not pinchéis on the link of the video and make a DVD right now. It is worth the attempt. The Declaration of love for Hepburn for Connery is an intensity that excites and leaves without words. And is that beyond the colorism and luminosity of the version of Curtiz, Robin and Marian is an example? as already was without forgiveness on the western - adult deconstruction of a (the adventure genre) that I needed this mature vision and without more decorated than the real, that life imposes on us with relentless ferocity, and only from the beauty and the love we exorcizamos and overcome.Does Lester? known rather for two films of the Beatles and Superman II and III - outboard the best film of his career, without lapsing into sentimentalism or repetitions to the use of this overused myth of the bold Bushranger and desposable Princess. And gives us a strong and at the same time touching film about lainmortalidad of illusions through the history of these two tanned lovers.</body>
</review>
