<review author="Kamala" title="Paris je t'aime" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Best thing is that not all the shorts revolved around the idyllic Paris of lovers, but the real European city, with their problems and their adversities. For this reason, this movie made of minipelículas can be found some wonderful pearls.</summary>
	<body>I parí, I Parí? How many atrocities committed in thy name? I know that the quote is distorted, but who says "freedom" can be said "Paris". And who says atrocity can say "short-inside-of-a-movie-of-short".18 shorts in a movie. 18 shorts, but not all of the same quality. I did not know some of the directors (do something positive, because those who Yes knew not surprised me: the short of the Cohen, brilliant, but from the first level you know what Cohen &Cohen; of Isabel Coixet? great Sergio Castellito and Miranda Richardson - is 100% Coixet; Gus Van Sant, is unfortunately, Gus Van Sant? this man is on the decline)do, there who understands you!-?. The only one that surprised me, although it did not excited me, was Wes Craven. (One expects a Craven in pure State if the wheel in Père Lachaise!).Best thing is that not all the shorts revolved around the idyllic Paris of lovers, but the real European city, with their problems and their adversities. For this reason, this movie made of minipelículas can find some wonderful pearls: - the short of Walter Salles and Daniela Thomas, with a wonderful Catalina Sandino Moreno as immigrant mother; - Interestingly, the other Latin American, Alfonso Cuarón, also spoke of motherhood in his short, with Nick Nolte envejecidísimo; - shorter of immigrants: Olivier Schmitz is very hard and pure cinemacomplaint, of tenderness, of love, of mercy? - light, beautiful and hopeful is that of Gurinder Chadha, the Quais de Seine; - the couple Ben Gazzara and Gena Rowlands in a short directed by Frédéric Auburtin and Gérard Depardieu, and written by the own Rowlands. When there is talent don't need nothing more! - the couple Bos Hoskins-Fanny Ardant in a short that isn't at the height of his actors for his screenplay; - Vincenzo Natali short surprised me. Very style comic, refreshing in the progress of the film. That Yes. Elijah Wood doing the role of Frodo, once again. Very nice the metaphor of the "Vampire love"; - sad and lonely of Alexander Payne, which puts an end to the film. Is nothing out of this world, but it is a good culmination and a nice way of saying Paris, je t? aime?</body>
</review>
