<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Hannibal: El origen del mal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hannibal: The origin of evil is one of so many thrillers that Hollywood vomits every year: dark, gloomy, and with a horrifying bordering on al gore, pure and hard.</summary>
	<body>Let's be honest, in the current film there is an alarming lack of creativity and originality, whether by both virtues complete absence, or lack of executives that risk with new and fresh proposals. And having said that, do have never felt curious as to who was the Chief Executive of Hollywood who decided that it was a good idea to make a sequel to a great taquillazo, but going back to the past and reviewing the origins of this story? And who would be the creator and disseminator of the word prequel? What reservation destination for two real visionaries like these? Even by speculating, they may have separate places reserved in the sixth basement of hell with the assassins in series, rapists and lawyers emerging on television, or perhaps have share suffering with the inventor of acrylic furniture.After three movies, which are actually four that the Red Dragon was the remake (sorry, new version, that with so many terms one confused) Hunter, is something not already know the public about the work and miracles of Hannibal Lecter there? Finally, similar existential doubts and such filósoficas and moral disquisition is them leave you, dear readers, are the most appropriate judges. Hannibal: The origin of evil tells us, how well it reads its title, traumatic childhood and youth of Hannibal Lecter (Gaspard Ulliel), and the fact that became it a bloody and ruthless Monster. After that excellent film that is girl with the Pearl, Peter Webber faces a similar challenge without complexes, and signing a more than acceptable tape of suspense, dark, although it is in excess of truculence. The first thirty minutes are the best of the film, which has just falling into monotony due to a somewhat weary rhythm and an excessive duration (requirement of the producer). Gaspard Ulliel is correct in its interpretation, but who find it a worthy successor to Anthony Hopkins does crude oil, with forgiveness.Hannibal: The origin of evil is one of so many thrillers that Hollywood vomits every year: dark, gloomy, and with a horrifying bordering on al gore, pure and hard. We actively encourage all those who come to see the tape that do it on an empty stomach and digestion made, though there will always be a spectator to the peculiar culinary tastes of Hannibal Lecter produce hunger. In that case, bon apetit.</body>
</review>
