<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Lola: La película" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lola: The movie falls in all the defects and topics of the biopics, but it also has some exceptional performances as greater virtue.</summary>
	<body>Until a few years ago, say that someone wore "a life of film" was more a phrase than anything else. But that was before that Hollywood discovered the film potential that had certain public figures, especially artists. Since then we have witnessed an explosion of biographical films or biopic, and as so many trends, it was soon imported by the rest of the world.In Spain it took longer to import such a trend, more than anything because it is difficult to make a tape of these characteristics than something new or different input with the existence of certain television programs. If first Camarón de la Isla, you now is the turn to another of the myths of Spanish flamenco, Lola Flores. Lola: The film tells the first thirty years of life of Lola Flores (Gala Évora), focusing on its human side and his turbulent personal life and various relations maintained with men as Manolo Caracol (José Luis García Pérez). Miguel Hermoso (who went to Lola Flores in Truhanes) faces the challenge with courage, but unfortunately fails to give the film such a vision that distinguishes it from typical biopic. The film lacks originality and freshness, it is full of very well-worn situations, and incurred a large number of topics. The pace prints Miguel Hermoso is not the most appropriate, such slow that just becoming tedious and monotonous. However, and despite its flaws, the film manages to convey a great deal of realism, with a very elegant atmosphere. The best of the film, is undoubtedly its exceptional cast, bright all, although particularly highlights a great José Luis García Pérez and Ana Fernández, David Arnaiz. Big words deserve exceptional interpretation of Gala Évora, genuine revelation of the season, away completely from the imitation, giving his work a great strength and sensitivity. The young actress Cadiz full screen in each appearance, and no doubt we recommend actively go looking site for the Goya Award for best actress.</body>
</review>
