<review author="Dragon negro" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is fill all expectations once seen the film? I already think so yes, 300 is everything that promised, action without limit or barracks, a fascinating visual and auditory experience, violence and blood.</summary>
	<body>300 were men that King Leonidas called his guard personal, 300 were the Spartans who accompanied him on a suicide mission, 300 men handed over to their King and facing more than one million of Persians, 300 was the comic of Frank Miller and Lynn Varley 300 is now the last film by Zack Snyder based on the same comicdo, one of the most anticipated films of the year and one that higher expectations to lifted since they could see their trailers.¿Se fill all expectations once seen the film? Already think so yes. To begin with, and something that anyone who has seen the trailer or images already suspected, is the visual aspect of this hotel is spectacular. The grey skies and dull and dry yellow fields are mixed and contrasted with the semi-desnudos bodies and the red blood of the layers. But that's nothing compared to when starts the action and battles are happening one after another, violence erupts without truce, the Spartans levelled their shields, swords and spears without mercy, and started members and traversable bodies blood splatters the screen slow in some contests of cruelty as rarely seen on a big screen. Everything comes accompanied by one thunderous sound, another of the great successes of the film, sound and music always in line with the scenes, more writing in the battles, and calmer in other pieces.The film baby much of the comic in which it is based, with some scenes and practically modelled dialogues of the original, these are the best moments of the film, the most successful. The meeting between Leonidas and Xerxes worth noting it by this verbal confrontation and that majestic characterization of the Persian King that almost seems a giant and a really solemn voice. There is no doubt that those who have enjoyed the comic found many points in common with this. Anyway the film takes their concessions and creates new frames, as the son of the captain and the plot of the Queen in Sparta, both quite dispensable.Gerald Butler is superb as King of Sparta, his gaze is scary and her screams you makes you want to go to fight with him, not be that may be dubbing because the pass that I've gone has been in V.O. and is tremendous, I hope that not cagen with dubbing. Also this spectacular is Rodrigo Santoro as Xerxes, almost unrecognizable with both piercing and a height and presence almost divina.300 is everything that promised, action without limit or barracks, a fascinating visual and auditory experience, violence and blood, but apart from that feast which comes to claim the film, similar to the towards the comicIt is the sacrifice of a group of men by the system of life which believe, to live in freedom and not kneel to a divine King, it is the fight of democracy against dictatorship, a tribute to a group of courageous soldiers without which perhaps today Europe not serious that is. Since then I have no doubt that this film will be on lists of the best of the year when counting is done.</body>
</review>
