<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Scoop" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Comedy light, certainly smaller, although fresh, pleasant, full of hilarious dialogues, frothed that complicity that Woody Allen has only with his loyal army of supporters.</summary>
	<body>What Woody Allen has been committed is not a comedy that came you before round: is a missile with direct lacitos to the flotation line of society British Welfare, which is to be the aristocracy with shareholdings in Philharmonic associations and little or no taste for remangar prejudices and avenir to fraternise with the flat greywith the working class people that get to work and has no idea of Henry Moore (there is one at a table given by the artist himself) or of 18th century harpsichords... And makes deliberate and so flippantly because East Scoop (scoop, in English) is first and foremost, a perfect entertainment, a vehicle for showcasing for Scarlett Johannsson (increasingly more carnal, resounding in their gestures and in his presence) and a return to confidence in a great director who is justice this humble rebuke, not him leaving things as we would like (A made in Hollywood ending)(Everything else or middling crooks are mediocre) with the outstanding exception of Match Point (curiously) away from writing humorous and housed in the drama cuasifilosófico.The English upper classes are the Allen shows us: which still lowered to laugh with comedian (the third wizard got to detective or tanker Woody Allen borda) while do them tricks of letters in a "typical english garden" which is not missing nor labyrinth Rococo tables for the tea of the five.The abundance of gags excuse the lightness of the plot: a young aspiring American journalist that passes one season in London receives a ultratumba confidence: the identity of the murder of the tarot, plaguing London killing prostitutes in black and short hair. The accused is a man of success, son of a Lord, phlegmatic in its modernity, astonished at the spontaneity of who, in search of clues that diluciden the truth about the murders, just falling for the investigated object, as she is well recognized.The mess does not guarantee laughter: Woody Allen does not claim to such a thing. His humor (has always been so) is linguistic, solidly anchored in the solvency of its language, that scavenging complicity with a spectator already familiar with their twists and completely dedicated to his peculiar way of understanding life. Scoop, in this sense, is not murder mystery Maniatan, which is certainly debtor, but gives us the wonderful opportunity to recover that time between the traditional and film that involves going to the cinema (I unfortunately have seen in dvd format) and let us go by the occurrences of this geniecillo New York. Scoop is one minor work, no doubt. Those who wield its lightness are not lacking in arguments, but Woody Allen can do another Scoop this year and this scribe will soon attend the premiere. In the Kingdom of the blind the one-eyed man is King and this innocent (in appearance) comedy of situation that Allen gives after the punch at the table which was Match say point abounds in anthologies scenes that could well have crept into more tronío tapes. There is no shortage even those winks moviegoers as his: fatal Acheron, the boat with the dead and the uncompromising Lair of Woody Allen film of Bergman, who has never left him at all.</body>
</review>
