<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="The host" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Host is not a monster film, but that criticism to a naive society and another not so much. We are, therefore, to a social film.</summary>
	<body>So yes, with two words we could define the new film by Korean Bong Joon-Ho, director of the acclaimed Memories of murder. First of all, calling The incomparable as Host for several reasons: the press comparing her with two of the most famous monster-movies of all history, Alien (an absolute masterpiece) and shark (entertaining and nothing more), and I think that this comparison is totally unfair and inexplicable, since they have nothing to do with the other, unless they belong to the particular genre. And is that the film of Joon-Ho can only comprararse with the Spielberg by social criticism that there is stuck in both films (attention to the scene in which appears the monster in the Lake and the face and reaction of the entire population). Moreover, the bugs of all three films cannot be compared at all, because all are very different. But it is that it is not only this, but that The Host is extremely original, since it deals with many issues at the same time, has incredibly drawn characters and an atypical screenplay that, however much that follow the structure base, the film goes decanting by holes similar to the sewers where is found the monster, all of them sinister, long and with an end do not know where it ends. So we could say that the film is innovative, original in all its aspects, spectacular (tuned to the most important action scenes), is perfectly coordinated, has special effects that deserve an Oscar, and keeps you in tension during the footage, ultimately releasing his most dramatic and realistic touch. As I have said, The Host is also a social and political criticism, something that not only increasing the number of genera of the film, but that also makes it more interesting and beast at the same time.Everything in this wonderful film dazzles, absolutely everything. The most important thing of this film is that it knows to look good. Let me explain: when just a film of this kind (well, I mean only the monster movies) are typically used several topics in all of them (the bad bug dies and all, or except all, remain safe). Another thing is that they rise then forty times, as it is the case of Alien. Anyway, the film of Bong Joon-Ho is not that end up in a very different way (sorry with the small spolier, even if it was foreseeable), but note, and much that is different from all the others, much more innovative. And this happens thanks to the sensitivity with which the film is treated. Yes, it is a sinister and claustrophobic film, but it has several of the most exciting and sad moments which have seen in years. And this is what differentiates the film of all the other monster movies, his incredible ability to strike unexpectedly with atypical scenes in his apparent context, the adventure. And it is that the movie more than anything, has a moral and political background what I find that it is most interesting of all. The Host is not a monster film. It is a film that criticizes a naive society and other not so much. We are, therefore, to a social film.As I said, this is an elegant film, who knows how to attract the public. And one of the most important factors that make it so special being part of the hidden genera shows throughout the film, is his incredible screenplay. There are hardly any fissures, slippages of rhythm, orinarieces, aspects that do not come to mind. Thanks to its variability of genres, both fantastic, adventure, dramatic, politicians and comedians, allows your script to submit many details, anecdotes (how I laughed with some scenes amusing and depressing at the same time!), etc. And of course, like all good script, presents a formidable, strange, clear and precise structure. I am especially excited to this sudden change of story which unfolds while the desperate family of the girl is looking for by the sewers and suddenly, looks like a father and a son that van desplaçándose out there, because they have no home, and suddenly, the director it chooses to continue its history until a terrible event happens and mixing both stories. You will not need to say that there are many spectacular scenes in the film, and therefore does not highlight any big, since they all are to each more impressive.Finally, highlight the formidable performances of each of the performers. All of them, mainly those of the family, make some brilliant performances, rare grimaces no useless actions. Perhaps Song Kang-ho the most expressive of all, and more appear, since that is who plays the father of the kidnapped girl. Does your paper a great creation of the dismissal and the courage at the same time. Although I would not be satisfied if not appoint that portraying his father, Hie-bong Byeon, with a nostalgic and courageous role, also (very alert with the scene in which confronts the monster.) (Awesome). And finally, also I have to nominate the kidnapped girl, which makes a put superb, worthy of a high recognition, at the height of Dakota, Ivana, Haley or Freddie. Their role is strong, but above all, intelligent.A wonderful film, rara, quasi perfect, entretenidísima, unpredictable and spectacular. It would especially recommend those who are looking for something new and know that it is not neither Alien nor of shark, which is The Host.</body>
</review>
