<review author="Luis Zueco" title="La vida de los otros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The lives of others is a film of these which is keen to be able tell is someone that he go to see her.</summary>
	<body>We live in the 21st century, we are a generation that has had all, freedom, good education, possibilities to do whatever you would like to listen to the music that gave us the win, read any book to say what we think? You have been able to always choose, this is what our fathers fought, and that seems to us as normal. Not you usually miss something if you do not lose or if you have not had never. By all these privileges that we had and we have, it is a great joy to someone, or German, Chinese Spanish, get back the fear, resignation, resentment, frustration, hatred, rebellion, pain, struggle and who was supposed to live in some parts of Europe for 30 years.The lives of others is a film of these which is keen to be able tell is someone that he go to see her. The main actor this simply spectacular, but very careful with the writer, with a presence and that gives her character that mixture of penalty, poetry, rebelliousness, indignation, need to survive without which the film would be impossible. The side are also at a high level, both the journalist, the Prime Minister and the Lieutenant Colonel. The actress makes a very complicated role that you fall in love and you hate in equal parts, but that is without doubt a great performance, overshadowed in part by the two male protagonists.The captain of the Stasi is no doubt a smart guy, convinced the Communist ideal, but at the same time caught in the dynamics of the game prevents him to see in what has become his country. Live the life of another person makes him see reality from another point of view, something so healthy and that makes so few people today (committed to see things from a unique point of view, with the danger that this, that is the wrong). See things from other eyes makes you wake up from his dream and takes you to sacrifice everything, rather it was nothing by a text, that surely could help to send some wall was not far away.Apart from a beautiful soundtrack, an atmosphere that makes you feel that you are in the GDR in the 1980s. With scenes excellent in cases of interrogation and the placement of the entire system of tapping.</body>
</review>
