<review author="Luis Zueco" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When premiered letters from Iwo Jima it does not disappoint. Some liked the film and others liked it because it was not part of flags of our fathers but it was different and clearly superior. A Dipticon taste of the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>To complete her diptych on the battle of Iwo Jima (February-March 1945) American director Clint Eastwood (San Francisco, 1930) decided to adapt the novel Picture letters from commander in chief, based on the letters written by Japanese general Lieutenant Tadamichi Kuribayashi, during the battle itself, as it is reflected in the film. So told, as lately it is usual, with the collaboration of Paul Haggis, which already signed the script of Million Dollar Baby or flags of our fathers.Eastwood (without forgiveness, Mystic River) is faced with this project one of the most important of his career to try to tell the story of one of the most important battles in the Pacific in World War II from two opposing points of view. While flags of our fathers represented the American vision of a few soldiers returning victorious to his country after winning the battle on the island, and are used to represent all those young people who are risking their lives for their country. This second film shows the Japanese side, and life is also young soldiers but the other side as they struggled to try to maintain the small island of Iwo Jima enemy out of reach.It is not insignificant to note that the director has taken risks to perform this kind of película-dual as if it were the two sides of a coin. The making and directing two stories, which might be very similar for the context of the battle, but each one shines in fact separately and with their own light due to their differences, is a challenge that does not carry out every day a director. And as a result the two films do not shine with the same light, nor with the same intensity, even with the same color.After the premiere of flags of our fathers, which would not lie to say that passed without penalty or glory ahead of the billboards and the eyes of the spectators, the widespread both criticism and public comment was wait to see the next stop see had more to say director. Expectations frustrated in the first film became quickly build up in front of the poster announcing for a few months letters from Iwo Jima. The proximity of the premiere of both stories was one of the keys of which the first was more or less unnoticed without criticism or public cebasen too it. Somehow the strategy worked them to the producer and the Distributor, but this also sparked more interest by the second movie.When premiered letters from Iwo Jima it does not disappoint. Some liked the film and others liked it because it was not part of flags of our fathers but it was different and clearly superior. It is history from the Japanese side, the film obviously lacked all these American and American symbols which both flood any American production where the military aspect is present. And he is appreciated. So we also have an approach to the mode and life of the Japanese army and his soldiers, and see what because we knew that they were not so different from American soldiers.Even so, Eastwood not leaves throughout the film a classicism which somehow lastra production not leaving show everything what could have been. We miss a more courageous and fresh way to deal with history. It gives the impression that the director after the completion of the first film immersed in the spirit of the same, and stayed there. With a much more interesting story with an actor starring as Ken Watanabe (the last samurai, memoirs of a Geisha), showing just a part of how much that is capable of doing, letters from Iwo Jima should have been much higher than its predecessor, and when it comes out of the film comes out with a strange taste. On the one hand that like most and which is higher than flags of our fathers, and on the other that something is missing that don't know what, it presupposes good managers and they translate into their projects.Clint Eastwood has had a fairly irregular career throughout his life. Both acting and directing. Since a few years ago are you comes considered one of the best American directors by chaining projects as well received by critics and public as Mystic River and Million Dollar Baby. However we should rethink this as categorical assertion. You have 77 years and make films aren't two sufficient arguments to say it is one of the greats. And less after the completion of his last two films, which you don't have errors in the direction (which would have been intolerable) but both are a clear "eastwood style", and do not go beyond the classicism and the theatrical.What saves letters from Iwo Jima, a part of a much more attractive and suggestive story, it seems at least one much more careful production. The possibility of filming in the island itself where he succeeded the battle, gives the project of some natural sets impossible to recreate with any site. Also the film also has very close to the black and white color treatment, perhaps to provide draft a more historical feel, that only uncheck a little when shown the flashbacks, in which the color is much more present in the images that recreate the past, on the island. Another factor which helps to create a very personal atmosphere in the film is its sound. Although the story takes place only in a small island (flashbacks aside, of course), sound and different mixes of it with music or simply the bare sound cause that the viewer feels surrounded by the island everywhere, provided the projection has a decent equipment in order to provide all the nuances that we offer through the ear. No wonder therefore that the film leaving award-winning the Academy Awards gala with the Oscar to the sound editing for (Best Sound Editing).In the film there is also a sequence (the suicide grenade) could be eliminated or at least shortened. A sequence showing so much blood and amputees members to show the horrors that produces the battle is not necessary. This is one of the examples is when a good director knows cut these images in the editing room or directly dispensed from shooting them. However keeps them Eastwood, I do not know very well what to say. Perhaps to offer some blood to persons who have paid an entry to see a war film. Even so, view Japanese soldiers during World War II kamikaze is already very light by the general public, and those scenes just help to strengthen already known.However, the film can be seen well, especially for their actors and the soundtrack, with a simple Melody with Oriental reminiscences that gets into your head as a delight for the ears. A reduction of the footage, eliminating certain scenes from the second part of the film that seem very similar and redundant as to what you want to convey, had set up a pace more harmonious to the last part of the same. Photography, art direction and music shine throughout the film, however is you miss the hand of a director with own talent that had known to give the film the magic that has &hellip; but not shown. A pity.</body>
</review>
