<review author="Luis Zueco" title="Infiltrados" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What many call style may not be as good quality. Call it style gives positive connotations, but when these characteristics are so repeated and repeated for so long they become negative points towards the work of the director.</summary>
	<body>Martin Scorsese signature with the direction of this film one more of his works. Neither more nor less. Despite being a remake of Infernal Affairs Asia, the film has all the keys that make up the style of the American director. Mafia, violence and power form the triumvirate which reigns everywhere and at ease by the already extensive filmography of Scorsese.En this film, once again, are male character underpinning the entire weight of the film (as was already the case in Taxi Driver or one of ours). His new actor Leonardo di Caprio, shows once more isn't a bad actor, and that age will providing you greater presence on the screen, which also means greater intensity in their interpretations.It should be noted the reunion on the big screen of Di Caprio and Mark Whalberg after having agreed both at the beginning of their film careers in diaries. It seems that the years have also improved the interpretative quality of the latter. In counterpoint to them you can see Matt Damon bland of usual along with a Jack Nicholson already not sobreactuado but rather caricatured if same.Otherwise little more needs to be said that the originality of the story are we owe it to the writer of the original film, which makes that we give your head against the wall to be awarded the American screenwriter for "tuning" an already made script with an oscar. Highlight however always fluid and successful mounting of his usual Thelma Schoonmaker, which Scorsese should pose put in the opening credits at the same height and with the same font and body of letter to his own name.A film director that already surpasses the seven decades of existence and that belongs to that generation of so-called "bearded" directors, should give us something that captivate us. What does however has an aftertaste to already seen. Somehow the insistent location of all his films in his native New York, shows the impasse in which submerged. A claim can lift many blisters among his followers but often if you look at the branches can be that the tree don't you see the forest.What many, both critical and public, call style perhaps is not so good quality. Call it style gives positive connotations, but when these characteristics are so repeated and repeated for so long in a format so similar, as they are the majority of his films, they become negative points towards the work of the director.They say the worst thing that can happen to an artist is his work generates indifference. Dear friends of Coppola and company have had his career films that have marked milestones in the history of cinema for one reason or another. Although currently their careers can say that they have evolved to a point where they are lost. However fidelity likewise Scorsese, many admire, my view is what has burdened his genius and his career has been sentenced. It is not enough that a couple of his films have elements more than notable and worthy of a great director. Sometimes it is preferable to make a great movie and lose the course of your career, that address more than a veintena and realize that after nearly forty years, your feet have budged an iota of the streets of New York.</body>
</review>
