<review author="Kamala" title="Dreamgirls" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you like musicals, you have to see Dreamgirls. The criticism is divided: that is superficial, on the one hand, it is fantastic on the other. I think it depends on the film tastes: If you like musicals, you'll love this movie. If you do not like, better go to see Bobby or Rocky Balboa.</summary>
	<body>If you like musicals, you have to see Dreamgirls. The criticism is divided: that is superficial, on the one hand, it is fantastic on the other. I think it depends on the film tastes: If you like musicals, you'll love this movie. If you do not like, better go to see Bobby or Rocky Balboa. Dreamgirls is the story of The Supremes, which is sweetened. Or rather, of Diana Ross &amp; The Supremes. All the protagonists of the real history have his alter-ego of fiction.Dreamgirls is, above all, a musical of success on Broadway which premiered in 1981. The legendary Michael Bennett directed and choreographed the musical (there is an "in memoriam" do to him at the end of the movie and appears in the opening credits? although appears to be that this is forced in any adaptation of a musical film). The success of this musical was enormous. He won 6 Tonys for the year following (was nominated in 13 categories) and the agreement between critics and audiences on this occasion was total: was a fantastic show. Bill Condon, the director of the film, saw this legendary montage of Bennet when I was little. So did Eddy Murphy, who participated in the film playing a kind of Smokey Robinson. And it does it very well. Condon decided he could bring to the screen, preserving the good and giving freshness. Therefore requested 4 new songs to the man who composed the original music, Henry Krieger, and decided to find a huge ensemble cast: Jamie Foxx, which has a best gift of character, Curtis Taylor Jr. (i.e., a kind of Berry Gordy Jr., the man who created the Motown and The Supremes created) but, unfortunately, not seized. Is a very rich character: very intelligent, very active, very fast, very "aggressive Executive", a man with a vision for the future that uses to the of his around to achieve their goals; Jennifer Hudson (putting it on the place protagonist it deserves.) Detail on the sidelines: is the winner of American Idol, the OT of USA. Or, that is the "Pink" Yankee. (And gets in the movie) is Effie White (in The Supremes, Florence Ballard), the woman with a marvelous voice that is relegated by the voice of "white" taste, more nuanced, more light, Deena Jones (do Beyoncé Knowles, which here obviously makes Diana Ross? notice the similarity of names in pronunciation). Together with them, Anika Noni Rose, which is the third in the Group (Lorrell, i.e., Mary Wilson, who wrote a best-selling book telling his experience in The Supremes). It must also include Keith Robinson (C.C., brother of Effie, composer and choreographer? a mixture of the composer of the Holland-Dozier-Holland Motown and Smokey Robinson). Together with them, Danny Glover is Marty, representative of Jimmy "Thunder" Early (Eddy Murphy), a singer who comes to the white audience and will always be close to elimination. They are The Dreams, the girls, that will do.The film is a great musical. On many occasions you have the sensation of being in a theatre and want to applaud at the end of many of the musical numbers. But admit it, is not a great movie. The relationships between the characters only have intensity when the characters sing. For example, there is no passion or intensity in kissing or romantic relationships of Curtis and Effie or Curtis and Deena and Jimmy and Lorrell everything is very cold, very distant, very little real. Do you often wonder whether Curtis and Effis are couple, aren't, if CC and Michelle are?If the R &amp; B is so intense, so passionate, so provocative why are relations between singers, musicians and artistic scene so puritanical? It makes not much sense. The "white" escandalizaban "black" music because had sex, there was passion, intensity, clarity, explicidad in the lyrics, the music, the movements? It is what attracted young people. If it is in the music and not the relationships between them, everything is very cold. This is the movie. But I wanted to speak here of the Supremes. And it is that, after getting into the history of The Supremes, the history of The Dreams seems light, very light, in fact. It seems that Diana Ross was pretty bad bug, something that Deena Jones in the movie, no. Interesadilla, but does not seem to bad bug. And from here, who has not seen the film, which is expected to see to read what follows. The film is very faithful to the broad outlines of the history of the Supremes (in fact, Diana Ross never wanted to see the musical and, however, Mary Wilson titled his autobiography "Dreamgirl: my life as a Supreme"). Apparently, it is true that one of the Supremes, in fact its founder, Florence Ballard, was relegated by the more pop voice of Diana Ross to get to the "white" lists of successes, objective of Berry Gordy. It is also true that Diana Ross was bundled with Gordy. Florence Ballard (pictured), relegated once, he continued in the group, but is depressed and began to drink until he was unable to perform. It was dismissed, but not recovered. Although he tried to pursue his musical career, he had no success and died in 1976, very poor. Truth is also that Holland-Dozier-Holland left Motown for a fight by royalties, not by what was doing with his music. The dispute was by property rights. It is true that The Supremes became Diana Ross &amp; The Supremes, but some of the songs from The Supremes recorded without them (apparently, the song "do Someday we? ll be together", the ultimate success of The Supremes) was recorded by Diana Ross and other singers, not Mary Wilson and Cindy Birdsong, who had replaced Florence Ballard. Yes, it is true that Diana Ross reunited with Mary Wilson and Cindy Birdsong in 1983 to sing together "do Someday we? ll be together" in celebration of the 25th anniversary of Motown. While in the film they meet in love and company the four The Dreams, in real life incidents. During the television program broadcast by NBC, Ross pushed Wilson away from her and then took the microphone from the side of Wilson when she was inviting to Berry Gordy, sitting in a Theatre box, download and join everyone onstage. Although all these incidents were eliminated from the Edition that ran, were widely reported by the media.So ya see. The reality surpasses fiction.</body>
</review>
