<review author="Kamala" title="Brick" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good work of Joseph Gordon-Lewitt (but also the rest of the cast). Highly recommended to enjoy and also to remember these classic movies, that never go out of fashion, that have grown and they helped us to love the film.</summary>
	<body>Yesterday I went to see a movie before, but far from now. And he is appreciated. Except for the duration, which follows the line of what is happening lately (two hours and thanks, that now is the style everything lasts more than two and a half hours.) (Yet to be be grateful) and not as it stressed respect for the viewer and the movies formerly lasted what have to last: hour and a half; as much an hour and forty minutes.The case is that I went to the Madrid premiere of "Brick", the last movie of Ryan Johnson. The penalty, which was not in V.O.S. From here to ask retailers to make a preview in original version! This movie is to see it in its original language, to enjoy it as if we had recovered to Philip Marlowe, Sam Spade, Dashiell Hammett and Raymond Chandler. It has the classic: hard detective, dead girl stuck in trouble, femmes fatales, bad, thugs and black, negrísima, dark, plot to non lacks nothing. Since then, Johnson, author of the script and director, has seen many times "The Maltese Falcon" and "The big sleep". But also "death among the flowers", "One of ours" and some "L.A. Confidential".It is curious as the modernization of the classic is given by the environment, not by gender. It is a pure genre, is film black, but developed in Institute and their plots with drugs. However, the action flows at a very special rate within a research in occurring the tracks, which the detective does not sleep and where the why is summarized in a tirade that you find good little (as in "The big sleep") but gives you equal! Why has always been, in these films, less important than the path of the detective. What we catch is how discovers everything what you want to hide, how his mind is more rapid than that of his dangerous opponents, how everything that makes makes it for something.It is a success that the protagonist is a normal type, a type in jeans and jacket, with glasses, a type that all have known, a type that we have all been. So far the realistic granting of the character. Then becomes in Spade, a loner with a loyal friend, his assistant, looking for the answer to the murder of his ex-girlfriend (quiet, this is counted in the first minute of the movie). A boy who seems fragile, but is the hardest. and the smartest. A good work of Joseph Gordon-Lewitt (but also the rest of the cast). Highly recommended to enjoy and also to remember these classic movies, that never go out of fashion, that have grown and they helped us to love the film. As Ryan Johnson.</body>
</review>
