<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Voces en la noche" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>That could have been and was not suits this desmadejado attempt to revalidate the dramatic career of Williams with a psychological thriller of series B, false, impostado, and at the end of the footage, hollow</summary>
	<body>Listless and impostado exercise of melodramatic thriller with a Robin Williams focused and solvent, disaffected of tics, credible, greased the seriousness that the character demands, though one can avoid that anytime you make a mohín, twist an eye or, if this is possible, look into the camera and ask us, witty, mischievous, if us is enjoying the mess.In this night listener which is here entitled voices in the night (there can be more overused and suspicious title) there are delicate matters that do not get relevant responses. The exquisite statement of facts collapses farrulleramente when the director, in view of the castle of signs has raised, warns that there is no hand or charm to finish them. Creative licensing orphan, arrumbada to the shelf of the failed projects, voices in the night excited timidly: the history of a radio announcer who was fascinated with the existence of a book written by a fourteen year old boy becomes manifest Existentialist about love and loneliness, feelings and the need to invent someone to cope with the weight of the routine, the tough evidence know that there truly anybody who loves us or for those who have. The book of yore opens the pandora of dark, desangelados, beings to the point that Gabriel Noone (Robin Williams) ends up wondering if the child writer and his mother (with whom only spoke by phone) there are indeed disenchanted.His sentimental precarity (has been abandoned by a lover infected with AIDS) does that you dwell by the boy that, on top of evils is also infected (some abuse in childhood) and lives overprotected by her mother (a wonderful Toni Collette).The clever (and sorry) night announcer makes us private investigator and flies to Montgomery (Wisconsin) to submit to the polygraph in his eye the veracity of the story and discover (behold the very fragile central point of the story) mother and son shall not, in the background, a lonely and disturbed if, and assure you (oh dear reader) that I do not damage to the viewing as already in the first few minutes is the own Noone / Williams who puts in dance this speculation. Patrick Stettner narrative pulse is more than decent: no sins of resultadista, not rummages in what others well could have rebañado, this is merely detective aspect of history, and offers a magnificent cast to fill that, surely, do not forget: the argument is flagging towards his half and that moving towards its denouement, interest goes back until there is no interest. Claim to be based on real events can be one burden rather than a candy: we need an intelligent writer than descuadre the orthodoxy of the truth and it rub all of pure fiction. Me (now) can spy on me and make a movie about my daily tráfago: would lack a teacher of teachers to make my day (today, why go any further) gave a notable film. Different case, desirable case would be that on my boring routine of Friday (oh is Friday, what well) a clever writer introduced the minimum elements of digression as to which Ethan Hunt, by my side, was a timid public servant. This is not, nor speak, the subject of which we speak. Not enough that Robin Williams is superb or that the treatment of light is one character: need (such is many times) that the story is attractive and we do not have the impression of having been deceived, but lasts less than an hour and a half and (to be honest) at the end all pass in a plis plas.Okay both punishment and a walk along the shore of the River in an evening of rain. Anything goes if we do not mind wet us. The film wet (avanzo) is capitalized, but there will always be who (eccentric, boring, caprichosito) want to that moment of intimacy with the rigors of mother nature.We must, however, remain pending this Stattner, saving that, elsewhere, would be pyrotechnic first-rate material now that they are failures of Valencia in its heyday.</body>
</review>
