<review author="Jamfris" title="Ice age 2 el deshielo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Succession of very good gags hilvanados with a little story with small interludes of the squirrel</summary>
	<body>Do a couple of weeks ago we went to the cinema to see this film to the film, as he was eager to? already with the first I enjoyed it very much, and hoped that this not me disappointment. I loved the movie.The argument is not too complicated, basically, a fairly large group of animals kills the time in a valley next to the glacier, the prehistoric squirrel still in search of its do nut? It avellana?, and the mammoth Manny, believed to be the last of its species is a female specimen with which try to flirt? a from there little secret.I think that compared to the first, this suffers from a much less elaborate script, is rather a succession of very good gags hilvanados with a little story with small interludes of the squirrel, some posts a little with shoehorn. Something like what's happening with Shrek 1 and 2. The history of the first is very good, and in the second they are limited to chaining jokes.Do anyway that not worthy the final result, which is very fun, especially with the inclusion of two new characters, opossums, comic relief? and very comical. They have a pair of stellar moments (when making the gesture of "I am watching" or the farewell to the rapper) and in general are the best of the film. Others maintain the level, Diego teeth less fierce sable and a kind of parody of and-go-a-la-ruin scurry (reference Prachettiana), which would be able to sell his mother.At a technical level, is the animation really elaborated, especially regarding animal hairs, although the can of water is also very well done? do while in this type of films becomes a secondary argument? I am referring, of course, important thing is more history/characters, although it is always appreciated that the representation is worked.No doubt a highly recommended film for all audiences, ideal to spend a fun and entertaining film time.</body>
</review>
