<review author="Isabel Aparicio" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the things that fascinate me most of this film is the evolution of each character, perfectly symbolized by the road (a journey to the interior of each). These disparate personalities together are van complemented each other, to conform to the end of the film, as if it were a puzzle, the structure of family.</summary>
	<body>One of the films that lately has captivated me is little Miss Sunshine, Jonathan Dayton and Valerie Faris, independent film very well received by the various international film festivals. Winning two Oscars, for Best Original Screenplay and best supporting Actor (an impeccable and amazing Alan Arkin), swept a day earlier at the Spirit Awards, the equivalent to the Golden statuette of independent film.The hope and enthusiasm of a girl by make their dreams come true, together with their fear of mediocrity, are the starting point of this wacky adventure. Olive is summoned to participate in a child beauty pageant, so ludicrous family full embarks on a dilapidated yellow van bound for California.Una of the things that fascinate me most of this film is the evolution of each character, perfectly symbolized by the road (a journey to the interior of each). These disparate personalities together are van complemented each other, to conform to the end of the film, as if it were a puzzle, the structure of family.All actors shine with their own light. Olive (Abigail Breslin) is a sweet girl and plump who lives in a world of fairies and dreams of being a Princess. His brother Dwayne (Paul Dano) is an eccentric teenager, angry with the world, which meets a strict vow of silence to get their greatest aspiration, to be pilot. Although he hates everyone, needs his family, and you wish to in their own way. The character of badass Grandpa and drug addict (Alan Arkin) is a turning point in the evolution of the protagonists (family who gets involved in a mess together, stays together), and more confidence has deposited in the talent of the girl. The picturesque Uncle (Steve Carell), homosexual depressed after being rejected by his great love, stars in a failed suicide attempt, which leads him to become part of the clan. It works as a link between the members of the family, trying to soften the conflicting episodes. The father (Greg Kinnear) is a seller of stories on the success doomed to failure. Their vain attempts to control the situation and lay on the triumph Chair rub pathos. And finally, the mother (Toni Collette), only normal character with a very special vocation: to care for his family.I believe that the substance of the story is of great importance. The feeling of being a loser in a society obsessed with success. The script is masterful. Combines satirical dyes with black humor, situations that invite laughter and images that leave footprint: all members of the family pushing and going up, one by one, the old van without a door, underway. In my opinion it comes to represent, even if the external structure (the wrapper, surface) is obsolete and damaged, if you struggle teamwork by a common goal, the goal can be achieved. The final sequence which Olive shows her skills as a dancer is that shocked me. Despite being very funny, caused me a knot in the stomach. The reaction of the family of the girl is brilliant and unexpected. It is reflected that support and affection are shown not only with words but also with acts. And also the misunderstanding by firecracker of society (participants and jury of the beauty contest) and the more superficial sector is clear.If still you have not had the opportunity to enjoy this film, I advise you to not be her escape.</body>
</review>
