<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Sneakers (Los fisgones)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that guarantee entertainment and where, unlike so many with more name and best critic, not enough or a minute. Or lack.</summary>
	<body>Sneakers or the snoopers takes place entirely in a chapter of novels of espionage at the time when the Russian spy and Americans were being monitored. Or it was upside down or happening both at the time and we will put skewers of tortillo tourists in Fuengirola. Sneakers is not worthy of a Clancy or a Forsyth material, but in cinema is a worthy example of entertainment with message, although everything is here diluted kindly thanks to the skillful layer of overwhelming commercialism that fills all the footage. Hide, however, a relevant discourse about the consequences of high technology in society highly tech and to embroider the joke, let us dive (without air, sweet bareback bottle) the responsibility of open one than another civic awareness regarding the Muskat argument proposes: a kind of decoder that accesses any computer network of the world (behold the omniscient God)(, the eye that monitors, the old theory of the demiurge constantly on alert by the barbarism of its creation).Sneakers opts for not apabullar with social ramifications: it wasn't Robert Redford then for messing the blanket to the head after the fiasco of Havana or indecent proposal, and here gets in the hands of a skilled director who puts on a platter of gold a dramatic, novel, film show where there is side of luxury (Dan Aykroyd)River Phoenix before falling to the ground sobrevitaminado of adrenaline, Sidney Poitier, Ben Kingsley and James Earl Jones. ).The script takes here and there until the mcguffin hitchcokiano us costs and can tell us the story they want because already swallow. The final inconsequential, that not knowing what we're playing really, but how nice game have had, (loosely) refers to games of war, John Badham, but are different films made at very different times even if they are ten or perhaps less the years that separate them. Thus the times. The writers of that are the writers of this. Case of Snekers had been filmed in Europe by European hand, we would have a more genuinely social Ribbon, a banked product exploitation of the political bis that arañara (a zarpazos if they could) the consciousness of the Viewer without either spending excessive rooms.As the film is made in Hollywood, rather than scratching consciences, it rubs, slightly plays, hedgehog skin with much tact, not going to be flaming fire of artifice that we have sold to affect us too much and we descreamos the system to the point that not him let the current as we have been doing so far. All of these signs are evidence of the direction the American cinema of the early nineties was catching: narrative shortcomings offset with verve and ex officio, with distributions of bells and (almost always) measured expectations.Today (again) times are changing. Bob Dylan said. And with its trogloditas Loquillo. And now what I say because seeing some years later gives extra information, a plus in purely objective kind, i.e., in the informed idea of what you are seeing is a good film, one good, really, without folds, live, endowed with sufficient charms to forget its frivolous nature in the background, although exposed cartoon has its miga and its nasty.</body>
</review>
