<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La Caja Kovak" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without prejudice to foreign glories, worthy example of autonomic thriller (almost) with attractive enough to enrapture the audience and earn a place in the desolate ranking of gender in Spain.</summary>
	<body>The national thriller has little background so that we obviemos this piece strange in our cinematography that has value in itself and what it represents. Away from the formal selfishness of other products of the genre, Daniel Monzón (a critic got to director, the man crossing the mirror) clings to the Hitchcock film, to its elegant, and elastic frames in debit with the literature of Patricia Highsmith and B movies of the sixties (there are implants and the evil of the film with nod to the bad guys of the Bond series or a vulgar Manchu). Nor need look grateful to Ray Bradbury and the greedy American production of the 1950s with threats Psychotronic and terrifying theories about alienation.The Kovak box is a fast-paced film paused when necessary, embastada with discrete moviegoers notes and performed as a macabre Symphony whose final (in some very well thought Cuevas del Drach) deserves to go to the history of the patriotic cinema for the simple reason that we are not, in any way, accustomed to that whiff to end made in Hollywood. The doctrine of monsoon is entertainment, a meticulous sense of the filming as a vehicle of transmission of entertaining content. And the tape, complete, entertaining over not being able to. It cracks by the artifice of the script, which gives the impression of being very forced, although writer (own monsoon with writer Alex de la Iglesia, Javier Guerricaechevarría) engasta all the excesses that everything flows gently, with a package to great classic movies occasionally. Not in vain started quoting Hitchcock that monsoon extracted from the estimable Chair of Don Alfredo the twists and the wordplay, monumental levels (scenes from the airport, the rush of the House to the vehicle that is giving away the dangerous roads of the coast) and, above all, the mechanics of the fascination, that is, the way in which the film takes place until its outcome, it may seem a forced point (also), but there was no other unless we resolve a purer version of Sci-Fi, nothing relevant. Timothy Hutton, Lucía Jiménez and, above all, David Kelly (Grandpa of Charlie in the chocolate factory) are great, although the role of Silviia / Lucia is raised, not explained if we are aspiring to earn a territory in the thriller with solvency, not thing of trying (taking into account our holganza in everything that it smacks of risk) strain us already with carpet and fanfare in science fiction. Time, no doubt, it will be. While to savor Spanish films like this, so pleasant in the formal, so enjoyable (again).A commentary from the director about Gloomy Sunday, the song that the tape plays Billie Holiday and underlying all the plot: "Is a very special song called Gloomy Sunday and which has an incredible legend." Wrote it a Hungarian Rezsô Seress in 1933 and later committed suicide. In the following years, was a song banned in the radios of the United States and Great Britain because they said it was a song that induced suicide. Indeed, it was found that many suicidadas people had heard the song before the kill. It's a song actually very sad, with something very special and mysterious in it, which is one of the songs more versioneadas in the history of music. "I have tried to give the film a tone very similar to the song, i.e., dark, disturbing, but with a large underground romanticism".</body>
</review>
