<review author="Luis Zueco" title="Closer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Chive Owen, performed an interpretation of the sublime in his relationship with Julia Roberts, despite their corpulence of his physique, knows occur as helpless, weak and desperate.</summary>
	<body>Yesterday he had the pleasure to see the film "Closer" again, and the truth is that I liked more than when he saw brand new. Of course there are two performances on leave on the Quartet of actors, the two that we consider most secondary within the fame which have four. Are Clive Owen, excellent, intelligent at the same time simple. But a simplicity of those which is not exactly a bad thing, but just the opposite, of a man who makes her his strength. Someone who sees things so clear that they have the intelligence of draw roads as who draws straight lines with a ruler on a map on the table. The great Natali Portman, of which you can not fall in love over and over again. Here it's an excellent role, especially in the scene in which leaves her boyfriend, how someone can happen to a person madly to let her love, not hate her, but simply not wanting.But turning to chive Owen, performed an interpretation of the sublime in his relationship with Julia Roberts, despite their corpulence of his physique, knows as someone helpless, weak and desperate. Thus making guilty to Julia Roberts, who is vilely emotionally blackmailed by him. What makes Clint in the film happens in reality though normally not we realize. There are cases in which a person to retain your partner, who already don't feel absolutely anything for her, what does is play to make her feel guilty. And no one likes to feel guilty of the evils of other, even more if we wanted them to ever. Guilt is a great weapon in the hands of someone like Clive who know how to use it in such a way that it binds first to Julia Roberts and then pulls her until he returned to his side, which will hardly already separate. Here Clive demonstrates the strength of the weak, that not for the sensitive. Clive romantically manipulates Julia Roberts as you want, using his sense of guilt, while the really sensitive, helpless and insecure is the other male protagonist, Jude Law, however it at least does not use guilt, not takes advantage of this. That happens that at the end end of losing everything, just to have something of dignity. But in love, in life, we must choose, or have enough dignity to not manipulate people or take advantage of it, which hardly we reach something, or if, by what you surely get much of what we propose, even happiness, but at that price.</body>
</review>
