<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Hannibal: El origen del mal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The return of Hannibal the Cannibal, popularly known among us as Hannibal the Cannibal, has left us cold. A notable boredom, dotted with cuajarones of blood, that ends up leaving a bad taste in mouth, honestly.</summary>
	<body>The return of Hannibal the Cannibal, popularly known among us as Hannibal the Cannibal, has left us cold. As everyone will know at this stage, "Hannibal, the origin of evil" does, precisely how the famous Doctor Lecter became the monster to which all have known and feared in the film, with the face of Anthony Hopkins.¿Por what expected something important from this film? Well, mostly because the script is printed the signing of Thomas Harris novel father of the character, what did predict a good development of the plot, a logical origin of the character and furthermore in the cannibalism myth so good and so bad times has made us enjoy and suffer in theaters.And the thing starts well, counting the death of the family of Lecter in World War II and, subsequently, the humiliation suffered by his sister and him from the hands of a group of Nazi sympathizers. Their flight is well and synthetically told, as well as his arrival in France, where he begins a contradictory relationship with her aunt of Japanese ancestry, performed by the attractive Gong Li, that does but win in beauty and magnetism with each film.This first part is very well told, is interesting and can be seen with great interest. But then. Oh then! After the episode of the butcher, very revealing of the future hannibaliano nature, everything gets out of hand and the film banalized, becoming a stupid and unbelievable story of revenge that only relies on gruesomeness and jets.The trip to the USSR and the episode of the hut marked a turning point that turns what was an interesting and worthy film that was elaborating on the keys of a series as interesting as Hannibal the Cannibal, in a Masque of death and destruction quite idiotic, poorly told and worse resolved.Arrive yawning, eyes to the phone to display the time, the roar of guts asking chicha and uncomfortable movements in an armchair that already click. He began a remarkable boredom, dotted with cuajarones of blood, that ends up leaving a bad taste in mouth, honestly.A penalty, to sum up, note how the Laurentiis, holder of the rights to the character of the Doctor Cannibal, are ending credit in the series, in an attempt to exploit the goose that lays the golden eggs that their latest sunsets you are smelling to rotten. More and more.In short, a disappointment.</body>
</review>
