<review author="Luis Zueco" title="El Efecto Mariposa" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great movie. It is for many reasons. The first and most important for what makes you feel.</summary>
	<body>Because many people will not be agree with me but for me, this is a great movie. And Moreover, I say this sincerely. A great movie. It is for many reasons. The first and most important for what makes you feel. At this point we all know what is the "butterfly effect", well in its atmospheric aspect (the flutter of a butterfly in New York can cause a hurricane in Tokyo, of done comes the name of "Butterfly", in his "chaos theory" (or as a small change can trigger an infinite disorder) or concerning the spacetime, if we make a small change in the past)so that the future change in an effect chain of unpredictable consequences.In this film feels the effects of this theory in any other who has tried to. This is the main achievement of the tape. Do you feel that each decision in life, every action that you perform, every gesture, Word? You can check the future. Say one thing or another in an instant of your life can mean from dying at a precise moment, to lead a happy life, or living a real hell, from one end to another cone a terrifying ease. In a situation of total chaos. The protagonist uses a few notebooks wrote small to go to the past, always at the same point, and although he always tries to fix things, never succeeds, comes back, and is always worse. As if the past could not, or it should be changed.The excellent end, a way to change things is not with a small change but with a total reversal. And that is what makes the protagonist.But just as there is the butterfly effect also appears at the end a concept unless so interesting and mysterious like him, the destination. As much as we change things as much as we fight the events, if two people have to find is love, sooner or later in New York or Madrid.A also highlight the female protagonist, usual of small beautiful girl in film roles for teenagers, but it shown here very consistent.The excellent soundtrack, especially the final track of Oasis "Spot Cry your Heart out", with the scene where in the street.</body>
</review>
