<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I heard that this was a small film and, indeed, has some fine. Although his influence is enormous and its field of action is greater still. Social cinema, film critical, harsh, corrosive, film good-humored in the background. Film which aspires to catch the viewer and ask, once again, get excited. You can still.</summary>
	<body>Indie: Jesus said be the film that voluntarily deviates from the traditional circuits and brewing with the very clear intention of being independent, not contaminable tics of the majority consumer film. Then little miss Sunshine is not a tape indie, as they sell it, although Sundance endorsing her with their brand. It is independent, paragraph of the traditional circuits and massive commercial pretensions (in the style of Caribbean pirates or Spiderman in any of their deliveries) is his humility, his reluctance by apabullar: there is nothing in the script that might raise the amazement of the audience accommodated in a film of fireworks of fair, platonically shots or indisputable special effects. There is not an easy film and that (well looked) gives a status of rare piece in this world of ours in which everything is conducted through the affordable, easily chewable, but as the tape has participated in the Hollywood Oscars and has entered the ring (say) of industry, it seems that it should be evaluatedcriticized, understood as one movie entertainment family in the style of those listed above, both worthy and the pleasure of this digital scribe.Little Miss Sunshine is a road-movie anthology, happily acid, corrosive in his simple way of showing diseases of a society, the American, too delivered to satisfy delights immediately and convert everything in fast-food fast consumer product, is a hamburger, is a book, is a film. This is a dysfunctional family, which is a fashionable word. The Hoover are the paradigm of the broken family: nobody has the head where it should. There is a teenager between the grunge and the Nietzschean does not speak for imposing discipline (ay if San Juan de la Cruz raise his head), a grandfather pornographer who sniffed heroin in the spare and advised the free love and fornication as a hobby, a father hooked to Sociology light to the Paulo Coelho, a brother-in-law gay fresh out of a suicide attempta girl plump that wants to be miss and a selfless mother, authentic lung of a family destined to burst any minute of the day. Welcome to hell, says the autistic mozalbete at one point in the film.Friendly, acid, perverse, intimate, colloquial: there are many adjectives. The quality, however, most dominant is the optimism, the crucial fact that a road check North, the future. Or a desmantelable van in pure junk not pursue their final destination: the hotel in Redondo Beach, California in which will take place a unique competition, the choice of Miss Sunshine, aberrant contest girls where, at the end, the fabulous outcome, a kind of metaphysical climax in which one reconciles with the goodness of the film occurs, with its holy catharsis. In other words: now that it is not possible to see it in cinema, come to the nearest video store. They have one close. Or one of those impersonal ATMs that eject the dvd as if it were a condom in a night of partying and had one all enfebrecidos instincts.Go. To run. You will not see the best film of the year, but it is (strongly) one of the most fresh, ironic, scathing and, above all, pleasant.</body>
</review>
