<review author="Silvia" title="En tierra de hombres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The interpretation of Charlize Theron became the epicenter of the film and makes it worth waiting to see the predictable end</summary>
	<body>The mines are not for women. or that is what they believe the men of North Country when back in the eighties, they begin to working women in the mine of that region. However, there appears Charlize Theron to prove otherwise. "Land of men" is the film that nominates Charlize Theron for the Academy Award for best main actress, for the second consecutive year. The interpretation of Theron in this film returns to pleasantly surprise after his transformation into "Monster", tape in which he played a prostitute and assassin, sentenced to death in 2002. In this new drama, the actress embodies the character of Josey M'aimes, a battered mother of two children who returns to his hometown after leaving her husband and decides to work in the mine because the craft he reported more money than anyone else. Of course, the fact that women work in the mine isn't appropriate in the traditional North Country people by what the character of Josey confronts with his parents (Richard Jenkins and Sissi Spacek) and fellow of the mine, who see their jobs threatened by women and downloaded their iras with sexual assault and humiliation to her companions. But the character of Charlize Theron is not resigned and struggle to ensure respect for their rights by presenting a lawsuit against his superiors by his indifference to the harassment suffered by women at the mine. Josey counted with the support of their peers for filing the demand, a judicial action that became the first joint demand ("class action", in English) by sexual harassment, and ending by modifying legislation in all America. three plot lines intertwine in the Indent at three different times: the trial, problems in the mine suffered by the protagonist and the adolescents in the town are displayed Alternativelyas the statement as a witness of Josey unfolds. At the end of the film - pretty predictable - bind three times the script pretty fluently. Abuse, sexual abuse, unmarried mothers, degenerative diseases, problems generates international between father/daughter or mother/son, kidnapping of children conflict undoubtedly seeking play the chord of spectator, which is why in this film there is no room for comedy. Another weak point may be the fact that perhaps because of the enormous amount of characters that appear in the film, it is impossible that all of them appear perfectly psychologically outlined. The interpretation of Charlize Theron, instead, has become the epicenter of the film and makes it worth waiting to see the predictable end.</body>
</review>
