<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Bosque de sombras" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What could have been and was not: a failed, although worthy, example film ruined by a dash vulgar, devoid of any claim.</summary>
	<body>It could be another movie of visitors stuck in a spiral of violence in a hostile atmosphere full of locals wicked, but is in other rural thriller coined by all the conventions of the genre. Smells like Sam Peckinpah (straw dogs) and also gives whiff John Boorman (Deliverance), although there is no blatant plagiarism and is all in evidence shows respect and tribute to these two masters of cinema, but Bosque de sombras (The backwoods) lastra a script of an amazing precarious taking into consideration almost craftsmanship of a director (Koldo Serra) who spoils his work and it is of a quality without saying: shines photography, acting appearance and a sort of location for foreign that we didn't have news in the recent national cinema.The argument we punished a slow exacerbates: is not an appetizing delinquencies on which rest some Wicker of the script. We all have certain of the direction on which to tack the fabric. Partly because we have seen straw dogs, or perhaps because the work of writing has not been so to the height as everything else. Or an absolutely great Gary Oldman (who wins integers in this little in his career, but in his filmography of quality role) get that we can get more involved in the film. Well-stocked to use clichés that populate the genre, Bosque de sombras no cares in retouch them, lead them to their land. Stylistic patterns are filmed with superb style: is one very pleasantly impressed by the light (there are scenes that are attached to the memory after seeing the movie), but desastra the whole with a noise that encorajina us because we would like to (is my case) that the tape contained other merits to get fully where points: towards a round film in a rookieyou look at what most difficult subject. Jorge Sánchez-Cabezudo succeeds in its exquisite the night of the sunflowers, already criticized on these pages.This rugged and dry portrait on violence and incommunicado detention ends up Suomi their undeniable successes with an also rugged and dry finish where we do not know more and (jobs to be fascinated by the plot) rather than it would like. This lack of information does not help that the review is more golosa in beautiful adjectives and joining this unfortunate inventory of great films (without hypocrisy) (some almost masterpieces) die from any reviewed bleeding, a bug in the screws which means that the building come down just at the moment that we were more enjoying his climbing. To highlight the presence of Lluis Homar in State of grace in the role of vengeful garrulo surrounded by morons garrulos. The three films that I know (La mala educación, Los Borgia and it) show a huge job and a future (and already has the man his years) to consider.</body>
</review>
