<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Admitido" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Youth film about some kids who create their own University. They do not have hilarious moments, or take advantage of the potential that could be, but can be seen. Video store meat.</summary>
	<body>It looks that these American student comedietas rarely me like. All this roll American Pie find it me boring, and is American humor (except the Scary Movie type) I do not get. To say that one only I am amused when the girl said "Music Camp got the flute pussy" I tell everything about this type of film. But as I am brave, I myself therefore to see this, only because I owe to my public.The film is about a somewhat void, but clever, student is not admitted in any of the eight universities to which chooses. To avoid facing their parents, get an orondo buddy makes a very realistic web page on a fictional University, where if it is admitted. To finish the farce, with a few not admitted, they rent an abandoned building (a former psychiatric hospital) and give aspect of University. But things get complicated when hundreds of misfits and not admitted occur, upon payment of the registration, the supposed University.Well, well, what most curious movie, of those that adorn the shelves of the closest video shops. History is not bad, it is original but rather incongruous. Develops through semi normal channels, only that the thing loses the North, reaching the peak in a subrealista trial that I was not interested, nor to me towards the end. The cast of actors, well what is expected of a tape of these, very prototypical. Although the idea of creating a University, say that special, I thought it was very funny and I liked. Although the final outcome of the work I did not at all.In short, youth film about some kids who create their own University. They do not have hilarious moments, or take advantage of the potential that could be, but can be seen. Video store meat.If there is material and interest, why not leave mancebos and mancebas in leather?</body>
</review>
