<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los 300 espartanos" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Epic film about the 300 Spartans who fought the Persian forces in the Thermopilas Strait. A must see classic of ancient battles. There is no great special effects, but or lack making it. The script, sets, actors, in any amount, makes a peliculón of those you must see.</summary>
	<body>300 criticism has now the glorious Tito Chinchan, measures with the same reliability goals from Romario, who says that he already has 1000 accounting to which they gets their children when playing with them. And of course, what better to critique 300 that criticize the movie 300. Nothing, of course. So I went to the origins, to the source, at the beginning and I've seen the original film 300. None of the fag that based on the comic by Fran Miller, no, no, no. Much better this, which has that stale taste of old film, where the fighting are childish, but that everything stays involved in the drama of a good script and actors delivered a great final result. OLE than most nice peliculón.The film is the Emperor Xerxes of the Persians who decides that he has to conquer the world. At that then those who took the cat to the water in the West were the Greeks, so the Persians sent the most powerful army ever known against the Hellenes. The latter, for a change, not completed the danger, not quierían see it or what was I, so only the Spartans and Athenians were allied against the Persians. But not all the Spartans, who said they were on a spree and not out there or kidding, if not only 300 to stop thousands of pissed-off Persians who were going to leave this done a lot. Then with two balls that fought these Spartans. Sparta alive and the mother that bore, alive.I think that the topic is already being enough profiling, no? The film tells a story of Government intrigue, posturing, honour and courage, of impossible amorios, aberrant betrayals, fighting, power and miseries. And all seasoned with those impossible dialogues and some very elaborate decorations. But to elaborate. The fight scenes falter a bit, but it does if not enlarge the epic of the film. And this is to say nothing of the end, makes the hair like hooks from 23. Wow, and the voiceover that tells us the facts that happened later us levantá of the couch to go to release Sparta, or at least to go for some popcorn, or piss.In short, epic film about the 300 Spartans who fought the Persian forces in the Thermopilas Strait. A must see classic of ancient battles. There is no great special effects, but or lack making it. The script, sets, actors, in any amount, makes a peliculón of those to be see. tremendous clasicón!!!!</body>
</review>
