<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Hannibal: El origen del mal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unpleasant film about the most famous fiction canibal. It is long and is long. It is unpleasant and remove the stomach and consciousness. Anything I liked, but I recognize him that he manages to convey.</summary>
	<body>That laughter with my medium Zucchini, which I say see Hannibal's and tells me that I did not know that they had recorded no film of the conqueror. Hey, since it would be nice that they take one of Hannibal with his elephants charging on Rome, rather than these you prequels that are already beginning to smell. They could even take advantage of sceneries and extras and make a "Hannibal and the Jedi against the orcs of Persia". Tremedo peliculón, with Peter Jackson doing the extended for 6 days and 200 DVDs of extension. Jajajajaja, is that as the movie is bad, I have to give a touch of interest.The film is about Hannibal Lecter, a boy who lost his childhood and his family at the end of World War II. Total, which already teenager decides to devote his life to chase that ended with his family and step eat their cheeks. And also get a Japanese who lost everything with the atomic bomb and a police officer who chases the bad guys but not to eat them. And little more, really, are all the time with flashbacks of those.Well, the movie I did not like absolutely nothing. It is disgusting, with a continuous reminder of a horrible and scary scene. Which children have small, abstain from watching the film, then you will have nightmares. The actor who plays Hannibal is extrañísimo, with a deadpan face that hit nothing. We then sell this canibal as a sort of vigilante swordsman that softens not the Fund, which is what then eats them. In positive terms, photography is very good, with a few magnificent plans, but simply that good.In short, unpleasant film about the most famous fiction canibal. It is long and is long. It is unpleasant and remove the stomach and soul. Anything I liked, but I recognize him that he manages to convey.</body>
</review>
