<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El caso Slevin" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The tape is ingenious, the original idea is good and perfectly fulfills the role of entertain more unpretentious</summary>
	<body>"The case Slevin" (Lucky Number Slevin) Paul McGuigan is the films that needed a certain complicity of the Viewer to be fully satisfactory. If one accepts the approach (what might be called "get in the game") you can enjoy the history while that if it does not likely will be disappointed.It is difficult to explain the plot of the film without gutting anything so I will comment on that history is a mixture of film noir with touches of comedy and some dialogues with spark. This mixture can mislead those who go looking for a more classic film noir (something type "Usual suspects" that we understand). For example the character of Lucy Liu, ready to investigate a disappearance of someone of good first, reminded me of the style of characters played Katharine Hepburn in "Bringing up baby" and other tapes of Screwball Comedy (bridging the gap, is clear). Even the villains of the function are friendly and somewhat cartoony.It is clear that if we have too many questions the film falls apart because there are some loose ends, which do not have much logic or elements are not well explained. The alleged great surprises are not so much if one is trying to discover them before they happen (which I don't do), and those that are seem somewhat improvised. By finishing with the defects of the film I would add that I think can spare you explanatory flashbacks which were not needed to understand the plot twists.So I think that it cannot be denied is that the tape is ingenious, the original idea is good and complies perfectly with the role of its leaders that is to entertain more unpretentious (what is welcome). It also boasts a very charismatic actors (Morgan Freeman, Ben Kingsley, Stanley Tucci, Bruce Willis) and others that are not so but carry out their duties (Lucy Liu and Josh Hartnett performed his best role here).As conclusion I will say that when I leave the film happy and humming the main melody from the soundtrack (a more than correct work of Joshua Ralph) I do not have any cause for complaint.</body>
</review>
