<review author="Evasee" title="Concursante" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Contestant is a desgarrada and vitriólica criticism of the economic system and the banks and the plot hooks you, with a history that is both macabre and ironically funny. Film fun, intelligent and done here.</summary>
	<body>Last Thursday I went to the preview of the contestant film, kindly invited by however friend and executive producer Xavier Villaverde, author inter alia of the great "13 bells" or "Finisterre".You know my deep animosity towards much of the Spanish film or Spanish music (well, does not know it but now yes) motivated in large part by a whole class of clunkers (subsidised a large majority) with which flood us the billboards and radio ora Yes, ora also. When a story is good, when the script is good and also the actors are great it happens that we have a good movie like this. Contestant is a desgarrada and vitriólica criticism of the economic system and the banks and the plot hooks you, with a history that is both macabre and ironically funny.Production and above all the post-production (digital, which gives some moments of the film a dreamlike atmosphere) are very collected, and (I'm going to say is not pejorative, but I say this as a compliment) makes that at times you feel to believe that what you are seeing is a harbinger of Audi. Of those that you like to see, that they consider not you idiot? Mr Sbaraglia borda, his role as poor wretched, unable to handle what comes on top is good, and he exalts. Myriam Gallego his wife is great, and of Chete Lera, little can be decír. I always thought that it is one of the best players in the world. Luis Zahera also is that secondary, likeable and bastard that makes each of their inroads made very funny moments.Some foreign are shot here in A Coruña and its sea, its foreign and its Sun, manage to be a perfect counterpoint to the gray and rainy images of the city, or the Bank. The music is another great success, media times, or the hardest guitarreos, even the electronics fit perfectly with the story. Maybe can blame you it stretches a tad in excess the end but my modest understanding, is something that overshadows not a job very well done. Film fun, intelligent and done here.</body>
</review>
