<review author="Red Stovall" title="Concursante" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The more risky product that has seen in years in the panorama of the Spanish film. Proposed wild at times, rebel to 100% and made with lot of passion. Only for this reason, the film deserves that you déis an opportunity.</summary>
	<body>Spanish Cinema urgently needs new blood to radically change things, is something that is obvious. Do last year had three materials operas that us hiceron rise to hope on the future of the Spanish film?AzulOscuroCasiNegro??The night of the sunflowers? and?Do a Franco, 14 Pesetas?, three great examples that make back to other films of more established directors. East 2007 is poised to offer us the same, and now comes the proposal of Rodrigo Cortes, someone whom I refiriré as the enfant terrible of our cinema, a nato provocateur, who knows what he says and defends tooth and nail that what you think, cinematically speaking, of course. And so he doesn't mind rebelling against the system and offer us the more risky product that has seen in years in the panorama of the Spanish film.The argument of?Contestant? tells of a young Professor of economic history to one day win the largest prize ever awarded in a television contest. What originally should be a huge joy, is becoming, little by little, a hell to discover that millionaire costs money has no. Initially it will try to fix the problem by asking for a loan at the Bank, but this won't do more than make things worse.The film is a complete Act of rebelliousness towards what we are accustomed to seeing out of these lares. Made with a very long value, it is how to make a double somersault and without network, something I think that Cortés has gone away, at least insofar as the work of direction, I think simply exemplary. Without hiding his influences of American cinema, ranging from Martin Scorsese (their particular God) to Paul Thomas Anderson, the film is a true Prodigy in Assembly is concerned, inferring a rhythm to the truly dramatic film, in which there is little time to think about things. Thanks to this frantic pace that does not give any respite, the criticism that the film makes of the current economic system is simply brutal, leaving no puppet head. In that aspect, and bridging the gap to the film course, could pair you with the wonderful David Fincher film?The Club's fight?, although Cortés film lacks a better definition of characters.And I think that therein lies one of the loose film, that leaving aside the main character, I think that everyone else is neglected, some to the extent that virtually no paints nothing in history, as for example that of the girlfriend of the protagonist, which almost forcibly disappears the narration and before that the fact that in a few moments is incomprehensible is the typical dumb aunt to not be He finds nothing, and in others it is more espabilada. We also have the character of a lawyer without scruples that find it me excessive and burdensome, intentionally exaggerated, but I think it clashes throughout. Add to that a coworker of the protagonist and an old extravagant Economist that may be unmatched support for our protagonist has his moment of showcasing, but that we miss more than what it should.In terms of acting work, clearly shines itself a sensational Leonardo Sbaraglia, under absolutely all the weight of the film, one of the best tour de force which has been much time, achieving in addition not fall in the histrionics with a character given to it with ease. KET Lera is as Obi Wan Kenobi's role, providing us with Sbaraglia, the best sequence of the film, one that explains how banks, using a game of chess, a unique and extraordinary, moment that makes you want to not ever ask a credit to the Bank as a metaphor. Miryam Gallego and Luis Zahera are the worst affected, with two barely interesting characters, even though the first is the girl in the film, and the second a striking character, Yes, but empty.The formal aspect of the film can be said that, at times, ends up drowning in part some aspects of the story, as if it were the trees that can't see the forest. And it is that there are certain plot details that do not convince me or the least. For starters, the main character profession: Professor of economic history. It is a little shocking that someone with your knowledge is so pardillo on a subject who knows more than most people. The relationship with your partner is not very well defined. The issue of a loan from a bank is not entirely clear. And finally, something truly shocking: a millionaire uses a mobile card and no contract? Not I think so.So?Contestant? It is a film interesting but failed, or if you want to put it another way, failed but interesting. What I am I very clear is that Rodrigo Cortés has much to say in our film, because you know perfectly what noses happens within our cinematography (something already I speak another day, if he deserves the opportunity), and the way they manifest themselves perform a proposed wild at times, rebel to 100% and made with lot of passion. Only for this reason, the film deserves that you déis an opportunity.</body>
</review>
