<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Tristram Shandy" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story metadiscoursive which is sceptical about the crazy world of the film and the vicissitudes facing those involved in a shooting</summary>
	<body>** I have to confess that did not expect me such an outburst of astonishing Winterbottom humor before seeing your cock &amp; bull story (story of a cock and a Bull). Weeks ago I had seen a film of his, code 46, halfway between science fiction and romantic drama that left me quite indifferent. And before this wacky comedy, presented in competition in San Sebastian, the director had also premiered here 9 songs, a drama of high erotic content. This Copernican shift of gender emphasizes the unquestionable ability of the British to move a record to another. In this case, I think that Yes it has initialled a round film to merge in a same script adaptation of inadaptable novel, the life and opinions of Tristram Shandy, and a history metadiscoursive which ironically on the crazy world of cinema and the vicissitudes facing those involved in a shooting.The first thirty minutes pass at a frenetic pace from an absurd dialogue in which the two protagonists chatting on the "no whiteness" of teeth of one of them. Then they leave the makeup room and both begin to incarnate the roles of the film roll: the adaptation of the inclasificlable and mocking novel by Laurence Sterne. At the time roll, Steve Coogan plays himself, turns to the camera and gives his opinion on how children embody her character, Tristam Shandy, during childhood. It is the most comical see him criticise the performance of one of them when it recreates the moment in which Shandy caught the penis with a window. "Looks, because I believe that it should not scream, seems forced;" "I think that it should do it another way?" Or more hilarious and surreal is the endless labor which will be born Shandy, in which the mother is about to burst while the men of the House, quietly, chatting about battles of the past to the waiting to arrive the doctor with a forceps for delivery; medical gadget will come but, given improved little that was to 18th century, it will be marked Shandy of for life with an aquiline nose.After the rapid start, the pace normalizes without losing the comical situations lived in a chaotic film. Shows the usual vanities rivalry that exists between actors and, at the time, producers, writers and actors are saying about films or actors who they like or dislike. Here, Winterbottom dispatches to taste with some colleagues (the dig to the most commercial American cinema is evident) and also praises to their favorites. Producers, as is often standard, put into question the waste of money for certain scenes, while actors and directors to defend his stance to preserve the artistic result.And although they stay in expensive hotels and earn enough money, actors, as happens to the great comedian Steve Coogan, also spend their small potholes, unsafe and fearful of its capabilities at times, and malsanamente envious with alien success and the compliment to the partner/rival. In addition, as his endless immaturity led them to commit some other sexual peccadillo, must pay certain easements to the press to bury such lapses. And more inri, in an intense day where these avatars are mixed with calls of the agent by proposing new work, barely can meet its duties as a good father and meet his partner in bed. In short, a chaotic life of which screenwriter Martin Hardy has managed to get an original comedy seasoned with the typical British phlegm.But Winterbottom, who did not want to be so cruel, took pity on a few characters who has not shown invariably capricious or worrywarts. It also left them to express a more humane and warm part that does not usually appear when the navel of one captures life itself. Although, for artists and people from the show, perhaps is them can forgive a certain excess of ego for the sake of a profession as escrutada and subject constantly to the minds of the public.At the end of the film, our actors, writers, producers, actors and the director who had adapted the life of Tristram Shandy, witness a first screening of the film in a small room. They seem not very satisfied with the result, but the two protagonists, oblivious to the seen tostón, return to the lelo and to bite each other retaking the absurd and comic dialogue of the principle. The comedy of Winterbotton does not end or in the opening credits; the immaturity of the actors and their crazy secure lives that will also continue beyond The End. ** criticism originally published in elojocritico.net 12/17/05, after its screening at the San Sebastian Film Festival of that year.</body>
</review>
