<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Empieza el espectáculo" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Biography of a unique director Bob Fosse. Musical an apotheosis, legacy of a genius.</summary>
	<body>As I does not attract the musical, begins the show (All that jazz) had not generated me any interest when a more than well stocked payment channel her scheduled some time ago. The interference of the music in the film was not (isn't it yet) Holy of my many devotions, but fell in the generous Act of sit to see when it was released on DVD. I pertreché a good dose of patience and I said that I would endure until the end because has the fame that has and the soundtrack. Only for the part On Broadway performed by a vitamin George Benson (I said) already worth the drink. The reality imposed on my prejudices: usually occurs. I have no problem asking for forgiveness or backtrack I: I enjoyed it very much, I found a unique and unusual, blatant, philosophical and cheerful, combat dramatic film and covered by a thin layer of bad milk great mark of the House, that is, of the great Bob Fosse, who had seen years ago Cabaret and of which I still keep miu pleasant memories (even though)(in spite of being musical film, clear).All that jazz (I'm going to call it instead of the less protein begins the show) is a Vertigo of ingenuity, a demonstration of the talent of a man obsessed with death, this autobiography filmed the choreographer and director Fosse, stripped and rarely cinema has shown a man presented letters of his death, evidence mortuary of a life escorada always to the excessrepresented on the screen in the character of Joe Gideon (a never more convincing Roy Scheider).The choreographed pieces and music occupy a considerable part of the footage is not without prejudice so that the film is not entirely musical. Music and dance are resources of a deeper idea: that of the descent to hell of a man who has escaped to his demons (to their vices, their sins (and now look how health undermines their challenge and arrumba le in a bed, where he makes danceable epitaph of its transit around the world.))</body>
</review>
