<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The truth is always written in the plural. A necessary film? unthinkable in the America of Bush - than good conciliator in this Spain our so desmemoriada with its history might encourage the spirit and so susceptible to the I am of Peter, I am John...</summary>
	<body>If flags of our fathers ran in continuing temporary fragmentations that danced between the reality (of the fateful battle field) and the drill (orchestrated by the powers that be of the moment), letters from Iwo Jima opts for presenting a more linear editing - and why not less discursive in its anti-war approaches and the presence always recurring memory of those who fell on the island (this time from letters that unnecessarily strove) (for sending their families)-, to the rhythm of a waltz as a slow waves (for who is not motivated, two hours and half it will be storm surge) without losing the feet on the island, evoking through letters and short scenes on the life of some characters the human side of the war in the Pacific, (common to both films) order to dismantle any ideology that leads to perpetuate the Manichean and hackneyed version the war hero, and in turn resize the true (or at least that gives us Eastwood) entity of heroism - most of the involuntary and casual - time of the soldier. This incessant effort deconstructor is and insurance will remain an effective and mature imprint in the Filmography of this great filmmaker.Now, what in flags of our fathers was a direct criticism of the political farce mounted around the heroes returned from Iwo Jima, here it declines Eastwood by an analysis more subtle and poetic of the absurdity of the war, focusing on the recreation of the event from the Japanese angle, or rather, looking for a sincere empathy with the experiences of the Japanese soldier who resisted the onslaught of American forces, but altogether devoid of criticism to the model of Japanese honour (with the suicide or suicide by dishonour as a backdrop) and, in turn, of self-criticism to American oblivion of a story that sold them (and we sold to us also indirectly) as good and bad, through war films of postwar. We must not forget the patriotic bloody Arenas (Sands of Iwo Jima), in which John Wayne calm as always saves America of the cursed charlies, while his dying soldiers fired with stoic penalty and plunges in to flag ' atop Mount Suribachi. Because of the unbearable Pearl Harbor (Michael Bay, 2001) or speak, right?In fact, few examples we have in the history of cinema that have dared to approach the Japanese point of view with respect and ideological nonsense. Include recent films such as the Empire of the Sun, by Steven Spielberg (who co-produced the film of which we speak), in which a young Christian Bale noted with admiration and curiosity to Japanese soldiers and their antler aircraft from his confinement in a concentration camp. Or the already legendary and not so distant in the Japanese Nagisa Oshima Merry Christmas, Mr. Lawrence, memory, where--from the unprejudiced look of a British soldier, interpreted with ease by David Bowie - already is given, in letters from Iwo Jima, an anthropological approach about the Japanese honour and sense of suicide, only that this time without the critical depth Eastwood stresses to describe the dehumanizing consequences of Japanese ancestral customs. The bridge on the River Kwai, David Lean, although to a lesser extent and with clear ideological positioning, we see how also appears to us the Japanese army humanized and understandable in their actions, in a strip and tug of war that it will lead towards the known end.However, there is no forget that letters from Iwo Jima is a film made by an American and focused a priori so her first visionen fellow, and then the rest of the so-called free world. It is not entirely a Japanese approach. But this does not only emphasize the courage of a narrative which shamelessly portrays the other (until recently the enemy) with a rigor and respect that reveal the universal intentions of Eastwood. This is used as a cultural bridge to the characters of general Kuribayashi (a prodigious Watanabe) and the Olympic and vitalista Baron Nishi. Both are accomplices of the Western Viewer, with which to identify their values and at the same time approaching conflicts typical of Japanese characters. For its part, the scared Baker, Saigo, serves as a thread conductor of all the plot - with which identify the rootlessness that produces on humans throughout war and the need to live that you encouraged in those who suffer from her - and in turn will be the innocent hand that will make possible the letters buried by time and historical oblivion be recovered so that we ourselves must not forget that these fragments left after the horror lived only everyday by way of wishes which fill our lives (a dog who escapes, skewing the hens of the neighbour; or a mother who asks his son to make only right and will protect them from bullets). We never stop being human, despite the horror of the war. The first dialog of the film opens with the following statement of the Baker Saigo: "this island is nothing sacred, for me her staying Americans".Also suggestive is the story of the military policeman Shimizu as Saigo no resists the absurdities that indiscriminately makes all conflict. For this reason, Shimizu is unable to kill the dog - and how much less a human being-. For its part, the character of the strict Lieutenant Ito is revealed as a pathetic grotesque of despechugado martial courage - a Japanese and impaired version of John Wayne - for whom if his fate is to sacrifice for the greater glory of the Emperor, will be the same fate who you rehúya and decries his sacrifice.It is this set of Russian dolls by way of small stories, placed in small facts about the general tapestry of the plot, which enriches so lucid and beautiful letters from Iwo Jima. At the same time enjoy also a more than ideal picture leaked in blue tones - sulfurar you as the volcanic island-, almost in black and white (the color of memories of those combatants). Eastwood knows what it does, and places the camera in the right place where count only what you want to, without further details that we despisten. Flat generals of the island are very beautiful, and quilting the tension of the scenes in the tunnels.Letters from Iwo Jima is a film needed - unthinkable in the America of Bush - which could well encourage the spirit conciliator in this Spain our so desmemoriada with its history and so susceptible to self I am Peter, I am John. Filmography of Eastwood is determined to unscrew, based on humanism without folds, clichés and prejudices of the old 20th century, where human beings are fragmented in good and bad by vested interests, ideologies, corrosive, and above all by our own fear to seek the truth, pelá and mondá, without additives.</body>
</review>
