<review author="Florinda Chic" title="El síndrome de Svensson" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is the influence of Sunrise which is not little, and that kind of absurd humor that it but with an abusive tendency to navel-gazing, what is the largest failure of this film and so many others of the recent film Spanish. What was invented the acknowledgements in the closing credits section?</summary>
	<body>Stendhal could see this film quietly and without palpitations Svensson syndrome is not a majestic masterpiece that had made him lose the sense. KEPA Sojo premiered in the film with a clueless film composed of: colorful characters, rocambolescas situations, metachistes, all the movies that we have seen, the music man who hears and his colleagues.Because this film sucks to colegueo, as if when he wanted to make a movie in the bar of a gambling den, had sworn to all the capacity that you would give a role. Apart from directing crap like this, Kepa wants to make clear that he has seen much film and the subtitles. Do do do I tell these winks?,? tributes? and parodies: psychosis, Bienvenido Mr. Marshall, the night of the Hunter, Ordet, A true story, Thelma and Louise, an Andalusian dog, with death on the heels, the husband of the hairdresser, Requiem for a dream? And if you've enjoyed all these films, as I wonder when I hear Garci shredding the films of George Cukor? why when you do a long do this?, anyway.The film is a road cañí movie in which stories on the road from Madrid to Xátiva intersect: a man looking for the woman of his life, others believed to have found and are going to get it back, a cataléptico, two rappers, two cocks, two truck drivers, a man, a pop group, a cooking?. With some you parts and it is true that the movie has moments of joke as Nacho Vigalondo dialogs or performance of secondary of the Rosa-that to see if it is to live up to its name, is an actor of first-. The cast is full of other familiar faces: Red rain, Fele Martínez, Adriá Collado, Eulalia Ramón and Pepe Sancho?The soundtrack features themes of Nosotrash and La casa azul and is another success of this tape is light and soon passes. In this?How great is my film? Sojo is the influence of Sunrise which is not little, and it is this kind of absurd humor but with an abusive tendency to navel-gazing, what is the largest failure of this film and so many others of the recent film Spanish. What was invented the acknowledgements in the closing credits section?</body>
</review>
