<review author="Silvia Giner" title="El síndrome de Svensson" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The balance sheet while it is good, I have to say that the film needless you footage. As it is a constant running gag, facing the viewer would have been most grateful remove 20 minutes...</summary>
	<body>Kepa Sojo arrives and brings a fresh comedy, fun with Absurd-Pop atmosphere and using a lenjuaje of the most delusional to tell us a story that could be very simple but is complicated and the characters end up interlacing with each other in a way peculiar muyyyy.As I admit and I assume geek, I have to admit that my movie I loved it and I have not stopped of laugh from the beginning until the end, although is that the majority will terrify. The gags are great and well the soundtrack going you can download it from the website http://www.elsindrome.com/index2.html and you will see that it is very funny.Svensson syndrome is a film unassuming, focused from a humility that is what makes this story end conquistandote with these characters that we can find "but not you you believe it" in the deep and panderetil Spain in which we live.The actors are all great, but honestly to my the Dick me sobran in the script. We also return to the same (they are higher for the role), but we are going which I have left is Enma poor has a very neglected skin (I recommend to buy a regenerating cream for the skin, is heche oil baby always after showering, drink much carrot juice and moderately sunbathe). Ay! Say that my favorite character was the singer of the group the balls, I think Orlando Bloom...The balance sheet while it is good, I have to say that the film needless you footage. As it is a constant running gag, facing the viewer would have been most grateful remove 20 minutes. This is something that said much in the premiere. It is not much less a film to win the Oscar but how nor the pretends you are going to give ** stars out of 5 which is very good and you are going to laugh much with her.</body>
</review>
