<review author="Txapulin" title="Una verdad incómoda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do feel me bad say this so crude form, but the film is a political pamphlet of Al Gore, who, as he presented himself,? was going to be the next President of United States? in the 2000 elections.</summary>
	<body>I have a few mixed feelings about this movie I'm not sure know to express. Basically I'd rather talk about the movie than the film itself. So I would like to be brief about the movie and then I extend on climate change.Feel me bad saying this so crude form, but the film is a political pamphlet of Al Gore, who, as he himself presents, "would be the next President of United States" in the 2000 election, Bush won by only a few votes in Florida. In a way the movie is a version of a presentation (a slideshow) that Gore has been doing since that same year worldwide, a talk that anti-Bush scales in its objectives among a consciousness on climate change decision-making and a plea. If you focus only on the first goal would be great, but the second adds that touch of tension so in keeping with the times, that do nothing but fill a little more my level of tired of politics in general. To me the latter undermines first thing, and is a shame that, in the end, each bar for your home.On the subject of climate change and global warming, will not be me who deny it, when it is evidence: just have to see the spring winter we spent and the drought that we have, and that looking out the window of House, to which we are to look at the TV we see how badly distributed rainfall. In addition to the known data, Gore provides interesting data in the movie, as the drying up of large lakes in Africa and Asia, the graphics of possible floods by melting and sea level rise, or oceanic flows that regulate the temperature of the Earth due to salinity, a large machine that can stop if a large amount of fresh water as the one on Greenland in the form of ice came pouring to the sea, something that already happened in the latter was glacial. After putting so of apocalyptic, the documentary ends with a "this can still save: saves energy, go by bicycle, recycle, uses an electric car, join an NGO, and especially not votes to Bush" (the latter does not say so clear, but means it obviously).In this topic I'm extremely pessimistic from the point of view human (this is cannot save) but optimistic from the point of view of the Earth as a "living organism" (call it gaia). If the land to survive, have to load all the humans, it will do. In other words: we are part of one larger system that we can not load, but that it can make of us if we are doing putadas. Ultimately, we are the first victims (or the fourth after the whales, seals and penguins), but there will be new species stronger and resistant to whatever it is that we have caused that they make this planet still alive. What is more, even think that you we need to make it so.Of course, this reasoning does not give us letter free to pollute, go by car to buy bread and the newspaper, spend loads of light and water, not recycle and vote to Bush, and to another level, doing wars for oil, build throughout the coast, hunting whales, etc., because the more we delay the revenge of Gaia, therefore better.</body>
</review>
