<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="The river king" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fu fa nor do or re or the or so neither my nor du or you have very clear here occurs the genuine existential uncertainty. Who don't I understand? It is the film leaves you Catatonic as a larva in a block exposed to the Sun's March on the roof of my house. I would now like to film to replenish me. Good.</summary>
	<body>This considerable nonsense covers the need we all consume pobretón film to distract us a little and to lift the look, get lost in domestic tribulations or leave serving to stretch the legs. If viewing occurs at home it is right time to exit to the terrace or go to the room of the computer if the cousin of Burgos has sent us this e-mail that we have been promised by sms where a powerpoint makes you stalks you laugh. This telefilm is the best that can be seen, but it is not a telefilm: it is a film with a veneer of seriousness and made for the screen is big, and that imposes a respect. Sometimes there are filmmakers (I think using the term correctly) go to pay respects and billed clunkers, or in this case, imperfections, grains in a clean skin, do not know, excessively straight lines when what we love is shortcuts.The king river is pleasant, formally correct, with some narrative pulse and its plot flows from less to more, with gentleness, apaciguadamente. There is no escenas-impacto. There is no sudden changes in script. There are no gruesomeness in other films to use. We could name ten films sister to this and that could spearhead this criticism. Yes: it is a reseña-comodín. The picks up one and applied to lots of tapes without fear to wander. So predictable and neutral is. It's empty. And that which did not attends supernatural solutions (although there is a hint of ghost species) or offers a Cartesian solution to the byways of his suspense. It is not a film that fill with enthusiasm and can even that certain public find attractive. It depends on what one calls when it comes to the movies. If you want to have a good time or take an exceptional time or simply leave hang out or amplify the time and convert it to the time, that is, the time The River King, that I do not know what is good, but I barrunto that something big. And I'm now going to the terrace to see if I forget or put you a post-it to my memory (faithful and accomplice) her preserve virus and improperly and can I, in the future, remember with affection, think: what good time spent watching The river king. Yes?</body>
</review>
