<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Extraños en un tren" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential classical film. Hitchcock us dips in the anguish of a poor man who sought only to separated from his wife and ends up becoming his life in hell. Tremedo clasicón.</summary>
	<body>Alfred Hitchcock, of which I will always remember the fear that I gave with the movie the birds, had a habit of leaving in all of his films. In a papelín helper, but always left. Well it seems to me, but man, perhaps a little more should select their roles. This comes up the train and give us a map of the butt of this gentleman that I doubt it is your best profile. If I were him, I would always draw in jacuzzis surrounded by ladies in leather and drinking champagne between her breasts, though he was the movie of birds, ja, ja, ja.The film is about two strangers who know casually on a train. One is a famous tennis player, is on the rise, the other a heavy fan heir to the first. Total, they engage in conversation and at any given time, the Crown tells him that if he kills women's tennis player, this must kill his father. It is the perfect crime, given that there is nothing that related crimes, and much less do suspect to the police who have been them. The tennis questions, but worse than the no.¿Que heir can tell this humble server on one of the masterpieces of cinema? The movie I really liked, but since then he notices it has age of retirement (56 Anita nothing less). The idea is superb, putting on the table a problem very well developed and executed. The actors do wonderful, and photography is very effective, aided by the soundtrack. But it also has things that give a bit of laughter, given that old it would be "evil" but now are childish. For example, to show us how bad is the heir, not think something else click the globe to a child. Muahahahaha, that is the sound made by the evil to the laugh.In short, essential classic film. Hitchcock us dips in the anguish of a poor man who sought only to separated from his wife and ends up becoming his life in hell. Tremedo clasicón.</body>
</review>
