<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El velo pintado" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The work of Curran stands out above all in the main and final parts, showing a drama more exenso and deep where relationships are being opened and closed depending on the moment.</summary>
	<body>After seeing that the good German was not receiving a good critique, I chose to go unnoticed, since before I wanted to see her. And fortunately I saw that had premiered the painted veil, another literary adaptation with classic atmosphere. Thanks to this intelligent decision, can enjoy two hours of a very good film, classical, that Yes, but less magical than others of time.The film is beautifully directed by John Curran, almost debutant, given that it had only directed independent and unknown Praise and we are no longer two. In her second film employs techniques, dialogues and belonging to a very classic romantic era, and that situations does not mean that it is a film without personality, not. This is a film that behind his apparent simple face of simple appearance hides a personality with an enormous beauty and a delicate sense of understanding the human personality. Yes, you look like I'm echagerando, but when you see her you shall give account to the painted veil goes far beyond the typical classical adaptation, although they can hide and apparent be like this. I said at the beginning that the film is directed by an exceptional ability and is lucky to not be boring, because I've seen some films in style serve rather than as a movie as a sleeping pill (as Cold Mountain). Although Curran work stands out above all in the main and final parts, showing a drama more exenso and deep where relationships are being opened and closed depending on the moment.Another good aspect of the film is the magnificent script, based on the novel by w. Somerset Maughman. In fact, in the 1934 Richard Boleslawski shot the veil painted with Greta Garbo and Herbert Marshall, which Ron Nyswaner is not only based on a novel but that has also made a remake. And that is perhaps one of the few flaws of the film he seems too much a remake, but well, this already are used. Anyway, as I say, the script remains a unique and wonderful piece without barely cracks or slippages of pace, slow, that Yes.After talking the outstanding direction and the wonderful script, I could not finish this criticism without before naming the couple protagonist, Edward Norton and Naomi Watts. As you adored, due to the large amount of great performances that have made during his career, the two are sublime, offering us some papers human, Avengers, tender and naive and intelligent at the same time. For my taste, Naomi looks more, and is the main reason is because it goes far more than Edward. But luckily, both actors, along with secondary (Liev Schreiber and Toby Jones, mainly), make a few interpretations bright, full of charisma.Finally, emphasize more technical aspects such as the picture (great levels of landscapes, above all, or the close-up) and the music by Alexandre Desplat (winner of a Golden Globe Award for this film), which highlights the main theme on piano, which is quite exciting.In short, we have a round film, very classical air, with a formidable script and a couple protagonist rubs the Oscar. Hopefully all the modern adaptations of classic books were like the painted veil.</body>
</review>
