<review author="Matías Cobo" title="300" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Voluntarily away all realism and assuming completely present in the comic-style, 300 offers two hours of bloody battles, artistic forcible any limbs and heads, but, first and foremost, a surprising visual result.</summary>
	<body>Frank Miller, renewer of the comic book in the late 1980s and one of the consecrated geniuses of the ninth art along with the legend of the Alan Moore graphic novel, begins to envision a new future for the pairing to vignettes and celluloid are starring in recent years: "with 'Without City' and '300' arises a kind of hybrid film." I love the energy that provides animation. And that, coupled with the visceral impact of the actors, manages a good combination. (?) It could be a long 'affair' which has become marriage. (?) Earlier, normal was that comics expoliasen. They kept the name, but the 'movie' could go up by a parody of the comic book. "It is time for my trade out of the jungle and take its place alongside other art forms".I would add to the words of Miller that within this boom of translations of the comics to the movies might be a gradation to the already established in the comics for years: separating the adult comic strip from the rest of comic books aimed at a mainstream of heterogeneous ages. Thus, if on the one hand, they would be created mainstreams to destroy the box office with titles like Spiderman, Superman or Batman, on the other would suitable for adults only tapes based on cult comics such as the upcoming Watchmen, the sequel to Sin City and this 300. The objectives of both types, given the disparate financing requiring some and others, are very different: while some pursue considerable income that transcend the generated only by the film, the others, without renouncing the commercial success, born from the respect to the substance and form of the adapted work. And it is likely that they are much more profitable in the long run, judging by their content budgets.Without going any further, this adaptation of the succinct 300 comic has had a budget of around EUR 49 million and has already garnered 100 million in its first ten days of exhibition in North American cinemas. But in addition, focusing on strictly cinematic aspects, the result of this 'adaptación-traslación' is spectacular. Visual and arguably, the Ribbon is a calque of the mythical Miller comic. Shot entirely on the merits of a blue screen, used as a canvas to which then add creative funds arising from a Mac, the film captures perfectly the main virtues of the comic: the magnification of heroism in the battle of Thermopylae between a handful of hardened Spartans against the huge army of the Persian Empire.Voluntarily away all realism and assuming completely present in the comic-style, 300 offers two hours of bloody battles, artistic forcible any limbs and heads, but, first and foremost, a surprising visual result than the apt director Zack Snyder (the dawn of the dead, Watchmen?) has the primary responsibility. It is also faithful to the discursive line maintained during the comic book: the stubborn resistance of Sparta against the unstoppable Persian expansion was the last hope that democracy and freedom citizen perviviesen in Greece. This 300 is a risky play that Snyder could only have initialled so successfully. You would recommend to those who are willing to embark on an emotional epic tale with an absolutely innovative aesthetic and without waiting for any concession to the conventions of the genre.</body>
</review>
