<review author="Jesus Lens" title="300" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I loved, has fascinated me and hit me. Does this mean that is a perfect movie or a masterpiece of cinema? Well not. But it was not what was requested of it.</summary>
	<body>What about "300" he has not said already? At this point, everyone knows that it will battle between Persians and Spartans, which takes place at Thermopylae and faithfully based on a comic book by Frank Miller. All of this is factual information which is collected on dozens of websites and blogs, magazines and newspapers of more varied. So, let's go with the subjective. And the subjective is that you found me a peliculón, which has made me a hundred, that has made me upload keystrokes, that I made drop chutes of adrenaline and has revolutionized me the endorphins.That I loved, has fascinated me and me has impactado.¿Significa that a perfect film or a masterpiece of cinema? Well not. But it was not what was requested of it. Failure, for example, the character of Xerxes. In the comic is more impressive, more noble, more Almighty, more enigmatic. His half-King and his half Dios are better achieved. In the film Xerxes is, rather, a drive, God of death. And the effect of grandeur that was the comic book that a little lastra.And the grotesque monsters also reach tire. Luckily, elephants, give them matarile very quickly. But the film is colossal. One is identified both with the history, that wants to be Spartan. Directly. And that asked it that the film: that was quite a sight. And it is. There has been much of the fidelity of the frames to the graphic work of Miller and Valley, but it is that they have been inspired, in turn, in reality. Or, at least, in reality we have at our disposal: own step of Thermopylae or classical paintings as David Jaques-Louis. And this have been added to the Christian iconography of, for example, San Sebastián aseteado, of a Jesus Christ passing the night in the garden of olives or a Judas who sold his master for thirty pieces of silver.Snyder, to shoot this film, has also benefited from another great classical imagery, as the stabbed Julius Caesar. And the spirit of war films here, of course. With a few dialogues efectistas and mythological, with strong phrases as the fight in the shade, with sequences such as the vessels arriving to the coast, we have seen in "Troy" or "Letters from Iwo Jima".We could talk about the theme of East and West and the protest that has made Iran on the treatment that is made of the Persians, but look at. Step. At least for the moment. Because I left the show so amazed that we have seen that talk about the reality I not want absolutely nothing. A spectacle of blood, violence, and manhood that is called on to alienating many and very diverse groups, but that to me I has mesmerized altogether.I'm going to re-read the comic book, surely will come back to see the movie, and if get me the bolunto, I buy up Spartan a sword and a shield to hang them on the wall of my house. Because the "300" deserve that and more. piece of film!</body>
</review>
