<review author="Rafa Marin" title="Plan oculto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Plot ingenious and fun with some depth charge that reveals the shortcomings of the system</summary>
	<body>It is good contestarios geniuses fall from time to time to the sands of blockbusters, inter alia because they often provide different and even personal points of view. Both are met in the last film by Spike Lee, hidden Plan (the original title, Inside Man, has a lot more bad grapes, a game of mirrors that against which only can play the title in Spanish), because since the first blueprints to see New York and its streets with a look and a light that had not seen before, and above the director does not hesitate strain in a witty and funny plot any depth charge that reveals the shortcomings of the system. It is a movie of bank robberies, of those that we have seen so many times and we have bored half of them, and yet here, despite the long footage, the Viewer does not have time or of even blinking. Lee moves the camera on his shoulder, nervous, when the false painters led by a masked man Clive Owen lían the taco in the Bank of Manhattan, and has time to create strokes of personality both in him as in his opponent (Denzel Washington, aging dignísimamente and waiting for his own Clint Eastwood) or in the enigmatic couple make up the cold negotiator (Jodie Foster) and the President of the Bank of yore (a raymondiano Christopher Plummer who was sorry) (that does not have the almost ninety years must have their character). Not happy with the nervousness of the situation, waiting, the panic of the hostages and the hieratismo of the hijackers, Lee jumps in a fast forward burned image of what happens after the assault and the release getting increase the mystery of the reason for the robbery and the personality and the actual number of the assailants (so these, very intelligently)(, they dress to the nearly 50 hostages in the same way as them). The film is, above all, a pure entertainment, almost the serious version of this little gem which is the jungle of glass, although without shots. Lee is able to go giving us clues, from the first scene, of what is happening, and however cheats us at all times, until the end, what the thieves (and himself) are brought in hands. Knowing that the Viewer often become part of the bad guys in this type of robbery (they should ask if not Cary Grant - well, he can not-, Robert Wagner, Robert Redford or gang of George Clooney), here also reinforces that empathy loading of moral reasons to Owen (or downloading to Plummer), albeit not until the end to see discovered his Robin Hood type bluff. Ultimately, Spike Lee cannot denounce, from fun, the origin of the money and much of psychosis post 11-S in the USA. Priceless the detention of the Sikh hostage and its confusion with an Arab, as priceless is the scene with the violent videogame the child teaches Clive Owen and the reaction. After more than two hours of film, one is still under wanting more. And a curious detail: is the first time that I see that receivable refers to all the musicians that they interpret the soundtrack.</body>
</review>
