<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="300" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bet Snyder by making the bed to the sedentary patriotism American, leaving point at various times of the film that the Spartans are fighting on the side of logic, freedom and Justice against barbarism Persian, delivered to hedonism, racial Exchange and religious superstition. Well could have signed with his blood Mr Bush this script.</summary>
	<body>An effective advertising deployment and warlike ardor of comic fans have enough so that theaters are filled to watch what promised to be quite a sight with an innovative aesthetic and a groundbreaking and reactionary style that would bring us to enjoy the Nice. Both promises, its aesthetic proposal and its political incorrectness, are insurance? in addition to their best assets to play his biggest weakness in the box office - and in my opinion, the most resounding cause of his mediocrity. Why not they River certain aspects that protrude to the spectator comfort.Aesthetic proposal, 300 is a product of previous products such as Sin City (as regards the adaptation from the comic and the attempt to simulate audiovisualmente) and also Gladiator or Trojan, which takes not only narrative elements, musical keys and Visual enhancements, but also the fact of having been shot in a great little per cent using famosilla blue screen. This dependence of the virtual sets is an entirely necessary resource if you want to "resemble" the comic that aims to emulate (respect or loyalty, they call him), and in no case should, if done with craft work and artistic sensibility, detract from or disappoint fans of the cellulose format. That is not the sin of 300. His demerit comes to manifest itself in the way to assemble those frames and try to give emotion and epic. Here is where Snyder succumbs to the helpings of the music video or the advertisement appeal, underlining a vacuum estecitismo that one ends very soon tired despite the beauty of some frames. Preferred content to the teenage public (which goes to the movies) to give depth to the whole without why lose force visual. The slowdown in some images is peregrina, as well as the stale romanticism which we will do rest as much Lanzada Hoplite.Do likewise, the all-powerful presence of the Narrator? resource never used by Miller in his comic - multiplies the information without unravelling the gaze of the viewer and loading too much the scenes of a narrative which themselves provide for themselves. This same remedy yet in Sin City was ideal, as the script relied less on constant action of the characters, but on human decorations which were ranging over all the footage. On the other hand, Sin City baby not only of its reference paper, but also of the black novel, in which the Narrator becomes as a figure in the story, guiding the reader into the final tragedy.The script for 300 required unfolded along two axes narrative different, if we did not want the viewer end filling up as much battle. Thus, Snyder and Johnstad happened to recreate the parallel story of the palatial intrigue between the faithful wife and opportunistic political. The alternation between both stories would thus fill almost two hours of footage, provide an apparent adulthood to the script and at the same time, as we have already suggested, have entertained the capacity until the foreseeable end, without decline his interest.It is a pity that use is made of this virtual technology without an artistic purpose which support. Hopefully next filmmakers gave us products in which the concept of beauty is less virtual and opportunistic. The comic we forgive his closed aesthetics and staff, but their passage into audio-visual language wanders by a thin line that glimpse of the emptiness of their frames. 300 not excited, it rather puzzled by its roar without shrapnel. It is as a fritter of wind, big and bloated, but without more content than imagine our desire.Does the use of the two narrative axes may be understandable, but it is on the one hand to divert from the comic, and by another opt for strengthening the political and ideological nature of a proposal that has only place (who has a true sense of ethics and want to why not let have fun watching savagery) if we take this film for what it is? or should have been -an audio-visual show no more. Tarantino is an example of a filmmaker who understands well what should be the essential of this genus rule: do not take himself very seriously. Snyder, advocates making the bed to the sedentary American patriotism, however, leaving point at various times of the film that the Spartans are fighting on the side of logic, freedom and Justice against barbarism Persian, delivered to hedonism, racial Exchange and religious superstition. Well could have signed with his blood Mr Bush this script.If I hurry, I could strain the message of the importance of will and effort to cowardice and tradition. Or simply the description without intellectual crutches of the stark reality of a war based on pictorial pictures retouched with photoshop. But no, 300 seems more a spot to recruit marines (the pass of Thermopylae acts as Iraq), or progressive video clip who sells strange thing as cool, than a film to have a good time. (Canned) beauty resides in the power of the frames, that isolated result, as in the comic, beautiful and evocative. But when the movement enlivens them turn into zombies (which is the specialty of Snyder). Nothing for now seems to resist the force found one when it passes the Miller comic view. If not you have enjoyed, make the great orientation Edition published by Norma.Por now I am satisfied to see on DVD (by my neighborhood premieres for spectators with acne only arrive) the promising appearance (also) A scanner darkly (or A Scanner Darkly, as the maltitulan instead of A dark Explorer), based on a short story by Philip K cineable. Dirk. And if not, we will always the less strident but solid the lion of Sparta, from which indignamente says feed (parasitize is more accurate) 300.</body>
</review>
