<review author="Alex Largo" title="El buen alemán" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To my the movie seems good. Although it has a few aspects to improve. Perhaps with more time to finish the script, and an idea closer to what was going to do, another rooster would have sung, and without place to doubt for the better.</summary>
	<body>I do not understand the criticism that has been made against this film. Admittedly, it has flaws, as all movies. But all his faults are summarized in one. It seems that no one knows very well where it is.George Clooney makes a very correct of protagonist role, though his character is not someone with whom we can identify. Tobey Maguire is perhaps the most unsympathetic is made to the public. As Cate Blanchett, which is as always superb, only say that at times is a little bland.These, and indeed all stakeholders, seem a little stunned. They act but do not know very well that they are doing, or at least in some moments of the film.Stress also the criticism of "the little chemistry" of the protagonist couple. I wouldn't say that little chemistry there is between them, if not almost to their respective roles to forcing them to maintain that distance.The script perhaps should have "suffered" a couple of more rewrites, as it limps in some plot threads. And seeing the book is adapted (nothing to envy to "what the wind", but in volume) we can say that the work of the writer is not outstanding, but if approved.As regards the direction of Steven Sodebergh. since. bad. Sosa one-way like few, a poor direction, without personality. And that sometimes is very bad (the scenes in which there is a fight or a fight are totally emotion), and is a real shame, because the film could aspire to much more.Best of all is the art direction (some impressive sets and that they have not even received (inexplicáblemente) a nomination for the Oscars) and the band Sonora of Thomas Newman (has this if her nominated to the Oscars, although sometimes not "connect" with images and a little goes outside parva).As for the picture. Yes, it is good. but not maintains the style of the old movies. The camera moves too, restandole credibility to his look.Another problem (which is sometimes otherwise) is the theme of black and white images of file. The film attempts to seem old, Casablanca style, and sometimes succeeds (and how), but other times not, in such a way that the film loses much charm.To my the movie seems good. Although it has a few aspects to improve. Perhaps with more time to finish the script, and an idea closer to what was going to do, another rooster would have sung, and without place to doubt for the better.</body>
</review>
