<review author="Alex Largo" title="El último rey de Escocia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film greatly improves with Withaker on-screen appearance. And is that the film comes to what you truly want to tell: the story of the dictator Amin. Instead of a doctor that is going to Uganda...</summary>
	<body>Ignored that this film has been ignored is truly outrageous. It won the BAFTA for best British film. As I said at the time. Why the Queen won an BAFTA for best film and not the best British film? I thought that "The last King of Scotland" had given him the BAFTA for a little to promote the film. big mistake. the film is far superior to the "La Reina" overrated. The film has very bad moments, and the tape difficult to boot, and is that there are a couple of things that should have fallen in the mount table and slow the story (especially in the beginning).Everything changes when the character of Withaker (Oscar winner for best actor for this film) appears on the screen. And although the real protagonist is the character of James McAvoy, Forest Withaker, leaves all the actors under their shade (especially to McAvoy), although this does not mean that they do you wrong, or at least almost all actors do well with its work.Except for James McAvoy, which turns into the worst of the tape, with a performance which lacks personality, bland like few others, he shows us that he is a bad actor (and ugly). Although more than we can blame him to McAvoy bad makes it, did worse director/ra of casting, choosing this young man that everytime you get only spoil the movie.As we said, the film greatly improves with Withaker on-screen appearance. And is that the film comes to what you truly want to tell: the story of the dictator Amin. Instead of a doctor that is going to Uganda. And it is that Withaker knows to fill the gap of the film (which are few) a brilliantly.The movie is the adaptation of a novel, the novel I don't know, but the script is frankly poor, not bad, but nothing good. The script goes lurching is not a sound basis for the film, and the somewhat forced history occasionally.With regard to the work of the director, Kevin Macdonald, can say that it is good, auque, to my, particularly, I to seemed a little bland, but as I said has done a good job, that although cost him the British Independent Film Awards to my seems to me something dull and lacking personality. But as already said they do well man.Miraculously, the film is very good, especially since the final leg is unbeatable and leaves a good taste. But do not believe that the movie will be for posterity.</body>
</review>
