<review author="Josini" title="Hannibal: El origen del mal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The bad go accompanied to the cinema is not always you choose what you want to see. So this time went back to having to endure two hours (over these bad movies last always two hours) of mediocre and commercial success.</summary>
	<body>The bad go accompanied to the cinema is not always you choose what you want to see. So this time went back to having to endure two hours (over these bad movies last always two hours) of mediocre and commercial success.I think that they want to impose by law one minimum quota of European films in cinemas. Retailers argue against that would lead them to ruin, because roughly the European cinema does not more than seven percent of the benefits. Hollywood instead expressly makes the kind of movies that kids demand and therefore gives a lot of money. This is an obvious reality, and the consequence is that supposedly all those who love the cinema of quality, especially film buffs like me, we should rejoice.I am a very atypical spectator, I think. When I decide, I know what they'll see, and nobody I tima. Get it first sniffing in the history, and thus I see films whose subject I am interested in. I do not often choose films by actors or their archetypes. You do with Gary Cooper, but is dead (as everyone knows, Gary Cooper is in heaven). Secondly control a bit of managers who are good and those who are of the lot, it is very simple, the bad is I have no head for more than me marketinicen. In the third and last place, when cuando dudo I doubt I can pull criticism, always with a bit of care because the critics are also human and, as such, have their tastes, as well as their patterns in many cases.This simple methodology I've fought for example torrent and its sequels, movies that copied the reason for American success. And I have also enjoyed of Ridley Scott's Gladiator or Gungs of New York of Scorsese, proving that Hollywood can do good works if, the problems is that normally does not want to (will simply make a pigswill Burger that everyone eats).I believe in free competition of ideas, so it seems wrong this measure. I do not obstacles though they seem to have sense, job well done can go adding little by little and reverse the situation, you only need the intelligence of the Viewer. And of course, if you want the powerful to consumistas and not freethinkers, then give the public what it wants. Moreover, I believe that the public not to give him what he wants or what expected, but what you want to give. Only thus move a little thinking cells.</body>
</review>
