<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="300" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I had really well, but not it surprised me absolutely nothing to see with total tranquility and stillness. So I think that I not take much to forget her.</summary>
	<body>Entertaining epic, framed in the Péplum, as the rating of the illustrious Spain Rafael in his excellent book: "The Peplum." "Old film".It is not a remake of "The lion of Sparta", very nice film directed by Rudolph Maté in 1961, with Richard Egan protagonist, but the famous and excellent comic of Frank Miller.Y it shows, for good and for evil.It must be made clear that, at least in my opinion, gets very good time because it contains everything that it could and should expect: spectacular, violence, heroism, love, loyalties, friendships, betrayals, and also doses of sadism and cruelty. It handles everything pretty well Snyder, which already had dazzled us in his previous work "The dawn of the dead", film already cult following among lovers of horror movies.Here, in "300", the narrative has, as you might expect, as important as the visual work. This aspect, its careful and painstaking scenery, is of vital importance, because everything is dependent on it.The picture of different colors depending on the events and hours which happen events, syncopated Assembly and the artistic direction, they want and I think that they do greatly, be faithful to the original, the work of Miller. And it is there where, perhaps, is the only negative point of the film, which does not depart almost nothing of the comic, so it loses some freshness and, above all, originality and imagination. I think it should, at least have to try, create something new that was strictly film and wasn't nearly a calque from the world of cartoons, very attractive to this outside.But leaving this aside, at the end and after an opinion is absolutely subjective, the tape taste with pleasure, provided that like the epic stories full of blood, sweat and tears.Takes his time to reach the battle of Thermopylae Las and the characters believe that they are well developed, although certain historical aspects shine by their absence when aren't strangers, and even little credible.As to the character of Dillios told his countrymen at the end of the film a year has passed (that thought understood) from the famous battle of the 300 and now again to see the faces with the numerous Persian army. However, agreement, but. what has been done since this cruel army? where has it been stuck? Do remain arms crossed waiting for the Greek armies is feet?. I don't know, something does not block me.As for the music, in the family scenes, note a lot the influence of "Gladiator". So I think that it is very nearly a plagiarism.But well, I had frankly well, but not it surprised me absolutely nothing to see with total tranquility and stillness. So I think that I not take much to forget her.With regard to the controversy that has arisen in Iran, ancient Persia, I don't know the exact reason why be angry. Seems to be that it is because it portrays them as too cruel and evil. If so, I think that it is not for both. Also the Spanish, English, estadounidensee, French, German, Russian, Japanese...etc, etc, be them has retratato as well in other films.In what it could have been enfandado a bit is in the frasecita of Dillios at the end of the film, where it says something and that we must end with the Persians and thus its mysticism and I do not know what else more. That about mysticism, of course, is harvest of the times. An opinion with which many will agree, but we should understand that he can touch noses and other parts of the body to a number of human beings, for example to the current Iranians. Or maybe not.</body>
</review>
