<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Concursante" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>According to the sophistry of the guru, any person who receives money from a bank not only will have to repay the loan and their interests, but it also will lose all their assets; the fallacy that is not worth rejecting her is so evident.</summary>
	<body>Orensano Rodrigo Cortes is, fundamentally, an author of "video clips", and it shows in this his first feature film. The truth is that the beginning is brilliant, from a few titles of very elaborate and showy credit (so rare in Spanish film, unfortunately) until an unusual boot, with the narration in first person of the protagonist, then died an hour before the time in which the action starts. It is not that the appeal of the Narrator fiambre is particularly innovative (recall, for example, William Holden in "The twilight of the gods", the unforgettable "Sunset Boulevard"), but it is truth that is eye-catching and intriguing, especially if it truffle in this case, as experimental jueguecitos Visual in the manner of Michel Gondry in "forget of my" (see criticism in Criticalia) or Woody Allen in "Desmontando to Harry". The plot has its interest: a Professor of history of the economy, which serves three million euros by the unlikely name of Martin circus Martín, wins the highest award of the television (do though in the film always half a billion pesetas: are older than the balconies of palo?), although in kind, not in cash: a mansion of 18th centurytwo or three cars to which more cool, a light aircraft, motorcycles, travel? In short, awesome. The problem starts with a girlfriend affected by the nueva-rica - buyer-compulsive syndrome; It continues when the protagonist learns that you have to pay almost fifty percent of the prize to finance, and has no money to do so; continues when the Bank paid six hundred thousand euros (again say it in pesetas: hundreds of millions of old blondes), but pignorando you all won in the contest; (e) item with the Adviser financial are encouraged, devoted body and soul to pamphilus such fleece. In this context of unmitigated disaster, the pardillo (improbability of the script: how a Professor of history of the economy is as lerdo in economic issues?) (Do good question, I would say the director and screenwriter Rodrigo Cortes: now make me another?) It uses an antieconomicista guru and a point anti-globalization in his spare time, which preaches the good news of the absolute treachery of banks, to what the director devotes almost the rest of the footage; man, no I anyone who says that the Bank, in Spain and everywhere, not win a lot of money, but the demagogy with which the matter is here smells like it sucks. According to the sophistry of the guru, any person who receives money from a bank not only will have to repay the loan and their interests, but it also will lose all their assets; the fallacy that is not worth rejecting her is so evident. A Bank has had to make a big mess this man so that you have a very huge desire to that business, but this should not make you lose North, a story which aroused interest in the initially hollada path, that of a normal man hit by the Fortune at a time seems to smile, but you're really giving him a back stab. So, soon lost the brilliant beginning to focus exclusively on accumulate matters arguments in the diatribe antibanca, in that effort is going to Cortés full force, and the film most of its interest. Finally retrieves the thread in the scene in which the protagonist is dead (does indeed, as more avaricioso than Harpagón?), but already cannot recover lost time. There are things and details: the guru that composes Chete Lera, which even more false than a three euro coin, is a peculiar, dweller character of a House tabicada of large bundles of newspapers and a mother Catatonic that feeds on the energy that emits the TV; or Professor Santillana, the superior of the protagonist, which seems to result from a cross between the witch from snow white, Cinderella's stepmother, Miss Rotermeyer of "Heidi" and the presenter of the program "The weakest". An irregular set which confirms that if its director forgets their phobias and is dedicated to filmmaking seriously, it could be to become a world-class filmmaker.</body>
</review>
