<review author="Caruco" title="300" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The merger of comics and video games with the seventh art seemed inevitable. With? 300? reach full communion, and makes creating some images and more forceful and powerful sequences never seen in the film.</summary>
	<body>Welcome to the cinema of the 21st century! And Zack Snyder, a visionary, just become definitively reference filmmaker and director of worship.The merger of comics and video games with the seventh art seemed inevitable. With "300" reach full communion, and makes creating some images and more forceful and powerful sequences never seen in the film. To immortalize this film, enough with the scene of the young of the Oracle dancing before giving his prediction or the image of the discovery of a decorated tree macábramente with corpses of villagers.Or the sequence in lateral travelling, of King Leonidas, advancing to the "Old boy" among his Persian enemies, while the image slows down, freezes, then progresses rapidly, while background, the music sounds just as emphatic and overwhelming. It is the entertainment, excitement and not triumph goes by providing graphic novel by Frank Miller, and hiperbolizando her, with the strength and innovation requiring its adaptation in images and sound.In addition, Snyder has managed to extract poetry of the horror and the brutality that plasma and, like the graphic novel by Frank Miller, makes it very clear that you are looking for is not historical accuracy, but also his inspiration to create a totally new story. It is the presence of characters and so grotesque as fantastic creatures.More 'gore-historical'.This is matched with a set of extraordinary interpretations, especially Gerard Butler that is out by his charisma, or Lena Headey as Queen Gorgo, combining beauty and character.And one imagines Snyder enjoying not as one, but also as a thousand dwarf, rebuilding the material shot with the infógraficos effects, adding all the sets and Visual effects; do in addition to trufar his images of abundant hints of? gore?, and some others, more than comentadísimo, filogay. Do do a courtesy of the Persian king Xerxes (Rodrigo Santoro), turned in a? travelo? two meters and a half in height; and some of her dancers? drag queens?.Or the very same Mel Gibson would imagine that in a few weeks apart, another pure and simple spectacle of adventures would rival their "Apocalypto" in splashes of blood and gore-historic Court show. And much less approved King Leonidas dared to turn back on Jerjer, leaving your hands in men this warmly sit while he recites it a: "Is not to my lashes to what you fear most?". All stuck between burly men and women of large nipples.Film-feeling. of course, that imperfections there are. Among his dialogues, which echoes magnificent and grandiose, escapes any replica of dialogue in plan chistecito out of tune (as in the encounter between Leonidas and Jerjer); and between his scenes, some other, call it artistic license, to give an effects and easy resolution to key moments (e.g. at the appearance of the desperate Queen before the Senate).But they are perdonables errors. So we would be talking about a masterpiece undisputed were it not for a detail, and it is that masterpieces are accustomed to talk about us humans, and "300" only looking for sensation and the impact. An exaltation of the cruelty stained heroicismo. And it reveals as a prodigious but empty, devoid of heart, brain and soul show.It is a formidable carousel for nearly two hours and never to bore, which reflects perfectly the tenets of what will be, or already is, cinema, entertainment now, and the future. And Moreover, it is consistent. Seeking only the feeling and impact, even the script is responsible for everything is easy to understand, everything is adequately chewed."300" Is going to lead to legions of followers, there is no doubt; just as, by its aesthetics and its form, it will be one of the most innovative, influential and representative in the coming years. Certifying that the violence has become the best show, and business.</body>
</review>
