<review author="Josini" title="Dies irae" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Never cinema has benefited both to symbols, being able to relayed the field of understanding to wrap the lands of the spirit. No doubt Dreyes is the filmmaker of the spirit.</summary>
	<body>This Danish film is, as others that I've seen of him, a criticism of intolerance, in this case religious intolerance, as well as Gertrud was a criticism of intolerance in love. It is an inquisitorial process for witchcraft in which overlooks the revenge and the curse, that Herlofs Marte begs for his life to the Inquisitor to, however, has a lot to hide about witchcraft and his family.He is says something which is strictly true Dreyer's: is the only filmmaker who has been able to reflect the same spirit. This is the second time that I see this film and I again moves from the first image the figure of the elderly witch, so old and so fragile, with a quite good-natured face that reminds me so much of my mother, and that during the following scenes over and over again begs for his life, to the same end. It is not a good character exposed to evil and intolerance, it is much more: is the same goodness and the same fragility, an idea, a concept that transpasa corporeality and until the death, which is timeless in the same story, after several viewings of the film or to different viewers. It is a similar AWE to the of having seen a spirit, but one that not surviving us very deep fear but a compassion and a penalty.I feel the need to continue talking on that spirit, that not so reflected as plasma character, which could undoubtedly also applies to the female character of Gertrud. Herlofs Marte collides head-on with the inhumanity of their inquisitors but not breaks out of rage or despair, but facing her focusing in their aim to avoid fire. Does not believe in their monsergas, not accept them. The old is hard, as one of them says.And what words could wield to praise the scene of torture: or the scene in which open to the intestines to William Wallace at Braveheart overwhelms both. Both scenes are based on the visual ellipses. Here we see the impassivity of the faces of the inquisitors while we hear real screams of pain in the room, as if they were processed crude judicial paperwork. And we know that it is a fragile old woman. And we see it crying. By the way that these cries are so real in the version dubbed in Spanish, which must be something international and indescribable in this scene from physical pain.Also the old Herlofs Marte to repeat how much that fears death and fire. It is a genuíno animal fear, one that feels as its own when says it an old implorante aid and shaking a cold there must be greater than that which could feel those wet peasant stay where history makes it tiritar.And all this is just part of the story because then there is the second part in which a forbidden love bursts with the heartbreaking death. And here we have Visual symbols embodied with a success as ever in cinema: never wheat fields, the tall grasses of the meadows where strolling lovers or los altos and leafy trees that become his witnesses have been for me so close to my experiences. Never cinema has benefited both to symbols, being able to relayed the field of understanding to wrap the lands of the spirit. No doubt Dreyes is the filmmaker of the spirit.</body>
</review>
