<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="300" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This unique digital effects with alleged historical background binge opens again the eternal dilemma raised by film adaptations.</summary>
	<body>An adaptation was never so true, although on the other hand, we do not agree on whether a film and the book on which it is based (or play) should or not to share something more than its essence and plotlines Basic. 300 is the story turned into legend and taken to the extreme. The battle of Thermopylae and the truth about Greeks and Persians, or rather, the truth according to Frank Miller who has finished taking body in an audiovisual binge that represents a turning point in the epic, pulling to the fantastic cinema. Little to do with Alexander the great, Gladiator, Troy, etc. with fringes of the battles of the Lord of the rings, but we refuse to establish parallels in the end lastren the objective that we want: applaud the audacity to bet on a genus and a few different ways. We are not surprised find schematic interpretations at the service of the aesthetic enjoyment, exaggerated largely, although faithful to the spirit and the content of the graphic novel. Good ones, which are few, they face the evil and horrendous, and war stories despite sublime moments with an introduction where mingle metaphor, myth and cinema excitement without the parade of muscular and bloody gross that takes place during the 90 minutes of footage.This duration is appreciated because as well not just being monotone narration. He is supported, especially if one is regular reader of graphic novel, as Sin City and V for vendetta, it goes to the movies with open mind willing to contemplate how risks or (suicide) a quasi-Rookie, that only highlights the Filmography of the director dawn of the dead. The magnitude of the project could apabullar more than one but the belief to do feet that he was not inspired, but that it commemorated the self-titled comic, convinced him that he should flee from all prejudice.The film has many readings, some impregnated with a marking dye ideological antimilitarist and antitodo. Do but not go out there: far from be carried away by critics who accuse the racist film? by the monstrous portrait of the Persians - and be full of clichés? that is, and many - I advise you that it penetrated in this remarkable recreation retail reflected on the role that, as audiovisual narrative, works and entertains.</body>
</review>
