<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="El jardinero fiel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Three good reasons to watch this movie</summary>
	<body>"The constant gardener" is based on the book of the same name, written by John le Carré, famous English writer who has already brought to the big screen other novels of espionage, as "The tailor of Panama" (2001), starring Pierce Brosnan.Hay three good reasons to see this película:1. Director: Fernando Meirelles, who was nominated for the Academy Award for his magnificent "city of God" (2003) (a film like this, based on a book). 2. The protagonists: the excellent British actors Ralph Fiennes (the English patient, 1996) and Rachel Weisz (the Mummy, 1999). 3. The issue: the serious charges against the world's pharmaceutical industry, which performs its tests using the most vulnerable humans on the planet and therefore the more "disposable": the poor of the African continent, the perfect humanillos of the Indies. In this case, children, which makes the complaint more hawkish.Long ago, when I was working in the area of communication of the International Red Cross, I was surprised a note as well press issued in Geneva entitled something as "not international donations of medicines for the third world". "The Red Cross became crazy", I thought, but reading the contents of the note I realized the reason for your request: most donations consist of past drugs that would cause more harm than relief. Watching "The constant gardener" I me realize that the problem goes beyond past medicines, but that involves medicines in test for the major pandemics that are coming to us.Perhaps seeing the numbers, cold and calculadoramente, currently deaths from these tests, prevent millions of deaths more in the future. But who are these industries mafias to decide on thousands of lives?In a moment of the film, the protagonist asks why pharmaceutical companies make their tests directly in human and replied you that because it is easier to correct than prevent, also that in that way, be they advanced to other laboratories in the competition. A strong enough denunciation.</body>
</review>
