<review author="Silvia" title="Tapas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Any of us could be the protagonist of this story. Or is there maybe someone that not "tape" anything?</summary>
	<body>Prawns in garlic sauce, croquettes, anchovies in vinegar, baby squid, Squid in batter, omelette, spicy banderillas. There are covers of all types: more salty, sweeter more acidic. The film Tapas menu brings together all the ingredients and flavors to achieve the status of five forks. After success at the Festival of film Spanish of Malága, where he earned the award for the best film, the audience and the best actress award, the success of this tragicomedy seems assured.On the other side of the Firebox, José Corbacho and Juan Cruz chefs have developed his directorial debut simmered, since that have taken more than four years in shaping your master plate. A bittersweet ration in which mixed the stories of ordinary people who lives in a neighborhood of city and glimpse their fears, their hopes and their disappointments. Directors and screenwriters Corbacho and Juan Cruz carried the viewer of tapas in a neighborhood of the city of L'Hospitalet taking a walk by the lives of five characters so everyday that they are family. They are very different characters but with something in common: all have some secret that hide, something to cover. All cover their misery under a false appearance of honesty. Hence the double meaning of the title of the film. On the one hand the tape speaks daily covers lunch with which everyone has grown, while on the other stresses the secrets or insecurities that cover people daily. The character who gives life María Galiana ("Solas") is one of the most surprising in terms of unspeakable secrets referred, especially for the bonus you get wheeling and dealing with young people who sell drugs without anyone suspected. In a society like ours in which the most important is not but seem, hypocrisy and lies are the order of the day. There is no more than a ride for any bar and take a few lids to check feeds insubstantial social contact of gossip about neighbors or superficial comments on the future of the country. Conversations in which this kind of banal communication serves, perhaps also to cover or mask the existence of oneself.For the film parade characters we could find in any neighborhood of any city. Surely, we all know the typical owner of the bar in the corner of the neighborhood as Lolo (Ángel Andrés), whose wife leaves him because it puts your business at their relationship and, in principle, is not able to swallow your pride and go to look for her. His new kitchen Assistant newcomer China, revolves around the story of Lolo and Mao, some of the funniest and most satirical movie scenes. Perhaps also once we will have crossed with a pair of unconscious adolescents who only live to flirt and cover in drugs to escape from your everyday life. Rachel, on the other hand, is a woman that haunts the quarantine and refuge in the solitude of cyberspace without hope of finding a loving real until that one day a young man gives life believed lost. A brilliant Elvira Mínguez who does lack words to express bitterness and disenchantment that exudes his character. The history of love without limits of the old woman who lives only to satisfy her sick husband gives the film a brushstroke of tenderness. And it is that although the film takes the tone of light comedy, in the cracks of the narrative strain imperceptibly an air of sadness that frozen smile to make it a painful grimace. And it is that life - as reads the poster of the film - is like the padrón peppers, sometimes itches. and sometimes not.In the style of other Spanish directors such as Fernando León de Aranoa (quarter, Mondays in the Sun) or Icíar Bollaín (flowers from another world, Te doy mis ojos), but with a dose of humor, Corbacho and cross to portray the reality of the Spanish society of quite faithfully and without stridency. In time special effects and blockbuster Hollywood is difficult for a realistic dye film survive in the charts. However, the film brings together the precise ingredients so that the public is hooked to the seat during the 93 minutes that lasts the tape. Perhaps its limited duration prevents the Viewer to deepen a bit more in the stories, which better taste a dish that can leave hungry for more. And it is that when the room lights are lit, the viewer still digesting history, in which anyone can see reflected their own lives, their hopes and disappointments. Because in the movie appear universal themes such as loneliness, death, love, sex, friendship or hope. Cotidianidades with them living together the characters of this film and that they all face us on a daily basis. Because any of us could be the protagonist of this story. Or is there maybe someone that not "tape" anything?</body>
</review>
