<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Closer" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do could qualify to?Closer? (blinded by the desire in some Spanish-speaking countries) as a bloody wonder. Closer, in some real way as life itself.</summary>
	<body>Good is that you're watching a movie and comes me to mind quite a few ideas on how to approach my criticism / opinion, and good is the feeling that one has after the screening to foot and as a play begin to applaud, if could be described as a "Closer" (blinded by the desire in some Spanish-speaking countries) as a bloody wonder, the suffering is something to play, nor happiness is something that we see with ease on screen, where they have become accustomed us from our most remote childhood as spectators with something so easy and banal as "boy meets girl, they chatting and they fall in love", however in the last film by Mike Nichols (famous among other "Weapons of woman") all schemes we have Super-Duper memorized by the film break. For those some other time have suffered some breakup "Closer" represents everything that has happened, unstable loves marching as the foam on the sea, bizarre situations that end up turning into something real, more real than one thought, and is that the film is perhaps a small "bite of reality" in screenexcellent performances of Natalie Portman and Clive Owen, I think almost the best, perhaps by Jude Law I start to get bored on screen and Julia Roberts despite the fact that I love it looks already "entradita in years" hurts! Someone told me that "Closer" bore some similarity with "Lost in translation" and yet not find such parallelism, maybe just unhappiness are the protagonists and that not everything is always as easy as the film made us believe. One of my fears was as he was going to see a play so like this on screen, represented as everything happens at a dozen scenarios, (created especially for the occasion thanks to the bulging budget), where most raw the dialog that sets, perhaps this dialogue sometimes suffers from chabacanas expressions which certainly does not cease to be peculiarly beautiful, that show in some other time the brutality of one or another character (the Larry played by the "King Arthur" Clive Owen). We can travel in the film between very peculiar personalities, between brutality already annotated Owen (perhaps what I least liked of him was his way to change responses, so quickly), youth insecurity of Alice / Jane (Natalie Portman) that reminds me of some person that shared a year of my life, the instability of Jude Law (neither with you nor without you have my remedy evils) and the adult affirmation of Julia Robertsknowing full well that he wants anytime, but end up making up its sad error. One of those movies not rang with too much force and currently leads two Golden Globes, one for Portman and another for Owen, though perhaps, as a negative note is that brutal change of emotion in the characters in some moments of footage. Closer, in some real way as life itself.</body>
</review>
