<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Hitch" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Hitch" is one of those movies with a single argument, which opens up a wide range of situations and close them all seamless and in a quite simple way get even get sometimes play with the complicity of the patio of armchairs.</summary>
	<body>This is one of those strange films begin importing me a cucumber and end up being quite attractive (damn promotion campaigns that end up getting you the film by eyes), the trouble is that you a time seen the trailer and 50 ads that you miss on it (which are the best moments of the film) when you go to the cinema is very difficult to see something that makes you grace, even so some other point started me some that another laugh."Perhaps the best of the movie with Will Smith and Eva Mendes (my God, this girl this tremendous) is the presence of the American comedian Kevin James that manages to boot (Pepe Viyuela style and its already legendary"joeeeeer") best comedy of the film situations.""Hitch" is one of those movies with a single argument, which opens up a wide range of situations and get close them all seamless and quite easily, even get sometimes play with the complicity of the patio of armchairs, that give you additional information that the protagonists have only "very on top". So Parties with some plot "advantage" that makes us a tape where the "good roll" and not always politically correct, is prevailing in the film, even though you leave with that same situation of cinema, once finished the projection.Thank God we are not to the typical romantic comedy starring Meg Ryan, Sandra Bullock, Julia Roberts. or any of the actresses given that kind of movies and although the "moral" or "moralina" final if fits perfectly with this type of frame, the shadow of Will Smith is elongated and his humor "coñón" and "Socarrón" appears during much of the plot (fans Will love, that no, better not see).Finally, synthesizing, that I am extending more than normal, a comedy "sanota" that makes you leave the film of "buenri".</body>
</review>
