<review author="Taliesin" title="300" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>300 is an orgy for the senses, in which Zack Snyder has created a new cinematographic language which allows a comic to the screen with great fidelity and without falling into the ridiculous.</summary>
	<body>It should take into account several things before going to the cinema to see 300. Firstly, it is not a historical film. It is an adaptation of a comic book by Frank Miller, which in turn is loosely based on a historical fact narrated by historians of the era, mainly Herodotus Alicarnaso (which is not a guarantee of fidelity). Secondly, the comic book on which it is based is very visual and doesn't have too many dialogues. The translation of this screen has been made with such care that 300 is above all images and sound, which is why the dialogues are far from being bright, saving two or three memorable phrases. Taking into account these two things, start.Runs the year 480 BC and the army of Xerxes I, Emperor of Persia, moves forward relentless aiming to conquer Greece. Leonidas I of Sparta decides to deal with them and to know outnumbered chooses to present battle in the pass of Thermopylae. It is estimated that the Persian army had 250,000 men, with about 7,000 Greeks, who stayed in 1000 following the withdrawal of part of the soldiers. There is that, after several days of fighting in the Persian numerical superiority eventually defeated the Greek tactic, the army of Xerxes saw reduced their number in 20,000 troops, against 1,000 Greek casualties. Nowadays it is thought this sacrifice, seemingly useless, served to give time to the rest of Greek armies to take positions, finally stopping the advance of the Persians. And is at the battle of Thermopylae in which focuses 300, and account as Leonidas with three hundred men of his personal guard facing the Turkish army. There are some stroke of policy, but the battlefield is the undisputed protagonist and the footage takes place between combat and combat. The clashes are shot in close-ups and the action freezes at times, as marking the vignettes of the comic book on which it is based. We will see on screen enough blood added digitally, which quite rightly have become an aesthetic appeal more. Rigour is more towards work of Miller with the historical fact, so no one is created the Spartan soldiers went into battle with a loincloth and a red cloak, for much success of the uniform among the female audience. And it is that, first and foremost, 300 is an orgy for the senses and the image is more careful than historical accuracy. It is visually an almost continuous feast in which photography, computer graphics and post-production join forces to offer the film that most has approached the aesthetics comic without falling into the ridiculous. On the other hand, the sound section is outstanding. Many times the music becomes protagonist, enhancing the action on screen and reaching epic dyes.In the negative section, most acute is the scene in which Leonidas is submitted to Xerxes and it seems that we we will see a continuation of Brokeback Mountain. If in a scene that should make a large difference in the plot half of the room is laughs, is that you've done something wrong. I thought it was a problem of dubbing, but in the original version the thing does not differ much. Again, fidelity to the comic is absolute, but Miller's Xerxes does not work equally well on screen than on paper and they would have to have noticed.In short, with 300 Zack Snyder (the director) has invented a new cinematographic language and has unmarked from the convecionalismos which both abound now that everyone is engaged in adapting comics. We would appreciate that a so special as the Miller's work has been so respectful treatment, but the result is more a visual spectacle that a memorable film, although if you go to the film knowing that it is what you can expect, I assure you that you will not be disappointed.</body>
</review>
