<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="The Queen" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Glamour, tears, the Planet Zog, the Protocol, the tea of the five deer of Balmoral, the Princess of the people, imperial phlegm, labour, the gossip, the lackeys, the magnificence and the circumstance. God save the queen.</summary>
	<body>In a moment of the film, a Blair adviser says that the British Royal family live in the Planet Zog. In another, the Duke of Edinburgh, that character halfway between paid idleness and the most exportable British phlegm that might be on the screen or in Carnaby Street, says that a fourteen-pointed stag has been seen in Craggy Head after hearing the television news in which realize the death of Lady Di, in Paris, with her boyfriend.The queen is a nothing hagiographic portrait: an elegant exercise of sentimental voyeurism which operates from a very British way of looking at life and that, ultimately, examines the status of human beings in these times of confusing morality and fickle political adhesions. Do not put your finger in the yellow. Nor does barracks in the gossip. It's telling the pulse between the Blair labour, newly installed in 10 Downing Street, and the Queen, which has already seen the presence of ten Prime Ministers since that Churchill sit front of her to ask him, in solemn Protocol, the executive officers of the motherland.The merit of Pete Morgan resides in an almost non-existent script, based on the vitriol of always understandable dialogue, although the casual viewer lacks adequate political training to understand the hatred of the monarchy to a laboralismo represented by a newbie, but firm in its determinations, Blair always attentive to the Protocol and things will be aware that, in the end, made according to its whim. They are those who surround the Prime Minister which most stab the figure of the Queen and Blair himself is that ultimately opts for appreciate the value of a figure representing an ancient institution that the people admired and which never, perhaps low no circumstances, it will give back.Film of a prodigious, nothing overload containment to no frivolity, is an academic example of how to make excellent movies with very fragile mimbres because the film does not give much of it. Put one to tell what it is, concludes the explanation in a short minute. What about everything else?Helen Miren, which I have not spoken and am not going to say anything in fact because everyone has written and said Excellencies and now I have the verb fluid for the sake of time or fatigue on Monday.Abur my friends.</body>
</review>
