<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Hannibal: El origen del mal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Maybe lambs had to have been silent. They have already mentioned much. They have been told too. Silent lamb, nice lamb. Or lamb with potatoes, but not cheeks. NI on skewer. Anyway... That already desbarra one...</summary>
	<body>I have yet to Dr. Lecter in my particular bestiary. There was an inargumentable Lair by this bad film bug. Blamed for a perfect Anthony Hopkins, above all. Just like the Hitchcock mcguffin in these stories of bad fascinating do not wish, in any way, dive in the backroom of the myth. It is not necessary to know what games practiced small, if you climbed the slopes to his cousin or if hidden, read manual of comparative anatomy with a principle of baba Chin to fall down. The mystery, once dead, is a photograph in an album. And it seems to me that this installment of the franchise has managed that: dismantle the metaphorical principles of the wickedness of the protagonist, tell us without blushing the origin of their phobias and their vices as if a pink Novella is involved and we pretendiéramos, in two hours, exercise of greedy public of gossip at a psiconalista meeting. Hannibal, the origin of evil, does not compromise the future of the series. The history of Thomas Harris has plots that nor he knows, but will open as HARLOTS procaces as soon as Dino de Laurentiis move the bag of coins and you feel in front of a laptop to remind us of the reasons for the Wolf, as I said a short story.Sobreabunda in gruesomeness: is arroba very dubious category of unpleasant film when we all know that to move or to make us shudder of panic you don't have write a M on the chest of a botched or burst a neck with equestrian traction. Worst thing is that David Webber, the architect of this mess, it took us for fools. You think we're going to be satisfied with four stunts circus cannibalism: that our fascination with capacity enough with a refregón of blood in the jaw of the monster future when (I insist) what you were looking for (and I have not found) is a coherent explanation of what already we know. Let's say that we have screwed up the character with a marranada of three to the fourth with so little discursive intention as psychological depth and that it only deserves to be saved by the setting (never marrada) and some simplifications in the form of telling us the story. This is A more B more C then D finiquitando her. We do not know at any time the underlying causes of their perversion, the birth of his dark side. The episode of the girl is not well unspoken (not desvelemos much plot) or not the revelation of evil as the ideal vehicle to complete revenge we understand, from the outset, rayana in pathos. I see more intent dramaturgical in the parliaments of Grissom in the C.S.I. Monday. This comic book justicialism not school: we have already seen many movies to make us become entangled so easily. And the reference in the silence of the lambs weigh much.And not everything is disappointing. One warns well looked at as a whole, a desire which are choreographed with a loose budget and a desire rather than sincere produce a film at the height of its predecessors which, with ups and downs, were worthy. As soon as I have time, I'm going to store my films and look for an edit twice (with many extras and cardboard box instead of the classic and cold plastic wrapper) the silence of the lambs. I there redimiré me. Come back to the simple appreciation for this cabronazo method that will go down in the history of the cinema as the deranged erudite, intelligent, attractive and fascinating that mother has given birth. And now we know it was Lithuanian and that killed a blast of nazi shrapnel on a cold morning near Kaunas. Oh, and that someone explain to me about the mask. I do not hear.</body>
</review>
