<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Invisibles" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A breathtaking experience, beautiful, rough, tender, sober....</summary>
	<body>Isabel Coixet, Wim Wenders, Fernando León de Aranoa, Mariano Barroso and Javier Corcuera, driven by the inspiration and the money from Javier Bardem, have written in images the sadness of a world or their destruction for the sake of their indifference, their barbarism of its charisma stubbornness by to look away when it comes to lend a hand and raise hopes. The invisible is that, still, are not. They are not fantasmagorias or missing. Their presence is his complaint. What these small documentary show is the degree of confinement to which we have come to cope with the enormous weight of life, contaminated in a hurry, settled in ghosts, manumitida its beauty to throw her at this unworthy of a feast few who enjoy the sentimental and physical poverty of many others.Congo women raped and ninguneadas, apocalyptic drugs that hide fearless business, Colombian pariahs resembling characters from Steinbeck, mortality exacerbated in Bolivia and children who flee the adult depravity and took refuge in his childhood and do not want to make a fist with a weapon.These invisible living in our forgetfulness. They live in our memory, but we do not give voice: we arrumbamos them, we leave them, we impose them rough rope which is not ours. I do not know if incumbent us more now after it was invaded by the germ of this documentary. It is only a documentary: unfortunately. These forgotten crises ameliorate them anonymous NGOs, groups such as MSF (doctors without borders) and individuals as wayward as alien to all kinds of public relevance who contribute with their work or their economic effort so that, ultimately, change.The life that comes after the movie not returns us to the film: I guess that somehow also proceed with it as with all that therein show. We leave it in a prominent place in our memories for a long, but her then discard as experience and her rename in a chapter apart from name always very doubtful and that they have to do with the indifference, with solitary confinement. Unfortunately. Except for some (all know someone close) that has got more precarious artefacts, the heart of the world and perfect to go beyond smile where their collaboration is essential to readjust the errors in this world of ours so doomed to the paltry design when it is proposed.</body>
</review>
