<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="300" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Impressive epic film about Leonidas, a Spartan king who halted the advance of thousands and thousands of Persians with only 300 soldiers. A masterpiece setting and action, with so much action and fight that ends up getting tired.</summary>
	<body>"300" is an adaptation of the comic book by Frank Miller of the same name, this so everyone knows. What not everyone knows that this story was already shown in the cinema, at least once. The film in question is called "The 300 spartans" which was translated into English as "The lion of Sparta", and is the same as the 300 except it was made 45 years earlier. Although the movies basically have the same development, in the background are quite contrary. The original was more based on the facts and in politics, while this second it recreates more in the atmosphere and in the fight scenes (which in the original gave a tad of laughter).It has generated a great deal of controversy by statements as the rulers Iranian, who consider it a blasphemy. On the other hand, there have been voices that have drawn parallels with current situations in the world. I personally think both are absurd, this is a simple epic action film, which well might develop in time between Spartans and Persians, between Gamesianos and Venusianos, given that nobody can believe what happens in the film. No one in their right mind, of course. By the way, the end is very Braveheart.La film is about Leonidas, a Spartan king, which led to his bodyguard composed of 300 men to face against the troops of the Persian king Xerxes. Given that they were in obscene inferiority, he thought that the only place where you could stop them in the Strait of Thermopylae. On the other hand, Sparta is torn between going to war to accompany their King or follow with a holding his own.In two words "presionante im" is the best way to define this film. From my humble point of view, the better set the history movie, getting to make us feel within a comic. The choice of colors and above all in amazing textures. The fight scenes, as it could not be otherwise, are horrifying, beating all its predecessors (even to the orcs and the light sabers). These aspects are brutal. In the plain negative, the film made me long. Until the first 300000 Persian victims well, but from the nth dead I began to be a tad heavy. My medium Zucchini fell asleep tired of espadazos. The script of a movie whose poster to a muscular Spartan with the spear in his hand hundreds of enemies killed, given that you already have to know by the way, not can criticize what you'll find.In short, impressive epic film about Leonidas, a Spartan king who halted the advance of thousands and thousands of Persians with only 300 soldiers. A masterpiece setting and action, with so much action and fight that ends up getting tired.Besitos.P.D: of course, when it comes out on DVD I buy head, it better if it is the widespread and out zillions thousand Persians died for the cause.Pd2: Almost better birth only Greek Spartan, no? My mother that more poor children.P.D.3: I forgot to comment on the hot body of the Spartans, madrecita mía, that seemed a cavalcade of the gay pride parade.</body>
</review>
