<review author="Cp" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After so much criticism and disqualify her, at the end was what I expected, spectacular, visually stunning, fun, entertaining, and even epic at times.</summary>
	<body>Because I liked it. After so much criticism and disqualify her, at the end was what I expected, a film of heroic fantasy, that takes names, legends and history situations, to mount a fable. It is spectacular, visually stunning, trying to give an epic and heroic touch to the story. It is not a realistic film, it's not like it would be a Greek peasant with fire a few years later, exaggerating or just telling what the believed to be real. We can say that defending democracy and that women can say, is too contemporary, but well, Leonidas is the perfect hero, not only for the vision of the time, but for the viewer of today. It is hard, but fair, with a funny touch, and while it loses the original voice, Gerald Butler is perfect, and seems able to eat to Brad Pitt, I say Achilles, easily. The rest, because the bad guys have to be bad, bad, and my favorite, Dominic West, (McNulty!). The Persians, well, are masses of cannon fodder, with some enemy of final phase, but always shot in a very spectacular way. The truth is that the film seems to last only one hour, and worth watching her, provided that you know what you are going to see. It is a magnificent spectacle, and whoever else, has the television series Rome. To my I like both, and not there may be nothing more different, but both stay glued to the seat.Do but of course, have to leave dozens of wonderful critics, that speak of a movie where low the mask of the immortals Persians is there in reality? Orcs, as if it was really a disguised attempt of unseen forces and conspiracy to convince the poor innocent minds in the world, that we must fight against the Persians, or Iranian, which obviously is what thought Miller to write the story. I have read on different sites, 300 is francino (where?), who despises the Athenians (no, if the Spartans would speak well of them), that the Spartans are soldiers yankees (in reality, the yankees would be the Persians, well-equipped, with money and numerical superiority, but good) as overly handles are the Spartans (and nobody protests that are handsome!) is a film only to entertain and amuse (that is a category of cinema)(, at least for me, as respectable as the rest, to have fun to the public can be as difficult as convey a message, or more) or that the Persians were indeed wonderful Pathfinder, respectful and kind (already in antiquity the conquests were not bloody, mania of seeing things from our point of view) to emphasize how bad that really were the Spartans (no worse than many others)(, and even better than quite a few).In short, is a film of action and fantasy, of good and bad, funny, entertaining, and even epic at times, enjoy.</body>
</review>
