<review author="JohnTrent" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Miller and Snyder has been a film reference to take into account all the fantasy film aficionado. Do not miss the criticonas voices on this 300. Do including? most - critics still anchored in the past...</summary>
	<body>To start talking about 300, and for a broad view, we have to mention two key names: Frank Miller and Zack Snyder. Both together on this occasion or separately, have become soon a film reference very to consider for all amateur film in general, but especially to the fantastic. The work of this renowned author of graphic novels consists of very well-known titles like Batman year one, Sin city, Daredevil, the man without fear or the now before us, 300. Not until the second that I quoted, Sin city, Miller when really began to have relevance in the film, was hitherto quite reluctant adaptation of his works. Along with Robert Rodriguez, Miller also sat in the Chair of the director to ensure a faithful adaptation and quality, that do not stain the reputation created by his novel graphics, and thus it was. Do sin city premiered with a moderate commercial success? I guess that DVD will be sold like hotcakes, but Spain we still do not have a decent Edition-, but a legion of fans were very satisfied with the artistic results, as well as the public in general, with greater or less pleased, responded well just measured a very risky formal proposal for the times. After this, do not take to hear rumors about another adaptation of a famous work of Miller, is not one that this 300.Para this time we tried having another director of proven? him despite who gets upset, Robert Rodriguez is - in the fantasy field and with a powerful style that can get the most out of the novel not graphic in its translation into imageswithout losing the magic of the cartoons, as usual? or so they say many fans, since I, as you know those who read me regularly, not follow too the world of the comic - in other so many adaptations. The director chosen for the occasion was the emerging Zack Snyder, accustomed to the field of music videos and that triumphed with the magnificent remake of dawn of the dead, which even surpassed the legendary film by George a. Romero, unusual thing in the world of remakes and more even if we talk about so recognized original movies. Snyder was already confirmed in the first minutes of the dawn of the dead as a director capable of printing a force and a tension to the images that, today, are very few who get in their proposals. And that film was not a bluff, because now, in 300, Zack Snyder has become it to do with very pending suit Miller and without losing respect for the novel graphical or, from what I see, fans.Do already entering himself in the movie, and not in the novel graphic? that have not read, although I'm considering doing so-, we can already say that, after the long wait and high expectations, 300 doesn't disappoint. And it is that, as was the case in no city, visual experience which he proposes is something worth seeing in a good movie theater, with a giant screen and sound quality. Only this, 300 already merits view and recommended. Does now well, entering in other sections, the film barely lose force, being an interesting, entertaining, well performed work together?Does Gerald Butler magnificent, with a few flat brutal late-, mounted in a superb manner? do a comic in motion in structure, but not at the same level as the most strict city-musicada to perfection? customer such metalheads sometimes summits or to epic music that gets bristle you hairs - and chords with an invoice and a work of stunning art direction, making a trip to a modern well known film 300? and not pretentious, or modernete - seeking viewers of many types without becoming a mere blockbuster, and achieves its objectives through the fulfilment of his promises: pure and simple, show as well as innovative and even man character.Of course that does not miss the criticonas voices on this 300. Among them? the most - boring and view critical little wider, still anchored in the past and not innovation, in the progress of the film as art, now that the technology is capable of offering more ways. Do them there will be that, as was the case with no city, not understand? or do not try to understand - the variants involving such works in its conception, and the school that, surely, to create. Do actually there to be cheating, because 300 is a type of film with a public secured: the thousands of fans of the novel graphical or Frank Miller in general, fans to the world of the comic, fans of video games, fantasy fans, fans to the epic film purists unprejudiced? well, and within a few lines speak of thisdo, 300 not exactly noted for its historical accuracy, nor it intends to - and, in turn, the public seeking blockbusters, that has become the great success of what it took for year, grossing $ 160 million in three weeks and moving smoothly towards the 200 to this exercise in style? this speak more widely in the summary in the box office that is arriving.And as I already said, does not intend to seek a history class in 300, not. The film, as the novel graphical? which, I understand, adapted faithfully almost everything - are visions of the battle of the Thermopiles, which, indeed, fought Spartans against the Persians, in clear inferiority of number of the first. Do up here all right, but the section fantastic, even mythological, makes presence very occasionally, and narrative licenses do not know limits, I do not see as something negative, because to my knowledge no one said? Miller neither Snyder nor the respective protagonists - at no time intended to tell something true to historical data, but to create a solid entertainment and a dazzling visual spectacle to serve more as a film of genre as epic in the classic sense of the term. What also seem to emphasize his detractors is the supposedly xenophobic burden of the story, leaving the evil and stereotyped as villains Persians? the Jerje King is seen as an effeminate giant--which already point some 300 that turns into a plea pro Bush (!) in, say, an obvious metaphor of what is currently happening with its foreign policy. Do I, for my part, I think that people have too much free time, while it is true that the Persians do not go well unemployed, some what not to say, I at least do not understand even remotely, that the Arabs are the greatest evil of mankind or similar things, like seeing the passion of Christ was me unlike thinking should be hate all Jews by appearing on the screen? and There was also controversy, even some enlightened even said that that film would create a new extermination of the Jewish people (!)-.</body>
</review>
