<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Time" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Loses a point of improbability that certainly leaves abolished the interest. Metaphorical and sobering vision of love in these times of haste and mental fast-food...</summary>
	<body>In a tale of Benedetti, very briefly written, a man found in a woman not found in yours. This infidelity is not such because in reality is his own wife which has been thrown into the street and has become who overrides. The magician of Cortázar (hopscotch) goes on to say that "were not seek us but knowing that we were to find us". This game of identities gives rise to a comedy and also provides sufficient elements to build a melodrama or a thriller. In this case, the Korean Kim Ki-Duk exercises its right to check a film metaphorical, slightly saddened, restrained in their concluciones, but lyrical in its development.This story of sickly jealousy is written with already known materials. Balzac or Zola had already outlined the anguish of humans powerless not to find love in the way in which believes that love should be. However, Time is a nineteenth-century novelón nor a melodrama to the Sirk: nature provides a more ambiguous evidence of time cercando passions, of time cracking the beauty and stranding it in a vague limbo of emotions between the routine and how comfortable. And its protagonists are enlimbados beings, allow me, subjects of a destination invariably rogue that operates out of moral or philosophical considerations of their affected.Women that modifies his face and his ways to return to engolosinar to his beloved is not a new chant: has Time features of Greek tragedy, abound dialogues (the new thing in the head of the hermetic iron 3) and the flow of events refers to classical models, planned under Orthodox standards, always, subject understandable to Cartesian logic helm. This novelty, worthy of applause in a director as Kim Ki-Dak, nor (do not believe) excited. There is nothing here that it chirríe, although there is no beautiful arpeggios, uploaded on the telar musicality of the whole. The symbolism of yesteryear have now been readjusted to naturalistic dissection of the psychology of characters always escorados to the ends of the scales. As these statues in the park representing love and pain, the two points further away from the spectrum of emotions. A Time loses a point of improbability that in absolute, leaves abolished the interest which survives thanks to a practical montage where there is nothing superfluous and everything engarza with sober effectiveness.</body>
</review>
