<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Fundido a negro" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With this cast, it was difficult to make a crappy, but Walker succeeds and introduces us to an Orson Welles that seems a bulimic soplagaitas mainly and although it is presented as a thriller, it seems more a comedy because the plot and situations, if they seriously, are a joke.</summary>
	<body>One of the best scenes of Ed Wood is the dialogue between Vincent D?Onofrio and Jonny Depp. They fantasy a conversation between Orson Welles and Ed Wood in which Welles, gives this Council: Ed, is worth making own dreams is why moving life making the dreams of others?If Welles were had appeared in any of its forms to Oliver Parker you would have deterred you also make this film and to read the script would have surely killed you.Because fade to black, puts in scene Mr Welles reaching Rome newly divorced Rita Hayworth to shoot at the Cinecittà film series B under the command of a director of series C. dies in shooting one of the actors and Welles, converted into Jessica Fletcher Hall or Cluedo seasoned player, gets to investigate the incident. Adorns the plot a romance with the worst Paz Vega has ever seen ever playing an Italian actress who speaks English like me Mandarin. As backdrop a subplot of political corrupctión with Christopher Walken, Diego Luna and even the dreams of many hairdresser: Anna Galiena. Unexplained presences and they can call to deception.With this cast, it was difficult to make a crappy, but Walker succeeds and introduces us to an Orson Welles that seems a bulimic soplagaitas mainly and although it is presented as a thriller, it seems more a comedy because the plot and situations, if they seriously, are a joke.Maybe I am exaggerating but it is that I do not see where take it, it seemed a sacrilege, me angry and I bored me more than what I guess is bored Melanie Griffith watching the camino de los ingleses. And for films of Welles: Citizen Kane and evil thirst. Anathema!</body>
</review>
