<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A plasticity beautiful scenes, as well as other more raw, make up this work, in which fighting move halfway between slow and other tricks that will delight all fans to the epic films. A film that no one should miss.</summary>
	<body>It has finally come to our screens "300", another graphic novel by Frank Miller, who turns into images, after the exceptional "Sin city" of Robert Rodriguez. Zack Snyder, who really dazzled us with "Dawn of the dead", get that people are behind him, and he is already beginning to call director of worship. The argument of "300" is simple, Leonidas, King of Sparta, attends along with three hundred warriors defend the imminent attack of the Persian troops of Xerxes. To do so, and the abysmal gap of the troops, he attends a strategic point of its geography, the pass of Thermopylae. From here, and with other plot lines in the Middle, Leonidas and his, offer us some spectacular battles, showing us that the Spartan warriors are made another pasta, and even more, when we see the ritual to which they are subjected in his youth.Snyder and Miller give us the possibility, together with the technical and Visual effects, see a new way of making films and translate that particular vision.A plasticity beautiful scenes, as well as other more raw, make up this work, in which fighting move halfway between slow and other tricks that will delight all fans to the epic films.There are other details that stand out as the cast, headed by Gerard Butler (Leonidas), Lena Headey (Queen Gorgo) and David Wenham, who returns to films after incarnate Fáramir in "The Lord of the rings".A negative point is the excessive affectation of the King/Lord of the Persians, Xerxes, played by Rodrigo Santoro, who, apart from the negative voice, unfolds in a somewhat comical situation, in which the Spartan king turns its back, at the time that this ruler of the East, puts his hands on the shoulders and you loose a Pearl of dialogue. Except for this, and any creatures that might be more successful, see the Spartan hunchback, costume design, art direction and above all the image and visual style succeeded, make "300" a film that no one should miss.</body>
</review>
