<review author="Nüx" title="Paris je t'aime" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film friendly and recommended, where we can find moments of a quality and dramatic richness excellent along with other very renqueantes within the narrative and rhythmic.</summary>
	<body>This film is the product of join eighteen stories set in each of the districts of the Gallic capital. In general, I thought it was a film extremely pleasant and entertaining, from treacly and forced romanticonas situations, as a priori one might assume. Different managers have taken the task seriously, detail and working their mini-obras to fund. The actors of the stature of Portman, Buscemi or Elijah Wood have achieved, likewise, connect with the audience in the record time that implies a short film.Firstly, I would stress the short film of the Coens, Tulleries, in which an innocent tourist, sitting on a bench of the subway will be mocked by a Parisian couple couple.Contrary to what expected, also find the short of Gus Van Sant, Le Marais, thought me of an exquisite taste. Therein a French boy believed to have found their soulmate abroad a boy that attends discourse that it excited, being aimed stunned and hieratic. The work of Tom Tykwer, with Natalie Portman as the protagonist, likewise, was one of them that I liked. Here is reflected the idea that true love able to overcome all borders that should stand.Another kind of love is that appreciate the Place des fêtes of Oliver Schmitz, curious name to call a short where the story revolves not only love but also surrounding the death; because even in these recent wind of life, love still present.Likewise, the Tour Eiffel of Sylvain Chomet deserves special mention. This is, in my view, the more fun and original shorts, in which tells the colorful story of love between two mimes misunderstood by society.The short film by Alfonso Cuarón, which reduces to the more than predictable conversation of a father with his daughter, found me one of the weak and most disappointing of all.In the same way, nor except the fury of my flamethrower of Christpher Doyle, Porte de Choisy, which I cannot say anything besides the fact that I did not understand. It is one of those incomprehensible shorts in essence that tend to be qualified as "alternative", "symbolic" or "conceptual".Perhaps you you ask what such of the Coixet. of the lot, more or less at the same level as the rest of them that I have not named.It is, in conclusion, a film friendly and recommended, where we will find moments of excellent along with other very renqueantes within the narrative and rhythmic quality and dramatic richness.</body>
</review>
