<review author="Nüx" title="Time" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For those who, like me, you think that recently Asians are aren't doing the clip too much, this film will only confirm you that hypothesis, when not make matters worse.</summary>
	<body>I am going to tell you a little bit of a film which you've put the label of "criticism of Billboard", but that will make some months it was released in Spain. The movie in question is the Korean Time.Para who, like me, you believe that recently Asians are aren't doing the clip too much, this film won't but confirm you this scenario, when not make matters worse. Programs like yellow Humor will become small travesurillas showcases compared the psychopathies showing in Time. It all starts when the protagonist of the film undergo a cosmetic surgery operation to restructure their facial features, it expected to thus recover the passion lost with your partner. This is not an isolated case, multitude of aesthetic centres are engaged today desorientalizar traits, trend that seems to me a terrible embarrassing, therefore denotes not only the shortcomings of self-esteem of this people and surface of its society, but it also implies deny and despise roots that, not olidemos, go back to more than three thousand years old.This film reflects that criticism to degenerate current Eastern civilization from the point of view of one of its members, which is why, I think, should be taken into account as true, not wanting to say it, nor much less, which has not tended to exaggeration. But this is essentially a film of feelings. Some also exaggerated and surrealists jealousy intermingle with a sickly love to get to the key to the film: the eternal dissatisfaction of the human being. Participants join in a cyclic repetition of scope of objectives and subsequent disappointment, but which, far from the vision of cycle setting out my "Hellenes", it is not retroalimentativa, they, on the contrary, it is self-destructive.Addition to the room of the pathologically paranoid protagonist is suspicious and worryingly similar to mine, also noted as a curiosity the erotic beauty and special symbolism of the sculpture park that the characters create culture to come. This Park contributes largely to the nice picture of the film.Magnificent interpretations of the two main actors deserve more than this mention, but well, it is here said. After seeing them is inevitable to ask whether it is possible to interpret the psychology of a madman as well without being it. I doubt that this dilemma, seasoned with the horrifying and bloody images of operations, let me sleep tonight. And here I can (and want to) say of this interesting film which, however, gets surreal in one or another aspect.</body>
</review>
