<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Misión imposible 3" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The luxuries are not explosions helicopters and skyscrapers. The script is another luxury.</summary>
	<body>One way of enriching the fiction is attention to detail. The horror genre accuses her as an excess when he falls into the offal, but action films win much when it goes into details. Mission impossible saga is very similar to James Bond, but her decisively in the details. Ethan Hunt much more entertains with their robberies, kidnappings, bailouts, breaks, and fights. He is not the pleasure of seeing him win, he is the pleasure of seeing you do.Each delivery of mission impossible limelight of the public worldwide. The creators know that they have to be at a high altitude to satisfy the expectations, but so far none have been overcome by Vertigo. NI de Palma, Woo nor now J.J. Abrahams, who some will know by the series "Alias". Each sequence of the film, each section is woven with the same amount of ideas than a full movie of another firm; and, possibly, with one bigger budget. A chapter of M: i:III is like a feast of action cinema. And it is shot with that wonderful feeling of adequacy. The beginning of the film tells how Ethan tries to rescue a spy of Berlin with an excess of media and adrenaline that in another film of the same genre would serve to give us an end of apotheosis. But little pleased with doses of action, the persecution of helicopters and the bombs, the writers tell us that the rescued spy can die by an implant in the brain. This type of stunts, of "harder still" accumulate throughout the film. It is as if the creators knew that the viewer has already seen all the possibilities of a countdown of a "cannot be saved from there" and to complicate it to tell us: "That's not all". Personally I'm afraid thinking that it will be the film when mission impossible III is more like an action movie.The luxuries are not explosions helicopters and skyscrapers. The script is another luxury. And you have one of these narrative tricks which I usually complain. But just one, does not support history in retoricas. And it is so timely. I'm going to take the liberty of tell: the story begins with a scene of the end; Ethan has to give the bad leg of rabbit, because if it is not given the bad you will kill the woman he loves; and it has ten seconds to decide what it does.Holliwoodiense film has evolved from the good guys who gave his life for the sake of society, of the 1940s (Cayo Largo) the bad guys today that make the same heroic but only to help the person who want to. Today no hero dares to say out loud that will play the type for a high cause; unless the hero interpret it Bruce Willis, of course. Ethan hunt should take so many as an example by the balance maintained between the two extremes.</body>
</review>
