<review author="Robgordon" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Blockbuster well mounted, plastically perfect, very wild and entertaining. Flawless as epic film and special effects and that, without doubt, open a new path of palomitero film, more if we consider, that their collections at the box office are still heavy...</summary>
	<body>The aesthetic transformation of cinema show latest grilling has behind it to the figure of the artist graphic novels also screenwriter, Frank Miller. Theirs are the works "Sin City" and "300", which in addition has participated very actively in their versions for the big screen, codirigiendo, writing, producing or simply to monitor these adaptations and trying above all to the essence and appearance of his works, were reflected with similar scrupulous in the film.For this commitment in moving images of a comic to the seventh art more quote possible, Miller and Robert Rodriguez in "Sin City" and now Zack Snynder (responsible for the zombie revival which was "Dawn of the dead") have needed to carry out an original use of special effects, not so much in order to surprise the Viewer (although they have subsequently achieved that effect) but with the intention of docking to the maximum images and vignettes, with the film and visual evolution that entails.In this way, both "Sin City" as "300" are now responsible for a new evolution of the blockbuster film tapes, a new way of understanding the popcorn cinema, which bets in its entirety by the croma (i.e., the green background on which act the actors is then transformed into sets infográficamente), something that has tried and George Lucas in his recent episodes of the "Star Wars" saga, certain passages of "The Lord of the rings" or Peter Jackson's "King Kong" or those responsible for "Sky Captain and the world of tomorrow", but apparently, these adaptations of the worlds created by Miller and his attempt to be a reflection on the move of the graphic novels, have endowed this new film use, (radically opposed to the conception of cinema as such) of a perfect alibia justification for this absolute use of Visual effects to the detriment of the classicism of the film that we all know.Whether we like it or not, "300" already forms part of the history of the film's special effects. "Their proposal is radical and we cannot deny that his influence, such as"Sin City", which is taking will be decisive for the future of cinema show, that big budget film which is no longer unable to show us the most unimaginable universe, most unexpected situations or the most unlikely creatures."300 "is a piece of history to compose their world of fantasy. The battle fought at Thermopylae Greek between Spartans and Persians in 480 BC and Leonidas an army of 300 brave men fighting against millions of soldiers of the opposite side, is the plot excuse that Frank Miller created his graphic novel and now Zack Snyder has been able to portray avispadamente on the big screen.As already in Mel Gibson's "Apocalypto", historical accuracy is the least. The battles, the protagonists and places written in the annals of history, are only taken from inspiration to reinvent the history of the more lavish, colorful or fancy way. In short, to create a fast and fun entertainment. Because "300" is just that, an effective tape action and adventures of new generation, made with ex officio by Snyder and full of violence, testosterone and Golden colors.The visual power of "300", such as rabies and the force that appears in each one of its moments is undeniable. With a pretty little script that focuses on the battles from very soon, Snyder, based his film interest in the powerful figures of Leonidas (Gerard Butler, magnetic in his role), Xerxes (an amaneradísimo Rodrigo Santoro) and Lena Headey (great as Queen Gorgos) that focused the interest of history in their different points of view.The moments of battle, are well made, are clean and avoid this endemic evil of war scenes from the current cinema, that nothing can be seen and everything is confusing. There is also a certain abuse of the slow motion, which recreates in certain situations, but ultimately, "300" has the best battle sequences from "The Lord of the rings" which is again a clear benchmark on this occasion. As for the palatial intrigue, they have hardly any consistency, and it is a very weak throughout the history, though, point repeat the good do Lena Headey as Queen Gorgos.Resumiendo, "300" is a blockbuster well mounted, plastically perfect, very wild and entertaining. Flawless as epic film and special effects and that, without doubt, open a new path of palomitero film, more if we consider, that their collections at the box office are still heavy, it is to be the main thing for the producers of this film genre that so much money needs to be able to be developed. One of the tapes of the season.</body>
</review>
