<review author="Caruco" title="El último show" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do remarkable atmosphere, good work behind and before cameras, but a sleeping history that can only attract the interest of music lovers? country? do or? bluegrass?, unconditional and scholars Altman film or nostalgic nostalgia.</summary>
	<body>Ignored by critics and audience Awards, the posthumous work of the recently defunct Robert Altman is a charming and nostalgic look to the last day in the life of a radio program "A prairie home companion", which airs live from the Minnesota Fitzgerald Theatre, before that the building be torn down to build parking lots.Two last moments, the Altman as a filmmaker, and a space between the radio waves are linked almost by the whims of fate. But the vision of the Director of "Vidas cruzadas" is not intended to detract from tears and sadness, sinó extolling a few characters, despite the lack of popularity or triumph artísico and economic, they never cease to be free, nor although they rob them the reduced space itself.Synonymous with choral prominence, stars like Michelle Pfeiffer, George Clooney, singer Tom Waits (who had been involved in "Vidas cruzadas"), could not or did not want this time to go into the project. On the other hand, others known as Meryl Streep, Lindsay Lohan, Tommy Lee Jones, Lily Tomlin, Kevin Kline, Woody Harrelson or Garrison Keillor (the real presenter which took that program), Yes.Do and one of the attractions of the film is seeing them and oirles singing, especially topics? country?, as their characters they improvise or repeated to the rhythm of the melody, the advertising slogans of the sponsoring brands. But, despite the good weather that is respita among the artistic cast, the spark is very particular and rarely manages to penetrate the screen to catch the Viewer.Is a clear example the character of Kevin Kline, called Guy?Noir? and a prototype of typical dedective of film noir that intervenes as an observer close to what is happening, as well as a sort of Narrator, with interventions that contain jokes or reflections that does not stand out precisely or by his grace and wit.From the first image of the film, the heaven of the American Midwest, where different radio programs that talk about the price of meat pork can tune, about how they know better the noodles or how to save the soul, rarely manifests the interest. Only the scene in which the duo composed of Dusty (Woody Harrelson) and Lefty (John C. Reilly, one of the best side of the contemporary cinema), count and sing "bad jokes" get something animate function.As well as the curious presence, and in tune with the private dedective Kline, one that embodies? femme fatale? with sensual forms of Virginia Madsen. An Angel blond and dressed in an impeccable white coat that stands in the metaphor of the passage of time and death. Two issues in which it is easy to see how they aguijoneaban also to Altman, and however it portrays with benevolence and even beauty.Do remarkable atmosphere, good work behind and before cameras, but a sleeping history that can only attract the interest of music lovers? country? do or? bluegrass?, unconditional and scholars Altman film or nostalgic nostalgia.</body>
</review>
