<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do once clarified the blunders of some of our colleagues, so illustrious as ágrafos, and the memez feel offended for the sake of people that existed twenty-five centuries ago, we enter in the field:? 300? It is a quite comic book, a fast-paced action adventure and war is one of the first valid attempts to film the aesthetics of the game which today make all the rage in the world...</summary>
	<body>Let's go by parts: Let's break some of the presencing majaderías some illustrious colleagues of critique have said about this film: one, is not a film made against the Iran of the ultra-conservative President Ahmadinejad (remember that it threatens to turn his country into nuclear power and wiped off the map to the Israel State), for the simple reason that the new representative came to rule in August 2005 and "300" began shooting in September of that same year and, as you know lovers, a film (and less so mammoth like this) does not prepare one month to another; before Ahmadinejad was the reformist Khatami, which ran the country and relations with United States, although not totally, answers were developing clear restoration, until they reached the fundamentalist and jodió the invention. The second point to refute is the alleged lack of historical accuracy of the film; but let's see, illiterate mine, are dealing with a version of the comic Frank Miller wrote in 1998 libérrimamente inspired by the battle of Thermopylae, but without claiming to never have treatment tailored to the historical reality. Is that we will now ask rigour to a comic book? What will happen next, not to believe that the Kryptonite hurt Superman?Another thing: the rebound have caught the Iranians by the alleged ill treatment that gives the film its people are eager to humpback, not to say otherwise; the Persians who appear in the film were, supposedly, the inhabitants of Iran for more than two and a half thousand years; It is as if Spain us cabreáramos because the film release dómine sucks to the Iberians and Celts who populated our skin of a bull makes more or less this time. Once clarified the blunders of some of our colleagues, so illustrious as ágrafos, and the memez feel offended for the sake of people that existed twenty-five centuries ago, we enter in the field: "300" is a quite comic book, a thrilling adventure of action and war is one of the first valid attempts to film the aesthetics of the game which today make all the rage in the world: not only struggles, choreographed and ralentizadas as if a game to Play 2 or the brand new Play 3, but that even the scenery reminded powerfully virtual landscapes imagined by new creators of this art in the twenty-first century, which will have to go looking a numeral (to the way in which the film is the seventh art). Of course, the heroes led by King Leonidas are closer to the fantasy genre which history, with this iconography of supermen of the Neolithic, with their red coats, their heavy shields and fearsome javelins; not to mention already of these bodies carved with "body-building", with more abdominal muscles that we never thought could exist in the human body? Often, visually fascinating descuellan wonderful scenes, such as the rain of arrows, as it anticipates the emissary of Xerxes, literally darkens the sky, and that will have an estrambote formidable, iconic, conceptually speaking, in the final battle scene, when Leonidas faces impending death. Own visual creativity of the Miller, beautifully reproduced in the film comic brings us unforgettable characters, such as the own Xerxes, a Ramayana painted here as a cross between an NBA basketball player and a "drag-queen"; powerful instruments of war, as the fiercely dressed Rhino ride Persian soldiers; or scary characters, like the so-called Immortals, the personal guard of the dios-emperador, a tide of chilling closer to the zombie than man beings. To a comic book you cannot be philosophy, nor ideology, although those of always have rushed to columbrar that a film is pro-Bush to justify the invasion of Iraq and the (hypothetical) Iran. But the truth is that the central idea of this magnificent show, apart from the own joy visual see tremendous battles choreographed as if they were "Seven brides for seven brothers", is that we should always do right thing, what we think, whatever the cost, including life itself; and that must be done from the honesty, that rare Word: without doubt, today this is a revolutionary idea, in a nihilistic universe abomina effort, idolizes the beautiful task of navel-gazing and touching the nose and zascandilea outrageously with the scale of values of each. Not, if in the end will be that "300" is going to overtake on the left Lenin?</body>
</review>
