<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Days of glory" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Days of Glory denounces a deep historical injustice and pays deep tribute to those soldiers? indigenous?, but as film is not at the height of the story that counts.</summary>
	<body>The image that has always shown (especially American) film of the war is an image of patriotism, heroism, sacrifice and nobility, regardless of what conflict concerned. Cinema served in United States to lift the morale of a nation and encourage it to continue a war (World War II) liberated thousands of kilometres away, and therefore all war films of the era in general were mere pamphlets. Then became Kubrick in paths of glory, and the genre entered deeper oblivion with the wars of Korea and especially Vietnam.Pero wars are not like he has painted us them the film, that face values as the nobility of sacrifice are the suffering, pain, hunger, hardship for the civilian population, and the deathin many cases absurd and meaningless. With the purely propagandistic heroism always are unsung heroes, and in many conflicts there are always unfairly forgotten heroes. Days of Glory, Rachid Bouchareb tells the story of a group of these unsung heroes, of Moroccan and Algerian volunteers who fought against the nazi Germany by France. Days of Glory pays deep tribute to those men, and demand a fair restoration of her memory. This is the main virtue of a film that is nonetheless at the height of the story has. The tape is full of big ups and downs, and lacks the intensity necessary to catch completely to the Viewer, and the lack of pace and excessive length, ends up losing his attention. To any history lover film you will know, that stays on the surface of many things, such as practical accountability of the French Army (both homeland and colonies) to the invaders. The height of the absurdities is the character of Sergeant Roger Martinez, who barely know anything but that assigned an Arab origin. Performances are good as a whole, especially emphasizing Sami Bouajila and Jamel Debbouze.Days of Glory it denounces a deep historical injustice and it pays deep tribute to "indigenous" soldiers, but that film isn't at the height of the story has. After this, we wonder when will the time for France to recognize the Spanish Republicans who had fought in the French Foreign Legion, and were the first soldiers allies in walking the streets of Paris in vehicles with names such as Teruel, Belchite and Brunete.</body>
</review>
