<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Madrigal" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Madrigal is a film for lovers of the rarities of the enigmatic and incomprehensible, stories these posed a multitude of incoherent questions that do not offer any response, and allow an infinite number of interpretations.</summary>
	<body>In the absence of originality that suffers from the film, increasingly more abound in the definitions of the movies words like reference, tribute or nod, referring to scenes or very similar approaches with other films. Do this is not to mention the long list of words which themselves describe cinematographic works, as a sequel, prequel, remake? and so on.With Madrigal, Fernando Perez paid tribute to David Lynch and one of his last works, the touted by some as denostada by others, Mulholland Drive. They see what I mean? All have fallen to again tempted to use buzzwords to referinos to this or that tape. But what is that difference to a tribute of a crude copy zarrapastrosa? Then something very subjective, as it is the evaluation of the film itself: If the evaluation is good, can pass over the alleged lack, but poor of the director as the valuation is bad, because in that case it will consume in the fire for all eternity. This tirade is beside the point of Madrigal and their suspicious and dangerous similarities with Mulholland Drive (will turn a blind eye to the dedication to René Clair), especially in its final stretch. Fernando Pérez, as it already did Lynch, transforms reality to suit in the last act, twisting her and moulding it to your tastes. The two stories raised Madrigal are gimmicky excesivamentes while predictable, empty, and rub the absurd and the grotesque, in the worst sense. The film lacks originality, not to mention the absolute lack of pace. Best thing is the very careful technical aspect, and interpretations of their actors, yielding all to a good level.Madrigal is a film for lovers of the rarities of the enigmatic and incomprehensible, stories these posed a multitude of incoherent questions that do not offer any response, and allow an infinite number of interpretations.</body>
</review>
