<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Fundido a negro" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With fade to black Oliver Parker offers us a well structured and seamless thriller with one of the great masters in the history of the film starring: Orson Welles.</summary>
	<body>Rather than spread the fashion of the biopics, plague strikes the film without the least hint of pity or compassion, was not strange to see movies featuring real characters that unfolded in a plot of fiction, always with a real historical background (such as down the iron curtain, Tim Robbins). So he could bring to the average viewer figure of great characters, but not showing their miseries and glories, but showing an environment where it could function as a fictional character more.With fade to black Oliver Parker rescues the best spirit of such films, offering a well structured and seamless thriller with one of the great masters in the history of the film starring: Orson Welles. History tells us the arrival of Welles (Danny Huston) to Rome in 1948 to shoot a film, black magic. During filming, a the supporting actor dies in her arms whispered to the ear his last words. In this way, Welles is immersed in a dangerous plot of murder with important political ramifications. Based on the novel by Davide Ferrario, renowned British director Oliver Parker offers us a more than interesting thriller, with continuous references to the classic film noir, that keeps the viewer's attention until the last breath. In a story whose protagonist is Orson Welles, find the ideal actor to embody the genius always is a headache. Danny Huston, who knew the own Welles for friendship with his father John Huston made a bright, full of shades covering a wide emotional range, and interpretation without falling into the overacting or the grotesque. The rest of the cast components perform to high level, including peace Vega, whose international career looks every day stronger thanks to good performances like this.In short, fade to black is a thriller intelligent and honest, because it offers what it promises, that maintain intrigued the espetador from the first minute until its conclusion. It's a kind of cinema, pure entertainment, which is scarce today, or at least do the good examples of the genre. And it is ironic that a good mystery with Orson Welles starring movie has been done in the United Kingdom and not the Almighty Hollywood.</body>
</review>
