<review author="Cp" title="Misión imposible 3" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>May not want to go to the movies, but then do not miss on your DVD</summary>
	<body>I've never liked Alias, nothing of nothing, and lost no me has hooked, so much that even taking the chapters of the second season, I have not yet spent of the fourth. Thus, that although recognize you good ideas to Abrams, the truth is that it is not a copyright on my list, in the sense that when you create a new work, go running to enjoy it. As for Tom Cruise, I recognise some large works, along with other notable and some interesting. The truth is that it seems that it is boring at times, and not works, except when there is a Spielberg demanding.Against this background, mission impossible 3 was not on my list of essential films, but admit that seeing trailers and images he was increasing my interest, and in the end I went to see her the day of the premiere. And when I realized. the film had already ended. Taking into account that it is an action film, it is one of greatest praise that can be made to it. Combining scenes of thrilling action, along with phases of dialogue and where it tells us the life of the character, for the first time in three films.Perhaps style of camera very, very close, moving to crazy, not allowing you you do a general picture, and jumping like crazy, not me just convince. A current fashion, which allows you to hide poorly choreographed fights and little athletic players, but J.J. know move it, as well as Paul Greengrass in the second part of Bourne, and when you know how to use, is when a unique rhythm gives the film. The scenes of dialogue, we are finally creating a character of Ethan fuller Hunt, which although it will not deserve an oscar, Cruise makes it credible.Next to it, the rest of the actors are perfect for their roles. His performances are not excessively (except Philip Seymour to simply this perfect, especially when confronted with Cruise) but each actor fits the character like a glove, and you think. And that is essential in a film like this, where you must accept skills and feats of the characters, especially Ethan in a world like ours, but a little more game, more extreme, with impossible jumps, miraculous escapes and perfect costumes, but which now Ethan already shoot the bad guys without any remorse, repairing a detail of previous films I had not just convince.The story, well, a single argument with a hyphen well built and very well filmed, where you vibe with some scene (screaming "once cogelo" to Hunt in a moment that drop you an object between the cars of a Shanghai Avenue) and although not surprised you almost nothing leaves you sleep.In summary, breakneck action, a few touches of dialogue and construction of personal stories, actors perfectly coupled to his characters, a very bad bad, and a main actor believed his role. You may not want to go to the movies, but then do not miss on your DVD.</body>
</review>
