<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Tara Road" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do pleasant to see almost always, is a comforting though perhaps film too pacatus in its approach, reminiscent of bursts of a recently made movie? in the manner of the BBC?.</summary>
	<body>Sometimes not understood why some movies, with all ballots to enjoy an acceptable commercial career, staying on the shelves of the distributors. It is the case of this "Tara Road", a film that, without being nothing another Thursday, it is clear that may interest to a particular audience, mostly middle-aged or even something more, because it raises issues that are close to them, and is also served by a handful of known actors (MacDowell, Rea, Olivia Williams of "The sixth sense"). However, has taken two years to reach the Spanish screens, when any anti-commercialism bullshit (and without artistic value, is understood) opens on time. The film of the Scottish Gilles MacKinnon, shot in Ireland and United States with not only Irish performers and Yankees, but also Germans (Jean-Marc Barr), it raises in a mixture which is not, fortunately, be the usual macedonia decaffeinated with bits and pieces from different parts of Europe which all too often perpetrated on our continent. The plot revolves around two dramas: one, the terrifying, absolute tragedy of the death of the only teenage son in a well-placed Yankee family; the other, the trauma of separation, prior adultery and even stem out of wedlock, of an Irish couple in theory all happiness. Of these tragedies "tour de force" part of the film, the exchange of houses between the two affected, allowing them to rediscover themselves in a few environments so different from his usual, assuming that exchange more than a mere change of Habitat: also oxygenates their lives and gives them something so live. Nice to see almost always, is a comforting though perhaps film too pacatus in its approach, that reminds bursts of a recently made movie "in the manner of the BBC".</body>
</review>
