<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A little great film, brilliant in every way and with a cast in absolute State of grace. Remember, above all, the phrase that Paul Dano writes to Carrell: I Hate Everyone. That trembleth Dakota Fanning!</summary>
	<body>The indie film ever is improving more, which I find really fair. During the history of the cinema have presented us wonders such as Magnolia, Memento or Fargo (possibly these three which most notable in independent, for my taste) and all of them have been very well received both by critics and by the public. And here is another small wonder indie entitled little Miss Sunshine, which was released last year and so far I have not been able to see. One of the premiere of the 2006 is, without a doubt, more master, with permission of El laberinto del Fauno and children of men.The film is directed by the couple Jonathan Dayton and Valerie Faris, both beginners. Perhaps accused the film of being recurriente to several aspects always common in this kind of movies where the family is somewhat dysfunctional, but I think that this is not a judgement, because each character is superbly written and they have hardly any lack of common sense (well, maybe a little Yes, but what are you going to do if they are geeks). The case is that little Miss Sunshine portrays the life of a family, which is joined by the trip undertaken to carry the smallest at a beauty contest in an exceptional way. And it is that the theme of the family is not unique, since it is also noted that criticism to this type of competition, lack of personality of the organizers and the overcoming of oneself. In short, the film is a trip to the impossible, but also a journey that represents life itself, full of problems along its path and knowledge ever explored so far. This is therefore a film symbolic, poignant, tragic and funny, smart and really essential.As well as the direction, his screenplay is equipped with the same dose of intelligence and wit until you reach appear to be Oscar (that Yes, it is in this case). Perhaps also being accused of being somewhat typical for the independent films, to have several common places where occurs the action (do gas station, dining room, hospital?), and Yes, here I agree Yes, but I cannot find a point against it. The structure of the script is not that it is the height of the originality, but they are some of the gags that occur in the film (the police and the porn magazine, dinner that begins the film or the end of the film, absolutely incredible scene). That Yes, there is one of them that I think that there is extra: the encounter between Steve Carrell and her former boyfriend at the petrol station, nothing credible and totally out of sync. Moreover, we can say that little Miss Sunshine is really original and that, above all, you lifted spirits.But that does not just cracks in the film is, without doubt, the cast. It was a pity that they do not nominaran to Steve Carrell (the best role for me) for the Academy, as it was, in my opinion, much better than Alan Arkin (which gave her the unfair, especially for being too brief, award for best supporting actor). Anyway, that what really matters is that each and every one of the actors in the film estáns superb in each of his appearances: Greg Kinnear as the loser father who thinks only about winning; Steve Carrell as the uncle of the family, which is welcomed by all of them after trying to commit suicide; Toni Collete is probably the most normal of the family and all you want is that everything goes smoothly; Paul Dano, on the other hand, is the rarer, the more freak, but however, which falls best of all; Alan Arkin as the grandfather, splendid Yes, but appears too little; and Abigail Breslin as Olive, the small star and the center of everything, that makes an incredible role (worthy of an Oscar, no doubt). That trembleth Dakota Fanning!I can not fail to mention the magnificent photography and the computed Assembly, although it is not that they are the very best. All technical aspects are very worked, but I think this time, recognition it has more to the script and performances that not paragraphs more technical.In short, we have a great little film, brilliant in every way and with a cast in absolute State of grace. Remember, above all, the phrase that Paul Dano writes to Carrell: I Hate Everyone.</body>
</review>
