<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="300" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Overwhelming merely visually stunning epic, meticulous in detail, rich in reading, Opera: will go down in the history of cinema to open a new market, a different way of understanding the entertainment in the 21st century. And he is supported for this scribe is love with and that come predictable hyperbole in their considerations because that dictates the emotion that inevitably overwhelms him.</summary>
	<body>Confined to sporadic outbursts of mass consumption type Gladiator, the peplum epic film of Romans or adjacent civilizations it has always had ups and downs in his popular dissemination, small ridges and big drops, although when it succeeds (like the Spanish when he did that said) triumphs of truth. 300 is the pitch of the season and not only raises the adhesions or usual repulsas in whom we tend to give written testimony on this celebrity is the film that sometimes wakes up lit bar conversations, incendiary purpose of their benefits and their limitations. 300 Marks with it aims to their very savvy funders: everybody, you've read or not something the tape, has heard or not something on your content, go to the cinema, let the bitches and leave with an overdose of manly meat, muscular and tense, and that no one think that this getting me shirt of eleven sticks or tribulations filogay, who even in that wanted some search of arguments to this piece of film (already start the evisceration) should not see any film lover and gives the same leave excited as the Viking Vikie or sad as Buster Keaton in his good time 300 narrates a battle: basically (with small subsidiaries frames) what counts is ésothe savage onslaught of a Persian army huge and invincible on a handful of Spartans to heroic in number of 300 are courageous facing this inconsumerable numerical disproportion. The fundamental issue, which makes 300 not to any other movie ever filmed, is its nature pioneered certain types of film that extracted from as it surrounds him their formal material, its way to revolutionize an art that has always been attentive to the changes and that never has foregone innovations technological, either sound like color or dolby or hortero 3D. Then appeared the digital language and then the film, the seventh of the arts, renounced their share of the cake and adopted (for the benefit of the public goloso) points of view and ways of filming (and especially mount) surprised the viewer of the fifties when the peak of the audacity in special effects were somethings corpses of Jason and the Argonauts. Visual ventures of 300 colman many demands and a director that already promised in the undervalued is crowned (the gore genre anda fall viscus) dawn of the dead, Zack Snyder perpetrating a fantastic distraction that is not intended to delve into the history or pontificate on certain values but romanticize a series of events of eminently epic nature: the battle of the pass of Thermopylaea corridor to ras costa, a detachment of thrown notables of selfless spirit and vocation of martyrs and a mammoth representation of the enemy in the form of human flood.The speech of the film is not flat: contains an exacerbated tone military harangue of unequivocally jingoistic message that love the reservist Yankee and the viewer an accomplice of the nationalist iconography to use, but also reads a least overload ideology to primitive and crude fascism which seems to derive from the film, and many critics sing as inalienable nature of the proposal of Snyder can be drawn. I refer to the addictive staging, to his pursuers concatenation of scenes of a force out of the ordinary. If we look at the film as mere entertainment (without addressing its cultural sediment, without looking at their fidelity to history, without any unnecessary game of contemporaneity), 300 is an absolute joy, a gap in the movies next, a kind of point and separate so that the hard core of production in Hollywood know where they stand and onwards, not spare a dollar in the billing of films of this nature which combines splendidly (own) modernity (Frank Millar comic) and some aftertaste pulp, tribute honest to all literature of serie B and the exhausted graphic literature in which Miller Dove for shaping its history of Spartans and Persians, Leonidas (a great George Butler) and Xerxes (an effeminate Rodrigo Santero).Those who want to delve into other aspects, has material that get lost. 300 acquiesce to forge a new genre whose name would not know we here present. As if we hold a supported digital Baroque not only in a hypnotic plasticity but in a very solid script (when the argument seems to give so little) that even has a voice in magnificent, literary, captivating, off which seems to recite the heroic passage of Sparta brave defenders against the barbarian hordes who seek to invade.In the light of today, 300 acquires a relevant significance, we have already said. Can you take into consideration that the Spartans are the champions of what later has been called West or Europe and Xerxes and his Persian riding elephants, rhinos and other mythological bestiaries represents the interference of another enemy, who comes from outside and so seeks to penalty to refuse future impose on us its present. That is all very well. There is consent that the film raises it and similar dialogues, but it is also the incomparable the film grace as entertainment and then 300 is a work of art, a work of art written at the beginning of the 21st century. Like art, as human language, adapting to the times and is supplied from their signs to reform its ideology and face the future with some solvency and chances of success.The choreography of the fights is an absolute beauty and this scribe is no friend of fighting on screen and has never enjoyed scene with abundant minutaje where they call others. Here, for once, everything complies with the major dictation of a script that one believes all, lack of importance that the cash be recognized as truthful or we understand that all seeking Snyder is adapted to the cinema (and go adaptation) comics of Millar, who in turn adapted to graphic art an episode of history Herodotus collected in his book VII of Hellenic history. And then the world was Greece. 300 lacks modesty: not accurate wimpish concessions to orthodoxy. There is blood (that dance in the air as if he re-wrote a choreography to the beat of Spears) and there is a rudimentary sense of violence which has nothing to do with concepts of violence that we have been acquiring, almost accidentally, by pure film lover spirit, by the hand of Tarantino, Boorman or Stone. This is different: it wins our consent with only investigate the mythological nature of its plot. Meaningless search ethical commitments on the idiocy of the violence and all that so wise and so good looking in these times of political correctness (apparent, clear) which we have planted on screen is when a reading (one more) of a classic episode reading Latin texts when I studied B.U.P.</body>
</review>
