<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El último show" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The last Show is a vulgar movie, the lot, based on the failed premise of the portrait of characters also failed, and whose sole attraction is the interpretive work.</summary>
	<body>For some years, the translations of the titles of foreign films have entered a deep downhill. When does the original title, is added the translation as a subtitle, as Adaptation (the Orchid thief), or if not, a "free" interpretation and there are cases like the of forget of my!, whose American title came to be something like eternal shine of an Inmaculada.Pero mind for the last Show, while perfect refers to the story which tells the tape in the translationWe must recognize that it is a detail of titular tasteless as well to the posthumous work of Robert Altman. The film has the problems facing members of veteran radio program when you know the news of the closure of the station. All are counting their glories of yesteryear and their miseries, past, present and future. That is the main livelihood of the last Show, because the initial argument does not offer many alternatives. However, the portrayal of the characters (some absurd and desdibujados, by the way) is distant and cold, devoid of emotions. To treat a human tape, the main defect of the same is that never get to connect with the spectator, does part of the suffering and hopes of his characters, but rather lets indifferent to what takes place on the screen. The actors are the best of the last Show, among them the great Meryl Streep in a new interpretative Pirouette. It also serves to check the star of teen film and the tabloid press Lindsay Lohan can aspire to become a full-fledged actress if it continues the path that began with Bobby and continued with this work.The last Show is a vulgar movie, the lot, based on the failed premise of the portrait of characters also failed, and whose sole attraction is the interpretive work. The end point of the career of Robert Altman not will be especially remembered, on a trajectory of itself full of profound ups and downs, and some small jewel like Gosford Park.</body>
</review>
