<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Diary of a scandal dares to explore very difficult and controversial issues, but does so with great care, subtlety and sensitivity, without judging their characters.</summary>
	<body>More than one month has passed since presenting the Oscar, and when it seemed that he had completed the hangover of the winners (and losers), suddenly again come to the fore. And arriving at the Spanish charts one of the films that chose several small statues of the important (adapted screenplay, actress, supporting actress and music), British Journal of a scandal. nobody can doubt the good shape affecting British cinema today, both in quality and international repercussion.Richard Eyre offers us adaptation of the controversial novel by Zoe Heller, which chronicles the relationship that arises between two professors, Barbara (Judi Dench) and Sheba (Cate Blanchett). Sheba is married to one man older than her, Richard (Bill Nighy), while Barbara remains unmarried. Their relationship will be a turning point when Barbara discovers the adventure keeps Sheba with one of his students, Steven (Andrew Simpson). One of the virtues of diary of a scandal is that it dares to explore very difficult and controversial, issues almost taboo. But unlike what you sell trailers, Richard Eyre does so with great care, subtlety and sensitivity, without judging their characters. In no time the tape falls into sensationalism or in easy ways. The solid screenplay by Patrick Marber contains a few characters very well built, showing them in all their humanity, full of feelings, joys and miseries. The pace that prints Eyre film is excellent, and the duration is fair and necessary, one minute. Despite the virtues of history, above all include Judi Dench and Cate Blanchett, which performed a few simply colossal interpretations. Both embark on a real tour de force (the best in many years) interpretive, embroidering intricate characters, making them credible and close to the Viewer.Diary of a scandal is an essential film, a modern classic, that invites a viewer worried to reflect on the great variety of issues and questions posed by the history. And it is an opportunity like no other to see two of the best actresses in the current film scene in an interpretative duel that make time.</body>
</review>
