<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El caso Slevin" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I highlighted among this multitude of classics of the thriller due to its interesting outcome. One movie more than correct with an intelligent script and cast of authentic luxury.</summary>
	<body>Only in the usual suspects, that masterpiece of Bryan Singer, has managed to catch the viewer in its final stretch. Perhaps as commercial films as basic instinct or the sixth sense also did at the time, but it is clear that the Singer film was, and will remain, the thriller with the best surprise of the story ending. Among so many and such varied films of intrigue that have aired over the years, it would not bad stress, positively, the second work of Paul McGuigan, entitled the Slevin.Y case precisely what I highlighted among this multitude of classic because of gender, especially to its interesting outcome. You don't have the same ingenuity than the others, possibly because the others already exist and it has built a tad in them, but there is no doubt that the film you tricks until the end. Apparently, the film seems to be an entertaining thriller of action with comic touches without too much spark. This appearance is transformed into something totally positive and the result is, as mentioned, an interesting and ingenious thriller that does not disappoint in its final stretch, but it rather surprised.But, above all, the script of the Slevin case is somewhat irregular: its inception is incredible, as well as the outcome, but the crux of the story, or the part intermediate, decreases relatively, presented some another downturn and meaningless dialogues. But then, this small depression that suffers from the film, is recovered by a turn (perhaps somewhat excessive), which did not disappoint anyone.It would also be necessary to highlight the incredible cast after their argument. Perhaps the protagonist is it worse (Josh Hartnett without too much spark, although not entirely unbearable). But I must admit that the rest of performers are a few authentic cracks. From a great Bruce Willis (as usual), Morgan Freeman in State of grace (as always) to Ben Kingsley playing, in a peculiar way, a Rabbi without scruples. And the side include the Eastern beauty in person, Lucy Liu, in a totally curious role, Stanley Tucci, portraying the police investigating the case and Danny Aiello, which always makes interesting roles, although here, unfortunately, do not remember or to what role belonged.Within the technical aspects I would highlight its modern photography (careful with angles really claustrophobic fixed levels) and witty and almost perfect Assembly. It is not bad music, although not noted for high.In short, one film more than correct with an intelligent script and cast of authentic luxury, but some have other failure on the intensity of the story.</body>
</review>
