<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El buen alemán" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Failed attempt to bring a form of film-making classic, from the use of lenses from time to entenebrecer a black and white too strange and little real to this modern firing genius Vertigo.</summary>
	<body>This deception that is definitively to the black and white and taxed a tribute apparently goer to the immortal Casablanca is in the background, a failed attempt of greening the vintage of the time spirit, their hazy textures, the Warner Brothers logo descromatizado and the air between the nostalgic and the philanthropic (love of the cinema, you can understand) de la obra de Soderbergh.Lo that comes later is a heavy history of espionagein which there is no good nor bad but characters housed in a strange time of moral buildings reventadas by the war and a commitment to multinational by rebuilding devastated the barbarism that they themselves forged.The survival, the boarder of the sentiments, the hard-fought battle of the newly invented cold war generated a thick and little affordable script for the Viewer, ending slightly interested (how not) but unfortunately troubled by the grief of this political traces to guignol attends the patterns of the genre (romance, the lies, the elaborate dialogues) and accelerates them to the runrún of these times now so the impression is frankly sadder. Exits one as depressed the film, without having heard nothing concrete. In any case, to a pragmatic evidence of the instinct of man by accommodate the inconveniences of his own madness. Rate weary and burdened by an inappropriate cluster in occasions of small little relevant side plots, the film cares much more form than substance. Usually standard of this director and he has not yet made film where is the argument which lead images and not to the upside down.Resource insert documentary scenes in the plot makes a little more bearable as well as the acting effort of a committed casting it but George Clooney is overly broad in its role, it does what should not (and can avoid it as we assume knows), that is, overact, confer on its role as evidence of drama, of falsehood. Not happens you to CAte Blanchett, every day more classic.</body>
</review>
