<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Man to man" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Boring dissertation on ethics and moral values that remains in a reductionist prospect of cultures confronted not by the supremacy of science but by the glitz of the show.</summary>
	<body>The naturalistic scientism is a weak film genre, but has survived to hard-working tapes between the melodramatic and grossly documentary base. Da same as the founding premise of the film is the survival of a few macaques in Borneo or the desire to deal with faith and science, metaphor and pure logic. Anthropology of kindergarten, exoticism of travel magazine paper couché, simiesca caricature of a script that could have given more case that had not wanted to insist on Affairs of so little interest to a modern Viewer, alien to these darwinismos of operetta, to these files facilones where the clash of two cultures resembles the languid mating of two koalas.That the link lost and miraculously recovered for public display has hook to have produced a film with more sobriety, less stereotyped, much more interested in the moral distress of some characters in the loggerhead Didactics of a scarcely credible scientist and an anomalous situation, between the exotic and Plast. If this hybridization of epithets strain.There's more: is maníquea in their approach; naive in his solucionario and, above all, flat in what proposed, even though the galas exhibits are turgid and it seems that we are witnessing a magna opera, something incontrovertibly important.Man to man testifies that is soft to well done, but boring film. And the torpor is so enormous that one abandons the interest to find sense to this predictable and very vulgar sunset scene, by moments, it seems a Sunday sermon on the pre-eminence of the Catholic moral values (they flatten that flatten, go through where you pass) that a streamlined and argumentativamente attractive trip to the human heart, which appears to draw it in the first minutes of the film (the hunting of the Pygmies) they delude and lead to expectations that are later hidden by a montage delinquent, slow, an inefficiency appalling because a half-hour of screening all interest mechanisms are disabled and start one to look at the clock (what terrible thing in the film) and hope that the time passes quickly and we soon leave to pick up to the first unsuspecting bystander and entrust to it, without doubt, our conclusions. "Won't you, stay at home". "Not her rent on dvd: ask Babel or any modern Edition of strangers on a train with extras and all that".Go to Lynch and her man elephant, which speaks of the same (say) but more twisted and lucidly.</body>
</review>
