<review author="Bloody Will" title="The messengers" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Anyway, if you want to spend fear look at your accounts when you finish the Easter. I am sure that in these coming months will finally debut this film say? not sleep tonight?, but isn't this, I I assure you.</summary>
	<body>This film had already seen. Do I had seen about the child who sees ghosts in?The sixth sense?. Do I had seen about the possessed House in?Horror in Amityville?. Does he had seen the Gray Ghost in?The cry?. More grey hands, also in?The cry?. Do massacre family again in?Horror in Amityville?. Ultimately, all seen est´´a.Little, therefore, I can say a film that should not go for a viewing fast on DVD and in house, and actually promised more than what it has finally given. Its directors, Danny and Oxide Pang, who came supported by the saga of?The Eye? they have been deflated in the Mecca of dreams and offer us easy scares, predictable screenplay, ridiculous tension and an end of most overused. After so many remakes and remakes Eastern increasingly feels more, or enter pure gore, or that climate of yesteryear where you had to grab the seat compi of next is history.Maybe that industry has grown accustomed to launch u-b movies that have good commercial revenues, but everything comes to an end, and?The Messengers? This is a good example that the end is coming. We need good stories, not a catalogue of cliche situations.A family who moves to the field after glitches in the city, buys a House with adjacent terrenito in which cultivated sunflowers. From there disturbing visions for the smallest of the family, and a genuine harassment and ghostly demolition teen shift will take place. Do while parents remain incredulous until all jumps into the air and it is discovered the? inheritance? that came included with the House. Does this has been the best way to explain the plot without bursting the meagre surprises? It has the film, and believe me that it has been difficult to be so neutral.Does watching?The Messengers? It gives the feeling that?The Eye? made it an uncle who gave his honours to the Pang brothers. Pang pang their heads by committing one of the most disappointing jumps of an Asian filmmaker in Hollywood, which is doubly crime as two of the directors. Do succeeded actors borden worst performances, with a Penelope Ann Miller years light of?Carlito´s Way?. Dylan McDermott has not be lavished both in the film, but is not a newbie. Doesn't me do or feeling of anxiety or feeling anything, although it is really the girl in the movie, Kristen Stewart (?)(Do the room of panic?) which has on his shoulders the weight of make you shout, which you do only so that her they liquidate once and end up all. I will let John Corbett aside, that men owe him a respect for?Doctor in Alaska?.Anyway, if you want to spend fear look at your accounts when you finish the Easter. I am sure that in these coming months will finally debut this film say? not sleep tonight?, but isn't this, I I assure you.</body>
</review>
