<review author="Alex Largo" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Well, pretty good. A good film in which spend the money, which, in addition to being spectacular, heroic, amazing, etc, is very entertaining. But lacks? something? getting to be very good. A pity.</summary>
	<body>Remember a film that you have enjoyed, but that would have left them a strange feeling? Not be if I can explain. Do I refer to a film that is not outstanding, but that rather than excite them them to left something? I do not know? as of? "If, very well," but that basically know that something that you do not know very well what is and thus not him you've finished catch lacks it? "that".Is that not is. The movie I liked, and I enjoyed. But? lacks it something. What is it? I believe that it is the set of some things. Let's go by parts.As regards the direction of Snyder, well, good. Quite good, more than correct. Anyone can throw in face to this man that the way in which the film is shot is bad. It has style. Although perhaps is something does videoclipera? But very correct. Perhaps at times abused of certain resources, such as slow and the quick-slow-quick-slow, but as they do not compliment too, not arriving to become an ordeal.The battles are very well shot (although occasionally not so well mounted), it is obvious that they have been eager to shoot them. The film is almost in its 60% battles. And although is it missing something more dialog, the battles are very entertaining.As actors? Well the truth, no is who could say that they do wrong. Each and every one of the actors (although some sobreactúen sometimes) very well carry out their duties. Above all Gerard Butler (the Phantom of the Opera) and Lena Headey (the Brothers Grimm). The first splendid as King Leonidas, knowing give the character of a force and a charisma that make the character falls well to the public (also because it is one of the few characters that are not as a goat). The second fulfills its task far, although in somewhat dull occasions, but usually (especially in the final stretch) excellent.In the script? The dialogues are very scarce. Although not to the extent of "Apocalypto". But occasionally they miss at fault, that the film relies too much on images.For the special effects? Therefore it sobre valued. Although no one with two front toes may say are bad, occasionally are something? loose (will the Wolf, some landscapes, rhinos?). I do not understand how people can marvel at these special effects when we see other far superior. But still they give the film a very particular aesthetic, and more importantly, almost calcada to the comic.Posts to speak, I would like to comment on the (poor) responsible for make-up work. Although in the vast majority of cases right, in others, quite false (as it happens with the character of Ephialtes, or some of the many deformed that appear in the film). The soundtrack, quite rightly, conforms perfectly with the images, in an outstanding way. And the most machaconas parties are here justified given the large amount of scenes of battle.With regard to the controversy of the "attack on Iranian culture"? then? I thought that they exaggerated? but not. Do while the film is not intended to be historically faithful, show to Iranian culture as something "effeminate", not be? something? Well, the best thing is that you fijéis in the photo above, where Xerxes (the bad) "tontea" with Leonidas (was supposed that it is negotiating, but after seeing the film, I have not so clear). Already, Yes, it seems a cavalcade saccade gay (more specifically of the float of the Drag Queen), why I said that the film is historically rigorous (or so intended, as I have already said). Why no be taken too seriously in this regard. For this reason I advise: that nobody is going to see the movie thinking that going to see a faithful account of the battle of Thermopylae, that is in the history books, the film tells is all fiction.As for the film as well, in general. Well, well, pretty good. A good film in which spend the money, which, in addition to being spectacular, heroic, amazing, etc, is very entertaining. But missing "something" to become very good. A pity. As for those who claim it is a masterpiece and other work. well say that they are a bit exaggerated. The movie is good. but until that point?</body>
</review>
