<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Epic movie" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Out of the expensive film long, looks askance, remorse and an intense debate about whether or not some "puntazo" that rights worth. I did not see it.</summary>
	<body>Take time to make this criticism. Moreover, take time to read this criticism, is a great way to waste time. But perhaps a server, resquemoroso, resentful, hurt and somewhat embarrassed, can seek the apology at one of those inherent to the man needs: the share the worst of life with others.Error number one: get carried away. You know, always is the fault of others. That if Scary Movie was not bad, that if I want to laugh a bit, that if there is nothing better to do tonight. I find a thousand excuses, you could even argue that he was drunk (or that he wanted to be, I do not remember well), but the case is that the 6.50? It was worth the entry passed to other hands, perhaps wiser than the mine.Error number two: see it. One enters little waiting. outings. Maybe 3 "extemely"? A couple of gags for the memory? Some of these nonsense over time seem more funny? But nothing at all. The time was passing and I refused to lay me, to stretch your legs and enjoy a good sueñecito (as did fellow from next door). I wanted to endure. Six euros are well worth a little patience. With the expected 3 "extemely" the thing remained in two euros for "point". Today did not go wrong change. However, they did not. Not even a triple on the Horn.It would enter into details, but I would be doing a disservice to whom read me. This time things were going from parody of epic films: Pirates of the Caribbean, Superman, the Chronicles of Narnia, Charlie and the chocolate factory. Four orphans come in Gnarnia and try to defeat the White Witch. By the way go crossing with others (now a pirate, now a magician.) and finally. I don't know, neither remember nor care too much. The worst is not that it lacks argument (no one asked that), what is serious is that not even attempting to parody of such films, ridicule them, find the funny side. It's like a rehash of sequences of one and another, always staying about to make grace. The few moments that deserve a smile are those in which uses the sophisticated resource "give a blow to another", which ultimately is as old as cinema.Add to this discomfort at seeing so much untapped money (not mine, of the budget for the production of both stage and both costumes) and the unfortunate moments videocliperos (got to thinking that any retransmission of MTV had cast) and get a real waste of film. Out of the expensive film long, looks askance, remorse and an intense debate about whether or not some "puntazo" that rights worth. I did not see it.</body>
</review>
