<review author="Calaf" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although historically not reproduza with veracity customs, weapons, even more importantly, boasts many accurate data historians, such as the time of the battle or even phrases of combatants. Pure entertainment.</summary>
	<body>It is said that Xerxes I, Persian Emperor, to come up with the Spartans, meant that these marcharían to see the size of his army. It took four days and Xerxes, impatient, sent an emissary demanding the Greeks that they paid their weapons immediately to not be annihilated. Leonidas I, King of Sparta, replied: "Come and look for them yourself". Thus began the battle.The last adaptation of the famous battle of Thermopylae, which faithfully follows the style of the eponymous comic book by Frank Miller, who participated in the production of the film I've seen. No doubt there will be detractors and supporters. I am of those who enjoyed it from start to finish, with an entertaining movie where they exist.Although historically not reproduza with veracity customs, weapons, even more importantly, the number of combatants (the 300 Spartans would have added them other 6000 Greek allies) Yes account with many accurate data of the historians, such as the times of the battle or even phrases of combatants, as I have read.Actually can blame you many weaknesses to production: abuse of slowed scenes, history very flat with absolute mastery of (video game) aesthetic on the characters (only the King and the Spartan Queen have some personality), even there will be many who lost interest before both salad of blood and stringing in "the battle of the kebabs" as a friend said.Even so, it is pure entertainment. I liked the use of the descriptions, as if it were accompanied by images of a book. Also the narrative with voiceover, which also provides interesting things. It has humor (derived from the bravado of the Spartans or the surrealist character drag-queen Persian King). And has many notable phrases for the lovers of the harangues of battle type Braveheart or Gladiator: Spartans! Prepare the breakfast and feed you well, because tonight cenaréis in hell!The man is not a being of peace. He has to get it, but not at the expense of their own dignity.</body>
</review>
