<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Psicosis" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is still a master class of cinematic technique, a work in which each level is simply perfect.</summary>
	<body>Hitchcock is, without a doubt, the most plagiarized director in the history of cinema. And all of his films, probably none has been so repeatedly warped and "honored" as psycho (1960), a film that is perfect example of what what are talking about when we say "foundational work". It would be too long to offer here a list of all the movies that have earned it, especially those belonging to the sub-genre slasher, which Hitchcock tape is clear precursor. It is one of two "horror" movies appearing on the sacrosanct list of the 100 best American movies in history, according to the American Film Institute (which injustice), which occupies the 18 box. While time has diminished a little disturbing effect which took in his time, it is still a master class of cinematic technique, a work in which each level is simply perfect.But at that time certainly not him was thus that its production not differed much from any product of series B. In fact, psychosis was filmed in the same studies in which by then was the television series Alfred Hitchcock presents. Its budget was quite moderate, and apparently the only one who believed in the potential of the film was the director himself, who bought the rights to the novel by Robert Bloch (on which is based the script) and even bought all the copies that was able to make so lower the amount of people that knew about the end of the story.Today all we know: in an outburst decided to change once his miserable life, the fatal blonde Marion Crane steals a considerable amount of money to his boss and flees to California, stopping to spend the night in the paragraph motel Bates, where is served by its solitary and seemingly harmless owner, Norman. The rest certainly know, a history of transvestism, complex of Oedipus and mass murder.It is difficult to believe for our time that psychosis caused an impact so great in the public of 1960, but it was, and for many reasons. What sometimes escapes us is that this film was genuinely innovative in many aspects, from silly details (the first film where pulled a toilet chain) to decisions that changed the habits of the audience (was one of the films that broke with the old tradition of "continuing functions", at the request of the own Hitchcock)(, who did not want that people enterase of Janet Leigh, the only star of the cast, died in the first half of the film). But above all, gave to the public then a load of perversity that it wasn't used, an idea of the evil left being cartoonish or supernatural and passed to form part of what is most hidden in man: the unconscious. The Hitchcock film is undoubtedly the first thriller "adult" that inspired the idea of the horror could come from the heart of the American family.During the 109 minutes of psychosis we are constantly experiencing a sense of danger, crouched before waiting for something terrible. When this finally happens, in the already pervasive and hiperparodiada shower scene with no less unforgettable music of Bernard Herrmann, the impact is brutal. But even more dramatic and plot, Excellencies and above the main achievement of the film is having succeeded in establishing an aesthetic and a way of making films that dominates the Hollywood industry until today. Hitchcock, fully aware of the power of the camera man, polishes each sequence to perfection. The scene of the shower, nerve center of the film, is a clear example of that, with the water running in swirling until the drain where escapes the blood (and life) of Marion Crane, until that long zoom-out begins in the eye of the victim and which ends at the pile of forgotten money on the table at nightshowing us that the motive for the crime has not been the pursuit of profit, but the dark passages of madness. It is the irrationality of evil, summarized in the affable and even ridiculous figure of Norman Bates. Old enemies of America are gone, the World War II fascist were dead, and even Russian Communists seemed less dangerous than the horrors that could trigger deep in the heart of the country. If this is not the main theme of all horror movies to come in later decades, someone tell me.But isn't this what most impresses of psychosis. Their audience didn't scared and appalled by his erotic or violent cargo, nor by the sociological connotations of its plot, not even for their excellent performances. If something is left of this masterpiece, it is that film in its pure State. Without any doubt.</body>
</review>
