<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Descubriendo a los Robinsons" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is true that the end works, but the film is not round, because with less travel time and less fantastic worlds could have done just as happy feeling.</summary>
	<body>In American culture, the left is not a social in the European phenomenon. The left is so individualistic, heroíca and promoter of individual effort as the right. The difference between one and another to my seems me facade, nothing more. I don't understand why Tim Robins complains of having given the hand to the Mayor of Madrid. I do not understand what the difference separating them.The American left is Capra, crazy family "Live as you want", families alternative of Katherine Hepburn, as the aunt of Connecticut in "Bringing up baby", the Royal family of the Hepburn, the family of the Focker in "The parents". And the Robinson family. "The American left seems to be let children is no longer the soup without test it, or that practice ballet on the dining room table, while the grandfather try an invention that is useless in the kitchen.""Discovering the Robinson" not so much of the revisitación to a coiled progressive family in the 1930s, as a travel in time to the Charles Dickens and his Christmas Carol, or remastering "Click", or many other time travel. Terminator, the time in their hands, journey into the future, twelve monkeys, the planet of the apes, the machine of the time, Frequency and the sound of Thunder, first. I leave an aside to that surprised me most and less successful was: "The butterfly effect", where each change the protagonist makes in the past leads to a completely unexpected present.Engines of Disney's return, finally, to use the imagination as fuel.But I like his prose, I do not share the enthusiasm of Jordi Costa. Time travel is not a display of imagination, today is a well-trodden path. The collection of quirky characters not looks if they are not part of a gear that faces them and makes out sparks in front of us. Moral choices: looking forward, or live on the rancor, are not vulgar, but they would also fit in a self-help book.It is true that the end works. It will no doubt thrill. Will it make think if happiness is something that one left in some corner of the past or something that one has to Curran is. But the film is not round, because with less travel time and less fantastic worlds could have done just as happy feeling.</body>
</review>
