<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Days of glory" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very entertaining, with a very successful film mixed purely war film, with clear and marked notes socio-political - religious</summary>
	<body>Good French film that tells a true story, perhaps not as recounted the facts, but yes in its essence. I refer to the fact that the names and characters were not perhaps the true (do not know), but which are based on real human beings who lived through the events that we show in this hard war film with clear complaint socio-political. Perhaps tired of the various French Governments deferred financial aid the Muslims veterans who fought for France in World War II, Rachid Bouchareb and producer and co-star of the film, Jamel Debbouze, undertook the work of throwing light on this humiliating and shameful issue.The result is a film very entertaining, with a very successful mixed purely war film, with clear and marked notes socio-political - religious. Well directed, Bouchareb achieved a unified male performance, as evidenced by that at the last Festival of Cannes film, this choral interpretation of the four actors of North African origin to achieve this award.On the technical side, the work is commendable, with a worthy direction of photography, good editing of sound, and a few successful dialogues, credible at all times. Because the script which underpin the tape is brilliant, getting that the film may be of interest at all times.With regard to the action scenes, it must be said have claw and lot of dramatic intensity, although the final fight in the Alsatian people reminded me more of the account which takes place in "Saving private Ryan". Something that is reinforced in the may surplus but no less enlightening epilogue. Surplus because everything was already explained absolutely before, but enlightening because I know how many veterans of former French African colonies who fought for France lived after the war. Hell, abandonment, poverty, the I ninguneo social, he continued, not ended with the completion of the contest.The last minute proves with sadness and shame</body>
</review>
