<review author="JPastor" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Impressive. The fight scenes and the choreography are incredible, and leave the war stories of Troy in almost an anecdote. I saw in original version with subtitles, that help, because they use from time to time something strange grammatical turns...</summary>
	<body>Much told me about the movie 300, and although not me I read the Frank Miller comic - a God in this world - that is inspired, had wanted to see if adaptation is worth. And I already believe that it is worth. The two hours justitas that narrate the history of the battle of the pass of Thermopylae in 480 BC I went in a sigh, and I enjoyed every moment.Ago much who knew Miller was a genius, because among other things was responsible for legendary Marvel as the minisaga scripts?Born again? Daredevil, a classic sure that many comic book fans know, but already not collect, so I lost the track this and other artists of the eighth art. But it is clear that if one vale, okay. Apparently Miller was very over during production - something others pass, see the case of "From Hell" and the crappy movie that came out from a masterful comic - and this has allowed that the film faithfully reflects the greatness of the comic. I would say that it is very likely to exceed even to the graphic novel, because the film is pure plasticity in movement.Digital each frame shows impossible environments and scenarios, but do it in a way that is strikingly akin to the story. A history that is certainly some freedoms on what happened in reality - simply epic. Actors embroider. All of them from Gerard Butler - a spectacular Leonids - to Lena Heady, that as in other movies, is as a cheese in addition to do well.The fight scenes and the choreography are amazing, and dejan war stories of Troy in almost an anecdote, and the script – which is all in a film - does more than help. I saw in original version - with subtitles, that help because when in when they use grammatical turns something outsiders--and that because it is the lemon pear.Do do Imprescindible.PD: good Netámbulo has already made its own assessment of some scenes? suspiciously julais? does the movie, but the aspects less serious (as of the patronage of Suchard, tiny chocolate bars which had the Spartans by abdominal) he speaks now:-) PD 2: recently left meneada a column of Pérez-Reverte in which the always witty writer spoke of?The other 300 &#8242;, the almogáraves, who were also from here you hope. But as says Arturito, as we are in Spain, national does not sell, and they have been practically forgotten.</body>
</review>
