<review author="Alex Largo" title="El velo pintado" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A different movie, discover their virtues (which for some may be defects), well shot, well directed, with good performances, with a solid script and it stands out by its own merit in the technical section. The painted veil is a film for a select audience.</summary>
	<body>Unnoticed that this film is being is curious. At first I thought that it was because the film was somewhat bland, but after seeing her, I can say emphatically, no. The film is a drama, not a melodrama. And it is something that is appreciated. You could say that "The painted veil" is a film of love, but we would be lying. The film is not a love story. It's about the clash of two people married and totally different to that from one day to another they are in Shanghai. You could say that it is a film for a select audience. It is not a commercial film, certainly is. not be what it is. But it is not a film for everyone. That requires a minimum capacity of reason, a bit of interest, and some patience. And this is something we enjoy a small part of the world's population.The unknown (or at least my) John Curran, delights us with an address expléndida in an expléndida film. More admirable is the pace given by the director to the film. Without haste, because it is a film that takes time, but that at no time is long or tedious. In addition, Curran, uses small clashes between the protagonists (or what is the same, edges comments) so that the movie is not boring. And you have to say that it does, as do the movie won't be as cold and becomes more enjoyable.The (to anyone unknown) main actors, Edward Norton and Naomi Watts, do a brilliant job. Without shrillness, without sobreactuaciones. simply perfect. Both (producers of the Film) make a work that (inexplicably) not them to awarded prizes of renown (although to Norton if it has nominated you a couple of awards).The script is strong, without holes, without loose. Very well built. The script makers can be proud. Other highlights in the film are wonderful photography and the magnificent soundtrack by Alexandre Desplat, which cost him a well-deserved Golden Globe for the overall best band Sonora.En, a different film, who knows their virtues (which for some may be defects), well shot, well directed, with good performances, with a solid (and especially good) script and that stands out thanks to its own in the technical section.</body>
</review>
