<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Ciudad del silencio" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Monumental hodgepodge. Comparable only to the pain of the argument presented to us. So, crappy infumable and shame for their ideadores, who have failed (at any time) to live up to the occasion. The issue is serious enough to not stay in these half-measures.</summary>
	<body>Acaramelados as some were with the J - as of the glamor and the insured ass in not is how many dollars, this version of the Lopez promised collapse or genius, nothing of neutral media terms. And look at where the bet frog that has come. Do not look for Prince. Bordertown is a poor product of Gregory Nava, director bragado in television (American family or American tapestry) or in the biographical film without excessive artistic pretensions (Selena, with a ten years younger than Jennifer Lopez). Here he has been around long. It has not been able with a very interesting argument: the murder of women in Juarez and the apathy of the Government and their police bodies to tackle this Muskat. Barely saved by the excellent photography of the night Juárez, with his dirt, its urban deterioration and its criminal neon, Bordertown undertake with apathy the denunciation of an excessive barbarism has no (in the film) feet or head. Finished not know what are the crimes, although us of a mild smell where can come shots, and not precisely thanks to the efforts of a plain cast at all times. Antonio Banderas (with a ridiculous role) or Jennifer Lopez (as reporter coming Chicago with hazy past and desire to escalafonar in his career with a story of flashy) consent that we can add one point of interest.If someone wants information about the events in Ciudad Juárez, not search here. Wait: there is just a project of greater height. This is a telefilm to see in a private fashion when it comes to coffee, pastries and brasero creating that sense of home beautiful and that everyone loves so much. The problem (there are) is that the Mexican people victim of this small genocide would have deserved a better film. And they have not.</body>
</review>
