<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="El buen alemán" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Anyway, isn't that any last film is better, but at least leave them where are without cross-dressing under the thin veil of postmodern. We will always be the original.</summary>
	<body>It does not require much cunning or movie buff love recognize the good German as tribute to those films that beyond by the 1940s and 1950s (especially of the Warner), a rigorous black and white, with easily recognizable characters and music, they portrayed the difficult of its tormented protagonists loves under the backdrop of the second world warwithout diminishing among so much tragedy a melancholic and romantic look on the impossible love. Insurance Soderbergh enjoyed these films when young he was smiling in the darkness of a theater in his hometown Atlanta. It is not surprising that himself is the director of photography for many of his films.Since the beginning of the good German, when we see how the format of the huge screen is revealed as the unusual and square 1.33:1 (after the closing credits widens slightly, to a 1. 66: 1, approaching a little more our usual panoramic), and the color of the frames takes the documentary texture of a black and white lit the old-fashionedWe know that it is more than insurance Soderbergh aims to restore us to then, as if to this we recorriéramos with him that movie fan memory that one day (and today) was thrilled: the romanticism of Casablanca, the sewerage systems of the third man, the German capital destroyed by the bombings of Berlin West, the Dietrich shaming the Knights (when not to the ladies). All the frames in the good German are elected, framed and photographed for this purpose, as if an enthusiastic lover of the works of Velázquez had mixed (not without intelligence or passion) the surrender of Breda, the forge of Vulcan and the waterseller of Seville, paying this an intended homage to the master. As you can imagine, the resulting work as well as almost impossible a priori seems a collage without its own entity rather than a painting. This is the problem of the good German. His passionate formalism becomes cold the proposal, deleting the whole soul and depth Yes possessed their referents. In fact, could almost say that a yincana of moviegoers winks that us back to the beauty that do provide Tourneur, Wilder, Curtiz or Reed.En films is not substantially a film, but rather all scenes of the good German there is a rift that grates on the analytical rather than the creative. His characters are emerging acartonados, despite the strength of the character of Maguire or the always disturbing and magical presence of Blanchett. Clooney is not adapted to the sizing (both physical and psychological) of his character. Photography tries to emulate the expressionism of their original referents, but sometimes sobreimpresiona light, or flattens her without giving the scene of emotion. Note in excess will imitate, forgetting that a film is doing just that.Also happens with the narration, linked too much to the previous scripts. This hidden husband in the sewers recalls! to the Laszlo in Casablanca, but the Soderbergh Ilsa is less prim and more stormy (to the Dietrich) than the Curtiz. But the height of the emulator effort it is overflowing with the final scene. If at least Soderbergh had taken the Russian General Sikorsky as the endearing prefect of police Louis Renault in Casablanca, perhaps the tone affected the film had won in sense of humor and irony. But, all in the good German lacks the tyrannical rigidity of the geek.The good German marks the only mission to dust off our cinematographic memory, encouraging us to return to enjoy these delights of post-war which survives much of the current film, created mostly by European filmmakers who had fled from one of the two wars. In addition, another suggestion that feeds (although not many proteins) is the image of Berlin as a source of inspiration for many other films, distant in time (one, two, three, Germany, year zero) and not so much (Cabaret, Himmel über Berlin, Good bye Lenin!, the life of the other, Berlin blues, Berlin is in Germany).That said, the good German is more a document that pays homage to the film to a film about the gender of mimics. It is no good that Soderbergh used wireless giraffe instead of microphones, incandescent lights and fixed focal length lenses. This fact only underlines the impression of having more well attended Museum representation on the cinema of those times. But I fear that it is not enough to make us believe that she herself is a film. Fetish formalism of Soderbergh connects with other proposals of the current film, bent on repeating or recreate master formulas already shot and unnecessarily reproducible. In my memory is the monstrosity that tries to revive Gus Van Sant with his psychosis. Or the crematística fans of American cinema by the remake of successful European and Oriental films. Even the excellent Scorsese infiltrators rebuilds from its antecedent Hong Kong Infernal Affairs. However, rather than a nod or remake Soderbergh is a Faustian Frankenstein remendado filmic essences that isolated they exude beauty, but that malpegadas smell weird.Anyway, isn't that any last film is better, but at least leave them where are without cross-dressing under the thin veil of postmodern.</body>
</review>
