<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El último rey de Escocia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Whitaker gets to join in interpretation varied traits of the personality of the former Ugandan President: at times, naive and childish, though, in the background, a terrifying sadistic.</summary>
	<body>What are the ingredients of this alluring potion with which some leaders sprayed its population by immersing it in a sense of blind ISM? Do perhaps a mixture of charisma, false empathy conciudadana and dose of populism in bulk? I do not know but all the leaders autoerigidos in salvapatrias have been able to play perfectly with all of them.Idi Amin, President of Uganda from 1971 to 1979, is portrayed with these traits in the last King of Scotland, tape directed by Kevin Macdonald in which overhangs, others of his virtues, the excellent interpretation of the always splendid Forest Whitaker. As in other African regimes, are witnessing the Ascension of the President between an overwhelming popular acclaim. There no matter that the leader becomes charged with using weapons; in fact, it is common currency in these countries where the word democracy only serves as slogan. Once settled in power, these characters of zero qualifications (supposedly, Amin was illiterate) are seen as the magic solution to all the ills of the country. But as the illusion of his short-lived, soon will begin to emerge the darker back of any dictatorship.In addition to the face of the Amin coleguilla and Nice, the last King of Scotland shows quite another through the eyes of a young Scottish doctor chosen by one for personal care and his vast offspring. And Whitaker, with the characteristic perfection in it, get together in its interpretation varied traits of the personality of the former Ugandan President: at times, naive and childish, but, ultimately, a sadistic frightening that, under its mandate became more autoritorio and less productive, was empowered by a paranoid fear to an attempt on his life. And we know that, in brains of limited neuronal capacity, violence tends to be the common response to any threat. So, at the end of their bloody term, historians put the number of Ugandans passed to knife by the regime of the former boxing champion at 300,000.Although some of the elements of its plot sound topics and not finish function (the possible incestuous relationship between Dr. Nicholas - James McAvoy - and Sarah Merrit - Gillian Anderson - seems closed false), the tape offers a remarkable portrait on the strange power of seduction that these leaders advenidos as a universal antidote exerted on people, whether more or less legal. And step, with the last King of Scotland, the film returns to help expose another of so many acts of genocide committed in Africa while we looked for another side in the West with his testimony.</body>
</review>
