<review author="Caruco" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Between the socarronería and the black humor, this Miss Sunshine has a really bright start to lose much of its bellows to half an hour. An irregularity and a slump that no dates until the final sequences.</summary>
	<body>Perhaps it is not in the land of opportunity? And the success and beauty isn't the great ambition? So is the youngest of seven years Olive (Abigail Breslin), whose dream is to the win one of the many beauty contests which are organised to the length and breadth of the United States.UU. She is nice, not lacking in attractive, but rather plump and, physically, the lot. And in its goal, it will drag his entire varied family.Do do climbing the rickety van yellow Wolkswagen, no less apedazada Hoover family emprendrerá a peculiar journey which, as in any? road movie? who boasts, will be also initiation, of self-discovery of each and end of trip for any other.But you can expect with the crew to a grandfather who sniffed cocaine (in the face of the veteran and tanning Alan Arkin), a father who hides his mediocrity and failure giving lessons on how to succeed in life (Greg Kinnear); a gay guy who has tried to sucidarse because of a love failure (Steve Carell); a teenage brother who refuses to talk (Paul Dano), and a mother who is not obliged to put some sesantez in a family so bundled (Toni Collette).Towing them to California to discover the value of be yourself and know to be attached to your closest beings in a not always easy coexistence.And, by the way, tell a story of losers, even long before reaching maturity, as the brother of 15 years who has done? vow of silence? and you want to join the forces of aviation; or reel the same Olive.Hasta off, completed the pilgrimage, a criticism of beauty contests and the American dream, ridiculed in that scene, which is worth the entire film, of the final performance of the small Olive to a shocked audience. All a provocation which however makes clear how they teach and used from earliest childhood, the cult of the body and superficiliad models.Speeches, on the other hand, not especially innovative, or culminados in a particularly risky manner, but that gives us moments and phrases anthologies as grandfather Hoover to Olive's: "A loser is someone who is so afraid of winning of truth that not even try."Between the socarronería and the humor black, this Miss Sunshine and the strange family has a really bright start to lose much of its bellows to half an hour. An irregularity and a slump that no dates until the final sequences.But a comedy, at the end and after, peculiar directed by the (seems that) well avenido marriage composed by Jonathan Dayton and Valerie Faris, and which not only became the surprise of the Oscar, but also in the American independent production of last season, harvesting also millions of supporters.</body>
</review>
