<review author="Robgordon" title="Psicosis" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It was without any doubt a turning point in the career of the director, a shift needed to adapt to the new cinema that was gradually being implemented</summary>
	<body>In 1960, no one expected that Hitchcock would make a movie like "Psycho". Orondo British director wore during more than 20 years at the top of the world cinema with its elegant suspense, their persecutory plots and a very personal film with a clear Basic constants in each tape ran.Just prior to that year, Hitchcock was at its stage more mature and brilliant. He had just directed masterpieces like "Rear window", "Vertigo" or "death on the heels", in which both Paramount and MGM, had provided Hitchcock high budgets in order to satisfy your requests, i.e., the presence of actors of the stature of James Stewart, Cary Grant, Grace Kelly, James Mason, Kim Novak or Eva Marie Saint, precisely favorite actors of the director, or to be able to shoot in the best locations and with the best technique.(Moon would get an overwhelming dominance of color and handling of the camera in these three works, there is more to see the high investment made Paramount for the scene of the Bell Tower of "Vertigo")For all these reasons was surprised that Hitchcock was set in a small mystery novel, written by Robert Bloch, to make it his next film. Hitchcock, also decided that "Psycho" should be in black and white, without dazzling stars, with purely television technical teams. "Drastic changes were a priori not too covered by the producer and the environment of Hitch, but subsequently were confirmed as suitable, for a history of similar characteristics.""Psycho" would have been perfectly a chapter extended series "Alfred Hitchcock presents" great success at the time, though Hitchcock saw something more in it, he saw a terrifying story that could be used to unleash a new cinematographic vision. Because "Psycho" is nothing to everything that Hitchcock had filmed. If in his entire career, English was a lover of the suggestion, here chose to show, if you like select, luxury, here chose the austere and with all this, Hitchcock managed to establish a new model of horror film, a movie would be the mother of the well-known "psycho-killer" or cinema of assassins in series, as well as a way of filming radically novel that increased anxiety or terror of the public. "It could be argued, that would not exist"Henry, portrait of a killer","The silence of the lambs"or"Boston strangler", as well as all subsequent horror film if Hitchcock had not done so"psicosis".""Psycho" told the story of a woman (Janet star) who stole a high amount of money to his own company with the intention of being able to start a new life with her boyfriend (John Gavin). In his escape, he would stop to rest in a lost Highway motel run by a mysterious mother and her son (Anthony Perkins). The arrival at the motel precipitating some macabre facts, tragic consequences for the thief.Hitchcock was right in full in each of the decisions of the film. Black and white gave an additional who venia horror movie as ring to the finger to get the lugubridad Motel and the Bates House, or the facility in order to be explicit to show blood. The choice of actors was impeccable. A semidesconocido Anthony Perkins wrote a memorable murderer, shy and with complex edípico. Janet Leigh made his debut as "Hitchcock blonde". The director was right to think that she when was the actress more famous cast, his hasty death on the tape would be that staff descolocase. On the side, Martin Balsam, John Gavin and Vera Miles were suitable for their respective roles.Once again, Hitchcock used his famous technique of the Mcguffin, giving primary importance to the robbery carried out by Marion Crane (Janet Leigh) to suddenly shift the story was really interesting, the Bates motel and its occupants.Hitchcock got the fear in his body to the staff, who believed that it was before a new persecution film by the director, and he suddenly found with an explicit murder and a surprising killer.The shower scene was the logical impact on the Viewer, that still retains fresh today, reviewing the tape. Three keys of the excellent performance of this sequence, which have established it as the sequence were most popular in the history of cinema, as the cry more famous.On the one hand, the music of strings of Bernard Herrmann, the musical standard of Hitchcock and responsible for the greatest impact of many of the works of the English teacher. Initially, the scene of the murder in the shower wouldn't have more sound than the knife and the cry of the Crane, while listening to Hitchcock that Herrmann had composed gave more than the approval to the use of this music in the scene, on the other hand is Saul Bass, creator of the titles of "Vertigo" and "death on the heels" and who designed, hand in hand with Hitchcock and plane to plane the mythical stream of the shower. Finally, George Tomasini, habitual editor of Hitch, ride the difficult sequence perfectly.Great planning the sequence to complete already would if same famous "Psycho", but there were many more findings in the tape as to be displaced by the fame of this unique scene. No less brilliant and scary is for my the murder of detective Milton Arbogast (Martin Balsam). Displaying, Hitchcock by his handling of suspense during the undue entry of the detective in the Bates House, director finished off the scene with a plane in chopped of his murder at the hands of Mrs Bates, who sincerely put the willies."As I am well your writer, Joseph Stefano,"Psychosis"is important because lacks it predictability in Hitchcock until such a time." "Psycho" was unexpected, nobody thought that a director so elegant would show us for the first time in film lavatory, a corpse, nudity in a shower and above all a very clear coldness in the protagonists in the macabre, the sexual, the forbidden. It was without any doubt a turning point in the career of the director, a necessary shift to adapt to the new cinema that was gradually being implemented. And again, Hitchcock ahead.</body>
</review>
