<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The overall tone of the film is solid, robust, with that personal touch that only manages to British cinema, that often seems at time but develop in our days.</summary>
	<body>Richard Eyre is a filmmaker with a relatively short career, that has developed almost always on television; comes from stage direction, and this is evident when it comes to bring to the screen a film like this; not understood this as a defect, but as a mere evidence. His film, is therefore made, as said Vicente Aranda, "with actors and walls"; There is no place for action, adventures or special effects, but only (do almost nothing?) to faces of actors playing their characters. It is therefore fundamental in his film actors are first line, and in this case not you complain: Judi Dench is one of the great ladies of the theatre and English, splendid cinema also making Queen Elizabeth II or M, the head of the British secret service in the 007 series. Cate Blanchett, for its part, is one of the most brilliant actresses of his generation, which now frisa forties, a woman of rare Nordic beauty earned him even to interpret the role of Queen Elf in "The Lord of the rings" saga. "Diary of a scandal" crosses several bridges, with themes as glassy as the love between an adult (the character of Blanchett) and a minor and unpremeditated lesbian attraction that carries the young new teacher who plays Cate on the elderly teacher that composes Dench. Clear that the real subject of the film, on a stage with so many figurative quicksand, is the cloth of spider that weaves the elderly teacher on the incauta newly arrival, narrated in first person by the also metaphorical Weaver of this fabric. It is true that there is a true, diffuse touch homophobic in the portrait of this old lesbian that truffle its seductive strategy with the kind chicanery of friendship between the young and inexperienced and more mature and so wise; Despite this, there is no express pejorative tone about the homophile love today be meaningless. Dense drama with some percutantes scenes (the meeting where Dench calls on the adulteress Blanchett to abandon their paidófila relationship, finding thereby that the is "about to candy" for their intentions; the outbreak of the marriage crisis of the young teacher), the overall tone of the film is solid, robust, with that personal touch that manages only to British cinemathat often seems to time although develop today, perhaps because stage powerfully reminiscent of the Victorian stage that familiar it is thanks to the numerous television serials with the characteristic hallmark of the BBC.</body>
</review>
