<review author="Robgordon" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A proposal of quality that surpasses the plot handicap that get close it to the tone of telefilm, thanks to performances delivered, the brilliant music of Glass and the correct realization of Eyre.</summary>
	<body>If we look at the career of the director of "Diary of a scandal", Richard Eyre, we find, between not too many films, the 2001 film, entitled "Iris" and with which not a few things it shares the tape before us. Addressed both British soberly and without too much fanfare, both "diary of a scandal" as previously "Iris", notable mainly for a couple of reasons; their excellent and dramatic female performances and his inspired soundtrack.Although "Iris" gave an Oscar for Best Supporting Actor for Jim Broadbent, the tape gave us colossal roles of two English actresses of different epochs, Judi Dench and Kate Winslet. Now, "Diary of a scandal" faces in a duel with capital letters, the Australian Cate Blanchett (one of the actresses of the moment, for its abundant and successful roles) and back to a immeasurable Judi Dench. "Two generations of actresses in State of grace.""Diary of a scandal" has also the minimalist, Phillip Glass front of its soundtrack, which comprised here one of his best works, which can remind one of his last and most inspired works to date, Stephen Daldry's "the hours". "In the same way, the more intimate James Horner, made one of the best compositions of his uneven career, for the short movie of Richard Eyre, wrapping with his music the drama which required"iris".""Diary of a scandal" (perfect title), tells the story of Sheba Hart (Blanchett) a newcomer to a school teacher, and that it will maintain a relationship with one of his pupils, something of what Barbara Covett (Dench), a lesbian teacher who knows the secret, will be taken in their own emotional benefit.Patrick Marber, the playwright and screenwriter of "Closer", uncomfortable work about human relationships, here is responsible for adapting the original novel of Zo &#1105; Heller, printing history with a look widely critical, dry and detestable did the educational system, intimate relations between teachers and the lives of the protagonists, and all this, makes it through the first person narrative that carries out the character of Dame Judi Denchan old and irritable teacher carcomida his solitude and his hidden lesbianism, with symptoms of mental disorder.The British actress is the main protagonist of the event, both physically and emotionally. His reflections, his notes of a newspaper and the evolution of its "forced" relationship with Blanchett are which directed the course of this interesting proposal, close to the reality of schools, taboos and complexes of non-recognized sexual conditions, loneliness, unhappiness in the couple, the temptations and low and despicable human behaviours. The burial of a richly framed photo of a cat (only sincere partner of the character of Dench) and a newspaper are established as metaphors for this story of unspeakable desires steeped in morality. A proposal of quality that surpasses the plot handicap that get close it to the tone of telefilm, thanks to performances delivered, the brilliant music of Glass and the correct implementation of Eyre.En its final part, we find, however a plane heading did a few paths very different to that we have witnessed over the footage. "And is to close the history with a return to start by the character of Dench, is something that can do harm to the whole of the tape, and that closer to a killer tape in series, a history of madness and emotional needs that have emerged with the irrumpción of the beautiful Blanchett in a new school and the lives of those around her.""Diary of a scandal" managed four fair and well deserved nominations for an Oscar, Phillip Glass, Judi Dench, Cate Blanchett and Patrick Marber, which are, together with the director of the event, the great architects of the success of this film of undeniable British phlegm.</body>
</review>
