<review author="Alex Largo" title="La Caja Kovak" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Even with all the drawbacks which I have brought to the script and others, I can say that it is a good movie. We can be proud that it is above Spanish.</summary>
	<body>A very accurate, entertaining, good, film and non-event. These are the characteristics of this film. Very correct (okay well directed, recorded with some good performances), entertaining (it is a thriller film, and fulfils its task without bore us in no time), good (is a good film, which together like a lot), and 75th (American, Chinese or Spanish, is non-event and lose the memory of people before year's end (if not already done)).Responsible for (and do not say this as something negative) the film is Daniel Monzón, before putting this film, endorsed the critic. His best-known project is "The biggest robbery never told". I have not seen the movie, but he certainly enjoys the sympathy of many people.As for the movie before us, as well. I, of course, have not given by lost the afternoon. In general terms, the film is "intelligent". But as of usual in this kind of films, "enjoying" a couple of moments that should have fallen, not in the editing room, but in the first rewrite of the screenplay. And it is where all the elements of the film are supported in the script. Which has its shortcomings, their holes (or its gaps) and their slips. In general it is a good script, but it suffers from a few (say a couple as I say a dozen) of moments that do not contribute anything to the story and makes above do not we take it seriously. For example, the time on the plane, when the protagonist sees that sort of bug bloodied or whatever is on the computer. Tell me: adds something to the story? do you have any sense? It establishes connection with some subsequent event? NO. Those who have seen the movie know what I am talking about.It is a real shame that the script has many inconsistencies and moments that have gotten them shoehorn.With regard to the work of monsoon after the cameras we could say that it is good. But we would be unfair. The direction of monsoon has many ups and downs. There are moments in which man is seen enthusiasm and desire, are moments with an outstanding address. But when it comes to a moment that doesn't interest you too. just the opposite. But in general, as I have already said, good.With regard to the work of the actors. Correct. Only, exclusively. Hutton, in the title role. well, very bland. But correct. Lucía Jiménez, very correct, but on occasions, perhaps sobreactúa a little. The only really undertake its work more than, is David Kelly, in the role of the evil Kovak. And it is that every time that it appears on screen, actor, leave to others, to the ground.Another noteworthy aspect of the film is its superb soundtrack. Signed by the increasingly more international Roque Baños. even with all the drawbacks which I have brought to the script and others, I can say that is a good movie. We can be proud that it is above Spanish.</body>
</review>
