<review author="Florinda Chic" title="La flauta mágica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although I admire the audacity of Branagh, able to dare shamelessly none with any classic put him ahead, the marriage between Opera and film is complicated and this movie is tedious.</summary>
	<body>Does it goes without saying that although I have seen several operas, I am not the fan number one of Teresa Berganza, that I know all the lyrics from?A Penguin in my elevator? and none of the arias of Cosí fan tutte. Although I'm not profane in the subject, I knew a girl who spent years thinking that Pavarotti was called Tutto.Hecha this confession, I can say that the magic flute, the Mozart's most celebrated opera film adaptation, I bored nauseam. The marriage between Opera and film is complicated and this movie is tedious. Although the precedent of the director is the very upper Hamlet, which lasted almost four hours in this film they are almost reached the three-hour and trance, is far from smoothly.The main problem that you saw was the cast. Not all performers of Opera are great actors, with honorable exceptions like the Othello of Plácido Domingo. This fact, happens perhaps unnoticed in the stalls of a theatre - if seat is of the cheap, of low visibility--but in the foreground there who resist. The singers made a series of gestures and grimaces that seem more merluzos soldiers of the Mundial.Otro war first failure is that the original story - rather tontorrona in my humble opinion, although God free me criticizing Mozart - is not carried with no pace and only wakes up from the torpor at specific moments such as the duo of Papageno and Papagena and the aria of the Queen of the night. Scenarios that place the action in the first world war are theatrical and more relamido what does not help to maintain interest and visually appalling on screen.Although I admire the audacity of Branagh, able to dare shamelessly none with any classic put him ahead, knowing that fans of the original will stoned. They are his adaptations of Shakespeare, Shelley's Frankenstein or in this case, the sobrepedante, sleeping and megalomaniacal flute.</body>
</review>
