<review author="Nüx" title="300" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Shocking, stunning, stunning...300 is an undisputed technical quality and a perfect commercial product, so entertaining as shocking. Little more can be asked to a film.</summary>
	<body>I was very glad the news that a film about the battle of Thermopylae was being filmed. The worst, was me I afraid sincerely. I thought that the story is not only inventarían but it would also be a unbearable suckling pig. He was partly right, because it has been very little true to historical facts, but on the other hand, it has been entretenidísima. In addition, it should not be forgotten that it is the adaptation of a comic book, not a film to take as a direct source contemporary texts to the batalla.300 is a formidable film in almost every way. Visually it is a prodigious work, not running achicada this account not even taking into account the (ab) use has been made of the slow, because it reaches form an essential part of the photo set that allows you to highlight a specific image that otherwise we would go unnoticed, to merit this be well appreciated for its beauty, either by its plot significance.The plot has a rhythm that does not give truce at any time to the Viewer, forcing him to remain in tension throughout the film, without giving room to boredom, on the contrary that, unfortunately, often occurs in films of this nature. 300 is a tribute to the values of Spartan, reflecting them, as well as Customs (exhaustive selection of the race)(, fairly equal consideration of women, etc.), luckily, more faithfully than I expected. The Spartans have always struck me an exemplary people. I have them in a consideration of quite different from those that calling southern Lebanon of savages. But if even Plato praised the Spartan values and compared them, maudlin and embarrassed, that Athens autodestruída by its decadent democracy!Value, delivery, and the Spartiates self-esteem contrasts completely with the values promulgated by Xerxes, King of the Persians. Slave treatment of the Persian commanders exercised over his soldiers, contrary to the equal treatment which exercised the Spartans, is absolutely true so I consider bland in this regard protests arrived from the Near East. In addition, what will he be an Iraqi or Iranian with a Persian?! What will he be fanatical monotheism with polytheism Persian?! you what you have to see a prosperous, conqueror and flourishing town with one that plunge into poverty due mainly to its internal wars?! In the end. It is as if we tried compare (as it has been claimed by some sectors) the Spartans with the Americans. Sometimes, comparisons, are more than odious, quite ridiculous.Turning again to film strictly terms, point out the photographic atmosphere, clearly inspired by the comic; to those who you read, sure that this appreciation is you has not gone unnoticed. Tones, lights, the photographic set itself, even the narrative pace and intercalated simultaneously to the main action scenes of the city of Sparta, all evokes somehow he aesthetic of the comic that gave rise to the film.In short, 300 is an undisputed technical quality and a perfect commercial product, as entertaining as shocking. Little more can be asked to a film.</body>
</review>
