<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El ejército de las tinieblas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Terror of serie B, with a lot of humor, which is essential viewing. You have no excuse, it is short, vibrant, hilarious and mythical. To see with psychotropic substances accompanied by colleagues, be able to be.</summary>
	<body>Only is 92 this film? I thought he was older, perhaps by the amount of times that I've seen. I remember the first time (that I saw, not the other, that you are obsessed with the defollar and the demeterysacar) left me amazed completely, and even outraged by did not understand what they had just seen. With the passing of the years and the screenings, I noticed account I have to see her every year in order to reset the brain and see that we do not need hiperproducciones to have a great time.The film is of a type that works in a giant hardware store, until a series of avatars of fate (not to miss the cangrenada hand) appears in the past, specifically in the middle ages. It is that his arrival, accompanied by a car, a chainsaw and a trimmed, coincides with a prophecy. So have to retrieve the book of the dead (called Necronomicon) so the wise can send you back to their world. But it does not of another good and awakens the army of darkness.My mother, that film. If you see with serious metalidad, you'll see a shit that you're going to want to cut the veins with a spoon of coffee, to suffer more. But if you see knowing that this is a mixture of cheap horror movies, crappy special effects and unbridled humor, you're going to have a good time and you will want to have this wonder in your deuvedeteca as a server has. The special effects are pretty crappy mostly, except the skeletons that are not bad. Situations are hilarious, and cause more than one laugh. But what I liked most of the film is how quickly that goes. I.e. 82 minutes in which spend more than the 12 extended hours of the orcs and hobbits (mother what I have just said).In short, terror of serie B, with a lot of humor, which is essential viewing. You have no excuse, it is short, vibrant, hilarious and mythical. To see with psychotropic substances accompanied by colleagues, be able to be.Great. Besitos. p. D: there very large scenes, such as the cangrenada hand, when she breaks the mirror when we look at the shoulder, the flying monster that competes with the special effects of Ed Wood, etc.</body>
</review>
