<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Trastorno" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unnecessary, for repeated by trivial, by predictable disorder won't to any history of the cinema, or general or intimate so it will be payment of video store in neighborhood, of those which to me I love, for enjoyment when there is nothing, absolutely nothing to do...</summary>
	<body>Reventona topics, pregnant of clichés, never better said then the movie goes psychedelic pregnancies and maternal wickedness high the paroxysm and madness, disorder establishes a short dialogue with the Viewer, is always ahead and know, at all times, the byways wherever it goes to the plot and the way in which the director desembrolla for thatin the end, everything is nice and exit one of the film with the face of having had a good time. And it is not that this is bad sentence. It could have been worse, of course. There is a decent roster of actresses that her here pifian with high note. Ingrid Rubio not strain as homicidal manic and Najwa Nimri is as ida, disregarding all rigor in the characterization of a character who could have given more than it... His history of interchangeable pregnancies is almost never credible. And the script, fear be excessively heavy but think attend me all the reasons in the world, is the fundamental pillar of a filmmaker when not is a genius (there you have been and have waived sovereign of a plot to make imperishable products: put the reader names.) (I give to Kubrick to Eisenstein, to Tarkosvky, to mention distant cases in models and cultures).It is inevitable to bring to memory the hand that rocks the cradle because the arguments are based on similar budgets, but Curtis Hanson, not being or much less master tape convinces by the sobriety of the actors and the slow and almost artisan concatenation of events that are leading the Viewer to the final outcome.Disorder malea well early: undoes any possibility of interest when the narrative conventions occur without any shame. The plentiful cliches of the tape gives rise to boredom because, as usual, this is the film that, without seeing her, we have already seen many times. It has echoes of what happened to Baby Jane (especially in the final stretch) and this forgivable mediocrity of chapter of well-made telenovela (that suppose you have) by what disorder has its audience, but is not a movie buff, who like to be surprised and public which has already seen both movies that you see them come even with the covered eyes. Lacking inspiration, burdened by a simple script, the film contributes the scarce titles creative our film in the thriller, although we are already taking flight with directors as solvents such as Enrique Urbizu, Jaume Balagueró and Paco Plaza.</body>
</review>
