<review author="Alex Largo" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Overall the film is excellent. In all cases. The direction, the soundtrack, the actors, the production design... All. We can blame you the tape only some other hole (actually there is only one, but it is a gap).</summary>
	<body>Not liked anything what director Alfonso Cuarón did with the third novel in the Harry Potter series. This is my fine way of saying that not him I forgave the mess, the attack, the maiming of "Harry Potter and the prisoner of Azkaban". What is more, when I left the room I said to myself. "I will not watch one movie of this man". But of course, "do not say this water will not drink". So, encouraged by the critical acclaim that had made the tape, and the poor acceptance of the American public. I said: "because it has to be well." "I spend a day and her rent". And that is what I did.I got the disc into the DVD reader. I sat down. I waited that pass through the announcement of "LA PIRATERIÍA is A crime". I gave "Languages". I gave to "English". I gave "Subtitles". I gave "Spanish". And then. I did. I gave him to "Film". We say that (catch-up, since that is always the family asks that you "and that cloud of what?" and other eloquent questions that they leave the soul to some people) occurred. Only that. It passed before my eyes. When started (accompanied by the question of my companion "then go end shit, not can finish there.") ("Second party huh?") credits I could not feel more satisfied. And it is that the film is worth the trouble.Overall the film is excellent. In all cases. The direction, the soundtrack, the actors, the production design. All. We can blame you the tape only some other hole (actually there is only one, but it is a gap). Though don't know if these errors come from the novel on which it is based (if so should be having remedied) or are adaptation (an unforgivable error). And it is that the only thing that it lacks the script. Why? For what?. In no time, Cuarón (architect of the script) are worthy to answer these two questions. It is not that they are very necessary, but your response is missing. But we know that this man, what brings you to give explanations without care. Something that left us very clearly in the third part of "Harry Potter". And that is something I hate. You can not you just tell a thing without saying the why, you have to give the reasons why your story is as it is, and occurs as it does. Still, Cuarón complies to charm his work of director. A compliment that I never imagined I would say. What actors are concerned, they all meet their work more than, and more than one, you have fallen one or two awards. Include Clive Owen, which is sometimes somewhat deadpan, but gives us in a few moments a brilliant performance; Michael Caine, who gives us the best character of the tape and that unfairly not has been rewarded his work with any prize.Other highlights are the magnificent band Sonora of John Travener and photography, which has several awards, although the Oscar slipped from her hands. The film is shot in documentary form, as if the camera outside a journalist that records everything (even you jump blood to the camera). In general: a film to enjoy and to think. With some excellent parts, a production design breathtaking. The film is quite good, and enjoys an incredible moment more than one (and more than two, and more than three.) so that the GLUGs tears skip you.Also we must recognize him to the film the very successful critique of society, and it is that there are many parallels between that reality (for some strange reason we think something distant) and ours. A faithful portrait of the world of as it is today. What is more, almost a rebuke. That never comes over.</body>
</review>
