<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A remarkable story about the bitterness of enforced solitude, an interesting confrontation? rich in nuances? between two types of morality and a curious point of view on the relations understood as an object coveted by ende and precise, to fill the emotional void.</summary>
	<body>The inflexible Professor Barbara Covett (an exceptional Judi Dench) portrays herself when the film opens with one of their terrible dimensions in his diary of summary judgments about all the notes. While adolescents entering classes look with disdain, his severe voiceover, disseminated by the footage, says as customary is now requisition melee weapons or cocaine among students, when a few years ago to the more it came was a cigarette or a few pornographic magazines. "And that call you evolution", remacha the sarcastic voice of the teacher back everything that forecast for the future of their students, a black picture of oscillating between unemployment and terrorism.His solitary life has become a rancor and bitterness to give rein when, pen in hand, lifts Act of the mediocrity of the outside lives. But his chance to get out of its isolation will come with the incorporation of Sheba Hart (great Cate Blanchett) to the Faculty of its conservative Center. She, and the breath of fresh air that seems to represent, will pass through the relentless filter of Barbara. She is described as a bourgeois of easy life, moral led and writes franca about her private life.Nevertheless, the transparent Sheba will come to Captivate Barbara. Little by little, teaching veteran will be in his innocent pupil an opportunity to leave his social seclusion, find a confidant that, with time and his business dealings, can attract up to the fold of a relationship deeper than mere friendship. At this point in the footage, the character of Barbara becomes increasingly more depressingly manipulator to the point of bringing closer to the tape (a slip that of having consummated, would have subtracted credibility to the story) to the lands of the psicothriller.Do do with these mimbres, diary of a scandal, an adaptation of the popular novel by Zoë Heller written by Patrick Marber (Closer), offers an outstanding story on the bitterness of the forced solitude, an interesting confrontation? rich in nuances? between two types of morality and a curious point of view on the relations understood as an object coveted by ende and precise, to fill the emotional void.</body>
</review>
