<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>300 is a work 100% entertainment, 100% aesthetic quality, 100% rate and, in short, a well told story that won't think too much, but to be completely mesmerized spectators during two hours.</summary>
	<body>Sometimes one refuses to believe that more than one million people may be right. Time shows that box office figures tend not to talk about the quality of the product and, in a way, the demanding Viewer (others call him proud, erudite, arrogant, cult, alternative, arrogant, or none of these, or all at once) tends to associate taquillazo with pastelazo. However, these terms do not have to be synonymous to the force. It is the case of 300.Si well it is true that have found me a very good film, I must also clarify me uncheck those you see here a before and a later in the film, or those who consider that 300 is a perfect, total, sublime film. It may be a 10, as a product of entertainment but if the film is much more than that, and I think Yes, it happens not notable movie.The history, or the history of the history, already know. 300 recreates his way to the battle of Thermopylae, imitating the eponymous comics by Frank Miller, which in turn was inspired by the 1961 film "The 300 espartans" (translated as "The lion of Sparta"). Historical facts in it were collected by Herodotus of Halicarnassus (484aC-425dC) in his work "Historiae" or "Nine books of history", where this and other battles the Greeks maintained with barbaric peoples (especially against the Persians in the Greco-Persian wars) are narrated with more fidelity. His story has been the primary source of information for others.Despite this, no wait a historical movie. More is, that no one leave the film thinking that you know a little more to the Spartans and Persians (well, if to hear Spartan thought in a liberator of slaves, and to hear Persian only came you to mind a cat with long hair, then can that Yes, you can have learned something). Frank Miller has never denied that what attracted him all this was the essence. In fact, neither the Spartans were 300, nor fought naked, nor the ten thousand Immortals were dressed as for Halloween, or Ephialtes was a misshapen hunchback, nor a long etcetera. I.e., the work is not a faithful Chronicle of what happened in the Gorge, but for authors I must point out that they have never tried to sell it as well. Wrong who uses these arguments to discredit her.Now, a film must sustain itself. If you read a dozen of interviews the Director, critical tropecientas to what most lucid, and look at all the extras of the dvd so you it looks perfect, it means that something is wrong. I don't care if 300 lies more or less, but miss some of the context, some subplot with force, more than espadazos right and left. The captive film for its aesthetic, for his photograph, for its frenetic pace. but after a few days (the more savvy may not require more than a few minutes) you realize that leaves no footprint as much as it might seem. I will not remember with special affection any character (or even none of the actors and actresses that embodied), I will not highlight the argument in any conversation (300 hold the stakes of a million to defend his people), not particularly excites me the issue of Fund (the defence of the freedom at all costs, a patriotic roll very to American taste) and, in short, I can never consider 300 is a work as perfect as some claim.That Yes, the good thing that no one is removed. 300 is a work 100% entertainment, 100% aesthetic quality, 100% rate and, in short, a well told story that won't think too much, but to be completely mesmerized spectators during two hours. One of the best epic movies of all time.</body>
</review>
