<review author="Bloody Will" title="Hannibal: El origen del mal" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What remains at the end is a film with chained murders, neither more nor less. It could have been Lecter, Freddy Kruger it could have been. Absolute wear of the formula.</summary>
	<body>Hannibal is part of our lives for too many years now. They are already 16 years have been knowing Dr. Lecter through sequels, prequels, and now, origins. And so long can have only one consequence: the absolute wear of the formula. Do the only ones shown impassive this situation seem Laurentiis Dino, its producer, and Thomas Harris, father of the creature, yet remaining corners of the character to explore, but you want that he tells you, you can not always tell an interesting story.?Hannibal: the origin of evil? presented as a dark history where we would see Lecter inoculate this attitude of fierce psychoanalyst and soulless Cannibal, I wondered if the why of a way of life so mechanically heartless would have its explanation in surprising events, and even theorized sonçbre internal change that has happened to so wild available to kill (can see the fate of Ray Liotta in?)(Hannibal?). However, and after seeing? The origin? I found the typical story of crude revenge with preliminary somewhat diffuse. A film of killings, without tension and apparent plot. The? source? devised by Harris has outgrown to the aura of the character, much more complex than this decaffeinated Hannibal, and for me, I would have preferred to continue without discovering it.The film tells how a Lecter infante, which should witness a chilling event becomes a teenager Lecter who lives tormented by what has happened, and prepares his revenge against those responsible. A that cannot be more vague, because I do it deliberately to the simplicity of the script presented in this prequel. Two unique pivots underpin the film: the first half-hour, which tells us the why, and the last half hour where tells us how. Why come I want to kill, and how I do it to make it look sickly. Do nothing of this honour Lecter we saw in?The silence?, and appears to be a mockery of the Hopkins of?Hannibal?. How whether these two main reasons to become a so feared being is embodied in this prequel in a way as forced as sometimes absurd. I left the police, the aunt of Lecter, the butcher?.After watching the credits I have clear that first a novel and later its adaptation, and more clear still that Harris has been the architect of both. I say this because this usually leads to a greater fidelity to the original story, and that leaves me perplexed before the vanalidad that the writer has given your child from a decent source. Is how if had commissioned you a screenplay by co **, and with that obligation, draw the children of Lecter from the first form that has come to mind. Do before we see a minimal glimpse of cannibalism in Lecter no sample some of which the character is that? hunger? which leads to their particular murder. Not me it is very clear when Lecter decides to become Cannibal. And I have less clear still to do by lived experience of child, as the first victim of the character has nothing to do with his past. Anyway, an amalgam of inconsistencies that populate the half of a movie that should have been better planned, or in the light of the outcome, ever.Many people will say that the atmosphere is incredible, and correct interpretations, but was not what you were looking for in this film. The actor responsible for giving life to the psychopath has been apercibido show all the sadistic faces meet, but that do so also in the cheap TV movies, and are not Lecter. The scenes of Gaspard Ulliel and Gong Li are inconsistent. Can do even more when Lecter learns the use of the sword samurai (nonsense), and the figure of the police is intended to threaten the murderous tranquility of the protagonist, but not these, seems at the end its presence is due to reiterate that the boy is a? monster?, a resource quite helpings.What remains at the end is a film with chained murders, neither more nor less. It could have been Lecter, Freddy Kruger it could have been. If you ever hear the term? characters in two dimensions?, this film is his greatest example: what you see is what there is. If the history of the cinema has become the latest installment of the adventures of Hannibal Lecter, is a little fitting end of its predecessors, a deliberately commercial product with questionable quality. Should fans give a touch to Harris, who has finally lost its way?.</body>
</review>
