<review author="Bloody Will" title="300" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perfect combination of gross and consistent action argument. This film is the cane! The best of the year 2007, long and long...</summary>
	<body>Many hours dedicated to this film lead inevitably to a viewing with your eyes wide open. That does not escape the script, do not escape the actors and, by God, there are no to close those eyes to the half hour of the film. So much anticipation is often the worst enemy of a good assessment, although I have not sat to see her with the idea to scrutinize each of the details of? 300 &#8242;. Perhaps that is why I can say that this film is the cane!. The best of 2007, long and long.From that I saw?Infiltrators? He had not returned to feel that wild and illogical concern see as they are falling one after one on the screen. ? 300 &#8242; is violence, violence and more violence. The dialogues uphold such violence. The actors poses increase such violence and the excellent cinematography of the film is the result of violence. The rooms are going to fill with people who shouts on par with Leonidas? do Spartans!?!!!! While they plague the wind as if they had swords.Is this the film that consumará your revenge against your girlfriend by this time that you got to see?The journal of Noa?. Mind you, I'm not saying by machismo that is a film of uncles, but Snyder has been riding a 2 hour maxi-battle that must be addressed with a high level of testosterone. An example: my girl saw the first half-hour until Leonidas turned blood. There is over everything for her.The argument is simple: Leonidas hates the Persians. The Persians want to Sparta. Leonidas travels to deal with 300 men to the thousands and thousands of Persians. Fight. Battle. Blood. Mutilations. More fight. More blood. Female genital mutilation is quintuplican?The merit of Zak Snyder is that, with a great graphic novel by Frank - genius-Miller, it has managed to make an excellent movie without decay tension, interest and entertainment not even a second. That much is due to the history of course Council of Miller, but how many times have seen a good story in the hands of a sleepy firecracker. The succession at the battle of ordas Asians which Leonidas and company face becomes increasingly more stimulating, both visually and so fun watching the kids handing out everywhere. Do with? 300 &#8242; or leave the eyes of the screen? only perhaps to remove this imaginary splash of blood.Gerard Butler can only say that there will not be another pu ** ca ** Spartan better than him. They gave me desire to sign up with Leonidas where necessary. I'm going with him to kill Persians, not Persians, elephants or whatever you want. It me yell of Spartans!, that I shot to del rio if necessary.!! Lena Headey, the next Sarah Connor, is the wife of Leonidas, and surprised the hu ** gives her throughout the film. This really sends, and the sensual and sexual of his character is just know that if it were not for his son, would be with Leonidas auctioning firewood. Unrecognizable Rodrigo Santoro as Xerxes. This guy, appearing 3 minutes in?Los Angeles Charlie 2 &#8242; is one of the additions of?Does lost?, and as king Xerxes exits. One of the best villains we will see this year.What fails: the character of the hunchback Ephialtes. It adds nothing. And that a lot of people can remember you to?Trojan? mixed with the bad ost ** Robert Rodriguez. Do course? 300 &#8242; has nothing to do with the rest of pseudo-peplum that have visited us recently. If you think you attend a historic lesson, let him be for the history channel. They are 300 Spartans against a million Asians, so wait only brutality until there is one Standing left.With the aesthetics of comics green-screen gives? 300 &#8242; are two hours more acoj ** are going to spend in the film long overdue. Perfect combination of gross and consistent action argument. Should you avoid the purchase of arrojadizos objects (popcorn, bottles, cheetos, a simple red licorice) If you will not be tempted to use it against the brat that sits below, that since that I have seen him at the entrance to him I want to?</body>
</review>
