<review author="Bloody Will" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good film, with some fringe than another, but it leaves good taste, and with that I already have more than enough.</summary>
	<body>When a film opens already preceded by several nominations in the Oscars you biased that you aren't to any product whose quality you will discover as develops the footage. Original score, best adapted screenplay, best leading actress and best supporting actress, there is nothing, and after seeing?Diary of a scandal? their nominations are more than deserved. The film is basically an interpretative duel between two actresses showing their repeated nominations are not fruit of a momentary inspiration. Good film, with some fringe than another, but it leaves good taste, and with that I already have more than enough.If I allow a somewhat termism license, I would her call?Diary of Bridget bad?, but if we scratch something else we'll see the bad is not so bad, and the dead woolly has less moral than a white merchant. With a premise so warped as the relationship between a child and their teacher, the two protagonists weave one? society? of secrets where a takes advantage of the weakness of another, maintaining throughout history a characteristic of this type of friendly relations tension where? vouchers by which you shut up?, although the consequences following the breakup of one of the links are catastrophic.Sheba (Blanchett) is the teacher of new art in a London Institute whose most veteran teacher, Barbara Covett (Dench) has some predilection to engage in personal relationships with his colleagues based on the transmission of unspeakable secrets. When Sheba begins a relationship with a student in his class of 15 years, Barbara used the secret to handle it at its whim, always with the sword of damocles under his head. Needless to say, that veteran charged his revenge after a small snub committed by the child molester teacher.British cinema is one of the few that can treat pederasty with that so sophisticated and pompous. Unlike the rest of Europe, where we converted the story in a quandary amor-ley, this film makes a dilemma amor-suciedad. So stretched society cannot be so immoral, and Judi Dench becomes the diabolical witness to the ups and downs of his new friend. Do that? newspaper? the title is the book that writes Barbara with everything what happens around, and unlike the Bridget, his voice telling the miseries and secrets of those who surround it show us a bitter character but with sufficient hubris as to not be there.Thus, as the story we see as Barbara is doing with Sheba little by little, until that has it as already taken that you can do with his life, his family and their aspirations whatever you win, although the character of Blanchett not far behind. Drawn as a good history, we realize that it is as good or it is so innocent. Do with husband and two children, the teacher launches an own affair of?I am the Juani?, which he does not know, or rather you don't want to cut. Tell her friend seems the excuse a little more, but we do not quote, their actions are so heinous as the Dench.Si there is something that I did not like it might be precipitate that is desrrolla the relationship between the two. Do too soon to open the young professor to his? new? friend, and some inconsistencies regarding the relationship of Sheba with minors. It is what little I can highlight, and that as good a lover of movies with incessant dialogue, the rest I forgot a little.Interpretations can shortly tell apart from two nominations, which are more than reason enough to give you account that these two women soloists are enough to carry the film from beginning to end with the looks and gestures. Do the chemistry is undeniable, and that relationship between mother daughter or at times loving is interpreted in a masterly manner taking into account the ups and downs that run in your? friendship? peculiar. Attentive to the final scene of encounter between the two, when things end up saying to the face. It is simply to record and display it in the schools of interpretation. Bill Nighy is the man in the film, but is on the floor next to these two ladies.?Diary of a scandal? It is these films showing how cabr ** s can be sometimes when we eat the loneliness and need to the esclavito turn to the side. It is human nature, gather information if it can be thrown in the future. One we stayed in only thoughts, others materialized it in the most direct way. Here, Judi Dench, is the last.By the way, the poster is clavadito to the of?Do talk to her? in version? opposite?.</body>
</review>
