<review author="Bloody Will" title="El buen pastor" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Artistically it is one of the best I've seen this year? but for the rest, the disappointment has been tremendous.</summary>
	<body>Do returns Robert De Niro address after 13 years from the excellent?A history of the Bronx?. Do with a truly remarkable predecessor, and the unquestionable love and respect that I have for the actor not I lie if I say that I sat down to see?The good Shepherd? Avid of immerse me in a story of spies with the De Niro label. Much to my regret, and after half an hour of film, I realize that it is artistically one of the best I've seen this year? but for the rest, the disappointment has been tremendous.Do I hope to not be the only one who thinks this movie follows the trail of the biográficos-históricos work of Oliver Stone in?Nixon? or?Do do JFK?, or the type of? 13 days?, and although the founding assumption is not so famous, there is nothing more American than the C.I.A.. The previous, and others, are extremely Visual, and also extremely political work. Therefore the narrative ballast, heavy, cumbersome, and mostly boring, is expected in other filmmakers, to those who are can forgive more than Mr. De Niro. The director spent the first 50 minutes trying to explain the origin of the protagonist to then not show not a single scene of action within two hours of him remaining to finish. That is why I say that a length of 3 hours, without action, with an excess of information policy of the time, and a somewhat chaotic Assembly, seems to me A pain in the ass.The story tells of the founding of the C.I.A., or so it seemed when I saw the trailer. In reality it is the story of Edward Wilson (Damon), a man that step by step, from a lower position to the highest, helped found the center of American intelligence, but there is not a hint of emotion in nothing of what makes this man. Do de Niro has built a cold and calculating man who at times you get to leave in a State of mild drowsiness because of his repeated lack of? blood?. His early years at Yale, which to me me sobran, his early years as Spy, without a shot to the mouth, and his later ascent towards the dome, with the roll of bureaucratic plot, show me that if this character existed, he should die finally his own boredom.Special case is the parade of side that populate the film. Impress that names like De Niro, William Hurt, Joe Pesci, Alec Baldwim, Michael Gambon and Billy Cudrup are characters that barely sufficient to say more than ten sentences. Everything is focused on Damon, and that produces an overload of the protagonist who does everything he can to fill the screen, and that if you have chosen another actor do not really know if it had completed see. If Angelina Jolie was another reason for your viewing, sorry to disappoint you, because his presence is merely transitory, besides the fact that Damon chemical is null, nulísima. If this woman thought about retiring, for me he can do it now.Divided into two temporary sections, the film confuses many moments and ends up not contribute nothing to the genre of the spy. Much conversation, much theory, much policy, but low resolution. The life of the founder is seen from the Office or from home, or picking up telephones with a firewall of 1961, and not know if from the perspective of an American history is interesting, as if we explain to us how the PSC was founded but comprended me if I tell you that I can not stop thinking in Bourne, and good thing that would have been mixing both chatter with more voltagewhich is absolute absent throughout the film.Good performances, artistic direction, but horrible Assembly and horrible development. If De Niro had reduced the footage might had happened by an interesting film, but with such slowness and parsimony, and with just three flashes of concern, only it has managed to bore me to swear that I will be thinking twice to see a film that cuenté the glory and honor of a public administration, by very tite Bobby to lead.It will be a great movie for lovers of the political thriller of infinite footage, and I cannot deny that, as such, it is the best from years and years ago, but for me it has finished being a suckling pig, with an impeccable visual invoice, but the end and Cape suckling pig.</body>
</review>
