<review author="Dragon negro" title="The messengers" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The child who sees ghosts already became better in Poltergeist, the stereotype of a girl rebel believes anybody already tired, about the Ravens did in the birds and the pale under savannahs ghosts and climbing up the walls in The Ring and the curse.</summary>
	<body>Many were the expectations created by see the premiere in Hollywood of the Pang brothers and see if they could make a tape of terror in a position under its umbrella. The Pang brothers, Oxide and Danny, became world famous thanks to the movie The Eye, which is already prepared its corresponding remake with Jessica Alba as the protagonist.A family, parents, rebellious teenage daughter and the youngest son, moved to a farm almost in ruins with the intention of rebuilding their lives and start from scratch after being virtually bankrupt due to causes which is already explained in the film. There are intended to make a planting of sunflowers, which I am even asking the because that could have been just as parsley that the film would be the same, because I already explain get a plantation of pipes or oil which will bring economic benefit, but in the end, that that is not the point. Total that the House is full of ghosts which only seems to see the raised apart this traumatized and no word from causes which are also explained throughout the film. Then without coming to tell it sister also begins to see ghosts, but clear, nobody believe being a girl problems and such. Then there are more appearances of ghosts and half a loads of crazy crows who attack whoever menea. And everything ends with an explanation of the most silly and predictable, no, I will not tell which it is, a sea of easy and simple final and finished.As you may have deduced the film has been a total disappointment, a tape of terror that adds nothing new to the genre and that is equal to or worse than any other with haunted house of medium. The characters are as flat and predictable, what the child he sees ghosts already became better in Poltergeist, the stereotype of rebel girl that no one believes already tired, about the Ravens did in the birds and the pale under savannahs ghosts and climbing up the walls in The Ring and the curse. other failed horror movie and already have a few since the beginning of the yearto see when that film which again surprises us all and is not more of the same. I hope that now the adventures separately from the brothers able to give offer something better.</body>
</review>
