<review author="Jose Contreras" title="La cosecha" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Theology is an inexhaustible treasure of narrative skeletons for authors without imagination.</summary>
	<body>I don't know that critic said that new works are not invented from scratch, are bad rereadings of old. There is who manosea predecessors because he believes that you can improve them. For example "The harvest" is the re-reading of a spectator who was wanting to ship with the long-eared child makes of Demian in "The prophecy". This spine could explain average film. The end does not. The end belongs to fashion "poker" cinema of today, which is to get a letter from the manga that gives back to what he believed, women of the Mayor is not his wife, is a transvestite, the town is not a town, it is painted. However, with such surprise. A test to distinguish when tells you the story of an intelligent director and the tells you a fool as the protagonist discovers the truth. The truth can come from the hand of a scientist with white mane (the fast way) of a dying, a gossip, a computer, a secret that nobody should know (this tends to be the most reliable). The intelligent protagonists filter what you hear, discuss, refuse to believe. The director of "The harvest" has chosen a short cut shorter than the scientist's White mane: chose the mounting table. I still don't know if congratulations on the nose that gives her or tell you that it will do gargle. It has no waste, the protagonist learns the truth about the story because the editor puts forward the sequence of events as they occurred. Nobody talks, nobody explains, the scenes and we know that this was the case.The protagonist is a University professor who studies miracles to give a scientific explanation. It had been a missionary in Africa, but a tragedy made him renounce his faith. Now they call it a village, Haven, where a few Paranormal phenomena suggest that a girl is the incarnation of the devil. The havenenses, or haveneños, I do not know the patronym, experiencing one by one the ten plagues bíbilicas. The list of the ten plagues is as undependable as the seven deadly sins, or the four evangelists. Theology is an inexhaustible treasure of narrative skeletons for authors without imagination. Aware or not of the headache that means its proposal, the authors have put everything on their side so that at least it is not indifferent. Haven is the place where the battle between good and evil is fought. It is there where he is decided if the demon is going to dominate the world and therefore we are going to climb still more receipt of the phone, or if Hillary Swank is going to save us from having to wait in line in the window of the Bank. I wonder why the demon chooses forms so rare in movies when one is found in each corner with paseo clothing.</body>
</review>
