<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El buen pastor" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Beautiful invoice and effective realization, the tape weakens in many parts of its long footage and, at times, borders the soporific in his story about the origin of the powerful CIA.</summary>
	<body>Some exaggeration in the critical phrases selected for promotions of films is logical. But it caught my attention, by his bombast, one of the employees in the television advertisement of the good Shepherd. "The godfather of spy films", said the sentence awarded to a critical excessively enthusiastic. Because, truth be told, the third tape of Robert De Niro in the direction isn't much less for both. Beautiful invoice and effective realization, the tape weakens in many parts of its long footage and, at times, borders the soporific in his story about the origin of the powerful CIA.The history of this popular spy agency is told through the life of one of its most distinguished founding members: the agent Edward Wilson (played cold and inexpresivamente purposely by Matt Damon). In his youth years, Wilson is described as an outstanding student of strong patriotic convictions. But, as it is involved in the dirty work of the Agency, his life will be marked by continuous resignations: the woman who truly loved, his passion for poetry or to the care and protection of his son.To add some suspense to a story difficult to follow little to not be fairly fresh and neat, the screenplay by Eric Roth (Munich, the dilemma?) proposes a fragmented structure of the story. An inquiry concerning a CIA Bay of pigs fiasco planting an initial intrigue whose outcome will be postponed to the end of the film to tell, in the meantime, the details of how this agency was born and how Wilson was carving is a flawless reputation of cold and effective agent.De Niro directs the Pleiad of great actors of its extensive cast perfectly. William Hurt, Michael Gambon, Joe Pesci, John Turturro, Alec Baldwin or Angelina Jolie, in addition to the own De Niro, interpreted with strength each of their brief roles. Nevertheless, and despite virtues such as this, the tape loses interest in some of his numerous sub-plots. Other Yes substantial to detail how conceived this secret society aimed at directing, which global puppeteer, play the threads of international policy in favour of American interests. I would recommend for their testimonial value about the plumbing work carried out by spies lonely and away altogether of the glamorous image that the film has encouraged many other times.</body>
</review>
