<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La cosecha" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Muddy and predictable ration of biblical ghosts of Apostolic disasters that smell blockbuster of giant poster on the door of the video store, infumable sweet for some palates and attractive pasa-ratos for whom, in the background, not asking for much, except a bit of amenity. In that regard, entertaining, very biblical, is.</summary>
	<body>There as an archaeology of the Apocalypse, desire to confine the chaos and the enigmas of biblical nature in noveladas frames, suitable for immediate commercial consumption. As if theology could be reduced to distraimiento's Sunday supplement. The side effects of the tsunami Dan Brown dan frugal phenomena media who appeal to the religious startle, to the remote and revolutionary possibility of subverting the metaphorical or mythological scaffolding of Christianity and turn it into a master hack, in a deception lasted for two miraculous millennia.Just go to the shelf of any Bookstore news to understand the monstrous extent of this trend which now seems an epidemic. The harvest joins this anthology of the Ecumenical nonsense and confirms the idea that the viewer undemanding - soon of happy - going to leave happy and proud, convinced that their natural supernatural concerns have had a messianic, majestic, overwhelming and undeniable audio-visual support. Biblical plagues, miracles, antichrists and bastardías several of our Lord Jesus Christ snatch the formal believer and distract who only seek distraction. To all the others who create or not, are happy to care of forms and a competent livelihood of dramatic films such as harvesting bring fresco. Open you a little more eyes on the forced scenes of infographic luxury (here is, there is no doubt) and will break in yawning when the director deal with intermediate footage with gilipollescos dialogues and pseudoscientific justifications. The thin line between faith and superstition comes from the master in the management of a computer with a graphics card potenta.Frivolous, halfway between the biblical thriller and the apocalyptic docudrama, the film dispenses with all literary interest and makes his possible interest (not is it arrebatemos soon) in the expertise of the post-production, of course. This fantasy of loose budget adheres to a potentially harmful gender: the apocalyptic thriller, suspense with mystical speculative. I fear the worst: fear they freedom these incursions in the old and New Testament books fantastic, in the literal sense of the term, but indicators, ultimately, of the little imaginative bravery of the new writers of the cinema, that they are fleeing risk as if it were a cloud of locusts and embrace, impúdicamente, to this inexhaustible Philo and, to the amazement of producers, golosísimo for the viewer easily impressionable. It is only a matter of wait a few weeks and see how the film argues on screen, stealing his poster to other proposals which are less spectacular but more vitamin of cinema, of interest, of honesty.</body>
</review>
