<review author="Florinda Chic" title="El buen pastor" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Political thriller which, like the dark events that relates, is very cumbersome and requires the attention of the viewer and a some background on recent American history.</summary>
	<body>The magic of the cinema takes us back to an era in which the polígrafos were used to save the world and not to determine if the descendant of a folk resorted to moral distracted Demoiselles services while its progenitor relieved the nasal cavities behind the scenes.De Niro, while that remind us of the first uses of this device, performed in the good Shepherd a tour of 30 years of intrigue, secrets and lies in a political thriller which, like the dark events which he relates, is very cumbersome and requires the attention of the viewer and a some background on recent American history, and that the film has many narrative ellipsis and a bunch of characters.The first thing that makes De Niro is demystify the romantic idea that Ian Fleming, or Le Carré have been spies. Just as in the lives of others, the Spy - is red or blue, red and white - is a lonely, being with the State as the only friend and lover.The film features the fictional biography of one of the founders of the CIA which is forced to secrecy since childhood and is recruited at the University to join the OSS - the forerunner of the CIA--during World War II. Do do just becoming a leading member of the Agency during the war cold and well learned the motto:? but that look like an accident? combats the KGB, the advance of communism and becomes a player of chess efficient, calculating and emotionally dead.Save the world takes its toll and Wilson is not able to reconcile work and family life: his wife does not want him, his son is afraid and his friends simply do not exist. So the good Shepherd is a history of resignation, which, given that Matt Damon unchanged expression in the 160 minutes of footage, we do not know if the sacrifice was worth or not, if it is happy or if it is a wretched.Apart from leaving the room with this debate, there is another question unanswered: where's Max Factor? Rarely I have seen in movies so bad old characters and if you want a story that takes place over 30 years to be credible you makeup well the protagonists or occur moments as the father and teenage son seem to colleagues in the AUL and the mother - Angelina Jolie-, a cheer leader with 50.Los actors are not saints of my devotion, to Damon that seems relative of Dorian Gray doesn't move a brow lift, because I can hardly believe it to me. Do angelina for its part, does not have much presence and is rather decorative and example that the? celebrity? the actress has eaten.The other side is a wonder: John Turturro that should have taken more court, William Hurt, De Niro himself, Alec Baldwin, Joe Pesci, Tammy Blanchard, and curiously Martina Gedeck passing of spy - the lives of others - spy.In short, highly recommended, the film keeps the interest during the long footage, has an excellent invoice and secondary are luxury, given American cinema recently, a delight.PS: As curiosity sign "Skulls and bones" secret society to which belongs the Matt Damon character actually exists and its members include the Bush, father and son, and democratic presidential candidate Senator John Kerry.</body>
</review>
