<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Moscow Zero" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It adds nothing, do not have anything new, nor from a new point of view, it not hooked, not scared, am not intrigued, anyway... not get nothing of what you intend to, to tell the truth... I do not know what is exactly.</summary>
	<body>Moscow Zero. patatero. They will forgive me the easy joke, but it is that few films put him to egg and finally, I could not resist. Suffice it to say that the best of the film is that, one: saw in press pass (i.e., free) and two: it finished soon and I could go to the pass of "After the wedding", which turned out to be a peliculón. But that's another story.The case is that I left Moscow Zero as cold as I went (was rainy day). It adds nothing, do not have anything new, nor from a new point of view, it not hooked, not afraid, not intrigue, anyway. achieves nothing of what you intend to, but to tell the truth. I do not know what is exactly.The feature of the Spanish Director Moon (AKA María Lidón) is set in the subsoil of Moscow. There, father Owen is looking for a friend, the anthropologist Sergei Karparov, disappeared in strange circumstances when investigating the legends of the marginal society of Moscow underworld. In the search accompany three other men (do me not say who are exactly. a pair of mercenaries, a collaborator, something) and a woman (a vagrant that would have been the last Miss Spain Street). Together they travel dozens of narrow corridors, far left, far right, now I've seen a brand, now smell me that it is here. and meanwhile some mysterious children will be watching them from the shadows.Trite, empty and history with a smell of "The other". Parallel worlds where each one thinks that the demon is the other legends who want to seem very enigmatic and at the end. no surprises. Anyway, it is really boring. More claustrophobia causes fatigue and more than fear of laughter. The motivations of the characters are unclear and, in any case, are shallow. But as well as flat characters, there is a total absence of work in dialogues. Especially annoying monologues of Sergei Karparov, which is speaking only through the corridors as that does not want the thing: "Oh, an inscription." "I'm going to read it and explain it aloud." That Yes, we have to love story. After several hours hanging around by the happy galleries the vagrant decides to retire (is that everything is very scary and I can not remember to what came with the well that was eating rat wings.) (Better me again I by myself). Despite not having crossed practically Word with the prota (except a couple of indirect without coming to story) before leaving decides to plant a good morreo father Owen who, of course, receives the enchanted gift. Momentazo.NI even a couple of scares can take you. Everything is predictable. For example: Alec, one of the guides, sees a lantern that had been lost in a hole where you can only arm. He decided to take it and go!, the hole had trap. It takes out suddenly, screaming and looking at the brand of bite that has. All are concerned about what happened, but despite initial concern, just accepting that it has because of RIP with the stone. More careful the next time Alec!The only thing positive I can find to this is the faith that María Lidón puts in their projects. Something certainly does well to take them forward. Sold in advance in zillions countries, with a budget of 10 million dollars and a fairly interesting cast, Moscow Zero was filmed in real scenarios, the majority in the own Moscow. And already are three films with this. Finally, we hope that the third and fourth will the expired. Time leave us this pretentious grotesque, that someone dare to call cinema.</body>
</review>
