<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not melodrama and not a thriller, but he opts for spinning a very entertaining and honest exercise of sociological research of neutral analysis that rummages the sins of a broken society, pushed to forgive with interests, to be convinced of the lightness of certain offences to not spoil the exemplary calm of its appearance.</summary>
	<body>This modern Vampire Chronicle, based in an aseptic London, obvious Gothic component to the use and the romanticism of book, but portrays the same pathologies: what is radically different is the dress that evil is presented to us. Here occurs in broad daylight and does not require a single drop of blood food contest. The subject matter of suction is the entire personality and exercise it a teacher about to retire, harmless in appearance, cultured and crudely acid in the observations that records in his diaries on other newly attached to a faculty Professor mona, young and, in principle, easily inducible absolute manipulation pleasure.Diary of a scandal progresses slowly but afianzadamente on some sensitive budgets which, in other hands, with other view, had been able to engender a vulgar telefilm of shrill invoice with abundant evidence of reality show in its stark footage.Attending a prontuario frivolous on education in the 21st century, we can say that the film is a reflection of the light morality that fills us with: how instincts are the engines of our actions, although in this case the young idealist and bobalicona (sober Cate Blanchett) never seem bad at all, despite having contributed with his consent to a fifteen year old girl is her trajine with repeated insistence on an ardent here you rogue-here you kill.The sentimental blackmail the old teacher puts on the new leads every interest of the film: the troubled loneliness of the teacher slightly lesbian excited with the possibility of enslave the will of his chantajeada enables breakthrough agile in the history, no melodramatic, burdened for an interesting but in the end very heavy voice-over from the embracing storyteller of the plot, the vamp, the happy demiurge of the tragedy that his perversion has created. Judi Dench magistral recreates with astonishing naturalness a hateful, ambiguous, evil by nature, surprised character on the final slope of his life with intact Hymen and the nasty settled in that murderous look drag during much of the film.The intensity of the psychological drama open no lapses in no time: raises discussions of broad social significance as sexual intercourse with minors or the sordid consent of those who for one reason or another to take advantage of this dysfunction.The few scruples of the young professor to be activity by the boy are not less scandalous that interested permissiveness of the teacher aware of desmon, who plays his cards with premeditation, conscious always that the game is written by her and she establishes rules, actants and up the length. There is a particularly significant scene: Barbara, is the name of the character that plays gloriously, as we have said, Judi Dench, sits on the stairs of the House inevitably English where the tragedy has joined the mother of the newborn pervert student: this goes to give him a beating to induce Professor. The spectacle is sublime in the eyes of who has caligrafiado all the letters of the work.These notable evidence of good cinema and great history are lost when the film announces their twisted end, his resignation to be sincere with itself, because that gives us, in payment for more than one hour of attractive arguments, is a triumphant end, where everything is left to lead to meekness of forgiveness and where all the characters recoverbenefit of armchair, the tranquility and inner peace from which began.At the end we have the grey portrait of a dark, perfidious wife in his inaceptada solitude or perhaps truly remarkable is the ease with which we shed the closest important crimes if in indifference we acquired some benefit, a comfortable chair where the devastated an excessively overload the shocking society silences contemplate the ruins of morality. And also another equally depressing portrait: of the dysfunctional family (nothing to envy to the members of the little Miss Sunshine van psicotrónicos) Sheba, young teacher, which could be built, with due dramatic refinement, a more than solid script of Puya and apparent bourgeois júbilos the sabrosón rhythm of a calypso after lunch with pink hamgurguesas.</body>
</review>
