<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Después de la boda" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A strange feeling keeps you glued to the seat when the credits are lost and you think that with them is gradually extinguished the magic minutes earlier made you feel completely mesmerized. After the wedding is painful, emotional, deep and hard... a masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>From time to time one leaves the film thinking that something has changed there outside. Or there inside, rather. A strange feeling keeps you glued to the seat when the credits are lost and you think that with them is gradually extinguished the magic minutes earlier made you feel completely mesmerized. After the wedding is painful, emotional, deep and hard. a masterpiece.Nominated for an Oscar in the category of best film of non-English speaking, the film's Director Susanne Bier (brothers, I want to always.) tells the story of Jacob, a lone wolf who devotes his life to help the children of Bombay, India. The economic difficulties that goes through the orphanage where he works make that it is forced to travel to his native country, Denmark, to negotiate the proposed donation an important business man is willing to do. You will soon see that Jorgen, the altruistic in question imposes strange conditions to gradually charged sense and force you to take the most important decisions of his life.After the wedding is above all a story of reunions: between people, between people and places to which belonged, between past and future. What we thought we had left behind sometimes reappears with an unsuspected strength. Each watchful secret opens a new world, a new range of possibilities. And, always, to open a door closes another. Jacob progresses, and we with him, through his past for approaching a crossroads that leaves choice good, but not bad. Less is more.This poignant drama (his detractors will say that it is a melodrama) supports its solid script in some intelligent dialogues, that give to the action of a lively pace and an ever-growing interest. I remember the first mirror gives the protagonist to reach Denmark, tired and skeptical. His companion, son-in-law of the wealthy Jorgen, says: "it came out of nowhere and now has a fortune." "Although no note", to which Jacob responds "that come out of nowhere?". The irony, sarcasm and the subtext are always present. But if something stands out beyond the argument and the theme is for the superb performances of all its protagonists. Especially bright are Mads Mikkelsen (Jacob) and Rolf Lassgard (Jorgen). No doubt much of the success of the work lies with them, as they are involved in making the hardest scenes of the film credible and emotive.In short, we are, to my mind, one of the best films of 2006. I am afraid that it will go unnoticed at the Spanish box office, but this is the type of stories that worth seeing movies. If you order something more than entertainment pure and hard, empty and meaningless, go to see her without hesitation. I personally reply to complaints, if any.</body>
</review>
