<review author="Antoni Messa" title="El buen pastor" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A well-intentioned but failed, film in which Robert De Niro, despite placing the camera in a brilliant manner, has forgotten give life to their characters. Or rather, the character; Edward Wilson.</summary>
	<body>More than 13 years have passed to Robert De Niro, from the splendid A history of the Bronx, reinsert it behind a camera. Thirteen years that, in addition to continue playing, has dedicated has collect specific information in order to be able to film the good Shepherd, a film showing, among other topics, the birth of the CIA.The film focuses, first of all, Edward Wilson, a peculiar and man of few words who gives life Matt Damon and for whose construction have been inspired - in a manner very free - in the figure of Jesus James Angelton, the true founder of the CIA. The inexpressiveness and the usual sosería in the actor have become the unique traits that define the personality of such Wilson, a cold, extremely meticulous and (accidentally) Machiavellian type.The good Shepherd starts in April 1961, just after the failed Bay of Pigs invasion; a military operation frustrated clear ideology anti-Castro and orchestrated by the CIA; an intervention which sparked all kinds of suspicions in the minds of the American President, the by the then newly-elected John f. Kennedy. From this point, De Niro will miss hand (abusively) of the technique of flash back to take a sober and extensive look at the existence of the aforementioned Edward Wilson, one of the agents directly involved in the case. An extensive and excessive revision, of more than two hours and a half of duration, which will have place all kinds of facts, both of his private life of his actions as a government spy.A festival Matt Damon that it will delight the most staunch followers of the actor and that, in equal parts, it irritará to those who? as to a server - you do not find the trick to it. And it is that there is not a single scene in which the man does not appear; a detail, the latter partly quite logical, that everything happens through the sieve of his gaze. But my whole look, and due to his "required" stay on screen, another actor with various interpretive resources would have given more to the film and the character entity.Luck at least to alleviate somewhat the overdose Damon, you can enjoy the large campus of side excellent that surround the protagonist of the Bourne case. Some of them very blurred in their roles; other unused too long; but everyone, from the first to the last (except for one little credible Angelina Jolie), fulfilling its work effectively.Narrative delinquencies is one of the determining factors when it comes to prosecute a product which, without much loss of time unjustified, could condense into just a couple of hours. A little more than nerve and agility would have helped better digestion. And it is that this lack of verve and the slowness with which faces certain passages are contrasted, in part, with the amount of gaps, loose and not very well resolved episodes leaves along its length.It is undeniable that De Niro, despite its laudable commitment to inform the viewer of the beginnings of the CIA, has more care the visuals to the descriptive. Taking into account that the tape runs over almost three decades different (from before the start of the second world war until after the Bay of pigs incident), can be described as excellent the thoroughness with which has taken care of the aesthetic and scenographic background details. In this respect, it is not surprising that tiquismiquis of Francis Ford Coppola is credited as Executive Producer: everyone knows your desire, almost sickly, Coddling the final image to unthinkable ends.Distrust and secrecy: two concepts which define perfectly, everything that surrounds the protagonist of the good Shepherd; a well-intentioned but failed, film in which Robert De Niro, despite placing the camera in a brilliant manner, has forgotten give life to their characters. Or rather, the character; Edward Wilson, its almost unique character.</body>
</review>
