<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Alien Nation" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tape of my childhood. It verges on, without deepening the theme of racism and xenophobia, and this, in broad terms, one of the main problems in any society.</summary>
	<body>Let me you talk of one of the movies of my childhood, I was a tender child of 11 or 12 years old, when in my neighborhood cinema premiered this film, an interstellar "Buddy Movie", where a human COP Jarah one alien to the style of "Lethal weapon" the 2 cops had to support the one shoulder to the other to unravel a drug problem (as in vogue in the 1980s)(, where strange was the neighborhood in the world that did not have its commune of junkies telling you "Uncle Dame argo.")A tape which for me is a classic modern (I say modern although it already has a whopping 20 years), where James Caan, now fashion series "Las Vegas", accompanies Mandy Patikin, now fashion series "Criminal minds", secondary except for plenty of films of the 80's, including "The Princess Bride" (where was Iñigo Montoya).Makeup, that ran in charge of Stan Winston, father inter alia of the Terminators, or dinosaurs in "Jurassic Park", was then part of a television series, where the main plot of the film was lengthened during 21 episodes.The language spoken by the aliens slightly reminds the Aliens that Tim Burton translated it into "Mars Attack", mixed with splashes of German English, curious also is that most of the Martians on Earth acquire names of celebrities, and the soundtrack of the same is a retaila of music with synthesizer, cheap and effective, without a doubt.Finally, emphasize that argument that clears without deepening the theme of racism and xenophobia, being this, broadly speaking, one of the main problems in any society, and the presumption of equality between both sides, the Earth and the alien.Finally, finally, I only say I remember that film I started to make the shrimp (to my defense I will say that I only had 10 or 11 years) and that we almost miss the street. !What those times! And to think that I am that my 30 can not now stand at the "pipiolos" who make noise and bother me everywhere.</body>
</review>
