<review author="Jesus Lens" title="V de Vendetta" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Visual and pyrotechnic show of the first order, with a devilish pace and absorbent and addictive images</summary>
	<body>Now that channel four returns us "V", the mythical alien series starring that sinister eats small white mice, premieres on screen granda "V for Vendetta", the adaptation of Alan Moore and David Lloyd.Me graphic novel like to start this review by saying that "V for Vendetta". It's a peliculón as the top of a pine! Extraordinary. Excellent. Magnificent. Colossal. Well, all those readers who fear a possible spoiler or plot boycott already know our opinion. But, without going into the substance of the argument, the film traces that make sensational and wonderful comment.First, Natalie Portman. Personally, my film same, dress hat (Wayne, Bogart, Mitchum, etc.) or is photographed in white and black, with these muses of the noir genre, poignant and disturbing (Lauren Bacall, Gloria Graham, Gene Tierney.) But from that beheld "Leon the professional" I fell love with a young actress. fine has gone. In "V for Vendetta", Natalie is outstanding and the film, considering it is starring a subject camouflaged behind a mask of porcelain, needed the visible human face to prove credible and identifiable. And that was very special. Mission accomplished.Then, the film has managed to update the graphic novel on which it is based talking about some issues very topical. Firstly, the dismal work carried out by the media of mass communication, rather than inform, make propaganda. Secondly, illegal detention camps, Larkhill becoming a reflection of Abu Ghraib, sinister including hoods. Thirdly, fear of the other, the different, the immigrant.And the mega-macro-hyper Government conspiracies to perpetuate itself in power, reducing the freedom of its citizens to this supposed dichotomy Libertad-Seguridad. And the eternal controversy on whether violence is a legitimate method of self-defense or not. Where ends the hero and begins the activist? Where is the boundary between it and the terrorist?There are many and of much depth the issues raised "V for vendetta", and does so through a visual and pyrotechnic show of the first order, with a devilish pace and absorbent and addictive images.So, if the substance and the form are so good. Why has mounted in cholera Alan Moore, the father of the creature, before the final film product? Perhaps because they wanted to use his name to promote the film. Or, say others, because the character of V is less subtle on-screen in bullet, less ambiguous, more kind Hollywood hero.Perhaps so, but repudiating the adaptability and heaping abuse on the film, as did Moore, seems excessive. Because the film is excellent, because it points toward topical issues, because it takes clear party for democracy and freedom. and because Anuca and I we had as the Indians, in Neptune, enjoying an old-style adventure film!</body>
</review>
