<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Descubriendo a los Robinsons" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film animation from adults to children, but bearable. It has comic, tender, emotive and moments of action, as well as a couple of messages that always good recall. I was delighted.</summary>
	<body>Go ahead, as already know my dear readers, which I like more than a silly animated films a pencil. And if a good animation, join you an interesting plot, its fun moments, its intrigue, its sensitive moments, and a superemotivo end, because her pussy gives me palmas (with forgiveness). So now you know that I am nothing objective with these movies.The film is a child of 12 years who is orphan. His mother abandoned him at the door of the horfanato when he was only a baby, and he dreams of meeting her. In addition to this, it is inventor, with a gifted intelligence, what makes anyone you want to take. Neither he nor his roommate, a very rare kid. Total, which happens to invent something that extracts the memories of his mind, to get to know her mother. But the invention doesn't work very well, which makes him desist remain inventor, until a mysterious kid appears in his life.Well, as supondreis I loved. The beginning of the movie was very infantiloide and did me lose a little illusion, but shortly after this takes another pace, more imaginative and absurd, that I love. The animations are as always, the host by bicycle. The variety of characters usually I assumed a handicap, but find it me very successful. The plot is very good, perhaps too prepared for a film, with an adult can not bored. Moreover, there are two morals or conclusions that can be drawn from the film, and the two I like (see the movie and the know). What most surprised was that they sing at the end (or what I dreamed) given that no sticks to the rest.In short, animated from adults to children, but bearable. It has comic, tender, emotive and moments of action, as well as a couple of messages that always good recall. I was delighted.Very interesting.Besitos.P.D: not be if go to the specialist in compulsive "llorones during watching movies infantiles";-)</body>
</review>
