<review author="Luis Zueco" title="El buen pastor" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie is good, but who wait an adventure movie in the style of the "Holy" or "Case Bourne", precisely with the same actor will be disappointed. De Niro says ways, however will have to wait for new developments to see where can be reached.</summary>
	<body>Robert De Niro gets us into the dark world of the CIA, with the novelty that makes it at the root of this powerful spy agency, for years I control, led and put Presidents on half the world. The context is the end of the second world war and the Postguerra.Los actors are Matt Damon and Angelina Jolie in addition to the director, Robert De Niro. While it is a spy film isn't a spy to use film, because we are at the beginning of the CIA and this activity was not even as professional as today, and see scenes of family life, unthinkable for a spy in the modern world. There is le film sins of boring.In fact, Matt Damon seems anything but a spy, not be if in those early years of the CIA they were really so, but the truth is that more seems an official that a spy. But the truth is that the the idea that gives me spying in Spain. But the image that occurs in the film is always much more than one hero, especially in U.S.A. Not to mention that his relationship with Jolie is impossible to believe too you cold, too distant, too little credible that he not die for her. on the other hand is too ridiculous scenes, in which appears regalia. For me, the movie is quite good, highlights the anti-Castro operation of Bay of pigs, or rather his failure, which also marks the storyline of the plot, because they will think it fails because of a snitch that must be found.It is artistically appreciated the recreation of the London of the world war or the post-war Berlin.Highlight the important actors who appear in supporting roles: John Turturro, Alec Baldwin, Billy Crudup, William Hurt Tammy Blanchard, Michael Gambon and Joe Pesci. The movie is good, but who wait an adventure movie in the style of the "Holy" or "Case Bourne", precisely with the same actor will be disappointed.To be his second film as director, De Niro suggests ways, however we should expect new developments to see where you can get.</body>
</review>
