<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Concursante" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Her won't escape. His wit, his broad sense of the absurd, his narrative nerve, his original commissioning scene and its critical spirit, do contestant? apart from a Supreme divertimento - the best movie buff dish served in recent months. Almost, almost, compulsory viewing.</summary>
	<body>Martin circus Martin is a Professor of history of the economy which, incidentally and in a quiz show, has won a whopping € 3 million in the form of lavish gifts. Several cars, a yacht, a plane, a giant mansion. Overnight, it has become a billionaire envied by the rest of the planet but, however, it has a serious economic problem: does not have almost cash with which cope with the immense debt just contracting with Treasury. Overwhelmed by such imposition, decide use banking to request a credit of 100 thousand euros. Without being there, just put in the mouth of the Wolf.This is, in short, the basis on which sustains one of the best films of the current scene, contestant, a splendid title in all senses. Rodrigo Cortes, director and screenwriter, with his first feature film and after several experiences in the world of the film proves to be in possession of a sense of humor certainly enviable. His work is cynical, full, hurtful and, above all, fun. Hilarious and combative. From Fincher in the Club of the fight, no one had dared to dynamiting to so accurately as Cortés. its bank rate is fully accelerated. There are almost no breaks. And where they exist, are totally understandable. Flash back and voice resources used in off in an exemplary manner, without distorting or damage the story which he proposes. Contestant progresses and regresses in time, so clear and nothing messy. To the contrary, their comings and goings with the camera are the true body of the film and thereby, and the collaboration of an unsurpassed Leonardo Sbaraglia, manages to transfer to the viewer the State of distress and abatement that is suffering the overwhelmed Martin circus Martin. And is that Sbaraglia, on this occasion - aside from increasingly resemble Luis Figo-, has found the role (in capital letters) of his life, that of a character with which it is easy to identify. As well the film critic Alex Gorina, after leaving the press pass, commented "this is a title that engancharía a lot of people, that few are those who can not be reflected on screen: who more, who certainly had to resort once in their life to the Bank to apply for a loan or a mortgage".The idea of contestant may seem far-fetched, but it is not at all. It may be exaggerated, swollen, but the things that plasma are as is, although to the beast, magnified, so that anyone you escape the strong garrotazo of the Rodrigo Cortes to the world of the economy. Taxes, bank interest and the free market, jobs in the pillory for an intelligent and Kafkaesque, executioner Professor Edmund (who gives life the always effective Chete Lera), an economist, with a lot of terrorist, that offers an unforgettable class, practical and visual, about the universe of finance against. A master class, in the form of ingenious game of chess which, at the same time, serves as a tribute to the Monty Python to the very bergmaniana the seventh seal. What I say: wonderful.Her won't escape. His wit, his broad sense of the absurd, his narrative nerve, his original commissioning scene and its critical spirit, do contestant? apart from a Supreme divertimento - the best movie buff dish served in recent months. Almost, almost, compulsory viewing.Notice them: this film think pass list. And I marcaré his faults of assistance as a very serious sin.</body>
</review>
