<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Después de la boda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is obvious that Susanne Bier has not wanted to make a thriller, but in my opinion, some situations are misplaced - as the discourse of the bride in her wedding - and are at the service of a drama, which for me touches the melodrama.</summary>
	<body>The Danish films coming into our country are discussed between the family drama, the shameful secret and emotional autopsy. After the wedding he is no exception. Mads Mikkensen is very far away from the role that mostly we remind you: in Casino Royale as a torturer of Daniel Craig in pelotas starring that so memorable scene in the agent tied to a Chair laughs in the face of this evil poker player lose while it tells him something - so little Bond-like:?All know that you died scratching me the fuck?.A role radically opposed, with the same face of man with a past, here is a soul of charity. Literally, that you find in Mumbai at the head of an orphanage bode of the bankruptcy. One day, get the offer of a Danish millionaire offered a generous donation in return that he will visit him to his native Cophenague.Once in Europe, the philanthropist invites you without coming to tell at the wedding of his daughter and there the drama for Milkkensen is reunited with his past. I will not say more because if something is not liked anything about this film is that it is absolutely predictable. It is obvious that Susanne Bier has not wanted to make a thriller, but in my opinion, some situations are misplaced - as the discourse of the bride in her wedding - and are at the service of a drama, which for me touches the melodrama. That, or the Danes love to use the celebrations to dust off the skeletons in the closet.To me the film I did not bored but not excited me as I have read in other reviews. Do some I see that like when a film is Iranian and has gone to see original version is a masterpiece, I think many were excited by the mere fact of being in a? offcinema? listening to eloquent parliaments in Slavic language - or Mandarin. I prefer other works of the same writer as Mifune or Wilbur wants to commit suicide - also with Mikkensen-this Rosary of existential dialogues that I specifically left me pretty cold.However, he refuses well primarily because the actors are great and impeccably carry the weight of a film that was nominated for an Oscar as best foreign language film - snatched by the much more exciting and contained the lives of others - justísimamente. I put it on my list of films overvalued in the history of cinema with the strength of love and the club of dead poets. Here I am, as Daniel Craig tied to the Chair, waiting for the clubs that I will fall.</body>
</review>
