<review author="Alex Largo" title="El Motorista Fantasma (Ghost Rider)" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film, only to the quarter of an hour, is a real torture. Imagine, there is a moment in which the protagonist, the rider jumps 90 meters along above a few helicopters....</summary>
	<body>When I finished seeing this film, the truth, a smile of satisfaction on his face. Since then, the film I didn't (3/10 speaks for only), just know that I suddenly saw a unique opportunity for gutting a movie that any human being on earth it has been like.Below: "of how Alex shattered"Ghost Rider""Is impressive."as in only one word can describe all facets of a film that never should have come to theater screens" That Word is. crappy.I'm going to start by reventa you argument, whatever some clueless might be called "plot twists". It is not want to annoy you, just want to protect you against what could be the worst way to spend the money. watching "Ghost Rider".The old demon kills the father of the rider, the rider just busy with the reporter, which lives in the graveyard turns out to be a Ghost Rider, at the end, the son of the elder demon dies because the rider makes him "the look of no-be-what", the rider manages to jump the helicopters, the rider does not die at the end, but if it is left with "the curse of the rider" to help the people. I believe that this will be enough so you can not see the movie.According to the Wiki (Wikipedia), "A film is a sequence of photographic images taken with a camera, and presented through a projector." "Using a speed of replacement of images more than 18 frames per second, in the human eye creates the illusion of continuity, without interruption between each frame due to the persistence of vision", therefore, and unfortunately, to "Ghost Rider", you can (but shouldn't you) draw movie.Resolved this doubt. Let's talk about the film.The truth, I consider myself a person with patience when watching film, moreover, only in a movie (of which does not say his name) left the room before the end of the projection of the same. And truth, with Ghost Rider, I missed very little to give me a shut-eye.It is not for less, from the outset, Mark Stevens Johnson, responsible for the "creature", leaves us very clear we have made a clear mistake to see this movie. Attention to the death of the father with the bike. Let's be fair. Nobody dies for this reason. Up the spots of the National Directorate of traffic are better filmed, best mounted, and are certainly more spectacular. Another curious detail is the "spectacle" of the father and son, who demons would pay to see a display that make it up in the Park from near my house?Well, as I said. the work of Johnson is pathetic, what is more, from this moment so I named my favorite to win the Razzie for worst director this year (and the next, and the next, and the next.).Sigamos.la film, only to the quarter of an hour, is a real torture. Imagine, there is a moment in which the protagonist, the rider jumps 90 meters along above a few helicopters. As well, well known God all my being screamed: that the jump is short and that the helicopter blades mutilated his body. Yes, ladies and gentlemen, until that point the film makes us late.Another very funny thing is escenita on the road, when John Blaze ("prota"), try again with the heart of his beloved. If you make the mistake of seeing the film, deléitense with the escenita of the Kiss (by the way, half of that Kiss, there in a close-up of a cow mugiendo.) (Do not think that I am exaggerating).In short, we can say that the script itself. without cloths hot. It is shit. The script signs it the film's director, showing us that it is not worth or to write a fairly coherent script, abusing resources that make the heavier script as the repeat throughout the film of the phrase: "We must live without fear". Phrase in mouth of Nicolas Cage only becomes a stupidity to a more than what it is.Now let's talk of. of. the. actors?. No. as say it?. the people that put in front of the camera.Let's start with Nicolas Cage, that man that I hate with all my soul and my whole being. Cage, is dedicated to walk ahead of the camera always showing the same expression (that expression as yours that uses all films, whether a drama or a thriller).Eva Mendes, three quarters of the same, but fails at the end of Nicolas.En as the other actors in general. To shoot them all, but they do it better than Cage and Mendes together (imagine the "professionalism" of the cast).Another "remarkable" aspect are the special effects. It is true, they are not bad, but they are far from being made special effects and rights. All fairly salvageable is the soundtrack, which although people seem to excite this new work by Christopher Young, seems to me only normalillo pulling for good.In short, a film that the only thing deserving is rotting in an old warehouse.</body>
</review>
