<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Pudor" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Modesty rightly portrays the problems of incommunicado detention faced by society today and fear to express the feelings.</summary>
	<body>If there is something that characterises the Festival de Málaga, in addition to the obvious, it is its great commitment to new filmmakers, as each year exceeds the number of works that are in the festival. And things you have the cinema, it is increasingly common to see players behind the scenes (some with more success than others): last year was Carlos Iglesias, the previous year was Federico Luppi, a couple of years ago was Jordi Mollá? Now, Tristán Ulloa add to that list, that modesty is his directorial debut, not to mention his brother David Ulloa (filmmaker tanning in television), with which he has co-directed the film.Modesty is a story that speaks of the isolation many families live, whose members, despite living together, are in the most absolute solitude. A family consisting of a man who knows that he will die soon (Nancho Novo), a woman who receives anonymous erotic (Elvira Mínguez), a teenager with the doubts which leads to the age (Natalia Rodriguez), an old man that love gives you a second chance (Celso Bugallo) and a child who sees ghosts (Marcos Rúiz). Modesty portrays rightly problems of incommunicado detention faced by society today and fear to express feelings, even to the beings dear and close. Despite the turn taking some of the stories at any time the film falls into sentimentality cheap. It's a very intimate film, shot with great modesty and respect for the characters and their emotions. One of the few buts can put you the film is in some moments of the dramatic knot pace lapses, and the story is slightly thick. At all times, the film conveys a great feeling of verisimilitude and proximity, with a few characters very well built, with which people can identify. Much of the merit of the credibility of the whole her deserve their actors, very well directed by Tristán Ulloa, which highlights a splendid Nancho Novo (calling loudly a nomination on the Goya), in one of his best performances to date.</body>
</review>
