<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Plan oculto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Torrent of images, dialogs and confusing situations with echoes and resonances of that mythical 'Usual suspects'</summary>
	<body>Is it true that Spike Lee, answer fly of African-American cinema par excellence, had been launched to shoot a classic thriller, a story of cops and robbers, without more? I wanted to believe it, but I couldn't. Those who have been following these reviews know that I like the film engaged with the reality and the society that surrounds us, but also know that, beyond the content of the film, what really matters to me is that the story is well told. And well shot.Therefore, although much of Lee's recent projects were interesting on paper, its translation into celluloid was quite bland, boring and failed. So I wanted to see good Spike with a film genre, beyond one of its inevitable films of thesis on the violated rights of the poor black man of modern America.The interest to see "Hidden Plan" was to grow as types of criterion as solvent as José Luis Muñoz, Álvaro, Rash and Miranda were glosando its good qualities and strengths, but the irrepressible desire to go to Cinema 2000 Neptune I invaded when the own Miranda, in the middle of a generous grilled meat, we connected via mobile phone with this musical joy which is the song "Chaiyya Chaiyya Bollywood Joint"performed by Sukhwinder Singh and Sapna Awasthi which opens and closes the film.Therefore, nothing more return of Sitges, Anuca and I went to see the movie with Spike Lee. and really enjoy her as guys kids, watching us swept away by the torrent of images, dialogs and confusing situations prepared by the writer of the film, with echoes and resonances of that mythical "Usual suspects", but passed by the traumatic post 11-S, the war of Iraq and the kidnapping and execution of hostages by the Taliban.But we are going with a bit of order. And concert. Suddenly, in the central Office of a well-known American Bank, based in the heart of New York, come masked guys and commit a robbery, leaving with more than fifty hostages between workers and clients. The police moves (and how moves that poli's Mayor Giulianni, with trucks, cars, assault, etc. commands) and sends one of their specialists in kidnappings. and the mess begins.A mess based on the classic who's who and why does what you are doing? Come into play ancient secrets buried, intriguing and enigmatic negotiators external, spatio-temporal games and a wide battery of narrative resources of all kinds that make the two hours of footage to pass in a sigh.The cast is impressive. Denzel Washington to Christopher Plummer through a surprising Jodie Foster, Willem Dafoe always disturbing and coriaceous Clive Owen. Up the footballer Vinnie Jones reveals his fronted become police assault.</body>
</review>
