<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Shooter: El Tirador" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Shooter: The shooter is a new and horrifying example of the action movie produced by Hollywood: a myriad of Visual stunts without ton haphazardly, with the sole purpose of stun and confuse the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>Today make a decent, already not good action film, is a genuine mission impossible, and not the majaderías palomiteras of Tom "sells-lo-to-sea" Cruise. Therefore, each new action by-product filling by the factories of Hollywood is a new experiment to attract an audience already jaded so photocopy.Although seems lie say a tape of action, Shooter: the shooter is based on a Pulitzer Prize-winning novel, which leads to a couple of interesting and deep thoughts, to which more ponderous. The first is to save himself who can!, because the film may be the most grotesque displayed on a screen of film since the retirement of Bud Spencer and Terence Hill. And the second is how low have fallen the past prestigious Pulitzer prizes. Because promotional machinery apart, and always bridging the gap, Shooter: the shooter is a crude approach to Rambo, i.e. to Rambo. After such an approach, it is inevitable to think that Training Day was no more than an accident in the career of a director who has in his filmography real jewels of tears of the Sun cult, King Arthur or the short The Call, pseudopublicitario mystery made exclusively for the internet. But we must be fair, the new work by Antoine Fuqua has given us really essential scenes, and that thanks to the tape we have discovered that due to the cross point anyone is able to extract a bullet as the painted. Not to mention the rest of pearls in the form of lapidary phrases that leave Harry Callahan in a fervent pacifist.Ultimately, Shooter: the shooter is a new and horrifying example of the action movie produced by Hollywood: a myriad of Visual stunts without ton haphazardly, with the sole purpose of stun and confuse the Viewer. Not to mention all the aura of patriotism usamericano surrounding the film, as tiresome as unbearable.</body>
</review>
