<review author="Bloody Will" title="Shooter: El Tirador" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>?Shooter: the shooter? It is a film of the lot, not higher than the average, but that does not mean that one will sleep after paying 6 euros and peak.</summary>
	<body>I have a serious problem of critical decision with this film. It is not to raise me put her back and a half by poor quality or bad performances, although it is really so, but is that not being no wonder, at the end I has been entertaining, and is one of those mysteries surrounding the film buff tastes of each. ?Shooter: the shooter? It is a film of the lot, not higher than the average, but that does not mean that one will sleep after paying 6 euros and peak. One of the major problems facing this film is its director, Antoine Fuqua, and taste so good that he left after?Training Day? or?King Arthur?. So one hopes that this form of cinema extends his following works, but as it happens with all directors, always be flaque.In?Shooter: the shooter? Fuqua has encountered a very bad adaptation of a novel, and that brings consequences. Without having read one captures that events, and not the action unfolds so fast that sometimes leaves a few startling gaps. If we had that prosecute the film for his screenplay pararíamos not remove defects, but even so, the way that Fuqua attempts to save the dishes is very commendable. Get a history requetevista and atolondrada give a rate that does not convert its 120 minutes in a unbeatable drink.If you have seen the trailer, practically you have seen the film. They are two pillars on which the film unfolds: an old retired military is betrayed by the Government to endorse a dead, and their endless flight will find in a good ally for desenmascar the plot.How many movies have seen with equal history, too. Do the initial sequence is a classic of? here smells like dead?. The next half hour is the ABC of Government treason USA and the escape and revenge is book. Nor has it?Shooter: the shooter? surprising to leave you open-mouthed, elements and the conclusion is more than predictable, but I feel hopelessly attracted to the development for a good reason: that touch of John Rambo has the film. Do do I missed already the persimmon along with foliage of the forest, where a hidden shooter is brushing one by one without dialogue, and to cure thugs? home? the wounds of the protagonist only lacks see Whalberg biting a machete. What memories.Unlike of?Do Training Day?, Fuqua has put in hand more explosions than dialectical warfare, but is that counting Mark Whalberg in superb physical condition leads to punches, kicks and other caresses are luxury. Nevertheless, and at the level of interpretation, is not the best film of Whalberg. A plain script and a sometimes stupid sentences leaves him as a mass of muscles with a target style of the donkey with the carrot ahead. Michael Peña is the another prota, and highlight your scene with a gimmick that seem designed by the very same Jigsaw. Elias Koteas, who gets in this film is as schizophrenic federal agent with an ending worthy of entering the Gallery of?Best execution?. Danny Glover is not a paragon of phrases of Oscar, and the girl, Kate Mara can do little other than put face of scared. Be grateful to see Ned Beatty.Tras read all this perhaps you can explain to me why so much debate between the Yes or no. Sometimes I think it has more eighties dyes than a film of action more according to the times, but even this approach has done that we do not see a new show of fireworks without sense. It is a good action movie, but it is not the movie's action this season. I have seen it to evade me awhile, and it has taken effect. For lovers of the genre of shooting distance or very loving of the anatomy of Whalberg.</body>
</review>
