<review author="Yul B." title="Cerdos salvajes" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For some time I not laughed out loud in the cinema, but I do not take it as good. It is a film of the lot.</summary>
	<body>I am an approved high for this film. For some time I not laughed out loud in the cinema, and that is not easy to get a public tired of cheap comedietas.You know the Act of faith that I had to see this film. I have assumed that everything that smacks of Travolta is essential viewing for marital prescription and?Wild pigs. With a couple? from wheels? It would not be an exception.But this time I have not suffered so much. Conversely, at various times of the film I was about to throw me to the ground of laughter; and stating that I was not the only one, because the reaction of the rest of the public of the room, including my santa, was completely synchronized to each gag and each mess Quartet protagonist that it was prepared to cause such hilarious effect.However, despite the compliments that I just throw, I do not take it as a good movie. It has undesirable gaps in script, bad few situations and dialogues of the sea bream (which attributed in part to the unexplained loose dubbing), that break in a sharp way the good vibes in general transmitting the footage.For starters, the presentation of the main characters is very clumsy and without spark of grace, a detail that makes it start on the wrong foot. I think that aimed to its director, Walt Becker, is to teach with some humor to the viewer the life so boring to have Doug (Tim Allen), Woody (John Travolta), Bobby (Martin Lawrence) and Dudley (William H. Macy) which want to evade making a journey in 7 days bike by the country; and my personally not sack me or a smile.Does this unfortunate start made me fear a meltdown because expected that were going to swallow us one?Norbit? in power, or what is the same, a film that makes you grace to its director and his team more direct (for rally), and to no one else.But its course changes just when it begins the journey of our biker. From great scenes that make you laugh until no more power there occur (in which for my absolute protagonist is the character of Dudley), which reassures (at times), with other sequences that make cry of how bad they are, matter that keeps you on alert for a possible bajonazo of the divertimento.Do do these ups and downs, often changing the pace of the mood of the spectator, he placed this film the title of King of the movies? heap?. Not because is it more? heap? in all, but because raises a little head as all of them. It will convert effortlessly in a fun, endless passes television clasicón, ideal for evenings dumb pipes and camilla table skirt.If you had to rate each of the four? floats? These notes would be the role of 1 to 10.Tim Allen, I put a 3. Completely out of place, recently and literally eaten by the interpretation of the rest of the band. Often portraying Santa Claus him has diminished its artistic powers.To John Travolta, a 5 raspao; Do have seen you more loose and best comic vis in less profitable products as?Do look who's talking?, as amazing as?Do Pulp Fiction?, or as indifferent as?Be Cool?. That Yes, are we put the willies of emotion when go you the legs to dance (in a scene his character Woody Dudley teaches a few steps to conquer a girl, the eternally attractive Marisa Tomei).Martin Lawrence, I give a 4 high. It takes little to walk that thug style which has been exhibited in his films blockbuster (?)Do thief police?,?Is this grandmother a danger? or?(Do two policemen rebel?). I saw low way, and a little fondón, do not know if it's because it was the script that overweight.And, finally, William H. Macy, a 9. Great, the soul of the film; the best scenes they have left him it. Personified clumsiness performed so absolutely elegant. Here has proven me to be a SUV.Outside this group, I would stress to Ray Liotta, with that face of pimp who has provided that it scares. Ideal in his role as biker thug eager to free-for-all.Done the review end of rigor I can only say one thing: throw toss the viewing of this film, and if you have to go to see her try to enjoy it to the fullest forgiving the shortcomings that I have mentioned, because you going to laugh to mogollon.</body>
</review>
