<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Alpha Dog" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An interesting film; a different way and original of telling a story already seen several times on the big screen. A criticism of an empty youth and without aspirations; of those teenagers who have had everything from his early childhood.</summary>
	<body>Two years after the sweetened the diary of Noa, Nick Cassavetes returns to the address with a completely opposite to this, Alpha Dog title. Slightly inspired by a real case, the filmmaker - also screenwriter on this occasion - takes to devise a cruel portrait on the more posh adolescence of Palm Spring focusing also on the influence parents (directly or indirectly) on their children. And all this makes rhythm of thriller; a thriller that never hides influences from films such as two days in the Valley and, above all, of the magnificent The Chumbscrubber, a product that was not released in Spain and which, fortunately, ended up being released on DVD.Youth gangs, drug war between bands, sex, violence, an atypical abduction and a deadly misunderstanding, are the main thematic ingredients that supports Alpha Dog. As was the case in the Brick failed, those who manage the roost are almost immature young, but in contrast to this, not intended to any forced homage to film noir, because the interest of Cassavetes lies in mostar, clearly, that the threads that move the actions of its teenage protagonists are managed by their own parents. This has (almost anecdotal) presence of a splendid Bruce Willis, Sonny Truelove in the film, a dealer of marijuana that hiding their craft using his son Johnny (a surprising Emile Hirsch) as main camel; a young man totally independent, with a large group of boys acting as hired assassins at your service and ready to mount any chicken to the minimum of change. A new Tony Montana has just been born.Raised as a false story, Cassavetes is interspersed with small fragments of television interviews conducted to the protagonists of the film. This makes it in a moderate way, not abused at all and with the intention of putting the Viewer on the track of what you will discover during the following minutes of projection. Step by step, step to step, filmmaker is shaping a tragedy Sung some time before. You don't want to catch anyone by surprise. And when that time comes, it does somewhat surreal, as if it were a children's story. Breaks the naturalness and realism that sketched the film for, at that moment, give it an extremely dreams to the situation: one night bluish and crashed, a Rocky Mountain and three characters face to face. Consciously, the night is one chroma cantankerous and the mountain a simple decor of papier-mache. Somewhat curious soften a brutal act.An interesting film; a different way and original of telling a story already seen several times on the big screen. A criticism of an empty youth and without aspirations; of those teenagers who have had everything from his early childhood, and to those who are not interested in anything else other than their own well-being; "well-being" in quotes, the only have known since childhood and thanks to his "great" (also quoted) parents. Drugs, alcohol, ultra-modern mansions and luxury cars: the comfort of the villains. Not only the purria know make a fist with a weapon. And this proves perfectly Nick Cassavetes in Alpha Dog. pity that mazacote make-up and false Gill who, towards the end of the tape, you encasquetan an aged Sharon Stone. Pity, I repeat, because all the rest (and despite its simplicity) works and fits perfectly.</body>
</review>
