<review author="Antoni Messa" title="La flauta mágica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite the undeniable Office invested in its realization (for me the highlights of the film), the magic flute is aimed at a very specific audience. They can hardly connect and enjoy with her who, like a server, have certain problems with Opera.</summary>
	<body>Firstly, I must admit that I have never liked the Opera. It has always seemed a musical genre bombastic and overloaded. Perhaps for this reason that, faced with the adaptation of the flute magic performed by Kenneth Branagh, I aburriese in a sovereign manner in the film.I can assure you that it is not fault of the script or actors, and much less than the work of British director, because the latter, in particular, shows extremely splendid. Their visual capacity and virtuosity with which the camera leads are of exquisite quality and a technicality. The lengthy and meticulous flat sequence that opens the film, for example, is worthy to be included in any anthology of the seventh art self-respecting. It is clear that the problem is entirely mine. And is that the Opera and I are not made for each other.Filmed entirely in studies and set between France and Germany during the first world war, through this priceless flat initial sequence already mentioned, Branagh made an extensive tour among French trenches, inside and cliffs follow the flight of several birds; faced with a large air Squadron; low back to Earth to show the enemy troops, and after several and amazing acrobatics more, ends that visual walk - by way of Overture-in the same trench in which began it. To get the hat. A wonder for whose realization had to dip the digital technology; the only way to be able to orchestrate an as captivating as this planning.The rest of his footage - cinematically speaking – is not so spectacular, despite having an attractive scenery cared for to the smallest detail. Avoids deliberately turn your camera in the main spotlight of the magic flute, giving the role to the music that Mozart composed in 1971 with the libretto by Emanuel Schikaneder, and how not, to the splendid showcasing (according to connoisseurs of the genre) of the singers chosen for the occasion.Anyway, the operatic most purists, have criticized the decision to have been sung in English rather than opt for the original German. I do not know if happened the same when, in 1975, the reputed and untouchable Ingmar Bergman (uncredited) performed an adaptation, aimed at the television screen, the same work.A tale of love, magic and music, combining perfectly the passages most colorful and festive with a good number of flashes dark and macabre. A work that departs radically from the usual view that the film has the Shakespearean director, and he takes it - by placing the action in the middle of a war contest - to launch a hopeful song of harmony and peace, very consistent with the rough current political and global scene. Despite the undeniable Office invested in its realization (for me the highlights of the film), the magic flute is aimed at a very specific audience. They can hardly connect and enjoy with her who, like a server, have certain problems with Opera. I tried it. And trancas and barrancas, I overcame more than more than two hours of duration. The visual charm of Branagh luck!</body>
</review>
