<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Balas sobre Broadway" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Woody Allen dismantles the intimate mechanisms of artistic creation. Masterpiece, deep reflection on the fringes of the art and the divinity of the artist....</summary>
	<body>With bullets over Broadway, Woody Allen desempacha cargo sentimental (Mia Farrow dressed in toga and mallet) and affiliates new and joyously to what he likes most and what more truly brilliant flashes shines his talent cinematógrafico: comedy. It flows cynical and blithely through the usual byways of the genus, but Allen, in love with the roaring as, its syncopated music and its perfidious choreography gross mobsters and without scruples and loggerhead damita filled with beads, negotiates with the viewer a subtle treatment: I give you a comedy so you throw a few laughs, but you let me as the view of intellectual satire on the vagaries of artistic creation. That is, ultimately, what most concerned Director New York, who recruits a spectacular cast (Cusack, Wiest and Palminteri, estelarmente all) representing a group of actors on Broadway of these agitated 20, overrun by cazurra interference of some gangsters more worried about a few lines in a booklet to a charger in the knickers with astonishing naturalness.Woody Allen is metaproyecta in David Shayne (John Cusack) and even another face us, made to see the face of Woody Allen even if not, don't need much to find the gestures that betray him, their neurotic tics, his hypochondria tendency to intelectualizar the gags and its territory of aesthetic influence fragilísimo.The purity and integrity of the artist committed to his work is desnucada when appears a capo of the mafia (the unpayable and regular Joe Viterelli) interested purposes cover theatrical mounting with right to her lover (the recklessness Jennifer Tilly) have their piece of paper. For anything out of what has been agreed by the mafioso, Cheech (Chezz Palminteri), his second, we who oversee the righteousness of the work and the dramatic demands of his boss, which become absurd, desajustadas of good taste.This plot Peripeteia enables that Woody Allen desenmascare the frivolities of the artist and the idea of that, as we will know his personality, acquire the true extent of his farce of his deception: in this case with the pardillo and paid Yes Shayne. Bullet on Broadway characters are, in the opinion of the own Allen: "intellectuals of coffee they are spent time making questions like what saved first, works of Shakesperare or the life of a stranger?" I loved that his works were rejected, suffer and so go hungry already that it gave them the status of artists, but the truth is that being an artist is a matter of chance, a happy accident of birth. Live as an artist not equals to handle disguised pathetic histrionic situations or events of frivolous nature that celan highly reprehensible or even criminal, behavior manifested once the enormous love of the author towards the theatre scenes, to the small eccentricities of the artist touched by the numen, or believed played by him be "This masterpiece of Woody, perfect vehicle."Woody Allen unmounted (also now says deconstructs it sounds more airtight) the intimate mechanisms of artistic creation, the unique talent and way, deliver a new catalog of wonderful, always escorados to the cartoon, but human beings clearly categorizables to its arrobada audience of faithful.</body>
</review>
