<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="El buen pastor" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The good Shepherd is a film honored and calmly shot (to exceed shamelessly in your footage), which unlike Munich becomes bitter and painful in its final resolution, without leaving glimmer to any hope. Employees of God.</summary>
	<body>Munich and the good Shepherd share (it is not basking that both proposals take ink from Eric Roth) some other air of family, especially by his will for humanizing - without falling into the moral justification - the life of such dark and presumably terrifying as the CIA or Mossad intelligence services. And they do so without stress in excess his gaze on the historical or political plot, but rather decline the camera towards the emotional consequences that the activities of these individuals to breed, as a terrible Leviathan that devours any glimmer of humanity in them, taking after Yes love, family and friends. The virtuality of the life of the agent becomes real-life, supposedly real and happy, is shown as a subtle lie that remain for the greater glory of the power that protects.The good Shepherd, however, raises that dialectical binomial life apparent real-vida (together with verdad-falsedad and confianza-traición) not as metaphors that can only be applied to the emotional world of his characters. On the contrary, De Niro aims through these binomials make us reflect on the nature of power, exemplified in one of its most effective employees: the CIA (Central Intelligence Agency), created in 1947, from the Office of strategic services (OSS), founded by "Wild Bill" Donovan, Catholic Irish, played by De Niro himself. An agency fueled by the future cream of America, composed almost exclusively by white men belonging to the?Ivy League? (elitist Association of eight universities of the East Coast), considered the best of States Unidos.En the good Shepherd looms the thesis according to which is from this elite aristocratic, mercantilist and with certain religious fundamentalism-laden dyes is built where the power of the United States. However, De Niro must moderate its critical discourse (by attend a patriotic box office?, by pressure from the producers?, by self-censorship?, who knows!) and allows politically correct licenses, mixed with lucid reflections of right bitterness. Among those we find recreation light of the controversial character of the creator of the CIA, which looms more as an old man suffering from gout and welfare of the American people, in favour of democracy against the totalitarian of the Agencia.Pero power always this not worthy if we take into account the considerations presented in such revealing scenes as the interview to the Italian-American (excellently played by an aging Joe Pesci), in which James Wilson reveals that America is for Americans (white and wealthy, God-fearing), and not for immigrants, mere visitors without decision (remember that De Niro himself is of Italian origin). Or that sad but revealing final, in which an impassive (bland up walking) Damon shamelessly burns the letter his father wrote before committing suicide. Do de Niro knows than reality? created by established power, that which devours its employees without possible reference - is imposed (anyone can request accounts to God!). He knows that Wilson elected to continue under the heat of the Agency, reproducing the farce until his death, before returning to his life, that which already hardly remember anything, except the memory of that true love of youth. Why returns the string to that radiant Martina Gedeck (also seen in the lives of others). Why outlines that ironic smile to read this verse of San Juan (8, 32) at the door of the building of the newly renovated Agency: "And you will know the truth and the truth shall set you free". And that is why the last frame outlines the cold figure of Wilson sank after this hive of offices.The good Shepherd is a film honored and calmly shot (to exceed shamelessly in your footage), which unlike Munich becomes bitter and painful in its final resolution, without leaving glimmer to any hope. Do it nobody redeems, everyone accepts without blinking? as if a Greek tragedy were - its role in the world that the Agency has issued them. Until the Professor of poetry prefers to follow his destiny to return to their classes at the University. Only the female characters seem to be aware of the sacrifice which is a life as well, or living outside their destructive machinery. The wife of Wilson? a Jolie more than correct - detects the Covenant which sellaba marrying an employee of God from the beginning. And already evening flees; only the distance avoids being devoured by insomnia and disaffection.In Munich, Spielberg (and with him Roth) prefers to advocate for a more idealistic and compromised resolution. In the good Shepherd nobody can escape, because God is omnipotent, omniscient and has the gift of ubiquity. There are no gaps for the confidence that the father of Wilson begged (like a prayer) to his autistic son. Maybe De Niro leaves too much oxygen to the Viewer to let live the son of Wilson. Perhaps all should pay the price for ever be human.By the way, a perfect musical nod of the scene in which some children sing choir ' You have the whole world in your hands' ('have the whole world in your hands') while the two agents (CIA and KGB) conspire on the future of the world. And great Ovid's quote: "Of your desires will be owner." I caught dust showed him a handful: few have bodies that dust, so many birthday to me I reached, vain, I begged him. "I went to ask young people also hereafter these years: with everything he gave me them, and eternal youth, if his Venus suffered."Those who decided to be used of God know that you can never look back, you never know how to cry their eyes, how loves without network, nor knows how a drink shared with friends. The State (the good Shepherd) should be cold and cruel, impassive to any desire, if their children (their innocent sheep) can sleep quiet and warm in the stable that protects them. Though this law we shrink the heart, indigne our sense of Justice, each and every one of us are to a greater or lesser extent employees of God for fear of losing his asylum and protection.</body>
</review>
