<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Pudor" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The existential crisis of maturity are more bearable when the narrates a Kevin Spacey who lives in an American urbanization or travelling in a yellow van. When the props are the dishes of Duralex and stage a district very similar to ours, we are too familiar and escuecen more.</summary>
	<body>Modesty is not a drama, they are five specifically. Ulloa - David and Tristan - brothers after the short film cycle return to work together to produce a film of those who leave bitter taste and not invite you to recommend it - despite being pretty good - because they incite to self-destruction and spend the night in the bar in the corner.The story focuses on a family on the edge of the precipice. Grandmother just died, the father discovers that there are six months of life, the wife feels ninguneada and is it mounted on their own, the daughter enters puberty with very bad foot and as if this were little, the child occasionally? looks dead. As is.It is true that all this can happen - well, about the child only to Bruce Willis - but as moving footage, such misfortunes cluster becomes quite unpalatable and is missing some nice situation for distendir the environment and a better, if end well I guess that it is from the book on which is based the fillmeno longer see light at the end of the tunnel.The Ulloa brothers have done a job on family held incommunicado, the things that we take it as understood and not say out loud and how can we become unknown to those who surround us. Something exaggerated in my opinion, already to survival leads us to seek us routes exhaust make us more or less bearable the existence and in the case of the protagonists of modesty, their distractions only serve to accentuate its shortcomings, with what the remedy that the disease is worse.The existential crisis of maturity are more bearable when the narrates a Kevin Spacey who lives in an American urbanization or travelling in a yellow van. When the props are the dishes of Duralex and stage a district very similar to ours, we are too familiar and escuecen more. But while in American Beauty or Little Miss Sunshine scripts has an important - and essential - component of black humor, on modesty, is conspicuous by its absence.The actors, except the children, are great. Nancho Novo changing registration completely and Elvira Mínguez, reaffirms the role mature in emotional bankruptcy. All very content, as well as conducting and music, the film is intentionally sober and stark. The camera plays an important role because it puts us in a position of voyeurs. The viewer has the feeling be spying on the characters and have crept up in the privacy of your bathroom. On the other hand, some stories and situations are too well-worn and that of the child directly, spare.</body>
</review>
