<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Misión imposible 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To see if it will now have to apologize for entertain the public with dignity...</summary>
	<body>Let's go by parts: has dispatched critical this third segment of the saga of "Mission impossible" Kashmiris it, disparagingly, as "pure entertainment". So what? Pure entertainment are not masterpieces such as "Treasure island", "Journey to the center of the Earth" or "Moby Dick"? To see if it will now have to apologize for entertain the public with dignity.Having said that, do not want to say that "Mission: Impossible III" is a masterpiece, or much less: it has great strength in an electrifying start, reminiscent of the best Tarantino sadomasochism, and continues with good pulse, with action scenes splendidly settled, such as the persecution of the helicopters in the field of ghostly mills of wind or the fighter attack on the bridge. Then certainly the tone decays, especially when we have to begin to explain the reasons for the betrayals (what would the series, despite the quasi redundancy, without betrayal), but even so the tone is, in general, satisfactory. There, it is true, reading about issues, but nor asked, as no one in their right mind is what he had asked, in due course, to the splendid eponymous television series that arrulló children's dreams of an entire generation that today is (or appears to be). adult.They are, of course, the typical facial masks that hide figures, which is one of the "leitmotif" inevitable in the series, both television and film, and there is certainly impossible scenes, such as balancing the hero of a building to another in Shanghai, with free fall through an inclined roof, a nonsense of impossibility, but that is more alluring. So things, J.J. Abrams, the creator of series televisvas of worship as "Lost", is confirmed as a man of good pulse also as director, which is his first big screen film. Cruise is already very secure in his role as Ethan Hunt, which he has taken the measure, and is convincing. But what takes the cake is, certainly a Philip Seymour Hoffman, newly oscarizado by "Truman Capote", which makes here a villain that leave footprint: cold, absolutely devoid of scruples and feelings, a bad beast with esmóquin that may require from a post in the Olympus of the big bad of the film.</body>
</review>
