<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Isi Disi: Alto voltaje" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Comedy to the torrent which did very good box office in his day. It has a sole motivation, the fun to the Viewer, beyond of hidden aspirations. Escape completely American stereotypes, as she proclaims.</summary>
	<body>Saturday morning, the baby rises to an immoral hour from any point of view. My medium Zucchini tells me to "go down, now I'm going". While I realize counts that I have cheated as a Chinese and that it has been sleeping. It's okay, I'm a Daddy with resources. I rebusco in the deuvedeteca something that can be educational for the small and I find nothing more and nothing less than the second part of the movie of Florentine and Segura. This is educational 100%, that verily I.The film is about a group of jevis calling the dead rat. By avatars of fate, faced with a stratospheric fine, leading them to participate in a new television contest seeking the heavy ever more brutal rock band. But after this, hide the Machiavellian ideas of a billionaire, who only wants to enrich themselves at the expense of these pringá you.I like these films, given that they are made by and for the divertimento. They have everything to like me, like women in leather, grumosos, dropping and famous jokes in various roles, cañamero humor, etc. I think that not me djo nothing. The argument is unimportant, although it has a script which continues at least in a straight line, with a small meltdown in the latter part. Famous payroll is very good, the stream style, with Luis Coll (in his last movie) of drunk, porn stars of porn actresses, Gran Wyoming wrong that acts of wonder, Arévalo of police (this not killing me), and a few more we should go looking for them (such as Mono Burgos). Not be why, but I left the box throughout the film, while the baby looked at hallucinating.In short, comedy to the torrent which did very good box office in his day. It has a sole motivation, the fun to the Viewer, beyond of hidden aspirations. Escape completely American stereotypes, as she proclaims.It is bad to die, but I I mondé laughter.Besitos.P.D: For more than 300 reviews I started the blog with the first part of this precisely. As time goes on.</body>
</review>
