<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La bicicleta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film tells three stories which link in common is the bicycle. To see a Sunday morning while you play with your baby and is too early to have any kind of programming on TV. Long roll.</summary>
	<body>Already a few months ago I got an invitation to a preview of those that bombard us from muchocine. The film was called the bicycle and had a synopsis as exciting as reading the readings of the boats of shampoo when you go to the bathroom and you forget the brand. Today I'm back to being duped by the medium Zucchini "Ve" down now will I and I decided the baby must have a complete film training, so I think that this is well complemented by yesterday (Isi &amp; Disi high voltage), right?The film tells the stories of three characters whose only link is a Dutch style bike (so they say). The bicycle is assumed to be the same (according to the synopsis, but cannot be), so the three stories live at different levels of space time, and unite to try to make this something of interest. A child trafficker, a Messenger girl and an elderly woman with new illusions are the conductive threads of the three.Puff, this is unbearable. To begin with, ICO funds already pulling me backwards. It begins the film and leave a few children of actors having left a camera, but nothing more. Then go about adults which is not to know Act for nothing. Luckily we have a couple of big players, that you like or not, admittedly they are. Sancho Gracia and Pilar Bardem. The stories do not have greater interest, and only the revindicativo sediment of the use of the bicycle against the tyranny of the oil. Nothing else, is that it is not even touching.In short, film which tells three stories which link in common is the bicycle. To see a Sunday morning while you play with your baby and is too early to have any kind of programming on TV. Long roll.Very weak, very weak.Besitos.P.D: It should be mandatory that all films made with funds ICO action scenes with actors and actresses in porretas. At least, though we we smell it is going to be shit, remove a joy for the visual.Pd2: Sure he likes to my</body>
</review>
