<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="River Queen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film of great plastic beauty (for his photography, scenery and success in the direction), well performed (including young Rawiri penis) and although dull at times, well told. Since then it does not shine too, but it was satisfactory.</summary>
	<body>Welcome to New Zealand. Forget about everything for a couple of hours and feel his armchair becomes a canoe. The visit, in the hands of Samantha Morton (in the role of Sarah O'Brien), will lead us along the Whanganui River, located in the National Park of Whangui (World of humanity, by the way). Do not think that working for a travel agency Commission, simply seems to me the locations of River Queen are one of its best attractions.The new film by Vincent Ward (Más allá de los sueños, the map of the human heart), shot with the blessing and participation of several Maori peoples, tells the story of a young Irish daughter of settlers. Halfway between two cultures and in the middle of a war between the British and native, Sarah he falls for a Maori with whom he has a son. After the death of his beloved, the most heartbreaking moment of his life get to see that the small Boy is kidnapped and taken up the river by his Maori grandfather. Here begins a bitter search and, after that, the story of a long-awaited as disappointing reunion. The time has passed and both she and her son have changed a lot.River Queen is a history of searches, not only that of a child, but of internal cultural identification searches. Sarah lives hell of having to choose between two realities which co-exist, but mutually incompatible. Although the tape has a fairly predictable ending, it is interesting to follow the ires and goings of the protagonist and one wondered to what extent will be that of "are is not where it was born, but where pace", or of "If you can't with the enemy, join him".The pace is somewhat slow in general, and the motivations of the characters are not always clear, but its aesthetic appeal is often offset these faults. On the other hand, almost at the level of cultural enrichment, we will have the opportunity to deepen customs and rites of the Maori people. In this regard, appreciates the work of Ward and his team for showing as is, without major pretensions.Ultimately, who are encouraged to see it will be with a film of great plastic beauty (for his photography, scenery and success in the direction), well performed (including young Rawiri penis) and although dull at times, well told. Since then it does not shine too, but it was satisfactory.</body>
</review>
