<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Moscow Zero" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Movie galleries and underlays, tells us that there is a world under the cities and that almost better not visit it. It is not bad, can be seen, tells a curious story and is very dark. I liked.</summary>
	<body>Once seen the movie, what you were looking for the cover to put it, I have encountered some data of the film. One says that it is shot in Moscow, as the name of the film implies, but I asked me, why are there thanks to the end the city of Valencia, its police, its paellas and up to the fallera mayor? I think that it was shot in Valencia, but not me do much attention. Incidentally, the Director has a very nice nickname, moon, what does if not see that it was shot in Valencia, or the Moon of Valencia is not famous? The festival of humor here, concludes I swear it.The film is about a researcher type who gets in subsurface soils of Moscow to discover a very strange story about men, marginal and demons. Everything is born from the era of the tsars, but it is shot in modernity. As it seems that it takes to return the waiter, mounted an expedition consisting of a priest, a girl, a resentful researcher and two thugs who do not have nor media host (one is Arturo helmsmen, camera Café). And they get into the subsurface, Hey, are excavated almost almost to the center of the Earth, and then they get with the works of the Gallardon. do well what you want to say you? To me the movie I liked, coinciding with my medium Zucchini. Fear, what is said of fear, is not. Come on, I have not heard that it was scary until I have not read a critique that put "of terror". The interesting thing is the story told, through the reading of a book on the events that occurred in that place and led to what happened next. The choice of actors is not bad, and Mr Kilmer should go to Corporación Dermoestética to slices, do you that does not fit into the plane. What I did not like nothing at all is that is so dark. I prefer a little less than environment and that will see better what happens.In short, movie galleries and underlays, tells us that there is a world under the cities and that almost better not visit it. It is not bad, can be seen, tells a curious story and is very dark. I liked.You have to be generous, to one that has funds of all and I liked.kisses.</body>
</review>
