<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Anacondas: la cacería por la orquidea sangrienta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Crappy, crappy, crappy, crappy, crappy, crappy, crappy, crappy, crappy.</summary>
	<body>Seven were the writers recruited to give birth the monstrosity. One with the head would have been enough. The descabezados who have perpetrated this abomination of film have not resorted to copy previous films of similar matter: have embarked on the Pilgrim idea of making a new film (according to the note of production account) that ends not sacrificing "the astonishment of the spectator" with predictable portions of striking images as the genre often. Therefore, attention, dear reader, here there is no surprise: there is (almost) visual impact. The anacondas are not causing any AWE. Sits one to receive a massive dose of crappy show B or Z and, in return, we receive only a drama of characters agilipollados in a jungle of Borneo that run, they talk, returns to run, they are swallowed up by the fucking bicha, pardon me, and then back to run and talk again. It is the bad selfish which exposes their congeners of race to achieve its purposes materials (a flower that gives eternal youth, here's the crux of the thing) and which, in the end, receive their just deserts, clear is. The silicone of feminists and made testosterone anabolic in the pectoral and biceps of the heroes of the day do not compensate for hour and a half of awkward romance with the foolish. It is that there is no edible bait: the anacondas out little and go wrong. There would be no pasta. The first appearance of the scrutinizing comes to half of the roll. It is as if one suddenly decides to swallow a porno film and the first wild penetration amazing forty-five minutes of footage and hardcore divos, males and females of turn, pull impressive rolls on the unbearable lightness of being and the heavy burden of the soul on a couch well escorted by minimalist music by Michael Nyman. No, please. Hardcore porn, without intellectual excursos. And here, what they want to tell, that I was looking for (Monday night, a digital channel of payment, had already seen the episode of CSI) was lunatic recreation, cathode spasms on the couch with the home cinema bellowing 5.1 the cries of the young girls and waiters (political correctness, eh) when the snack is the dreadful bicha. Goodbye simple pleasures.</body>
</review>
