<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Juegos secretos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It starts in a promising way, featuring the characters quickly and easily, although from the middle of the tape begins to deflate it.</summary>
	<body>There are films whose formal wrapper yells at the spectator so firmly that are, it is easy to be fooled by them and conclude that, indeed, they are great films both good and deep. "Games secrets" (Little Children), the new work by Todd Field after "In the room", I think is one of those movies.It has the film, the story of a group of people whose lives intersect in parks, swimming pools and streets of their small community. A bored mother (Kate Winslet) befriends a father (Patrick Wilson) who stays at home while his wife (Jennifer Connelly) is out working. On the other hand, Larry (Noah Emmerich), begins to worry by the presence in the neighborhood of a pedophile (James Earle Haley) fresh out of prison.One of the elements used by the film to be "deep" is the continuous comparison with "Madame Bovary". It is not necessary to comment on the enormous differences between the society of the 19th century and the current, still not as big as I would like, and which override entirely the simile. The author of the screenplay, in fact, is aware of these differences and invents an unfortunate argument to "justify" the infidelity of the character of Kate Winslet. It is believed that otherwise it would not be justifiable? Was it necessary? If the work is intended to be a critique of the society why gives the character an excuse so simplistic?In fact, the film exudes a reactionary whiff that cries out to heaven. I am in favour of not judging a film by their ideology and I do not but I would like to draw attention to the fact that, if I have noticed that detail is because the film not hooked me. To give a radical example I will say that when I see "Triumph of the will" of Leni Riefenstahl I forget Nazism, moved by the beauty of the images.But I don't want you to think there is no anything good in the film or has horrified because it is not. It starts in a promising way, featuring the characters quickly and easily, although from the middle of the tape begins to deflate it.It is also true that the actors are fine, but I think that he has exaggerated the quality of the interpretation of Kate Winslet (great actress that is at your level but without fanfare) and underestimated that of Jennifer Connelly, for example, in the scene of dinner (sorry for the cacophony) gives a lesson of how look in the film.James Earle Haley make up a disturbed able to equal parts pity and fear and that stars one of the best scenes deserves special mention. Including a great tribute to "Shark" that is very cleverly embedded in history will remain in my memory. If you have seen the film perhaps you adivinéis that scene I mean.As I say, the story will deflate gradually until reaching a final really strange in which characters make stupid decisions with the sole purpose of reaching the point desired by the director and screenwriter. I could understand it and it would almost make sense, if it were a ruthless critique of American society, but it is that this criticism is not for me, visible at any time. Sometimes the intuímos and I think that, as we want to see it, we almost got it to see but we cannot do it without fill the gaps with elements of our invention. I do not believe that to be the correct way to deal with a film.I cannot comment on the painful translation of the title of the film in Spain. "Secret games" is clearly designed to attract the public to the Chambers in the hope of encountering an erotic thriller or something. In fact, some friends asked me for the film ran panicking as soon as I told them it was a drama.The original title, "Little Children", gives much more sense to everything that happens. Because that is what all the characters are for director and screenwriter: toddlers unable to be clear about what they want, fight for it, become responsible, mature, treat her mental illness, etc? "A pity that the intended message does not end to the viewer or that intend to use for this script tricks that rub the ridiculous.""Secret games" is thus halfway of the fantastic film which could be but without either falling into mediocrity. Its critical impact seems to me, in any case, excessive and passing.Moonfleet.es rating: 5 out of 10</body>
</review>
