<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An entertaining film, that becomes short, shocking and emotional at times.</summary>
	<body>I always say that you better late than never, so I predicaré with the example and will tell you my impressions about the movie, although I already saw some time ago.As everyone knows, "Letters from Iwo Jima" (Letters from Iwo Jima) closes the diptych on the battle of Iwo Jima by Clint Eastwood with "Flags of our fathers", telling the story of the Japanese side and with even more satisfactory results this time.Passing on tiptoe through the technical aspects of the film, so perfect in sound (not in vain won one of the Oscars of sound) or picture as the previous one, to enter fully the elements that they make unique to this tape from one.From the first moment in which it was revealed that Eastwood was going to have the two sides of the same story, the Japanese history because it is a much more original and unusual for an American director approach generated more excitement. This atipicidad plays in its favor over the footage because never has the feeling of being in front of something already seen previously in other films.Eastwood advocates a more linear structure as in "Flags of our fathers" and fully succeeds because this structure, although dotted with magnificent flashbacks, helps to introduce us calmly in the history, to catch love to the characters, to live their misadventures with them.Interpretations could not be more fortunate. Ken Watanabe interpretative qualities were well known and most striking is huge which are all. For highlighting someone say that Tsuyoshi Ihara as Baron Nishi or Kazunari Ninomiya as private first class Saigo that serves as a common thread of history and which is easier to identify, offer outstanding and very emotive interpretations.Emotion that moves the viewer through the careful and, as always, elegant staging of Eastwood. And it is that another difference in favour of this tape to "Flags of our fathers" is the emotion. In "Letters from Iwo Jima" we were excited of truth and witnessed some moments of cinema of the great (Saigo talking about his future son, the suicide of soldiers, the letters, the dog scene &hellip;). Scenes of those which, with its brightness, betray that we we have more than a very good film: is a gem of a film.Get a result, Eastwood, perform the toughest anti-war allegation of recent cinema. A very hard attack on the war and politicians and statesmen that begin them and run without the slightest regard for the lives that have been lost.It does, in addition, with an entertaining film, that becomes short, shocking and emotional at times. A reminder that each new film Eastwood can make is a gift for those who love the film.Moonfleet.es rating: 9.5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
