<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El buen alemán" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A pity that a movie with so much interest a priori has ended up becoming one of the great disappointments of the season.</summary>
	<body>Steven Soderbergh is one of the most intelligent directors of today, among other things, for its ability to survive in the industry alternating commercial tapes, the more personal and, even, the experimental.In "The good German" (The Good German), in my opinion, it has tried to combine both facets, disguising commercial film which is in reality a nostalgic experiment. The result find it me somewhat disappointing.Indeed, the most important thing of the film does not pass through its espionage plot, based on the novel by Joseph Kanon, and which puts us in the ruins of the Berlin of the post-war period of the second world war where the journalist of the army of the United States Jake Geismar (George Clooney) will meet with Lena Brandt (Cate Blanchett), a former lover whose missing husband is wanted by the US Army and the Soviet.The important thing about the film is the revisionist exercise by Soderbergh, who created a film of the 1940s in the 21st century. The retro look of the film is so careful that up in Spain have been translated the opening credits, as used to be done in those years.The problem is not the slides to sing or that noticeable differences in photography between the scenes shot for the film and documentaries from the period from. These defectillos were present in the Hitchcock film, for instance, and not imported at all.The problem is that Soderbergh appears to have been forgotten that, among the great virtues of those movies, was the narrative concision, the pulse, the emotion. Elements that, in this "the good German" are missing.Before these, really serious problems, they can do little about delivered but somewhat lost actors who roam trying that his charisma is enough to fill the screen. Unfortunately, it does not.A pity that a movie with so much interest a priori has ended up becoming one of the great disappointments of the season. We will have to wait for another time to see if we can enjoy again with Soderbergh that made us vibrate with "Traffic" or "do Ocean? s Eleven".Moonfleet.es rating: 4 out of 10.</body>
</review>
