<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Tu la letra, yo la música" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie, in the end, as well-intentioned as suavona, innocent, aseptic and calm. A film that is not boring, sees without displeasure and forgotten two minutes out of the film.</summary>
	<body>Hugh Grant, he joked in the presentation of this film before the media, about his role in it: "It was a little drunk when I accepted." Do not know what's true and what of exaggerated in such an assertion, but the truth is that the good of Hugh has gone le a couple in interpreting that former star 1980s poppie coming unless.Hairstyles, the outfits, the dances and the cutrez of his artistic life in the 21st century are more pathetic and endearing at the same time we have seen on a cinema screen in recent years.The truth is that only therefore by the character of Grant, it is worth seeing the film. For this reason. and for little more. The crazy character of Drew Barrymore, in the line of the great romantic destroyers in the history of cinema, beasts of my girl and surroundings, adds nothing new to a type of character more trite and sobado than the bust of Ava Gardner. The character of the sister of Drew, however, is of the most funny thing, so female dominatrix crazy hysterical fan.History and the plot, as well built as light in his criticism of the great divas of music today, Cristinas Aguileras and Shakiras are mostly white glove: a musician without inspiration and any girl who passed by there and helps you to compose a song for the great Star of the moment: Cora, which conveniently, destroy her looking for immediate success and the recognition of some fans thatfrom music, they just want to see dance star.And arises the spark between the musician and the girl, and they enchant, and fall in love and. good, I believe that any reader would be able, without having seen the film, anticipate everything what will happen until that come the opening credits. Since then, if the reader usually travels by bus, already you know more than very well what awaits you with this "you the letter y yo music", a perfect example of cinema to see on a plane, or at home, a winter Sunday afternoon.Film soft, without edges causing laughter with some acidic of the Hugh Grant character replicas and smile with his light criticism of the current model of culture of the show in which we operate, including Affairs-basurera. I've missed, that Yes, some shots outside more of New York and its streets and cafes, Madison Square Garden and others. Too little budget?A movie, in the end, as well-intentioned as suavona, innocent, aseptic and calm. A film that is not boring, sees without displeasure and forgotten two minutes out of the film.</body>
</review>
