<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="La flauta mágica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that certainly isn't at the height of Branagh's best because at times lost bellows and has a tendency teatralizante excess.</summary>
	<body>Kenneth Branagh appears to be catch the taste to musicals; his last work in this genre is this adaptation of "The magic flute", the Mozartian Opera to Irish filmmaker has covered, placing the action during a dream-like world war I with the irreconcilable enemies Sarastro and the Queen of the night playing with lovers, Tamino and Pamina, in a film that certainly isn't at the height of Branagh's best (we would be speaking of "Henry V")(, "Mary Shelley's Frankenstein" or "Hamlet"), since at times it loses bellows and has a tendency teatralizante excess; as we know, with Lars Von Trier and his diptych "Dogville" - "Manderley", the hiperteatralización can be very cinematic, but this is not the case. Doesn't this say that this innocent adaptation of "The magic flute" lacked interest: acentuamiento of humorous footnotes that relate with the "opera buffa", as the character of Papageno, gives freshness and lightness, and the child's story, almost the entire film tone, gives a feeling of dream, a vision of dozing certainly attractive appearance. But it is also true that the Branagh version may exceed in their quasi naïve perspective: we know that everything in this world is likely to be treated with humor, even war (Oh, the great Gila!), but the shown us here, which led for years the name of the great war, until Hitler endorsed him an ominous ordinalappears as a clean, cute uniforms colors conflagration, where the dead do not bleed, although they are shot; they do not burst, although made by shells, jump into the air; they barely chillan, even if they are injured in the heat of battle. Do is clear that it remains a mere landscape, not just devastated, which can take place the evidence of the four elements which have overcome the lovers consummate their love to save the world: how nice, if not for that is falling?</body>
</review>
