<review author="Cp" title="Shooter: El Tirador" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What serious critics call a fascistoid movie, quite rightly, that advocates the eye for an eye, carry weapons such as right to defend themselves and go to the mountains and distrust of the federal Government.</summary>
	<body>Expected before going to the movies, because basically what found me, a movie-style action tapes and shots of the 80's, where the protagonist, disillusioned veteran of war is called out on a mission for his country, betrayed, and decides to take revenge for that have killed his dog (literal!, joke, but literally) fighting against a corrupt and full of incompetent system. Up there, perfect. A hard, very hard, protagonist is injected artisan serum alone, than loose very funny lapidary phrases, that falls in love with the girl, with his eyes (do not gave time more, so it would be by looking? well, or by the abdominal muscles, so deny it) that is finding characters that's so exaggerated, are very fun, and especially kill their enemies easily. And that is the greatest failure of the film. In the 80 see as Governor Arnorld eliminated bad twenty per minute was good, but in this era post-bourne, the truth is that I'd rather see something more realistic, and already posts with a good script, clear.In the end, what serious critics call a fascistoid movie, quite rightly, that advocates the eye for an eye, carry weapons such as right to defend themselves and go to the mountains and distrust of the federal Government. But that's not all. If you've been at it, boy, I am afraid that you are an izquierdosillo lounge, you think not much. By that? Because that to find a film that criticizes so clearly the Bush Government, large corporations of the oil, the international hypocrisy, to as treat Africa and poor countries, and as the army and American intelligence services are at the service of large corporations and their interests must be traced back to Syriana. Intermingled with the first speech, constantly find pearls of wisdom, especially at the mouth of the bad (which are very, very bad) making it clear that we live in a world where globalization unbridled capitalism allows Rumsfeld say in public that not Iraq they invaded by oil and not be lynched. Anyway, after this, should be a partnership between United Left and the anti-federales mountain in Montana, but already.</body>
</review>
