<review author="Pablo" title="Misión imposible 3" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We are probably in the best film of the trilogy due to the effective mix of action and dramatic intrigue</summary>
	<body>J.j. Abrams is inaugurated in the world of the film with a film of action very in line with the American series that are succeeding today. We are probably in the best film of the trilogy due to the effective mix of action and dramatic intrigue. The way to lead the viewer along the plot very well structured which leads us to return to be able to enjoy unexpected turns of script, technical who had disappeared in the second installment. The role of Ethan Hunt (Tom Cruise) this very accomplished, giving a much more humane approach, because that is left to lead in many situations by the emotions and feelings, yet their instinct of secret agent takes control of any situation as if it were a reflex Act. Mission impossible on this occasion is neither more nor less to rescue a captured IMF agent while he was spying on an international dealer of weapons and information (Philip Seymour Hoffman), has no conscience or remorse. The agent in question was the pupil of Hunt which still yet withdrawn decides to perform the mission by all means she for the. This time it's personal.J.J. Abrams says that the writing staff put a commitment special when creating a bad worthy of Ethan Hunt, one that was at the height of the hero. "It is the first time that Ethan Hunt is faced with an adversary so terrifying, intelligent, and mysterious as the character played by Philip Seymour Hoffman," says the director.I forgot to highlight family that becomes, once again, to see again work closely to Ethan and Luther. The chemistry and good friendship that exists between them is one of the more humorous of the entire film. It is likely that the director is not created a work at the level of the carried just by Brian de Palma, partly due to the lack of ex officio, but what if that note is the fact, that succeeded in appropriating the essence of the series much better than both of their atecesores. After seeing the film sales of cinema with tachycardia.Finally it should be noted that all the action scenes has been carried out by the own Tom Cruise without help of doubles. "So I think part of the challenge of making a film," said Tom Cruise. "Does there is no risk for no reason, but if one can train and do something to provide credibility to the film-?""Do well, makes it really?-, viewers are passed it better".</body>
</review>
