<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El reino de los cielos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film I liked.  Incidentally, it teaches us that religions have caused the biggest savagery the planet has ever known. Thank God I'm an atheist, but go disappointment.</summary>
	<body>I don't understand why they don't more movies of these Moors against Christians. They have all the ingredients for success, and is also clearly who are the good and the bad. The bad are the Moors and Christians the good. Or not? For Westerners this is so, and vice versa for the Oriental. And it is on issues of religion, there is no good nor bad, but nerve and deceived.The film is a blacksmith for coincidences in life, loses a wife and their employment in a heartbeat, but beat a father (who fought with an arrow in one testicle, had to say it). By more coincidences of life, the father goes to the Crusades and our Orlando Bloom (has name mixture of tomato and insecticide) followed as a faithful dog. Traveling to Jerusalem, to try to defend the city, and their lands, the evil Saladin and his army of Saracens. When it comes to town, realizes that that the Saracens are the bad guys and the Christians the good, it is not at all true.To tell the truth, the footage of the film is a bit excessive. Put another way, is long noses. The film is not bad, but since what interested us is fighting espadazos and not the love of our bisexual Orlando, us is a little peñazo. And is that these films are always cut by the same pattern. Presentation of the characters, reporting from the scene of the final battle skirmishes to go to focus the subject, roll and more roll on the human and the divine, and finally the final battle. And then there is a sort of corollary on life and death. And that is all. Sinvergüeza Trojan, El paso, the Lord of the rings, etc.In short, that the movie I liked. The final battle is the cane, although it has for me a little mistake. If know perfectly well where are the most fragile defence parties, because they do not attack her at the beginning? Do you like to see dying loved ones? But good, except this little problem, the film shows us wars "santas" so much damage been done. And incidentally it teaches us that religions have caused the biggest savagery the planet has ever known. Thank God I'm an atheist, but go disappointment.Besitos.P.D: Leprosy is a disgusting that not we as imagine.Pd2: At that time life was exactly the same as a dog cagarro. That sad.P.D.3: I think that Orlando is left with the desire to give a meneón the Saladin. Not be I if behind the scenes not are they desfogarían.</body>
</review>
