<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="King Kong" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If compressed in twenty minutes the first hour and a quarter, removed the bullshit of insects, and subtract you drama, we would have a great movie.</summary>
	<body>A joke told me the other day related to the film. This is a guy that not going to the movies for many years. Total, says that he is going to see "Tarzan of the apes" but wrong and gets in "King Kong". When he returns home asks the woman "about the film". "Very rare, very rare, Tarzan it does not appear anywhere, but you have to see the mona Chita the lug which has stuck". Damn, almost I fall of the sidewalk when they told me. I now understand how Chiquito raged with bad jokes.The film is about an unsuccessful film director that makes with the plane of a lost island. It's convincing producers to finance him to go there and thus regain his standing, but these refuse it, so decides to run away with all the material which is not yours to the island. As you want to record a movie, takes a girl that is down the street (quite pretty, by the way) and a Schleifer of cams, writers, etc. When found the island, discovered more than a lost landscape of the hand of God. And so far I can tell. Well, then get a monkey as a home, which as you may know, and Tarzan does not appear anywhere, je, je.Special effects on all sides. During the first hour and quarter, the truth that there are not many, but as soon as get the monkey, already breaks the budget. Direis, the first hour and quarter? Few there? So here comes the first problem, which are three cathedrals as three horazas of film. And there are times where nothing happens. The scenes of monkey are fine, but the rest is a truño. Peter Jackson has passed three villages, with special effects and the script. I do not know how it will the book, but the scene of insects is a sovereign bullshit that disqualifies the half of the movie. Fuck, and the end is a hell of melodramatic (albeit with some funny point).In short, that if compressed in twenty minutes the first hour and a quarter, removed the bullshit of insects, and subtract you drama, we would have a great movie. As they have not done so, we have a peñazo quite long, so I recommend take it on DVD and skip until you see King (booooooooooombaaaaaaaaa;-) only large special, but very long and silly effects.)Besitos.P.D: As noted the style of Peter Jackson, I was waiting that orcs appeared to thousands throughout the film.Pd2: A real story as life itself. We saw the film and in bed, while was laundered teeth my medium chandelier, I go to bed to do King Kong. The part of the blows on the chest well, perfect grunts bad the monerías. In one of these tumbling I figured wrong output of acrobatics and ended up with the back on the cold floor. That scallop.P.D.3: Look, not can silence me. We are going to see Peter Jackson, if you troubled a woman for five minutes running down the field, which is still the neck splits in two. You know.</body>
</review>
