<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La casa de cera" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you are cool scares of disgust, maybe you are interested. If searching the film of fear which appears in the trailers, better you alquilais the Exorcist or something so that this gives more disgust than fear.</summary>
	<body>I think there are two ways to be scary, with disgust or scares. For example, a film in the someone looks at a clouded mirror and when it cleans, sees that it has behind a gentleman knife ready, i.e. scare. If in the same case before, instead of a knife ready Lord, have a man with the face falling to horns, eyes hanging out the orbits and that one pulls the hair to locks, this is disgusting. The first way I like, the second seems nasty (though an extensive audience). If there are people who like films of Antena 3 at midday, why not you will have people who likes the giblets?The film is about some kids who deserve to die from the first scene (this it contribute I). By circumstances of life, decide to go to a distant city to see the end of not is that League. For the same reasons that nobody knows, they decide to go on secondary roads. When night falls, they camped in a strange place that smells a little weird. The girl becomes the brave and the next day, he decides to investigate the smell. It comes from a grotesque scenery in which a Lord that disgusts pulls the corpses found in the ditch. And with this shit of introduction, a Spanish Lord has done a film facilitates and a bad time.I think that it is the first time that the film telling, I put it to give birth. I always I hope this paragraph. In the end. The film is a Cobblers that gives much disgust and little scare. The characters, as I say, deserve to die in a road accident before arriving at the ghost town. The dumbest character is the brother of the protagonist, an expresidario that bad that you want to appear, seems to jerk. More forced character. The sets, that Yes, they are quite interesting, and the wax figures acojonan. The general idea is not bad, but that shit fattest development. Especially grilled give us until they reach the people that matters very little.In short, if you are cool scares of disgust, maybe you are interested. If searching the film of fear which appears in the trailers, better you alquilais the Exorcist or something so that this gives more disgust than fear.That ascazo!Besitos.P.D: The scene at the piano yet stir me the stomach.Pd2: now that I think may have to see the disgust that I gave the two bottles of wine which had been between chest and back. Who knows.P.D.3: House of wax if that cool, although physically complicadilla.P.D.4: If at least were naked breasts of virginal maidens, but not even that.</body>
</review>
