<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="El corazón de la tierra" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Missed opportunity to have done something important in the historical film Spanish. Again will be.</summary>
	<body>Entertaining saga of historical and assertive dyes produced, would like to believe, with the idea that a serious and tragic situation that really happened in Spain, don't forget to be reminded, by way of homage, the good people who they lived them (and died). And I say that "I want to believe" because I see very clear. Cuadri has strength and elegance to frame shots, with a powerful mise en scene, well using the depth of field and sometimes, getting a great dramatic effect, despite not having many mimbres.This is noticeable, for example, in charge of the army against the poor people of the place. There are no shots many extras, but more well than inches, but the good use of the frantic Assembly, close-up and appropriate music, get the desired effect. And so two or three times more. But, broadly, the story you are Manus, the filled rather crude form of numerous topics, a thousand times seen in the film. Little by little, a film by the interesting historic trail, derives the soap opera, with love, proverbs, hatred, vengeance and all kinds of human feelings mixed rough, noisy, little rigorous way and with no doubt rush, I think that to cover much of the foregoing in the novel in which it is partially based.The result is very irregular, never bored, but not interested too much, rather little, although the events are no problem any because the pace is not agile, or at least effective.But I think Cuadri fails a good movie, but little convincing auque careful and painstaking in the technical aspect. I hope that the undoubted international effort of the company does not fall on deaf ears, but gives a bit of penalty see how lost another great opportunity of having done something truly remarkable.Again will be. Ah! With regard to the (not interpretation, eye!) characterization of Fernando Ramallo, better turn the page. Already okay them.</body>
</review>
