<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Bienvenido Mr. Marshall" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Folk altarpiece of the Spain of hunger, these times now are not particularly different. There are other difficulties. It may be no hunger or censorship arguments of the revolution, but still colea the son of those Covenants.</summary>
	<body>The Spanish civil war did not last three years, although the textbooks, encyclopedias, wikipedia and some hubbub now lifted for pain of the dead, revivalista in three years of the war. Wars do not just when weapons are depuestas or a few chieftains well trajeados, smiling for the historical photo, sign a document in the light of flashes and rolls of celluloid. War seems just when faced staff hits the streets again, as said the Cuban Troubadour. Wars are wars subscription and there are none which, at its end, norm not already the germs which is nestling close to rise up and give his emboldened cry of blood. And now I've gone by the tangent and instead of talking about Spain, which is what I proposed, I finished writing generalities, applicable to Borneo and the atolls of the South Pacific Islands. Welcome Mr. Marshall is written not long after the settlement of the war. In it, there are still smell of gunpowder to backward hunger, desire to give cerrojazo to squabbles which others did not finish solve until comediado the 20th century. García Berlanga writes with nasty folk altarpiece of a Spain simple and down-to-Earth, it employed in its most intimate sediment to the Catechisms of the chieftains of the war and high policies, which were the champions of the new Spain to tow the caudillista of general Franco profile. Misery and hope, hunger and joy, intermingle in Villar del Río, the people that things would not be credible if we didn't have a (unfortunately) objective vision of what was Spain during those nearly 40 years of reductionism, bans, censorship and hunger happen.Berlanga, Communist covered by post-war needs, receives the task of making a film glamorizing the figure of singer of copla Lolita Sevilla. Along with Bardem, write a who altarpiece on the rural Spain, fed coplas Spain, the Spain stopped in time, looking with an eye to the United States.UU, called to revive the European economies, the major cultural colonizer. Altarpiece of customs truffled Comedy Italian style (miracle in Milan).Villar del Río adorns the American friend to enjoy the hospitality and the Gypsy clamor of a manchego village crossdresser in Andalusian above all things that you want to please so pleased after it rains the Plenipotentiary manna from the financial aid promised unashamedly high institutions of the State. Under the down-to-Earth and endearing baton of Pepe Isbert made Mayor of the pantomime, the entire village launches to represent the expected work, fanfare and song. Antológicamente (and is not a matter of gutting the end) nothing happens as he was believed.The paper used to shadow an Andalusian village is in the brain of his sudden Masons. Desires, in the secret hope of the yankee gold, are made in lists. There needs, but also as el capricho is legitimate. When reality overshadows the fictions, the glorious spectacle of wealth lowers to the gray routine of sadness. The villagers are happy, what remedy: are preparing with heroic enthusiasm to cope with disappointment and be solidarity, good, obedient to the cause and, finally, sentimental, humble to deal with every day that is upon them. Frozen in the idyllic vision of the American (Marshall PLan of Fund), they had no problem in PICT to achieve what wanted. As life itself. These times now are not particularly different. There are other difficulties. It may be no hunger or censorship arguments of the revolution, but still colea the son of those Covenants with the Americans and we live in a world colonized by Uncle Sam to inconceivable extremes. This miscegenation thrives and there are some governmental efforts by determining the patriotic American, distribution fees and delicate handling of numbers so that the abuse is not scandalous. And it all started with Pepe Isbert in Villa del Río; they are still in Villa del Río dressed Gypsies in a street scalloped and cheerful, waiting for the convertible Cadillacs of the benefactor of Ohio.</body>
</review>
