<review author="Pablo" title="Psicosis" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nothing returned to be the same and most importantly, no one returned to be equal.</summary>
	<body>There are millions of horror films a year. In fact, most are copies of copies of remakes of yesteryear. But that concerns us, reinvented the genre. Nothing returned to be the same and most importantly, no one returned to be equal. At no time do deny that this is one of the most overvalued Hitch, but just as happened with the Beatles the public connected in a special way, and when that happens, everything becomes a fantastic folly.Let memory, the great success which marked psychosis was due more to marketing that the novelty of the invention, this confused structure of script that left the Viewer without half of film the protagonist was still shocking. The public perceived as well a kind of horror that they had never before experienced in a cinema, a terror into the unknown, no one had no idea which would be the next move of the master of suspense. And it is that studying in detail the film one realizes that the protagonist of the novel is the terror in its pure State. The absence of a face that blame for the evil that is happening in the Bates Motel was that from the outset intended to the director, that as they tend to say, there is no greater fear that which is unknown. Simple and stunning scenes of acuchillamientos are to freeze us blood to the rhythm of this disturbing music which becomes owner of our nervous control and makes us forget bugs so incomprehensible as the fact that while Marion (Janet Leigh) this being stabbed in the shower is not a single spot of blood on the knife. If I had to do a brief overview of the plot for all those who have not yet had the pleasure of seeing her I would say that the film tells the story of a young malversadora who comes to the Bates motel with $40,000. Paragraph here is the have to do with a strange owner and her dominant mother.I remember the first time I visualicé the movie I loved it, was something avant-garde and to my liking, still retained his classic touch. Something that certainly makes it a unique piece. And although in years following its premiere published sequels that would attempt to profit through the successes of the original never reach him nor to the sole of the shoes (Psycho II / III Psycho / Psycho IV). Salvadorans as it is the case with most of the sagas of terror, if they see a character succeeds so they squeezed to the maximum, systematically destroying the charm and mystery that possessed. Even being one of the best films of all time, this was not free of a remake, so fashion are in modern times due to the lack of imagination and the compulsive need to acquire income. This fact denotes as currently the industry prevails over art. In conclusion I would like to refer to the soundtrack, which, in my opinion is one of the most memorable of the genre along with the glow.</body>
</review>
