<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Yimou returns to give us a spectacular shower of colors. Costumes, the visual beauty of the planes, the incredible fight choreography, photography and, ultimately, the part aesthetic, turns once again in its major asset.</summary>
	<body>It should take the medication every day. Without complaint and grateful. That is what we always say to Grandma. Who takes the syrup on time and that does not complain, but then come the ailments. She and stubborn. that no, that to him swallow the matasanos. Zhang Yimou should be living a similar situation at home, because everything revolves around a happy medicine during the first half hour. That if I take the, that if not I the take, if it do not looks good, be if taken you all and I learned not I that you leave something. Finally, the first bars are somewhat slow, but everything is going "in crescendo".Set in China at the end of the SX, the curse of the doradada flower tells the decline of the Tang dynasty on the eve of the feast of Chong Yang. Illicit lovers, family secrets and the envy, destroy in a few days to a family which should be exemplary.Yimou, far away from the intimacy of the "Red Lantern" or "The way home", to name a few, here follows the pattern of "The House of flying daggers" and returns to give us a spectacular shower of colors. The costumes, the visual beauty of the planes, the incredible choreography (though this time they are not excessive), the photography and, ultimately, the part aesthetic, turns once again in its major asset. From the first seconds, Chinese director us closer to the magic of the imperial palace with a great display of images and heady sounds. The pace slows down for almost half an hour, without fighting or other elements that enrich the visual orgy, and the real feast comes towards the end. The battles of "The Lord of the rings" fans here will have a new cause for rejoicing. Spears everywhere, rain of arrows, soldiers loading. In short, a bomb for the senses.The delicate criticize is the script. I read everything: Greek tragedy, Shakespearean, cheap melodrama, crappy soap opera drama. It is true that there is a large cluster of, say, dramatic events. If this is your true mother, that if that is really your sister, if I am the father of the son of my granddaughter and my grandmother's father. If one conspires, the other kills, the other is killed by the other, the other by the one. come on, I understand the negative criticism in that regard. The issue is that this must be seen as a Chinese tale, and never better. Asian narrative follows other parameters and certain licenses, must accept more when it comes to an epic story. Now, this does not justify the desmadre and one can be entitled to say "this will like in your town". In short, to attract or not the story and its characters will be question of sensitivities, audiovisual culture and tastes. I say.</body>
</review>
