<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Shooter: El Tirador" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>While his script bet by a certain complexity in the political thriller, Shooter stays on the grounds of a good and entertaining action movie proposal</summary>
	<body>We live in times of distrust and the cinema, as a reflection of their contemporaneity, comes as well laying it in many current films. The shooter (Shooter), a notable and valid attempt to regain the successful action film postponed today by the multitude of adaptations 'comiqueras', is an example of this premise. Its protagonist presents any concomitance with the iconic character of John Rambo more than acceptable first tape of this sequel (cornered) unearthed again by Stallone (John Rambo, last delivery is in phase of shooting). Like Rambo, Bob Lee Swagger (an effective Mark Wahlberg) elite sniper is now a military cornered and disappointed by the army and the nation by which they gave so much. However, in his crusade against whom he instructed as a lethal marksman from remote distances appear new sub-plots, and of greater complexity, to elaborate on the idea of corruption entrenched between the spheres of power.I.e., the film tells us in many of their current stories stories that completely banish any hint of Candida confidence towards those who rule the most powerful countries. So the new heroes struggling closer to the public and less lofty ideals: honoring a dead companion, save a loved, uncover an injustice or restore his own honor. Today already seems little credible and therefore difficult identification, the encorajinado hero that flag in ready, fight for their grandiose nation champion of freedom and more healthy values. The nativist fanfare has given way to a more domestic and human heroism.And under this premise is built the main character of Shooter, last work of Antoine Fuqua in which the director of Training Day returns to demonstrate his good hand when handling the levers of action. Its adjusted length of two hours resembles measured the millimeter to not leave space to yawning. And while his script bet by a certain complexity in the political thriller, Shooter stays on the grounds of a good and entertaining action movie proposal.The former model of Calvin Klein Mark Wahlberg leads a cast that, paradoxes of life, your enemy is a corrupt military played by Danny Glover, former hero opposite Mel Gibson in the lethal weapon franchise popular. It can also be seen an increasingly popular face of the actor of Mexican descent Michael Peña, already seen in films directed by Eastwood or Oliver Stone. Each fulfills its role, more or less prototypical, and make a film which returns to rely on an old and successful Alchemy Shooter: spectacular images more action without truce, equal to insured entertainment.</body>
</review>
