<review author="Silvia Giner" title="El número 23" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Jim, is little credible in this film, although note the effort made by the actor to interpret a role outside their usual records. Conclusion, do not waste your time and your money with this firecracker and rent Gilda in the video store.</summary>
	<body>Many expectations I had I created with this film, many of which came down when Jim Carrey was consolidated in the title role.The myth of the number 23 is something any friki computer knows, something so widespread by the network that reaches almost become a religion. Much has been said about this, has written and it has addressed, i.e. This is not the first film nor the last on the emblematic number but is probably the worst.If you expect to shed light to the myth, not to go see the movie because what you'll find is a pseudo-psycho movie, with pretensions of discover you something that fails, staying in a mere history of serie B in which the prota plays double borderline personality.Although the Assembly (mostly innovative) but with an estilillo that my I like, it is acceptable, sometimes this type of mounting excess causes a slight "dizziness". We are back to the levels of those of reverie that director (Joel.) (S) we are accustomed. Within the mental straws of Joel.S this is perhaps the least intense (thank God, pq after the Phantom of opera thought delirious starving by the torpor) but still wants to this boy think something that isn't, doesn't know to do and above makes it wrong. Joel, Joel Joel, when are you going to realize that there are also beauty in simplicity and that your films appear to a Meringue with double ration of Strawberry Jam?For my talk of the number 23 it is not talking about an encounter with a person and this number which is what narrates the film. Therefore failed film. 23 should have been much more, I do not know I can think of a thousand ways of looking at it, but good.Let's talk about friend Jim. Dios but even when I have to support this? see Jimy, read carefully. You've spent years consagrandote as this comic actor was which you has led logically to a typecasting hard hard as steel. You have enrriquecido, you have been comfortable in your routine, and now after you create in our minds a picture of absolute asshole makes us laugh, do want seem very serious and compelling? No, no, no, I'll tell you it will cost much time and many clunkers as 23 settle you as something more than an excellent actor for comedy, almost as much as that has cost you become what you are. Patience, I support you!Jim, is little credible in this film, although note the effort made by the actor to interpret a role outside their usual records, but we still lack some passion or enturage or X factor finally believing it to us.Conclusion do not waste your time and your money with this firecracker and rent Gilda in the video store.</body>
</review>
