<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="El número 23" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is presented as a remarkable film that part of a very interesting point, with good interpreters and dose of great film that will delight all lovers of suspense, thrillers and the great Jim Carrey.</summary>
	<body>The new film by Joel Schumacher irregular, a mixture of worlds (real and literary) presents us with very interesting way, in way that would elevate this film proposal, within the remarkable range of the director. Jim Carrey, an actor that I love, once again demonstrate that it not only has its comic vein, although this no longer absence after his excellent roles in "The Truman show", "Forget about me" or "The Majestic". "The number 23" embodies a dual character, that alternates its everyday life, with the Detective protagonist of the book which has begun to read, and which has a strange connection.Next to it, we find ourselves with Virginia Madsen, who already really dazzled us in "sideways" and "Candyman" (for the oblivious to the fantasy and horror), who plays the wife of Walter Sparrow (Carrey).Among the points to be highlighted is the photography. Matthew Libatique presents us two very different atmospheres for the real moments and narrated in the novel, giving the latter a comic aesthetic, than good we can remember to "Sin City".The script is quite complex, with certain moments that will make that the viewer will be delivered completely to the film, but then falls on an edulcoramiento own for everyone, with a moralina which could have been avoided, but that does have its charms, or that will satisfy at least a large part of the audience. The number 23 and chance, give a great game the screenwriter Fernley Phillip, with this figure, it forms a maze of mysteries and circumstances that bring headaches to the final Carrey.En, "The number 23" good is presented as a remarkable film that part of a very interesting point, with good interpreters and dose of great film that will delight all lovers of suspensethe thrillers and the great Jim Carrey.</body>
</review>
