<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El buen pastor" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A brilliant film, deep, long and dense, with an outstanding cast and an incredible technical section. That Yes, to you who like those of espionage, better that not go.</summary>
	<body>Robert De Niro is the director, producer and secondary actor of the good Shepherd. So it sounds like a little, but I assure you that her second film as a Director is one of the most elaborate at this beginning of year works. Yes, at first glance seem the typical peñazo of a man who left everything for their homeland, but no gentlemen, no. Do not fool yourself. It seem also aburridísima, but the truth is that a slow film and why not is less magnificent.This was one of the most anticipated films of the year, at least for me, and I am thrilled the outcome has given me, entirely satisfactory. Got me the hope with two criticisms that the left pretty bad, but luckily, then I saw and I was impressed. The truth is that it is not a film of spies and nothing else. The good Shepherd is much more: mainly with the subject of espionage, talks about human decisions and makes a deep analysis (too!) about these people ingénuas, ending without just personality. De Niro does an incredible speech about the human race, a speech which goes beyond the unthinkable until final, absolutely terrifying conclusion, and why not absolutely baffling, since that one is already expected to what is going to happen. So we have, the film of Robert de Niro as a true modern classic, which takes one to another reference of other classics (ancient), such as the godfather. By no means, the film lacks originality. Quite the contrary! It is not only a sample of the good film, but is also a sample of good and original film (many of the levels are really disconcerting, the script, of which I speak now, is simply brilliant and "strange", etc).The screenplay by Eric Roth, as I say, is absolutely incredible. I agree that the film is slow character, but absolutely I would add to those who think that the good Shepherd is a boring film. As I said before, the film is incredibly deep, and not so boring. Only with the beginning, one already is surprised at its complex form of portray the world of espionage, because he starts telling us small fragmented events (that Yes, with the date included). Once you get used to this kind of script, messy, confusing and brilliant, you you wonders again and again before such complexity. It is an experience really satisfactory to witness a script as of this film, and I say this because for some time that he saw no one so prodigious.Another noteworthy aspect is the number of characters that appear, especially side. Niro, or rather Roth, not only focuses on Damon, the protagonist, they explore all the characters that surround him with exceptional skill, without leaving none by the environment without destroying it perfect. That Yes, can some of them fade somewhat, as John Turturro. So, in short, the film features a prodigy of script, graph, retailer and let band topics.The same think with the cast. There is no any actor that is below the outstanding. Everyone, absolutely everyone, and mira which are many, are incredible in their respective roles. Start by Matt Damon, the absolute protagonist of the work. It is yours, the role more deep and detailed of all the solo and human or Humanized, because human hair it doesn't. From the beginning until the end the character suffers psychological transformations and also ends up being worse than it is at first. No doubt, it's one of the most incredible a main character analyses of recent times, coming to be really close to the Viewer. Secondary, should speak calmly. It is not to appear too all of them, some even appear as cameos, but the truth is that they are all magnificent. Start by Angelina Jolie, the fictional wife of Damon. Their role is not to be the best Treaty, moreover, is perhaps the worst, but the truth is that it is portrayed quite naturally and isn't a heavy character. Robert de Niro reserves a small role, although very interesting and with a couple of really great dialogues, like Michael Gambon, amazing English actor that appears more than twice, and three. Perhaps his role is that most interests me, because she has a hidden and intelligent personality that makes him the most outstanding secondary. Although the same can say about John Turturro and William Hurt, both splendid in their respective interpretations, full of charisma and secrets (tuned to the scene of torture, carried out by the first.) (Absolutely heartbreaking and tense). Alec Baldwin proves once again that he is a splendid actor, offering us a masterful performance, probably his best along with the infiltrators, and Billy Cudrup highlight also the small appearances by Timothy Hutton and Joe Pesci, which encourage the role rewarding way for both are always pleasant to witness, especially those of the second. Thus, the film win much, but much, with its incredible cast, perhaps a single defect, be somewhat separate each other, i.e., that many of the characters do not relate well to just.The good Shepherd is, first and foremost, a film dark, full of secrets and lies, hidden in a world full of traps. And therefore, nothing better than having a technical section of first quality. The photography is excellent, even worthy of an Oscar (look at the close-up, especially). Music is also excellent, with some notes which come to touch and mounting, perhaps not the best of the film, but is not nothing wrong. In addition, the setting is astonishing.Excessive all of the film is that it is a bit long (lasting two and a half hours, approximately). To me, personally, not me she became heavy, but who do not enjoy with the films of spies are dull, and much, because the entire film revolves around them. Do not think that I now changed his mind and I am off to the deep movie. I only say that its subject matter is espionage.Thus, we have a bright, deep, long and dense film with an outstanding cast and a technical section incredible. That Yes, to you who like those of espionage, better that not go.</body>
</review>
