<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La vida de los otros" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Thriller rather than chronic politics, although in the end the impression comes from having attended an existential drama to a melodrama of universal, Immortals, Greek, Shakespeare and classical dyes.</summary>
	<body>The downside of distrust is that it does not brake: once it has been launched, it is impossible to stop his Vertigo, his voracious inquina, her cancer slow. Something happens in this film. The Socialist dictatorship of the now defunct Democratic Republic of Germany lived 40 grey years of distrust, microphones hidden in plugs and bureaucrats converted in spies. The Stasi, a KGB improvised after the ruins of the second world war, became an implacable instrument of surveillance. The number of suicides at that time was very high: both the administrative hierarchy forbade the publication of these statistics.Florian Henckel von Donnersmarck writes without involving too much: he warns more in favour of not lose the thread of the film than thriller bear witness a political Chronicle. Its history, admirable, moving, is the story of every soldier at some point in the war: sentimentality toward each other, the fragility of its doctrinaire and awareness of the conflictual nature of his adversary. The guard understands the futility of its surveillance, but travel ranging from harassment to the redemption destroys homes and ruins the future of a country.I'm not a fan of the film: has perhaps been sold with an excess of fanfare. I understand that you arrabatese the Oscar to my amanda laberinto del fauno. Being both dramatic films with a political background, the German raises a number of readings and makes a more sober use of cinematographic material. When del Toro is Baroque and visually triumphalist, Henckel von Donnersmarck requires only an amazingly precise script, which never takes unexpected turns and a so huge problem that deals with care and elegance: the abduction of the liberty of a people, censorship as the only notary public today, fear as routine to face the unbearable Vertigo of decadence.And the art, the beauty, the word high to its most beautiful altar, hanging over the lives of all the characters. The playwright with a conscience Socialist, but disgusted of the barbarity of the regime, actress that lives, icon of rebelliousness, suspected of encouraging the sympathies of the undecided or ignorant, with media and its scenic desparpajo and (above all) the Stasi agent, the military to monitor the lives of others and that ends, which reverse syndrome of Stockholmcongraciado to the alien cause, indelibly disarmed of his hatred and manumitido of all forms of violence. That is, poetizado.The end of the film is very beautiful. Understand in detail the matters that the film is going to pose. And get one film with a huge weight in the conscience and the tranquility of that art, beauty, love or as we like to call it triumphs over ideas. They counted here, the history of the GDR, are not too different from those experienced in this our Spain of the post-war period. That also made me in my thoughts. And it was raining out of the film.</body>
</review>
