<review author="Ram칩n Balcells" title="Seduciendo a un extra침o" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Seducing a stranger it's erotic as the laberinto del Fauno of comic. The only thing that saves him perhaps Giovani Ribisi, in a role also absurd, but which at least has some grace.</summary>
	<body>After fascinate me with the good Shepherd, I expect of seducing a stranger, the new film of the earlier promising James Foley, a decent and minimally entertaining film. Because even that. Here are the 8 reasons and media to not see seducing an extra침o:1. By his absurd script. Really, one of the worst in recent years, lacking grace, sense and intrigue. It has absolutely nothing attractive, their plot twists exceed the idiocy, the last one, in theory, the most important reslatando. Pathetic 2 by the Bruce Willis character. It is one of those papers left over completely. His speech is purely designed to augmentar the salary of box office, nothing more. It makes no sense and is very badly drawn. It has its own personality, little you know nothing about him. Anyway, that if Willis fails to accept the role would have to have changed the "script". 3. By inexpressiveness of Halle Berry. As they say, it has only made a good performance in their life, Monster's Ball, and from there, his career has not more than worsen. Let's see, by God! There is very little love cinema to accept roles as Catwoman, Gothika, operation Swordfish and seducing a stranger. 4. By the lack personality that has the film. Even a mediocre film director could have shot a film with a bit of personality, or that is a little. Here there is no original detail or staff, and less a plane that is worth your while. They are all this style Hollywood lately is fashion, this where only focuses to the character and nothing else, that Yes, with very good image quality. 5. By his painful setting. So it seems, everything is shot on sets and occasionally gets some image of the street or a (very common in this type of thrillers) p치rking. 6. By both resemble a telefilm of Sunday afternoon (Antena 3, above). Up su, initially promising outcome is going to the pot using the technique of the final surprise, in this case, badly carried out, given that it makes no logical sense and do you not also believe not in jest. Really decepcionante.7. To see that it is an erotic thriller to the reality and basic instinct is a thriller to dry, because of erotic has nothing. What's the affair with the character who plays Gary Dourdan (the black of C.S.I.: Las Vegas)? Really, it is not account, because it is totally dispensable. It brings nothing, absolutely nothing, to history. It is not for nothing, but seducing a stranger is so erotic as the laberinto del Fauno of comical. 8. By this kind of final moral that does not come to mind. If you do a bad thriller, you do a bad thriller. Now that I do not come with logic and psychological things! A crappy is a hodgepodge, and more when it simulates wasn't. It must be very silly to make ready while you are going a tape like this. If you've annoyed her, her you have fastidiado.1/2. By the painful publicity campaign that has had. Their posters (both of Spain as the official) are really horrible, just a touch of originality (fiajos in the topical promotional sentence: until where be capable of reach?) and its trailer of the same, although the final part is a little more interesting (slightly!). The only thing that saves him perhaps Giovani Ribisi, in a role also absurd, but which at least has some grace.</body>
</review>
