<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Shooter: El Tirador" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Endures well and with some force to the end. However, his last quarter of an hour is more fascistoid that one can throw on face. An ending that makes think about the resurrection of the genuine Charles Bronson and the righteous philosophy of his action films.</summary>
	<body>Bobby Lee Swagger has left the Marine Corps. Retired in a small hidden cabin in the mountains, try to forget that three years earlier, during a mission as a sniper in Ethiopia, he was betrayed by the staff of their own country. But soon, convinced by a Colonel who has managed to locate his hidden hideout, will return to serve their homeland, acting as consultant to a possible attack on the President. His skills as a marksman, and his knowledge of long range ballistics, can be very useful to advance to a dreaded terrorist action.This is the promising start of Shooter, Antoine Fuqua's new film, a correct action thriller that, partly recovers the most thrilling of filmmaker style and refers to their two titles more achieved in his not very defined filmography: assassins of replacement and, above all, the excellent Training Day.La film has hook. His pace is frenetic. An expected (but effective) twist of script, a few minutes of projection, turn to Bobby Lee Swagger in another false guilty more joined the long list in the world of the seventh art. The Government puts price on his head and sends hunting dogs of the CIA, the FBI and State police. Only he knows that this is a political plot orchestrated at a high level. The action is the main dish of the function. Car chases, helicopters to punta Palau, several explosions, shootings at discretion, attractive females and semi nude in danger of death. A bit of everything in the service of the skills of an expert in the genre director.His filming is impeccable. Fuqua dominates the topic, and it shows. There is little rest for the Viewer. But in spite of this, the script weakens and tape clear, in general, true reactionary whiff. Everything sounds to trite, already seen too many times. But the craftsmanship with which it is made, saves outweigh the irregularity of his script, at the time that conceals zero packaging of its actors. Mark Whalberg is so dull and deadpan that it could have been replaced, with total peace of mind, by Matt Damon. And the viewer would have not noticed.The bad guys are nothing more than a mere caricature of themselves; some bad with very little identity as such. Danny Glover advocates the histrionics, just as it does an aging Nead Beatty. And this without forgetting the laughable presence of the most sobreactuado of all, Elias Koteas, a detestable and type loaded - way exaggerated - all the topics of the film evil par excellence.Shooter, despite its misleading casting and his little plot consistency, endures well and with some force to the end. However, his last quarter of an hour is more fascistoid that one can throw on face. An ending that makes think about the resurrection of the genuine Charles Bronson and the righteous philosophy of his action films: there is always someone who, protected by the system, you'll end up with what the system could not overcome.With both rifle and many violent deaths, the old man Charlton Heston will be enjoyed as nice watching the movie. Certainly, after the premiere of Shooter that unmentionable partnership of which he is President, you will notice a sharp rise of adherents, while the American gunsmiths held a large increase in its dividend. And then, of course, happens what happens.</body>
</review>
