<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Alpha Dog" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Children are idiots, the parents are idiots, children take drugs, parents take drugs, children have no future, parents did not last.</summary>
	<body>By what they say and not what we see, Alpha dog might well seem a porn movie: there is a linguistic routine based on sex and the absolute sacralization of the massive intake of drugs. There is no rock and roll: the musical plot is a hodgepodge of hip hop, industrial rock asalvajado and some strokes (very slight, very measured) of glamorous fairy tale melodies (Wild is the wind, David Bowie).History is always, but here it is told with some grace: it warns an interest out of the script and certainly at the end, like us or not, accepting that Alpha Dog is not one film of mozalbetes accelerated, titánicamente spliced and intended for meat of presidio unless a rush of speed the abotargue in one of these chairs of I don't know how many thousands of dollars that decorate the streets of these rich kids high-tech stuck to the drug lords because of small no read to Michael Ende and had generous portions of maternal affection while TV rumiaba Looney Tunes episodes. And if it works youth that Cassavetes portrays is not by necessity to random or is not because of a social or cultural revolution in the way they did their parents in the mythical late 1960s. The moral numbness and pathological stupidity of these Brats with 4 x 4 at the door and Mammoth sound chain in the living room reflects the absolute foolish of parents.The teaching of the film round that idea: these errant children have never had a family as God intended. This is shown in many sections of the film. Even the most deranged of its protagonists (Ben Foster as brother psicotrónico and placed on time total) there comes a time in which confesses that he had wanted to have a mother who you sobreprotegiera and give Cuddles in bed. In another scene, a girl almost rushed into the abyss beaten the door of his house and only manages that his mother, who celebrates the anniversary of wedding and asked it is absent for a few hours, interrupted the fornication with the husband and stopped the extra speed and pills taken to make the party complete. The mother, falls, sends a tomar por culo, crudely said.In another order of things, or is the same, Cassavetes excels in giving us an amazing parade of human waste, kids stupid and low blood flow in the area of the brain that governs the sanity and common sense. Kids who hocican the morro in beer (drink to navigate during the film) or in marijuana (smoke without stopping at the same time drink) when a problem occurs they front. Kids who consider sex a chapter added to the psychedelic trip, but without making rites of the delights not sanctify the absolute enjoyment of meat: fucked as they drink and smoke as they fucked, crudely said, of course.In this thread of things, there is a kidnapping and a revenge not finished see resolved because law catch offenders and there is no brat end that does not have its prison handkerchief. Bruce Willis, which leaves little and get content, is the padre-modelo of all this agilipollada rabble who sees in Tony Montana, the gross hero of the Scarface of Brian de Palma, the representative of his vital speech icon. Up at some point we see a poster of the film: perhaps the only reference metacultural of this Guild of psychopaths. Sharon Stone is a poorly drawn, overly protective mother as taken from a book of archetypes of cheap psychology. Both are far from supporting any weight in the plot and are lost in brief and very unnecessary roles. Disastrous, by not credible, the emergence of Sharon Stone, engordada, makeup so it seems a parody of makeup, as a mother devastated by the loss of the child.Everything is based on real events us does appreciate the good intentions of the film. All his possible kindness, their legitimate attempt that seems cinema of quality, is hampered by a drama sometimes impostado by characters that sobreactúan or by certain concatenation of situations that inevitably lead to a conclusion that is already scheduled to within minutes of film.</body>
</review>
