<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Xmen3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Highly recommended for lovers of cinema derived from comics, given that is one of the few films of this type who really like</summary>
	<body>Well, first of all, tell the poster that has been Spain is the most ugly of all. Still, it is quite explanatory of what the film. I am very fan of the saga, remember that when we went to see the second part, arriving home we were again the first to refresh memory. By the way, before I forget, there mutants that they have to be bad for noses. For example, a gentleman which pinchos leave you on all sides must be bad by definition. Although one him out hands blades also it should be and is not. What rare.The film is about a discovery which makes a pharmaceutical company to "cure" mutations mutants, turning them into "normal". A sector of the mutant population welcomed this, while another considered that it was an aberration and is preparing to fight the human being (and step seize the world, etc). In the middle are the X-men to spread wax to anyone here. On the other hand, we have sub-plots of various characters, such as miracles, explanations incredible, deaths and other ornaments that all science fiction film self-respecting must have. And new characters everywhere.Let's enter in the field quickly. The film is a cluster of special effects, led by a quite absurd script and incredible. Okay it is a science fiction film, but the script isn't even remotely to the height. There are characters that nobody understands why are, but it is to please fans of the comics (such as for example the of the wings). They are inserted with shoehorn and that don't like to neophytes. But if we set aside the script is very weak, we have a very interesting film. The bad guys are very bad and very good good, thing to thank for not having to think. I like the amount of mutants that appear, given that each has its moment, giving the matter until a comic vis. The trouble with this is they explore them little, but better as well, but would have been too long. For special effects, the film is out, although it touches the absurdez. But who will take the brain to these movies? I brain not I took, and the eardrum it lost in the number of explosions. Incidentally, the second end of the movie is what could have saved (later of letters) that does detract from the film (by the way, I've heard to some kids that is more faithful to the comics, what things).In short, movie popcorn and flat encephalogram. Highly recommended for lovers of cinema derived from comics, given that is one of the few films of this type who really like. Nothing to do with shit like "Daredevil" or "The punisher". That Yes, if you like scripts produced with depth of character, flees to the depth that I have been treated to a little pathetic.</body>
</review>
