<review author="Bloody Will" title="Sunshine" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>All are saved are the special effects, and the performance of almost all stakeholders, based on extensive of his role obviously stressing Cillian Murphy.</summary>
	<body>Where is the tension in this film? Why I had to swallow almost hour and a half of footage to reach something minimally? disturbing?; I might add that final part of the tape is equally disturbing that return you less cents after paying for a ciabatta in the bakery in your neighborhood.All what you promised?Sunshine? in all the trailers that we have seen over these months it crumbles completely when Palm first of the crew of the Icarus II spacecraft that travel the characters in our story, in the future year 2057, with the laudable goal of trying to save the final dying of the astro Sol.Y is that this film is of those who dies until the pointer. And of course, that you know almost surely, with a minimum margin of error, in what order it will happen; most have a face of fiambre that sings in length.The case is that I have always praised the cast of?Sunshine? in previous posts, and I opt not from what I have said so far. Do is a good casting, some actors are better that others is clear, but thanks to their performances, and other technical details, saves this film to be rated as? forgettable?. I think that the problem is in the direction. Do so that the spectator suffer for what is happening on screen, and theme for the life of any of his characters, is necessary to start with a presentation? open heart?, i.e. showing removed calzón the virtues, defects, vulnerabilities and potential of every speaker in history, to make it more close to the public. It may seem that you know of chiquitillos.Only thus you feel their loss, and obviously so it strains your body when you see have death attached to the rear, and when eventually moving to another district. Well, Danny Boyle has focused so much on show us the beautiful special effects has managed for the film, that we care about a pepper who, when and how dies a character or another. Man, as the film goes on, you have more attachment to one another, for his way of dealing with the crisis; but to none you so llevarías your home or for a coffee.With this little blood, the tension of the film is practically non-existent. And when you see how the first victim of the plot, with the tombstone hanging from the neck, her espicha hardly interest-free, you you fear the worst. There is more tension in the meetings of my community of neighbors than in this film.Only a detail to detect boredom: instinctively I searched in 6 or 7 times a more comfortable position in the armchair to continue watching the tape, and the kid in front has stretched so much in the end credits that have given me wanting to find a bed that will lend a sueñecito before you go.And to make matters worse, the peak, as it is the outcome of the story, with a medio-monstruo as the final villain, is mounted as psychedelic (with scenes in slow motion ending in hiatus, subliminal images or unexplained blurs) that makes you lose the reference of what is happening. So eager to had Boyle do an apotheosis end that unintentionally you crazy.I said, that all are saved are the special effects, some very cool (some other props do you grace, as the Golden space suits which makes them resemble the crew who wear them a chocolate Ferrero Rocher) and the performance of almost all stakeholders, based on extensive of his role obviously stressing Cillian Murphy (for his portrayal of good about the movie) and Chris Evans (by his learned role of rebel).Ah, I recommend you bring you forth sunglasses to the cinema and her have at hand because the going to need.</body>
</review>
