<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Seduciendo a un extraño" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Correct thriller that plays with that unwritten rule of the intrigues of the past twenty years which requires a turnaround in the script in the last scenes, and the truth is here Gets the surprise total emphatically effect. But it is also true that this quest for the shocking surprise must generally pay the toll of the lack of verisimilitude.</summary>
	<body>James Foley is on its way of becoming the great white hope of American independent cinema; author of the magnificent "Glengarry Glen Ross", has also left his personal mark in most commercial products, such as "Men face to face" and "Sealed Chamber", and even out well of an envite so complicated as it was to address "Who is that girl?", vehicle for the greater glory of Madonna. But he has failed to break into the great filmmaker who had been inside, and lately already there are several commercial products without greater relevance in which has been immersed. "Seducing a stranger" is a correct thriller that plays with the unwritten rule of the intrigues of the past twenty years requiring a turnaround in the script in the last scenes, and the truth is here Gets the surprise emphatically total effect. But it is also true that this quest for the shocking surprise must generally pay the toll of the lack of verisimilitude and a solidly armed script, and in both cases here cannot reasonably: suspects of being the villain of the film are all profiles that could indict them (less that really ends so, of course, as usual), but these profiles are often caught by the hairs are unlikely and are provided exclusively to try to bring some coherence to a story that certainly suffers from it. Anyway, it is clear that to "Seducing a stranger" can not ask you more than you you entertained for a while, preferably without taking you too the hair not to insult your intelligence, and little else. Of course that is what you will be asked to Joel Schumacher and other filmmakers professional but impersonal, but James Foley you would have to be able to ask for much more. Maybe already is has happened the rice? As for the actors, Halle Berry get airy of his character, while arguably has more holes than a gruyere cheese; You can not say the same Bruce Willis, do not know if because the character is a very important type, or simply because it has become carajote, it is unpresentable. Giovanni Ribisi, usual secondary, skillfully composed his character, though, surely the more glassy terceto protagonist.</body>
</review>
