<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Pudor" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The existential drama in this grey family cometh with all its power towards the end, in the cathartic meeting where everything will explode, and more later, when an unfortunate accident possible, perhaps only temporarily, the Union of all.</summary>
	<body>Here is one of those (rare) cases in which the direction of a film stripe over his script. And isn't that, ultimately, this family history of devastated middle class by the routine, everyday life and fatigue live has no interest: the husband, sentenced to death by disease whose name no one dares to say out loud; women, forgotten as a female; the sullen teenager (sorry for the redundancy?), confusing their budding sexuality, in his secret infatuation of her best friend; the small, whose step in the real world the ghosts occurs with the naturalness that can only happen when you have six years; the old widower, seeking their place in the world for the last bend in the road. But with twigs from the novel by Santiago Roncagliolo, well pickled for a smart script be interesting, maybe is the powerful staging from novice filmmakers David and Tristán Ulloa (although the first has a long experience as a Director of television and the second has amply demonstrated his sensitivity as an actor in films such as "Sex and Lucia" and "Savior"), with an enviable ease handling fragile materials where there: underground feelings, with a semblance of normality, where a furious source of unexpected meanders really runs. Filmed with intentionality, with stimulants you framing, mild virados photo, movements precise and accurate, the film is always attractive, although sometimes the interest decay (the storyline of the grandfather is clearly inferior to the others), and incurs the regrettable habit of wanting to be noted, as usual in the filmmakers neophytes. On the contrary, it seems the Ulloa brothers have been filming life, and the consequence of these tables outside this beautiful film. It is true that the beginning is somewhat hesitant, while David and Tristan are the tone required by the story, but when they get, it is early, because everything is on wheels: existential drama in this grey family cometh with all its power towards the end, in the cathartic meeting where everything will explode, and more later, when an unfortunate accident makes it possibleperhaps only temporarily, the Union of all. The sequence of the catharsis is magnificent, with dramatic tension and high-voltage emotional, but there are other, less showy, are also tremendous: the encounter of the child with the ghost of the pederast with dog, a little subtlety in allegorical darkness prodigy; the encounter of the mother with his anonymous lover course, resolved with an ability to master. Mention apart for the couple protagonist: above all, Elvira Mínguez, definitely the best actress of her generation (and there are very good), splendid in this difficult role; Nancho Novo escapes for a time of the zarrapastroso Bohemian think their brand to make honest family guy, a grey clerk cornered by the unmentionable disease and by the end of an existence prepared "mean Aurea".</body>
</review>
