<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Some time ago I thought to create a platform to defend the euthanasia of the spectators. The motto would be something as well as: "We don't want that they will save more movies." "We want that they leave us to die in peace."</summary>
	<body>The worst thing that can happen in an American film is that they save you life. It is a degrading situation viewers suffer without protest, session after session. The hero it is not enough to take away the girl, it is not enough to carry his rush of adrenaline, nor with dispatch to the bad or staying with the treasure. You are not even enough the six euros of the entry, we have to thank him. The villain has a weapon that will destroy the planet and if we leave the room alive is thanks to him, to the good. Some time ago I thought to create a platform to defend the euthanasia of the spectators. The motto would be something as well as: "We don't want that they will save more movies." "We want that they leave us to die in peace." Sunshine is an expedition travels to a Sun endangered to reactivate it with a bomb, and though it may seem, does not belong to the genre of salvadores-petardos was talking about. The crew are not heroes and no need to kiss their ass. Since that is not an expedition of children cool looking for medals, as Willis at Armageddon, is, at least, quite tolerable. Also the fact that spend half movie thinking as save them, and not save me makes tolerable to my. They have to make drastic decisions, sacrifice lives, choose who stays and who dies because there is a suit for one, or oxygen for few. The feeling of vulnerability is tremendous for the short distance separating them from the Sun. Their lives hanging by a thread that increasingly becomes thinner. And behind the need to save the mission is: If fail is over the Tierra.El success is, without doubt, the plot premise that fires the importance of each step. The bug is that fifth character that is out of the logic for my taste, to evoke a significance that is always so risky. It is not easy to get evoke the more beyond, as it showed "2001". And it is not easy because if they want to know my opinion, I would say that "2001" nor did.</body>
</review>
