<review author="Bloody Will" title="Tu la letra, yo la música" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Isn't the comedy that will make you stalks you, and you matter it immediately, but it has is something that takes you to view it two or three times without problems and cogiditos in hand with your partner.</summary>
	<body>We must officially appoint Hugh Grant as the Heartthrob of the comedies of the last 10 years. It Will Ferrel, Adam Sandler, Chris Rock, or Jack Black, which used a more crude humor, unlike Grant takes years and years parading with the most many-colored actresses of Hollywood romantic comedies that used the basic story of us know - something happens - eat partridges. Do already almost forgotten their incursions into the drama, as?Sense and sensibility? or?Do rowing to the wind? to have the actor rather than typecast in this type of genre that we are usually drawn by third parties. But not all films are equal, and with?Your letter, I music? Grant has managed to start me a few laughs, and that already says a lot...The director of this comedy, Marc Lawrence already has caught the point to the British and the type of story told. Do went you in?Love with notice?, but has also written?Forces of nature? or?Miss special agent?. All have their faults, and one of them is a genuine rollazo, but the best of?Your letter, I music? is that Lawrence is daja give many turns and going to the direct: a simple plot, allowing few gaps, and whose end is more than resabido, but that unlike other products, is extremely effective and highly entertaining, or at least so seemed it to me.Do do can not stop thinking that the director has been on the VH1 network one of those documentaries about the rise and fall of certain groups of the 1980s, and specifically of Wham!, band formed by George Michael and? if the skinned man?Andrew?Andrew Ridgley. This is all just about the film: the Wham Moreno. Alex Fletcher (Hugh Grant) is a former star of Pop lived better times with a group that was a success but disappeared after their singer's solo. Now, 15 years later is presented a golden opportunity when a star for teens, Cora Carmen, he commissioned the lyrics of a song, and Fletcher will make use of an insecure aspiring writer, Sophie (Drew Barrymore) to create the success that will return to the covers.With this premise, it may seem unoriginal is mounted a comedy without edges, without cheating and for its restrained duration even arriving to be a heaviness. Lawrence has thrown popular: singers ovlidados and clones of new stars, as such the Cora Carmen, whose got to the Brtiney Spears are tremendous. The scenes with Grant playing a crappy and ochenteras canciocillas rub the ridiculous and hilarious, especially when you see as their teenage fans are now señoronas something salidillas. The character of loser that distills the actor in the footage makes that you feel genuine devotion and sympathy for the protagonist, which I appreciate after seeing so many streams that they end up get you rile. Do still preferring in?Notting Hill? or?Does Bridget Jones?, but éstá infinitely much better than in most of the last carried out.And we say Barrymore. Also the girl in comedies lately is leathers, however in this film in particular could have been any different. Barrymore does not give your character the charisma that Yes gives Grant to their own. As a girl in love, hypochondriacal and hysterical is equal to another heap. It is not to do wrong, simply stays in a flat line. It is the weakest of the film and his smile is usually save the dishes, but that lack of personality joins with Hugh Grant has questionable chemistry. Sometimes it stick, but others think that the girl is dealing with his father. The truth is that the 15 years that separate both actors is too, and with another actress this film could have been muchísmo better. Perhaps is this lack of chemistry what has made your box office has been a disaster.?Your letter, I music? It is this offer that occurs on the Bulletin Board as a completely valid option to the pretentiousness of other proposals. With both requetevisto, both mystery thriller that isn't, and so many empty special effects, this film is the most simple and uncomplicated you are going to see. Isn't the comedy that will make you stalks you, and you matter it immediately, but it has is something that takes you to view it two or three times without problems and cogiditos in hand with your partner is extremely entertaining. Do something deeper we have to Aronofski next week?</body>
</review>
