<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Sunshine" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do in Sunshine, the lead torpor provoked perhaps due to its proximity to the Sun numbs the interest of a viewer want to that soon, as soon as possible, everything is reduced to what? according to its writer-all are: dust, only that, star dust.</summary>
	<body>The genre of science fiction has swung from a few decades ago in the demanding frontier that unites a cinema of leisure and popcorn? descreído of dialogues Grand and more excited about the bait offered by aliens, termineitors and any other creatures acampen thirsty by the screen - with another film pertrechado of intellectual openwork bandwidth issues, debtors of the discourse which flooded with great success its literary references, but transported to filmic language can numb the passion of the most naïve Viewer.This Lair to unite show and message have contributed excellent work? solidified some as myths of the seventh art-yes they got in his day (and still get) be been reread with enthusiasm and critical interest. These include the upper Blade Runner, 2001: an Odyssey of the space and encounters in the third stage, or the more recent but also interesting Gattaca, twelve monkeys and Minority Report.A some of these gems seem to have paid tribute the unequal Danny Boyle in his mediocre Sunshine, thereby building a spectacular script (the ink of Alex Garland, also responsible for the most interesting 28 days later) no feet or head, whose only contribution lies in the beauty of his images (which isn't anything significant) and the wisdom of focusing its narrative and aesthetic interest in the figure of the Sun - Star little used in this genre - and not in planets showy and disturbing as the Moon or Marte. Even so, even their contribution parasitizes (with dignity) spaces, times, and illuminations present already in the masterpiece of Kubrick. And the presentation nothing disturbing fifth passenger is close to the only entertaining final horizon of Anderson to the terrifying Scott.Boyle Alien overestimates, signing a pretentious and tiresome, product should be fun without sentencing, and rather than the reverse as well happens. A real shame, because the chosen environment was successful and commendable visual beauty (should not be forgotten that the firm Alwin H. Kuchler, present photography also in the poetic code 46 of Winterbottom). Perhaps history would have given more than itself emphasizing the mythological seduction by the Sun? as does the also unequal Soderbergh Solaris with its enigmatic planet-no monsters running around the ship, dispatching shamelessly one by one to each crew member. Or, perhaps he would not have been wise to decline the action by terror, deleting the script misticismos and other intellectual refinements. I do not know, I do not decide, but what I am clear is that when Boyle gives you by mixing ingredients salad was sour, while shipped separately from insurance would have been delicious.It will be why I like both Trainspotting, because in it there is no more ice cream than that puts on the capirucho and born with a desire to have fun, avoiding dramatize or poetizar the scene of drug use. Everything is agile and thug in Trainspotting: music, its images, the dialogues, all.Do in Sunshine, the lead torpor provoked perhaps due to its proximity to the Sun numbs the interest of a viewer want to that soon, as soon as possible, everything is reduced to what? according to its writer-all are: dust, only that, star dust.What pleasure to enjoy the decent secondary Cliff Curtis, incidentally, out of their cartoon of malicious terrorist? although, how not (sends the America of political correctness), be it aired the first-, or that Asian bellezón is Michelle Yeoh (memoirs of a geisha, Tiger and Dragon, tomorrow never dies), whose pose of sculpted seriously weakens my will and strengthens while other faculties of less noble noun.</body>
</review>
