<review author="Marta" title="Hard candy" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I have the feeling that, if it exceeds these beginner mistakes, this man could do very good movies</summary>
	<body>I like to discuss films without talk too much about the history feature, but in this case it will be difficult, because it is based on an argument really. Basically, it's a meeting concluded over the Internet between a teenager and an adult that just exchanging roles. Even so, get staying for more than an hour and a half without being heavy, something quite remarkable starting from a less elaborate idea. "Hard Candy" is an interesting film. However, it has some bugs that made me ended not convincing at all, despite the awards won at the festival of Sitges 2005.Empiezo by evil. Throughout the film, I had the unpleasant feeling that the director intended to play with a special and different photography and just does not get it. Sometimes - as the car-ride, the film seems totally an advertising spot. A MINI is lost between the curves and waits to be appear the slogan at any time. At other times, the pace becomes video clip, and in addition, the lighting changes blatantly along some scenes. Obviously I'm not saying that you can not play with this type of resources, see Requiem for a dream- but we must be skilled so you don't leave the hand and the image not be, simply, absurd. The director of "Hard Candy" is not. At the end of the movie I read the tab in the Renoir: "David Slade has won recognition in the world of advertising and music videos." (.) "Hard Candy is his directorial debut." I thought: "Vale, now I understand everything."On the other hand, the film was something "tosca" at times. Nothing more start is a poster of a girl that reads "Missing". That image is totally unnecessary and conditioned the Viewer, so that, instead of creating intrigue where could have created, I get that is Intuit what clearly is what will happen. In addition, some dialogues are very fake and unreal. Having said that, I still have the good. The idea - that sort of "Red Riding Hood" upside down - is interesting, and latches to the film despite the simplicity of its argument. The two main actors do a great job, and get even save some of the worst lines of the script. In addition, the film has the strange ability to alter the point of view of the viewer throughout the film, getting you questions who is good and who is bad, or, better said, if the actions of the protagonist are justified or not.I have the feeling that, if it exceeds these beginner mistakes, this man could do very good movies. We'll see.</body>
</review>
