<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Darwin Awards (Muertes de risa)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Comedy funny and interesting, very innovative theme. You don't have a continuous pace, with significant ups and downs, but that is worth the trouble to see it. Of the few American comedies that really make me laugh.</summary>
	<body>The Darwin Awards are supposed to be they a few awards granted, usually, as a posthumous. They take that name since they don't if not confirm Darwin's theories, to order the same evolution of kill beings so intrinsically stupid. Obviously, are given to persons who have died or are unfit to play in any more stupid situations. And certainly are very stupid, but much.The film is about a police officer whose job is to link data and events to solve crimes. Prizes Darwin, as well as when he sees blood, faint is has as a hobby and obsession. Total, that one day he loses his job for reasons which are not the case and decides to try to find a job in an insurance company. You want to create a pattern of people which cost him money to insurance. People who by their acts well could enter fully in candidates for Darwin. what prizes strangest film. I have to admit that you left me a bittersweet taste, such as sauces and soups of the Chinese restaurants. On the one hand, the subject is exciting and fun. On the other hand, development becomes at times heavy and leaves me with the impression that it could have done much better. I.e., the part of Darwin Awards is fine, but the history of the protagonists makes water. That Yes, I laughed a lot and I think as said Einstein, human stupidity is infinite.In short, comedy funny and interesting, very innovative theme. You don't have a continuous pace, with significant ups and downs, but that is worth the trouble to see it. Of the few American comedies that really make me laugh.Fun and funny.Besitos.P.D: Has very great moments.Pd2: Out of Metallica.P.D.3: by the way, the majority view from a camera is recorded. I.e., is supposed to be recording a journalism student, so the viewing quality is reduced. This not finished it to understand.</body>
</review>
