<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not bad, but nor however, you interested, but it results in excessive artificial, contains very positive elements such as the value of self-sacrifice for others, but it is clearly inadequate, and its technical package is enviable, but the plot suffers from roundness, clarity and true emotion.</summary>
	<body>Interesting film of science fiction? more on paper than in the celluloid.This "achievement", certainly must preparations are you to director Danny Boyle, who, with lighting, sound, and special effects achieved a zacchia film, where the trees can't see the forest (if it actually exists, that is another).The idea is good, contains, no doubt a plausible story from several points of view. As genuine science fiction and tape as a work of undoubted humanist nature. What prevails over any consideration, however, is the visual impact.This is achieved, perhaps, but just for letting in the viewer a sense of latent dissatisfaction, which makes think that it has missed a good opportunity to achieve something important really. The Union of several topics that have already played in the film, as of the kind of natural disasters, as well as those who scavenge the dangers come space through beings already earthlings already from other worlds, becomes so lead us to other times seen in other works, much more achieved, that this time everything happens with quite some noise but shallow.The script, including dialogue, escarba not enough on the themes addressed, resulting in the end an amalgam of ideas, but not annoying and interested in some specific moments (repair of the shield), not just conveniently curdling.The appearance, for example, of the fifth passenger of the ship, is less colorful and important what it required, still shooting all the sequences in which comes with a nerviosísimo "dance of St. Vitus", fashionable in the current film, which we tide and epata, but does not have much to say. "Sunshine" is not bad, but not well, has interest, but results in excessive artificial, contains very positive elements, such as the value of self-sacrifice for others, but is clearly insufficient, and its technical package is enviable, but the plot suffers from roundness, clarity and true emotion. A movie that glimpse of his potential, but not covered in any way. The epilogue, very nice.</body>
</review>
