<review author="Jose Luis" title="Misión imposible 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another tape that Tom Cruise will look, where ironically, which he wears is Philip Seymour Hoffman</summary>
	<body>At this point almost no one remembers that some decades ago a television program called mission: impossible, had a great impact of hearings to show a group of characters to solve team a series of operations, which as its name indicated were virtually impossible. And this owe it to Tom Cruise, who had the caprichito buy rights and turn it into a tape which was sent to the devil the original concept and that only served to show off its qualities of Star Hollywood. The first two tapes had a good commercial success of course, doubling the already if fat bank accounts of Tom and allowed him to perform the third tape, that supposedly closes the trilogy.Mission impossible 3, occurs in a different world that existed when the previous film in the series appeared, a world in which no longer exist the twin towers, which is why the meaning of the theme changed dramatically and is seen with new eyes. But that is not the only change from mission impossible II the date the audiovisual language of the genre is to modified and advanced, especially thanks to some series television as 24 and Lost. What is other intelligent send call to j. j. Abrams, that applied you to the tape the Vertigo of a good chapter of lost and although in the first instance we can say that it did and I believe an entertaining tape, we must also say that at times also it seems that is this seeing some chapter melcochero of a melcochera novel. Put that Abrams occurred to him humanizing the main character and adding one part romantic, so now Ethan and try to save the world, must keep secret his work to your partner and try to lead a normal life. So on top of being a secret agent who travels the world fighting evil, you have to take out the garbage every night. And although in general the tape runs fine, recovers a little teamwork supposed is the essence of the original concept and presents an extraordinary quite memorable scene within the genre, bridge, this is one of those movies that not cares about seem credible and instead one has to agree to concessions that requestsso that one can swallow the story that the characters can die and revive at the whim, learn self defense in seconds and that a team can enter and invade. The Vatican! Scene it is curious, as the Vatican, one of the themes of another summer film the Da Vinci Code, which by the way was very well in Cannes.En end another tape that Tom Cruise will look, where ironically, which he wears is Philip Seymour Hoffman as a villain of luxury, proving once more which is a great actor, to give life credibly to an arms dealer, that seem to only speaking in monosyllables.</body>
</review>
