<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="¿Quién dice que es fácil?" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Taratuto and Solarz opted for the comedy, and one can find more or less clichés, more or less commonplace, but for my taste, the formula returns to work.</summary>
	<body>It goes without saying that I am a "fan" of Argentine cinema. Yes, I know that saying "Argentine cinema" can be as abstract as say "Spanish film", where we find with films as diverse as "Torrente III", "The others" or "Return". May I refer to the Argentine cinema that comes to Spain, or to the Argentine movies most popular, to the intimate, concerned about relationships and the human characters, to films like "The son of the bride", "Conversations with MOM", "A place in the world", etc. The domain of the dialogues and the silences of the characters in the comic touch even in the drama of the dramatic touch even in the comedy, are some of the features of this "Argentine cinema" to which I refer. And "Who says that it is easy" is in this pattern, for better and for worse.Taratuto, following the success of "No sos vos, soy yo", returns to the fray with a similar approach to comedy, led by Diego Peretti in the role of Aldo. Owner of a small car washing business, his life changes when, in one of the floors that you rent, next to yours, come to live a young and beautiful photographer. Aldo of traditional values, conformist and cowardly in general, soon is captivated by the magic of Andrea (Carolina Peleretti, which live, incidentally, is both or more attractive). His new neighbor is bold, restless and a very active sexuality. Do love that comes between the two will be a head-on collision of values with a handicap added: she has an infant whose father not conoce.¿Y why, "for better and for worse"? If one liked "No sos vos, soy yo", you'll like this new film. If one hates the Argentine cinema, you will not find here anything new. I am that there is always mesmerized by these humble environments by such simple stories, from the drama or comedy, or both, always seeking universal themes as speaking time. The sexuality of women, machismo, the love between opposites, etc. are some of the themes coming out here to the fore. And, as always, characters somewhat chaotic, very human, without great adventures to tell, antiheros most, but always endearing.Taratuto and Solarz opted for the comedy, and one can find more or less clichés, more or less commonplace, but for my taste, the formula returns to work. They get most of the time dibujes a smile and, on many occasions, that laugh well to taste. I may be a step below his previous film, but it is an entertaining, profound work in many moments, and which one will have the possibility of finding himself.</body>
</review>
