<review author="Paula Zurita" title="Inland empire" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although the story is a collage of images that relate to each other as in a bad dream or hallucinations, the audiovisual part puzzled. Levels, weak color and darkness, the little sharpness of images, the movement of the camera, music. All with a digital camera who seduces, but crashes.</summary>
	<body>Fly from Barcelona to Egypt, read 'Love and pedagogy' de Unamuno or watch two movies of Antena3 a Sunday afternoon. That and a thousand more things can be in three hours. Also pass them in the cinema watching the latest film by David Lynch. In the reformed Maldà or the Icaria in original version with subtitles that distract. A challenge. Although the film was released two months ago in Spain, called considerations.After 'Lost Highway' (1997), the noventera series 'Twin Peaks' and 'Mulholland Drive' (2001), 'Inland Empire' (2006) is the normal evolution of a devious and strange film director. The name, again, is not more than a toponym. In the Venetian premiere 'Inland Empire' was everything a little: criticism and applause. The director also gave much explanation about the meaning of his creation. The only thing certain is digital video recording. The rest is paranoia and anxiety. And what is the story. David Lynch nor the actors know this. He was doing little by little. Intiutivamente. It seems an extreme provocation that screams in anguish. From the first scene, but not until the last, there is concern. The film could be summarized as: two actors star in the remake of a love story, but fiction confuses with reality. "It seems the script for our movie", says the actress to her lover. Does not realize that at that time were acting. A frivolous description for a complicated history. In addition, there is a woman crying while watching the television sometimes desintonizada and others that see the same movie scenes. A metapelícula. And the Poles, is evident from the co-production with Poland, fulfilled various functions, although all unexplained. Strange characters that distort the life of the actress are: her husband, the neighbouring etc. There are also unlikely scenes of three conejos-burros that keep disjointed conversations. While a plate, two others, the she, and are sitting on a couch. Seems like a play. And the Polish whores who are the old lovers and at the same time the whores of Los Angeles. Finally, there is a linear argument and many scenes are left without explanation. But although the story is a collage of images that relate to each other as in a bad dream or hallucinations, the audiovisual part astonishes. Levels, weak color and darkness, the little sharpness of images, the movement of the camera, music. All with a digital camera who seduces, but crashes. It is not difficult to get out of the movie with depression. If 'Inland Empire' has been a bad day, intenará wrecking is it to make it one of the worst of the year. All despite the end of the film which seeks to create a bit of normality. There are a father, the Polish husband of the actress, with his wife, which cried while watching pictures on the TV, and a child. Someone me whispers in your ear: are hallucinations of women because the characters living near a chemical plant and all were a bit touched. Perhaps, I don't know. Then, to encourage the audience tired of anguish and incomprehension, come the credits with a song that includes dance. But I don't want to describe it.</body>
</review>
