<review author="JLO" title="Eyes wide shut" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If he thought it was his masterpiece, is why contradict it, not?</summary>
	<body>Eyes wide shut both becomes a strange and achieved final Testament, of a personal and obsessive director, as also a film fascinating for its psychological complexity, its schematic construction - Kubrick - and his refined technique.With points high in the picture, scene and soundtrack release, as in all his films. We are in the presence of one of his best movies, the more personal, not only its final stage but his entire filmography. Also loads his grey points: a rapid difficulty of understanding, slow in some passages and plans, limp and perhaps disposable scenes in a more global vision. -At some point - minor problems if you want to. One is from the will, with several options of reading on various topics related to the couple: jealousy, loyalty - and at the same time - different levels psychic or psychological; real and dream-like moments. Complex characters were saying, duals and a rare feeling: to feel which is a unfathomable film even with repeated visions. Dreams of the story moved to oneself to get confused - and never know well - when they are the moments of dream or reality. An essay on human relations focused on the more complex relationship of all: the marriage.The title can also be translated as "Closed eyes wide open", analogy or play on words, which suggests a dream or close our eyes to reality. A walk for two consecutive nights by the mind of the hesitant doctor William Hackford, incarnated by a required envelope long but more than correct Cruise, squeezed by Kubrick to the limit to get an ulcer according to chimentos of the shooting. A doctor stalked a thousand times during that time, by the confession of his wife of a desire not done with a man that leaves William in a State of shock. A woman named Alice, incarnate and in an excellent performance by Nicole Kidman, making us feel and experience the duality of his role as victim / perpetrator.-Always repressed - sexual desire is packaged in several female forms through the tale of Arthur Schnitzer - published in 1926, in Spanish "Dream story" - text influenced and several points in common with the work of Sigmund Freud, that not by chance was a disciple and contemporary of Arthur.Se stands out for especially film, the constant question that one is done if allpart or none of this night journey belongs to the world of the dreams of the own protagonist. Never it is indeed unveiled although coming from a director as S. Kubrick, the reality is always more surprising that the darkest of dreams. Blue tones in confession scenes between the couple - related blue dream-the shades of Red - passion, wildness - ballroom of the Castle takes place where the orgy and the Victor (Sydney Pollack) pool table, give us a more accurate track.Therefore a sexual film, although always sex in Kubrick films are hip with dark, dirty, forbidden (Lolita, Clockwork Orange, Barry Lyndon). It is one of the many traces of his work, one of the most pristine. The soundtrack is excellent, minimalist and classic themes that seem to facts to the director by the use that gives them: expressive, dense - depressive - and at the same time strong.A previously unreleased female look dealing with female characters - where they exist - touched almost always misogynistic in this director. Eyes wide shut differs significantly from its predecessors. The female characters guide the protagonist in the film, becoming a primary part and are the only ones who really know where they are standing.The pianist Nithingale, the own Will, the owner of the local costumes, characters erratic, clumsy and full of doubts. Alice, the beautiful woman of the orgy that saves his life - and we will never know if it is the same that he saves first-, the widow who declares his love, the prostitute, until the girl/lolita store, on the other hand have certainties.Incredibly, in a moment of his career, Kubrick thought of making a film of soft/porn, with the tentative title of Blue Movie - in the middle of the 63'-and few technical achievements that he saw at that time in these achievements. It would have given us that experience knowing his perfectionism is unimaginable indeed. The scene of the orgy in a magnificent Castle, is in itself, a mini-film. Oppressive, tense and bella, a taste rarely seen in this type of situation, protruding a cosy soundtrack with a mantra of keyboards on dismal key.Not for nothing the password to enter the castle is Fidelio - work of Beethoven-that addresses the issue of relationships and jealousy. A film with a symmetrical construction, reminiscent of the misfortunes that happen to the protagonists of almost all of his films. A journey of roundtrip by feelings, experiences and learning final. As Alex in a Clockwork Orange, Barry Lyndon own Bowman in 2001, one in born to kill and crazy Jack Torrance in the shining. choice of actors alleged - at first sight-bad choice of Cruise and Kidman as leading, is contradicted by the film. We can not deny the attraction and the public - and the own Kubrick - magnet of the then couple and usual protagonists of covers of magazines. Kidman complies with its usual intensity, and even seems extent cloth. Cruise holds her character with dignity and character, in an unusual role in it, making it in a register or neutral tone that favors the film, but in contrast to his ex, without extent you nothing. We know of the excellent eye of the director for the choice of actors, are stars or unknown, in all his films.In sum, Eyes wide shut is constituted in one of his most vital films despite its leisurely pace, where returns to his above-mentioned obsessions, and perfectionism in Grand scenes highlighting and becoming a good shows of the best and most characteristic of his films. Where it incorporates a new and so far new vision: the express a sentiment close to the feeling of one human being rather than a machine, which was a repetitive criticism of his film from Clockwork Orange from critics.According to co-writer Frederic Raphael - I might add in his book "Here Kubrick" did not leave it very well stopped - he only cared filming interesting "situations" with the characters rather than psychoanalytic aspects of each one of them. Before his death, the same Kubrick believed that this was his best film and in fact us sounds not exaggerated, always bearing in mind the memory of 2001 that looms immediately.And to tell the truth if he thought it was his masterpiece, is why contradict it, not? A few days of having screened the film for Warner Brothers executives, Stanley Kubrick - on Saturday 7 March of 1999 - died of a heart attack while he slept to his 70 years. Probably thinking about doing the eternal touches for the last time to his new and final work teacher. "Without a doubt, so we will miss for a long, long time.""Kubrick considered Eyes Wide Shut the best film of his career."Julian Senior (Executive of Warner Brothers) "people may misinterpret almost everything that they coincide with their points of view." Extracted art what they already think. "I wonder how many people have changed its view about something important thanks to a work of art."Stanley Kubrick</body>
</review>
