<review author="JLO" title="Barry Lyndon" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It was the biggest economic failure of any of his films, due to the negative criticism raised in due course. Misunderstood in his time as almost all the of the filmmaker, who after ten years, automatically become classics.</summary>
	<body>After his eternal unfinished project - the life of Napoleón, is decided by a film of the same style and time. This was the germ and inspired by paintings of the same period became the great Barry Lyndon. Made in England, Ireland and Germany, it was the biggest economic failure of any of his films, due to the negative criticism raised in due course. Misunderstood in his time as almost all the of the filmmaker, who after ten years, automatically become classics.Here began the famous gossip around SK filming methods. A grueling filming of 300 days over two years. Filmed on Christmas Eve without holiday for the technical team, a way to address the work bordering on slavery. Excesses of a director - how to make 25 shots or more of each scene – which were already common. Shoot indoors with the light of the candles - manufactured especially as the same as the time of the film-problems with the locations because everything should find only KMS. of your own home, lavish sets and clothing, demands and bad reputation of the film before its commercial release.After the stabbing Clockwork Orange - performed four years earlier-, expected this with another spirit. Barry Lyndon leads us to the films, with lavish sets and clothing, being bland at times compared with its predecessor, but without any frame over resulting in a full adaptation of the book. The beauty of their images is not decorative or precocious as they criticize him, and the pace is quite difficult to achieve in a realistic film and the level of thoroughness of Stanley, without limits on the duration of a scene.The beginning with the duel is a frame of beauty rarely seen. As much as its soundtrack, where the main theme Handel Sarabande gives chills by its depth. In 2001, there are long scenes without dialogues - as the exquisite encounter on a balcony - if one is to print their thoughts and emotions. One of the virtues of SK is to use the soundtrack so that it is an integral part and not a simple accessory.Winner of four Oscar only in minor items, are you accused Kubrick not having chosen correctly the starring role, this time in the hands of an envelope notably demanded Ryan O'Neal. Forced performance to averaging the film, still well in the first part which is more relaxed and relaxed. Perhaps I miss character towards the end of a more serious and dramatic tone, although his work in perspective is correct and not the merits of the film blurs. SK among other things is a great director of actors and managed to take Ryan to a point of demand with naturalness and decorum. Windy with fair, Kubrick would take note of the winner of the Academy Award that year, Jack Nicholson, for his next film the shining. "Barry Lyndon: another masterpiece of Stanley Kubrick and go."The actors are basically producing instruments of emotions. "Some are always willing and well tuned, while others reach a high level of quality in a decision-making and as much who try, are incapable of repeating." Stanley Kubrick</body>
</review>
