<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps does not comply completely excellent expectations of its beginning, but returns some dignity to the space cinema after years of drought in this type of topics.</summary>
	<body>Read the synopsis of Sunshine? a ship manned by eight astronauts intended revive the ailing Sun through a powerful explosive charge and avoid the freezing of the Earth in the year 2057? parallelism might seem logical with films like Armageddon. But both tapes just share its proposal for planetary salvation, because Danny Boyle's aims is to package and pay homage to the best version of the science fiction film and space. His brilliant and aesthetic decor, with a crew member sitting in front of an impressive stamp of the Sun as seen from a great sala-observatorio of his ship, is already a declaration of intentions.So, for much of its length, tape try to evoke space movies more realistic and philosophical as 2001: a space Odyssey. The Icarus II will not find heroes muscular and dicharacheros in the style of the gang of Bruce Willis, but qualified scientists and characters with attributes as human as the instinct of survival.However, in this desire to 'homenajeador' so typical of the director of Trainspotting and 28 days later, the tape revolves in its last half hour to try to add to the story a little space horror the unbeatable Alien style. And it is here where both tribute converted the set in a deslavazado collage that reaches, even ruin the interesting virtues targeted previously. This ingredient of terror seems a strange annexed more than an element of continuity perfectly integrated into a coherent story.With a little-known cast, Excel where a regular film of Boyle as Cillian Murphy or Chris Evans, and a tight budget, Sunshine may fail to comply altogether excellent expectations of its beginning, but returns some dignity to the space cinema after years of drought in this type of topics.</body>
</review>
