<review author="JPastor" title="Xmen3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The third installment not disappointed, connects very well with the second part, and also deals with one of those great moments in the comic book saga</summary>
	<body>Although no criticism is objective, is it less because during a good part of my childhood and youth I was collecting comic books, and which I liked most were probably those of the X. So the arrival of this group of superhero films, as in the rest of Marvel characters, gave me much vidilla. It passes through the big screen has been uneven in the first two installments, with the first part which in my view was low in characters, and some serious errors in fidelity to the comic then have been dragging in subsequent deliveries. After seeing the three carried out so far I am aware that the second is, in my opinion, the best. Extremely entertaining, very successful at technical level and with those background stories that haunt all mutants of comic books and that precisely they gave that touch to the Marvel Comics. A friend told me long ago that prefers movies of Spider-man, which develops the facet of the character hero as his private life, something which is clearly true since it is not possible to do the same if there is about 10 characters in the movies of the patrol still so, the third installment not disappointed. It connects very well with the second part, and also deals with one of these great historical moments in the comic book saga. Those who have read them already will know what I mean, and probably being something surprised by the consequences of that fact, I, certainly did not expect. These fringes which is finally resolved in the third part of the patrullosos give cause for an interesting argument, but I think that it has been too complex to carry out to the end. The massive confrontation with dozens (hundreds) of mutants has been tested both the direction and the technical realization, except in that paragraph is impeccable. The special effects are as good as might be hoped, but do not give rude when suddenly you find that the X is has to do with dozens of superpowered remaining in super at a glance, and now. Massive battles are something ridiculous for something obvious: give each doll's powers and combine them to make a "coherent" battle between mutants is unthinkable today despite the technical resources that are available. So the director wisely mixed flat generals in which sees the mutant running and jumping (which does not distinguish them any BraveHeart battle) with the most specific in which Wolverine, beast or storm struggle with some bad that do have prominence. All previous events lead to these spectacular (although somewhat incoherent) final minutes, and obviously yours is that you see the movie, so I I ahorraré the details of a story that hinted at seeing the trailer. Finally appear many members of the X we we in lack, but I do not understand why the writers are still with those "infidelities" comic. And those who do not wish to spoilers, stop reading now. Pícara character, for example, which did not convince me from the beginning, becomes the Bridget Jones team, a personaja in the comic has an impressive character (although obviously is concerned about your problem in maintaining "relationships") and in the movie not it goes from being a niñata to all the confrontations has no role whatsoever. Inexplicably disappears Nightcrawler, a character who moved perfectly in the second part and which have been "replaced" by the beast, that it have been great, that Yes. Appears Angel, but as if not do so, and colossus, one of the most anticipated, barely appears although we finally see you a little in his role. Also get Kitty Pride, well determined almost everything except in who should be having circulation of junk, and bad stresses Juggernaut (who appeared more in other series, mainly against Spider-man). Pyro, for example, has an importance never had on the comic, and indeed the actor does not convince me too, looks too young in a kind of obsession with the writers (or director, or who knows) by would have duels between counterparts: in this case, obviously, with the ice man (or rather, the guy from ice). Less evil to save the mediocre is the great magnet that has brilliant moments, including the reference to its relationship with Charles Xavier. It is curious as in some things they have respected the comic perfectly, and in others her have cagado so brutally. But as you say, it never rains please everyone?</body>
</review>
