<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Borat" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I do not think smart, biting, or funny, or anything of what he wanted and what many want to see. Stays at the gates of everything and its escatological gags in the background are the only thing that saves.</summary>
	<body>I'm late to this criticism, but now I understand why. Something inside me was reluctant, said me that the he would not, he malgastase not the time. However, some more or less favorable reviews and that of "we will have to see it, is not that." I finally pushed to witness this spectacle. And when I say show not say "wow, what a show!", but "pff." often show. "."The argument is as simple as the rest of the film: after a quick presentation of the protagonist and his surreal environment, his country of origin, you have in the USA, where their heads are waiting to make a documentary that serves to Kazakhstan, to learn from the great power. There Borat starts a crazy trip full of rocambolescas situations. and anyway, if I did not give more details is not by not revealing anything, is because he does not deserve more.The fact is that this mockumentary strain not as a documentary, as fiction, or as a hybrid or as nothing. He is supposed to have two strong points: critical acid, corrosive, bla, bla, bla, and blatant and irreverent humor. Well, let's start by critics. Borat, in its way, meets characters which is supposed represent the deep North America. We have some racist, some xenophobic and other colorful characters. Intelligent criticism? I read that somewhere and I think that the standards are very low. It is true that there is a desire to get the dirt of a society really behind in many ways (at least one significant part of that society), but it stays always far of being interesting, shocking or crushing. It is a compilation of loose anecdotes which no can be nothing, except that one it has never heard of the USA. Bowling for Columbine is a damning criticism, not this. They may say that it is pamphleteer, but provides much and one has the feeling of having discovered something. Not here.The other issue is the humor. I think, after seeing many comedies of all kinds, that the big problem is that the majority of people lack sense of humor. One may not like it a running gag by two things: you don't understand, does not share such "jokes", etc. either is seen above. I.e., understand it, it is the kind of humor that likes, but fails their demands. If you are the type of people who laughs at family gatherings, desternilla with anecdotes of Uncle Paco and regards Ramón García as a comedian, then this film you will seem very blatant, irreverent and all that stuff. If you back, if you think that there are few people who have the ability to laugh at one to taste, if it is selective, has criteria and Los Morancos nor do you draw a grimace, then you will see that Borat fails, it tries to but it stays on the road. And good humor can be and criticism deep at the same time, no one is fooled. Cartoon "The Simpsons", "Family guy", type etc. are a great example, or "Life of Brian", to cite a film with real actors.Ultimately, I do not think smart, biting, or funny, or anything of what he wanted and what many want to see. Stays at the gates of everything and its escatological gags in the background are the only thing that saves. If it does not support the cruel jokes, the mockery, humiliation, etc., then neither arises to see her. The nonsense are only minimally notable.</body>
</review>
