<review author="Elena Suárez" title="El número 23" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You pick up seat with the feeling of just being robbed by a film production company. ?The number 23 &#8243; hooked me through an interesting trailer that invited me to spend a couple of hours drunk thriller but, rather, I ended up drunk of boredom.</summary>
	<body>How many times we have fallen into the tentative world of creativity and we bought something which, subsequently, has not exceeded our expectations. In these cases, is often the case that the advertising campaign is better than the announced product. Therefore exactly the same applies to quite a few movies. The trailer is quite attractive and adventure story that we will leave, at least moderately satisfied. However, the reality is entirely opposite and you pick up seat with the feeling of just being robbed by a film production company. "The number 23" hooked me through interesting breakthrough that invited me to spend a couple of hours drunk thriller but, rather, I ended up drunk of boredom.The parallel between the life of a reader and the character of the book which is enjoying will give foot into a spiral of obsessions that end up with a final bordering schizophrenia. One of the greatest mistakes of the film is the visual treatment that shows literary history that reads the protagonist: the artistic style chosen, of a comic, subtract all the mystery to the thriller and you therefore expelled from the narrative.During the script we have plenty of narrative traps enough suspicious: still do not understand why one of the characters enter his personal address between the leaves of a book that tries to publish anonymously; but it is that still I understand less as a hotel sits on the wall of a room full of blood and not only no one calls the police but that, years later, the blood still there.The end, as expected, is quite bizarre and any student of Psychology first may suffer a fairly strong mental collapse when you see. Finally highlight the strange partnership is that it makes the number twenty-three with certain historical personages, any resemblance to reality is pure coincidence.The best of the film, without doubt, the trailer.</body>
</review>
