<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Amor Idiota" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie in which strengths and weaknesses have a similar weight, and resorted to the usual clichés of Ventura Pons.</summary>
	<body>I cannot say that he is an admirer of Ventura Pons. In fact, has always seemed that his work often suffer from some provincial localism, and that somehow it hides some of the eternal complexes (I've never had very clear whether superiority, inferiority or half and half) of Catalan culture, permanently committed to mark a sometimes fictitious differences with the rest of the country.In any case, and precisely because of this desire to individualizador, the Catalan director has always been at the forefront in terms of technical narratives and filming techniques, which on the other hand always arouses the curiosity of the fan.Idiot love tells the story of a man of class media, Professor, that one night a woman who works displaying announcers posters of lampposts, encountered by chance and falls madly for her, arriving to commit outrages by approaching his beloved.The interpretation of Cayetana Guillén Cuervo as say Risto Mejide, is flat, while Santi Millán don't think he's an actor so worthy of praise as lately they seem bent on making us believe. In any case, the presenter of Spanish version has an undeniable attraction that seems to maintain immutable over the years and with which gives a special dose of curiosity to the committed sex scenes that are always present in the films of Ventura Pons.En the technical side, seem excessive to the point of evading, using the zoom and sudden changes of plans, and also some abuse of the narrative can be seen in first person with their pseudofilosóficos text messages. Script not may be denied it is imbued with the agility of its director, although you finf absurd at times.In general, a film in which good and evil can almost equate, and whose viewing won't be a waste of time but not excessive satisfaction will bring the Viewer.</body>
</review>
