<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excellent film by Yimou Zhang, which returns for its best charters after a stage something uncertain and irregular.</summary>
	<body>Excellent film by Yimou Zhang, which returns for its best charters after a stage something uncertain and irregular.Terrible story, told in the manner of the great classical tragedies, where their characters are not just peace and quiet, and must face both his own demons Interior as to the danger they pose their closest relatives.Yimou achieves an extraordinary movie in its formal package, with a beautiful colorful, magnificent use of lighting and costumes and exquisite make-up, which lead us to an extinct world where squabbles and political ambitions were the daily bread.But Yimou does not stop to achieve a stunning formal plasticity, but manages to fascinate through a story a thousand times view, but, certainly, it is nothing more than a soap opera, with their loves, hatreds, secret inconfensables, etc, displayed with a formal verve, uncontainable excitement and great interpretations, especially in charge of their wonderful actresses. In this sense, the admirable Li Gong manages, once again, a retrospective interpretation as a woman victim of misfortune, but able to fight using all weapons that are available.Characters in the hands of their inexorable fate, who can not escape his fate even though they try.Bright and dry dialogues and marvelous direction in the scenes of fighting and battles, with wonderful moments, such as the magnificent final battle. A battle that not only has nothing to envy to, for example, the of the vaunted "300", but that is obviously exceeds them by far in intensity and imagination and formal brilliance. I don't think there is doubt on this point.In short, that my understanding of "The curse of the Golden Flower" is a great film, fails to be a masterpiece, for example, by some falls in the central part of its rhythm, but that leaves the film uniqueness of Yimou Zhang, that record us has once again delight, but also to stop aching to show us some elements of the worst thing about being human. In this sense, the end of the film is totally conclusive and meaningless, I think, of moral.</body>
</review>
