<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The curse of the Golden Flower is a film of a great formal and aesthetic perfection, a pleasure for the senses of the spectator, which if left trapped by Zhang Yimou, will discover the poetry behind each scene.</summary>
	<body>Even only for a minority, the curse of the Golden Flower was one of the most anticipated films of the season, a lot more than the tape it megalomaniacal Hollywood which premiered this week. Zhang Yimou's previous efforts have only a possible adjective, and it is exceptional, scratching in the masterpiece, especially Hero.Yimou is a very personal director, although there will be many who did not appreciate his talent and only see a few mere comic of fighting in his works.Zhang Yimou manages what very few Directors have done throughout history, and do poetry with images. The script is a mere excuse to organize a real spectacle for the senses as not seen in a movie theater since the great Akira Kurosawa, although those are big words, and to Yimou still has much to even approaching the figure of the great Japanese filmmaker. The curse of the Golden Flower is proposing a story tinged tragedy at the end of the first Millennium Chinese court. A story full of palatial intrigue, conspiracies, wishes and desires in the purest line of Shakespeare, bridging the gap. There is who has written that this tape loosely resembles blood throne (adaptation of Macbeth, by the way), although if you want to search similarities with Kurosawa, should rather go to Ran. However, all of this matters little, as the huge visual spectacle that unfolds before the eyes of the spectator cloudy everything else. The forbidden city in Beijing is the ideal framework for Yimou make a sunset in really impressive scene, with some brimming with levels of beauty and poetry, such as family gatherings, the aerial views of the courtyards filled with chrysanthemums or throughout the last half hour of the film. It highlights the strength of the picture of Zhao Xiaoding, immense, with a chromatic palette worthy of a master, as well as the choreography of astonishing plasticity.The curse of the Golden Flower is a film of a great formal and aesthetic perfection, a pleasure for the senses of the spectator, which if left trapped by Zhang Yimou, will discover the poetry behind each scene and each level. Make a scene full of beauty and lyricism of a match only is within reach of a few chosen, and this is one of them.</body>
</review>
