<review author="Andrés Pons" title="Los Abandonados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Maybe it's the premiere more worthy of the Spanish terror of recent years. Nacho Cerdá must keep track</summary>
	<body>Nacho Cerdá came as a hurricane in the scene Spanish in the 1990s with shorts as "Aftermath" or "Genesis" becoming part of the bunch of promising young Hispanic horror. Even considering director of worship.Later its name was beginning to forget after not getting a debut which many fans hoped.After almost two decades of waiting it was announced trumpeted his highly anticipated debut in the hands of julio Fernández that practically is the King of the production of Spanish terror now "Let us not forget all the titles of the Fantastic Factory". With all these ingredients fans to the genre can also celebrate the inclusion in the script of the Martian "Karim Hussain" "Totally unclassifiable titles like"Subconcious Cruelty or Abscension"creator." Authentic delusions for tanned bellies.An estimate where virtually the entire weight of the action lies in two unknown Czech actors.Anastasia Hille "actress already tanned on terror with small collaborations on each other or The Hole" or Karel Rolden "Also." specialized in fantasy with interventions in the films of Guillermo del Toro Hellboy, El Laberinto del Fauno"The abandoned is a technically flawless film, a photograph magnificent, great atmosphere and with a really anthological director camera handling.Frank horror moments while they mingle with a script sometimes little clear, medium footage lapses throughout the tension created at an alarming rate to return to lift the flight at the last minute.The work of their interpreters is another point in their favor. Whatever the case and notwithstanding some imperfections the debut of filmmaker as soon as less hopeful, where it shows that that is known the terror and knows all their springs. Maybe it's the premiere more worthy of the Spanish terror of recent years. Nacho Cerdá must keep track. A 7.</body>
</review>
