<review author="Kamala" title="La vida de los otros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is one of the best films I've seen in a long time and I commend to everyone. Loyalty, friendship, betrayal, love, fear, value... Finally an essential movie.</summary>
	<body>Some weeks ago I saw this magnificent film, Opera prima, Florian Henckel Von Donnersmarck, who deservedly won the Academy Award for best foreign film. If the world just outside and the Oscars a few universal Awards, Ulrich Mühe and Sebastian Koch awards would have brought to best actor of this year. I do not know how it will be Forest Whitaker in "The last King of Scotland", but what is Ulrich Mühe in this film is im-pre-sio-nan-te. And Sebastian Koch you will not lag behind in talent, accompanied by a no less fantastic Martina Gedeck.Se remain in the memory frames of this film, shot in a very classic, simple way in appearance, without large stridency. In the great film always, most importantly is the story, which is telling. Is the film the vehicle that is narrated, and in the great works, the best technique is not note is, you do not feel that it is there, that is the story that takes you? This is the case in this film, however, has some moments of script not so round and who (now boy, a bit simple to oppose pureza-maldad) it could dispense with or who may be more marked (until the end do not know how long has been the captain of the Gerd Wiesler Stasi spying on the couple formed by the prestigious playwright and writer Georg Dreyman and popular actress Christa-Maria Sieland)by what becomes a little difficult to understand as "fast" identification between the principles of the military and the intellectual? (Time is contracted by imperative film duration and that that the hard movie more than two hours, passed flying).Are a few a little no "buts", I acknowledge, because the film is a work of precision, the silences and the dialogues are perfect, righteous, framed in a film planning (with very classic levels) and a photograph that? grey in exteriors, warmer in the apartment-very appropriate to situate ourselves in the GDR in the 1980s and check how it worked its espionage service, the Stasi.Es one of the best films I've seen in a long time and I commend to everyone. The loyalty, friendship, betrayal, love, fear, the value? are they transposed and are redefined throughout the film. Who is "fair"? what is being "fair"? Who or what? What is "treason"? If we betray ourselves, is the same do so out of conviction or fear? Survival or principles? Involvement against injustices, at the risk of losing life, or uncomfortable passivity? And it is that individual decisions affect everything that surrounds us, the story that we are creating. Three characters teach us that there are many forms of courage and integrity in a pequeña-gran story, of those that reflect one of the thousands of lives that make up what then it is in the books.</body>
</review>
