<review author="Pablo" title="Extraños en un tren" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hitchcock resurgio from the ashes and strangers on a train became one of his most personal works</summary>
	<body>A young and handsome tennis player from success, Guy Haines, is approached by an admirer, Anthony Bruno, in the course of a journey by train. This known to detail the private life of Guy and proposes to commit a perfect crime: an exchange of murders that would mislead altogether the police because the two would have an alibi at the time of the murders for which Bruno would eliminate the insufferable wife of tennis player, who refuses to grant him a divorce and prevents him from marrying the woman who really wants to and Guy, in return, would do the same with the possessive father of Bruno. Despite the refusal of the first, who thinks that everything is a simple joke, Bruno carried his Machiavellian plan and mercilessly kills the wife of Guy. Thus, without hardly noticing the young tennis player will be involved in a crime unresolved that you become it the main suspect for the police.After the failures of his two previous films, Hitchcock was in a delicate moment of his career that was not any history that was to his liking. A good day got their hands on a novel by Patricia Highsmith, who seemed to be written for him: a history of exchange of murder which addressed two of his favorite themes: the study of the malignant part of a model citizen and the figure of the false guilty. So Hitchcock resurgio from the ashes and strangers on a train became one of his most personal works. A tense, elaborate and shocking thriller which managed to penetrate the dark side of the human being to discover us a dramatic split in its interior, a demonic double who always travels with us and we believe controlled and therefore voluntarily forgotten but that coincidentally can become evident, introducing chaos and darkness in a world apparently tidy and bright. The character of Farley Granger would like to really get rid of his wife, but his "alter ego" scary is who resolves you the ballot. We can say that Guy and Bruno interpret a same character split in two.The film also features several famous and memorable, moments as the first sequence of the shoes, the killing reflected in glasses of the victim, the harrowing scene of the cigarette lighter in the sewer. but perhaps the most spectacular and exciting comes from the killer carousel, which reveals the estrema technical skill of Hitchcock. I read in a book that the actor who plays the Lord who gets under the carousel with the intention of stop it arrisegó really his life. In the words of Hitchcock: "If that man had raised a little the head." "never would have forgiven me it".</body>
</review>
