<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Los Abandonados" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An irregular and interesting debut almost in equal parts to a Nacho Cerdá that begins its journey in the long format and continues to be a brave and safe bet for the future of the most terrifying film of this country.</summary>
	<body>Nacho presented the film and dedicated parents who were in the room. Rumored that the projection for the press of morning didn't go too well, but in the afternoon, this another meeting, the public showed joyous and expectant, cheering even the opening credits. Much of the technical team and the two main actors, Anastasia Hille and Karen Roden, who make a great and hard work in the film, also accompanied the projection. The film, which is the debut as largometrajísta of its author, this fitted with a very remarkable technical Bill and the House of Xavi Giménez is, without a doubt and by own merits, a proven quality firm. Giménez already participated in some of the earlier work of Cerdá, "The Awakening" (1990), "Aftermath" (1994), and "Genesis" (1998). The latter are two medium length very linked to the genre Gore, who knew how to find its audience and put a dent in fantastic festivals and horror as small works of worship. It is footage who sponsor this first film of Nacho Cerdá, feature film which, unfortunately, is once again a perfect showcase of the virtues and defects of productions of terror of the producer, that not only are almost all photographed by the same cameraman, but that also end up view all a bit like cut by the same pattern. Of "Abandoned" it hooked me above all the principle, which is predominantly a mysterious and disturbing atmosphere, together with an efficient work in the direction of art. We submerged in a brilliant composition full of poetic and disturbing levels. However, soon, you can see a certain abuse of some obsessively dark, scary decorations, old broken wrists, moans of babies and a whole series of very recognizable clichés within the genre. Some omnipresent sound effects to a volume completely out mother and an endless succession of scares efectistas and free, unfortunately, begin to seriously irritate the viewing. History, moreover, downside inexplicably a special drop to half of the footage, where the plot, once shown the letters, stagnates and surprises, after such jam theatrical disordered and chaotic, already does not have the desired effect. When the tape is then surprising in its final outcome, it is too late, although it is true that some of my favorite scenes focus precisely on this stretch. Cerdá, however, shows great talent, becomes larger and teaches the teeth when bound to agitate, provoke, suggest, in some of those moments of reflective in the recreation of a logradísima oppressive atmosphere, tension and suspense, as for example when the protagonists seem to wait together resigned to its final destination, without any doubt, one of the best moments of the film. The public, something cold, dismissed the film with timid applause contrasted with the enthusiasm of the beginning of the evening, and my I was feeling of having seen something which could have been spectacular, but that stayed a bit by the way, in an exercise perhaps too artificial and confusing. An irregular and interesting debut almost in equal parts to a Nacho Cerdá that begins its journey in the long format and continues to be a brave and safe bet for the future of the most terrifying film of this country.</body>
</review>
