<review author="Dragon negro" title="Sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A well run and well shot film with special rather than correct effects that surprisingly change log and when he loses his grace. Highly recommended for fans of science fiction.</summary>
	<body>The Sun is dying and a spacecraft is launched into space with the mission to detonate a large bomb in the interior of the Sun to reactivate it. But the ship fails in his mission, and seven years later, a new ship is sent with the same mission that represents the last hope of humanity survive. As it is expected not everything will be a hook road.So far all good, the movie promises to be a science film catastrophic fiction where began to emerge unforeseen problems that will be solved with greater or lesser fortune to be able to see if they came to complete the mission or perish in the attempt. The atmosphere and the setting are indicated in a film of these features and it is very well developed, but we reached a point where some plot twist will ruin seen so far and the film loses its final stretch North and comes to crush in excess with Visual tricks and thunderous sound that does not lead to anything and that makes the film be weary and lost all his grace.And it is that resort to the captain of the ship of the first mission and transform it into a crazy obsessive filled with burns that aims to sabotage the mission with lapidary phrases about God that is murdering the crew is loaded all the film. One wonders comes similar plot twist without coming to story and badly raised and longer posts, as her pussy this type has survived so many years and so full of burns. A type which not even we see in detail that suddenly begins to abuse the Visual excesses, the blurred image and sound shrill when so far the film had a sunset scene more than correct.Only from that point is that you desvincules of the film, which so far had developed magnificently in its field, and that you you look from the outside, losing all complicity with the Viewer.A well run and well shot film with special rather than correct effects that surprisingly change log and when he loses his grace. Even and thus highly recommended for fans of science fiction, can be seen despite its patinated end.</body>
</review>
