<review author="JLO" title="2001, Odisea del espacio" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The definition of the initial word of the title is a good synthesis of the film. A long trip in one consistent exercise for the mind of a philosopher, for a common Viewer.</summary>
	<body>"After having her seen repeatedly, I realized that this is the first time I feel that an artist is"very"above me." Woody AllenOdisea (title of a Homeric poem): long journey which abound in adverse and favourable to the traveller adventures (encyclopedic dictionary Salvat). The definition of the initial word of the title is a good synthesis of the film. A long trip said (and add also metaphysical, lyrical and megalomaniac in equal parts) in an exercise according to the mind of a philosopher, for a common Viewer. Loaded of symbolism and interpretations that escape and rediscovered in repeated visions of the film, it is unfathomable, ambiguous and fascinating. Is this film a director obsessed by this masterpiece? Is it worthy of a visionary or a film pretentious and boring like few others?Wanting to embrace and develop the primitive beginnings of man, the extraterrestrial life with future technology and development and evolution sounds, the less, excessive for any mortal. Trying to Stanley Kubrick, it sounds not so outlandish. Comment on 2001 is made with some trepidation: the power not cover it in its entirety. With so many edges and varied interpretations as each one to strive and create view. Without fear of mistakes, it is one of the best films of its genre and an essential reference in the creative universe of this talented director. It brings together each and every one of his obsessions and successes, as well as its own flaws.Also changed the path of science fiction forever, being a minor - almost B class and despised genus up to that point. Number placed in the survey is made among the best films in the history.Dawn of the hombreEste before and after we pointed out, is because both its form and its content. The prologue with the apes transvestite perfectly, like the primitive steps and changes of human evolution towards the man. For this reason, the positions and almost human movements are necessary. This achieved by actors - mimes - highlighting "Moonwatcher" (Daniel Richter) for being the leader, and who stars in the mythical scene of the bone released into the air, which in a terrible and beautiful ellipsis becomes the ship Discovery (discovery). The alignment of the stars always anticipating a major event; the spacecraft to the tune of the Blue Danube by Johann Strauss simulating a sexual dance for its forms (according to Kubrick "a mechanical ballet"); they may be crazy as a trait of genius.Scenes of beauty and emotional depth rarely seen in a film until today. The flat monolith of black granite - symbol of superior extraterrestrial intelligence? or God?-is the only link that allows Kubrick to us in the film. Otherwise, develops it our own imagination (who wants some clue or meanings, will need to read the book by Clarke that abounds in them).Thus spoke final KubrickEl containing a new be pure and original (called the child star) is hopeful and an unpublished positivism in his films. All point out at this point, to the similarities between the content of the film and the book of the German philosopher Friedrich Nietzsche called thus spoke Zarathustra. Everything begins to relate the main leiv motiv musical of 2001, called precisely same, composed by Richard Strauss at the end of the 19th century based on reading the same book. Then everything drew Nietzschean theory of the "Superman" and the return of the new man, a being without the limitations of the race human (does the child star?).Ownership is divided into several characters, perhaps for gigantic figure of the director, the only real "Star" of the film. Recognizable side are already named Moonwatcher, Dr. Floyd (William Sylvester that converses in a scene with his supposed daughter (Vivian Kubrick); astronaut Poole (Gary Lockwood), and the character of greatest exposure on screen during the final part: astronaut Bowman (Keir Dullea).)The real star and protagonist of 2001 - and that more lives in our memory - we know is the cold, cynical and static super computer HAL 9000. A sweeping personality and who was born primarily on female version, changing to avoid the sexual connotations which distraerían by others according to the director. A cruel, intelligent and almost human machine with the neutral, serious and mechanical voice of Canadian Douglas Rain (voice of NASA projects). The only but may be too extensive and psychedelic "trip" final of Bowman by the black hole - 8 minutes!-, that leads it to its own evolution. As bright passage through his colorful as tiring as if Kubrick wanted to show us for the umpteenth time his master to achieve unprecedented special effects that Yes, so far.HistoriaConvengamos that being 2001 nine years younger than the first Star Wars (1977), and with its archaic procedure (frame-by-frame by moving the models 4 mm for the time) does not show too much lower in the field, and not to mention, the artistic distance (see quote from Lucas at the end). A vision that is confusing despite the enjoyment and the difficult access to the plot by the absence (said before deliberate) of a conventional and linear structure of script.Kubrick said in his few interviews that 2001 is a "non-verbal" experience and that everyone has to do their own interpretation of apparently; Judging to only loose signs, with a vague consistency as being the now famous black monolith. Dialogs occupy only 40 of the 141 minutes, almost with a purpose of dispersion. He became so famous that in 1972 the great Tarkovsky created Solaris, commissioned as a Soviet response to the success of 2001, roundly denied by the director himself. "Finally, the awaited masterpiece (which he any both according to his sayings during the filming of Barry Lyndon), think that it had already made it at the end of the 1960s a contramano of his time and is called: 2001 Space Odyssey."The film moves to the closest level with painting and music than with the written word. "Why films offer the possibility to explain concepts and abstractions without the traditional unit of words."Stanley Kubrick "I am quite happy that not have compared it both with 2001 (to Star Wars)." At the technical level they can be compared, but I think that 2001 is much higher. "They had ten times more money and time, and obviously came out better." George Lucas, Rolling Stone, August 25, 1977</body>
</review>
