<review author="Silvia Giner" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I cried, I have fallen in love, has seduced me. Absolutely great, round film.</summary>
	<body>The source of life comes to our screens to leave us speechless. A dogma faith that makes movie full of poetry and spirituality with a magical graphic show that will not leave indifferent.As its name suggests, this film uses the myth of "The source of life" or "tree of life" to tell us a sad and real story that mixes passionately with a spiritual plane and another fantastic giving as a result a full of mysticism and pain moraleja.At the end we are what we are and are not yet ready to drink the eternal SAP of the tree of life, our spirit is too poor and our attempts to pursue what we want are powerless. Only the soul can raise us up to the dignity of being touched by the universe and our internal peace, love is one of the tools to achieve that and impotence a barrier in the road that leads to the goal.Wonderful work of Hugh Jackman and in general of all stakeholders (including monkeys). I believe that our beloved Wolverine begins to separate from its viz superhero with enough talent, and is that this man is going to give that talk, by the way, that in 2008 we can enjoy it again in this role that Wolverine will be released. But calm that is Hugh for a while, then slopes as well as it has 6 more movies and a pilot for a TV series, tremendous actor gentlemen.We must certainly thank the film writer and director Darren Aronofsky this wonder that has given us, we did not expect less after the bombing that was "Requiem for a dream" which he directed and wrote. This guy is definitely decanting by experimental and it is certain that your bets are bold and offending. Great talent of Darren, I think that it is demonstrated.I want to highlight "The Fountain" the ability to repeat several times the same without bore it is very complicated, but achieves it. Both the BSO and many sequences are repetitive, but however never are heavy, slow or repetitive, but absolutely delicious and intoxicating. I cried, I have fallen in love, has seduced me. Absolutely great, round film.</body>
</review>
