<review author="JLO" title="La naranja mecánica" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film with successes and mistakes, has classic status, influence an entire generation of filmmakers and film buffs. From several points of view as the aesthetic, moral - up by its grim history of bans-, all dyeing of a staff and innovative style.</summary>
	<body>"Clockwork Orange is my favorite movie right now." "Had certain prejudices against her, but after seeing her, I realized that it is the only one that exists about the true meaning of the modern world." Luis BuñuelFilm with successes and mistakes, has classic status, influence an entire generation of filmmakers and film buffs. From several points of view as the aesthetic, moral - up by its grim history of bans-, all dyeing of a staff and innovative style. Excellent adaptation of the book by Anthony Burgess, tells part of his personal experience to be unemployed and be the victim of violence by the fact - little known-be your own wife victim of a violation by three soldiers during the war.Also this film bears all the characteristics of the filmmaker, its flaws and its virtues. Bombastic and pretentious, shrewd, dream-like, full of signs. Vital and strong. The should you mention as his film that became worse, because he composed the film with all futuristic icons (commissioned from the best designers of the moment) that languidecería with the passage of time becoming a brand of 1970s years.It is the film that marked his imprint of divide them into two antagonistic halves, like a journey of return of his characters in the background of the acciones-adquisiciones made by the road and its dire consequences. Showing us the violence without violence, almost of art form (if the look today at the time bans would be laughable) a more earthly than the Odyssey of the man who showed us only three years earlier in the film 2001.Acierto in the choice of an unknown protagonist (Andrew MacDowell), only known by the Love Store melosa, step after using Kubrick in almost all of his films - less 2001 - and the first players enshrined as Sterling Hayden, Kirk Douglas, Peter Sellers (on two occasions) and James Manson. ComienzoUn top powerful, almost intimidating. One of the best of Kubrick and any film. The murderous and cold eyes of Alex (preanunciando his incipient madness) which through a slow travelling becomes the Milkibar with your druggos/friends, that we stalk and is configured, in these early days he preferred to engage the viewer and keep it attentive to what is to come. According to an excellent appreciation of Spanish critics Felici and framework, this view of Alex is a continuation of the gaze of the last plane of its predecessor film, the child star of 2001. The hope and optimism that hits scene with the violence of it returning to the present typical pessimism of almost all films of Kubrick.Las large scenes are many. The aesthetic implementation where the fight with a rival gang in a theatrical setting, provides an ode to violence plan ballet. The shots "execution" idling on the edge of the pool by Alex reaffirming his leadership to the sound of classical music that dominates the film. The deadly dance with Ms. cat in his sexual room (with a giant phallus and a bust of Beethoven by each side as weapons) cause both her death and the fall/death of the own Alex. Oneiric passages of the Bible in the imagination of the protagonist (like video clip), are all shot with the delicacy of a sand paper passed by acid; scenes worthy of a true lover of film and music, as already show it the use of the latter in 2001 metaphysics. ProblemasFilmada during the winter of 1970 / 1971, one of the first drawbacks that raised you was to adapt the nadsat (Russian for "teen" suffix) had invented the author as the gang slang, inspired by his study of the Russian language. Kubrick solves faithfully transcribed word for Word of the invention, with the absolute understanding and acceptance of the spectators. Another obstacle were threats to the director and his family blaming him of violence in British streets by the fury of the film and its images. Kubrick decided shortly after the cancellation be exhibited in Britain. Despite all the reruns made an incredible profitability of the film - cost two and grossed 40-consolidate the independence of the director and ensuring the absolute control of all his subsequent work.However, the text has a last chapter redeems Alex - greater, already married and happy - all their facts, reinsertando again to the society that rejected and giving, an epilogue, more hopeful, Catholic and banal. Kubrick discarded it by inappropriate for the theme of his film and the book (release in fact without that last chapter in the US)."More than graphic is the appointment of a technical member of the staff of the film, which clearly exemplifies the thought of the director and of the same end of the film:" Kubrick with 2001, Space Odyssey shows us what we could have had, and with the Orange mechanics, shows us what we are going to get really. ""Man should decide about good and evil, even if you choose to evil. Deny that choice is to turn it into something that does not reach humans. "in a Clockwork Orange" Kubrick Stanley</body>
</review>
