<review author="JLO" title="El resplandor" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The shining does not become one of its summits works, up us seems one of the least successful. It is the only film in which he and his camera are not the true and only protagonists.</summary>
	<body>Five years after his first major commercial failure (Barry Lyndon), Kubrick would not stop thinking about his next project should be a resounding box-office success. And with the shining it, and more. Despite the excesses of budget (spent ten million more) and filming time, show us a more eclectic, and old Kubrick not having nothing to do this with efficiency and aesthetics used in the filmmaker. We could say that it is the only film in which he and his camera are not the true and only protagonists. His strong style leaves no note at all times and in several passages - visions, the use of the stedycam, follow-up of the axe - show us the same Director obsessive and cynical that we know. As the scene of children playing only in the shield and the rapprochement between fleeting and slow of a tennis ball all taken of course, in his usual plain fixed upward. Or the sea of blood in the elevator from Hall. (The same scene is the trailer of the film, one of the most beautiful that I saw by the simple and direct).The pomp of the ballroom and the ghostly characters entrecruzando, would be an exact sample of Kubrick and his film obsessions. But in this case the film is imbued with, by and for the showcasing of a Lord named Jack Nicholson. It is said that all the films by Kubrick in need of a hero albeit atypical: Alex, Barry Lyndon, the Joker soldier, etc. Perhaps each one of them is analogous with personality the director. This Jack Torrance seems to be the best example of this.All are converted into a version in acid of the filmmaker, a mirror of his more macabre side and that the figure and the representation of Jack Nicholson, finds its best exponent. The character, his overacting, unleashed fury, his slow, progressive madness, is "devouring" the film. A psychopath always on the edge of the explosion and dementia, express and from the first scene in the interview (is said that own actor was going through its worst mood and personal time with drugs). We see after detention in a hotel isolated with his family, he shows us its true face and personality - aided by the own ghosts of the hotel - and this whole process itself, is the most successful by Kubrick in the film.Do not explode, if that is not a slow crowned tour when his wife discovers among his things, five hundred pages with the same text: "both work and little play, makes Jack a very bitter type".The error of Kubrick is wanting to "re - define" an atypical genre, succeeding only partially. The idea of do it is both for having found a potential good script in the book by Stephen King (other than economic), as well as defiance of not accepting a few years earlier make the sequel to the super successful El Exorcist of William Friedkin (eventually turned into classic), catalogued with justice as one of the best films of terror in the history.The successful dreamy scenes of the Hall of dance and the bathroom with the spectra, or the same final scene with the approach to the old photo (demonstrating that evil existed always) become their best moments. Not let the film be stunning visually, losing thickness at a time that would have to be of the most terrifying, precisely by a too meticulous aesthetics devoid of tension and impact, or the slowness of its footage, as in the final persecution the child protagonist solving it with a fixed frame of the petrified and frozen Nicholson's face. Rarely successful and efficient, considered one of the best horror films in history, in a global assessment of the work of Kubrick the shining does not become one of his works summits, us up seems one of the least successful of the second part of his career, but keeps the pulse and intact quality of an original Kubrick", that it is never short."I think the best argument is that seems not to exist. I like the slow principles, calan in the public and involve it in the film, allowing you to appreciate the Gracile notes and delicate tones. "In this way no I have to complicate me life with plot resources and tips to keep the suspense." Stanley Kubrick</body>
</review>
