<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Sunshine" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sunshine is a hybrid of 2001: A Space Odyssey, Titanic (in advance we know that he won't stay or the pointer) and the final part, the shining.</summary>
	<body>When disaster films seemed finally eradicated forever, approached the new millennium, and a couple of years before Hollywood took to revive this type of tape. If first asteroid, epidemics, aliens, climate change, and the recurring stories in planes or ships. And when already it seemed that there was not any kind of disaster that could lead to the film, and that humanity had waged for ever this biblical plague, arrives Danny Boyle brings us Sunshine.Hablando of disasters, Sunshine gives us a really terrible approach, which our Sun cools and the Earth is facing a Solar winter. Come on, nor of the same centre of Bilbao in shirt going to withstand the cold if not putting remedy to the death of the Sun. An expedition composed of eight astronauts traveling on a ship, Icarus II (which chose the name was showcased, because if only already portends the tragedy), did the first, how not, fail, more than anything to give more sense of significance to this second mission. Although more that a ship is a giant bomb, to reactivate the core of our star. The film begins with a small apocalyptic discursito, although in the mind of the Viewer is the image of an astronaut on the back of the steering wheel shaking pump its shading cowboy through stars and shouting happily what yeeha!. Small reference to Stanley Kubrick, although the winks just not there, Sunshine is a hybrid between 2001: A Space Odyssey, Titanic (in advance we know that he won't stay or the pointer) and the final part, the shining. Because the film is transformed into his last act, a history of science fiction becomes a kind of space psycho-thriller. The tape has some calamitous details, as human error that triggers the fatalities, taking on the ship as effective computer (do not remember something?), it is unable to correct or even notice this.In its effort to constantly change gender and look for originality, Danny Boyle offers a bad remake of some of the classics of science fiction. And if outside little, remove from the ICU to a genre that was on its last legs, and it justly deserved to disappear. Because a disaster movie is a disaster in itself.</body>
</review>
