<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do is the source of life is divided into three stories, being the? real? the more powerful, interesting and best-armed of all.</summary>
	<body>Current film suffers a severe creative crisis, increasingly fewer films that could be considered original, and on the other hand abound copies or remakes remakes of earlier films. This problem is especially acute in Hollywood, although you can't know for sure if it is due to scarcity of writers with ideas or the scarcity of producers who dare to take forward different and innovative proposals.But it is also true that there are some directors are at the opposite pole, who in his desperate search for innovation and originality, spend the film limits. And Darren Aronofsky is one of them without any doubt. Try to explain what is the source of life is almost as difficult as calculated to infinity the number Pi, a task clearly comparable to the labours of Hercules. The film basically tells a story of love, loss and the search for a source that would prevent that loss. The source of life is divided into three stories, the "real" being the more powerful, interesting and best-armed of all; Here we can find the best moments of the film, some of a great Canora. The received story of the Conqueror and the Elizabeth Queen of Spain in the 16th century (great virtue show from the start which is a completely fictional vision of history) is well built, and manages to catch the viewer with the search of the myth of the fountain of eternal youth. In the third story Aronofsky is where fails completely, offering metaphysical ramblings without sense, and the theoretical poetry and beauty of this third story are totally invaluable, becoming a heavy ballast rather than a help. The truth is that the first twenty minutes, in which intermingle all three stories without ton or are left baffled up to the most enthusiastic spectator. But as the narrative becomes more linear and logical, the film greatly improves. However, when approaching the hour of truth in any history, Aronofsky will turn off the lights, and offers an ending that throws rushing past achievements.The best of the source of life, in addition to its short duration, is the magnificent work of Hugh Jackman, which continues to demonstrate his great interpretative gifts. For its part, Rachel Weisz (partner in real life of Darren Aronofsky) also does a good job with great naturalness that has always characterized him.</body>
</review>
