<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Dame 10 razones" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Give me 10 reasons is a fun, interesting and intelligent comedy that pretending to be a very entertaining while the Viewer, that you not offended or takes it for fool.</summary>
	<body>American independent cinema is experiencing in recent years a second golden age after several years of almost absolute mediocrity. In fact, with a few Honorable exceptions of Hollywood, most of the best American films of recent times are independent. There are some genres that is most noticeable this trend, especially in the comedy, given the shameful examples of major American studios.Give me 10 reasons is the story of a famous actor in low hours (Morgan Freeman), who visits a supermarket in a suburb of Los Angeles to investigate a charge character. There he meets Scarlet (Paz Vega), a vigorous cashier. Both engage in a peculiar and special relationship that will learn from each other. After his early work in Hollywood, Brad Silberling writes and directs this fun and interesting human comedy, never trying to be pretentious or moralizing. The script is agile and resourceful, with some especially acidic moments in what refers to the life of a big star of the interpretation. The tape has several virtues that deserve to be featured, as the sense of veracity that transmits like the pace that prints Silberling, suitable for a comedy of these features. There will be who critique its duration, but is another virtue that adding scenes for the sole purpose of extending the film is somewhat absurd, and in most cases end up harming. Another great virtue is the end, that we did not desvelaremos here, anyone who wants to discover what you need to come to the nearest cinema. The two protagonists are some very fresh and natural, performances with Morgan Freeman playing and laughing at himself, and a Paz Vega ever more based on American lands through papers such as this.Give me 10 reasons is a fun, interesting and intelligent comedy that pretending to be a very entertaining while the Viewer, that you not offended or takes it for fool. Let us hope that Brad Silberling will continue in this line and abandon the line of work as A series of catastrophic misfortunes of Lemony Snicket.</body>
</review>
