<review author="Alex Largo" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>But what is "Diary of a scandal"? As a telefilm that clothes in two actresses who could well have led Oscar to which chose each.</summary>
	<body>Certainly, he was eager to see this film. Four nominations for the Oscars. Best, best supporting actress, best soundtrack and best screenplay. The film promised. But what is "Diary of a scandal"? As a telefilm that clothes in two actresses who could well have led Oscar to which chose each.The film does not know to film, does not know anything, is somewhat dull.The work of the director (of "Iris") is very correct. Although only that does not stand out on their own merits, and I very much doubt that Cate Blanchett and Judi Dench have nominations to the Oscars for the work of the director, but rather by their nature of actresses (Yes, with capital letters).And it is that this is the most notable. The actresses. Two actresses that lifted the film with impressive ease. Judi Dench creates a real monster, but a monster under the facade of a lonely and obsessive elderly woman. Dench undertake its role and makes it one of the two highlights of the tape. This nomination well could have earned her the Oscar, but the overstated performance of Helen Mirren took the statuette Dench already won as best secondary for "Shakespeare in Love".The script is quite disappointing. Although good, it should have been given more than Yes. More "cool" is the nomination for the Oscars as best adapted screenplay. Since then, will be as well adapted that they want to, but for an Oscar.La last of its nominations for the Oscars was for best soundtrack. Let's face it, is a good soundtrack. The problem is that the compositions of this man seem much, it is more, the scoring of "The hours", "The illusionist" and "Diary of a scandal", resemble much among themselves.In general a good telefilm, with a few actresses of infarction and the Oscars more nominations.</body>
</review>
