<review author="Alex Largo" title="Hechizo de luna" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In conclusion, a film that could have given more of if, which back the flight in the last part to the delight of the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>Okay, if it is not bad. But it has not excited me. Above all the principle. The story is funny, but the first part is very desaprobechada. I am ahead. better let's go by parts.With regard to the work of the director. poor. Especially in the first part. Until that Cher is not going to the Opera director Norman Jewison (surprisingly nominated for an Oscar for this movie) does not begin to "work". And it is that since that time, the film moves from poor to truly entertaining.As for the screenplay (Oscar winner), well, but widely desaprobechado by the director. But if the script had fallen into the hands of anyone else, the film would have gained a lot.Talking about actors, there are three groups: good, Nicholas Cage and the dull. In the first group are all residents of the House of Loretta. In the second group, Nicholas Cage, something less cardboard as we see him lately, but equally bland and apavado.The third group is the fiancé of Loretta and all those who do not fall in any of the first two groups.Cher is which looks better (in fact took the Oscar), and gives us the best character of the tape and the more grateful. But somewhat exaggerated, that me I cannot see Cher doing a better than Meryl Streep role, was also nominated. As regards the distribution that is included in the collective of the third age, great, from the grandfather, until the mother. All stunning.Nicholas Cage offers a not-so-poor, poor performance as which us gives now. More surprising is how sometimes it seems even that changes of expression does will be a slight trace of what you gave an Oscar? There is no great aspects comentables escepto already counted.In conclusion, a film that could have given more of if, which back the flight in the last part to the delight of the Viewer. Even so, the film garnered some very important nominations in the Oscars (6 in total of which won 3), including (surprisingly) the nomination for best film nomination in which rose not winning (as in the best director), thanks to the divine intervention in both categories of "The last emperor".</body>
</review>
