<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The source of life has some of the most impressive scenes never before seen in a movie.</summary>
	<body>A whole blog would be required to discuss the source of life, the new film by Darren Aronofsky controversial Fund. I have not seen neither Pi and Requiem for a dream, but I do not think it takes to understand (if this applies) the third work of the director. And it is that it is not only to understand his work, but entering it, feel it. You could say that you love or hate her, although he does not want to say that you or a masterpiece or a crappy. The film is neither one thing nor another, but is, rather, an extrañísimo story, beautiful in every sense and full of anecdotes and really intended details of which you must forget more than one. The source of life is not only a moral, a lesson of life, of its challenges, but also a poem made into images. Such poetry can be seen in virtually all the footage, because its rhythm and structure, repetitive, slow altogether and beautiful invoice are assimilated to any poetry of a level that exceeds what is acceptable.The film of Aronofsky's pedantic, weird, boring, embarrassing can you condemn? Yes, are you can condemn, even if it is not, nor much less. This is a film, without doubt any original, strange, formal, repetitive, bonito, etc. I may not have reason, because as I said earlier, the love or hate her, but thinking about it well, at least I think this is the most risky proposal of the year. I don't want to dwell too much, as this is a film that has to see and enjoy, and fewer things to know it before viewing it, more her you apreciarás.Say, first of all, that the script is good, no more. What here stands out above all the direction and originality of Aronofsky is clear. It is true that without a script, the film would not exist, but it is here that the aesthetics and how is told is what truly stands out. The source of life has some of the most impressive scenes never before seen in a movie, such as, for example, of Thomas (a huge Hugh Jackman in the middle ages) hallucinating with the wise from the tree, absorbing her and aprobechándola with the intention that does not end. No doubt, this is one of the key scenes, which defines the human being in a perfect way, spectacular and, finally, as it must be realistic. Secondly, I would highlight the moment when Izzy (Rachel Weisz) tells everything about the last chapter of the book Tommy at the hospital. This is a film that is sure of itself, which does not want to be pretentious. Its aim is to reach people this direct message to "enjoy the time", talk to us, in passing, of love, real love and ask ourselves the question of whether there is eternal love. So that we have a bet incredibly deep (too!), full of wisdom and understanding.The interpretations it reprocharía nothing, absolutely nothing. Hugh Jackman is better than ever, in a role extremely complicated and difficult to interpret. Although it would not wrong saying that Rachel Weisz is even better than him, in an interpretation complex, risky and with a hope of immortality, that soon fades (go spolier!). Both performers show an incredibly realistic chemistry, full of nuances and sense (who not are always of Weisz Queen?). Another aspect in favour would be the superb music of Clint Mansell, with a main theme absolutely heartbreaking and exciting. This would be the third best performance of the work, the music.As only drawback would add the lack of sense that have some images, or at least that I do not understand. You can know what is this kind of medal that appears during several sequences! I do not know, will be paranoia? And perhaps that is too excessive, at times seems you do to explode the head of so much light. But well, as you can see, these small notes are really insignificant for the immense quality of the film as a whole.A wonderful film, deep until no longer to be him more, beautiful, exciting, complex, incredibly developed and with a pair of performances that deserve a big round of applause, as well as the address of Mr Aronofsky, which I will have slope throughout my eternal life. Requiem for a dream!</body>
</review>
