<review author="Marta" title="El jefe de todo esto" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Von Trier satirises the film process, labour relations and appearances in a hilarious movie, with absurd dialogues, strange characters and disparate situations.</summary>
	<body>I guess that there is no better time to talk about "The Chief of all this" the day of the worker. The last film by Lars Von Trier premiered in Spain revolves around a company whose owner decides to hire an actor to make go through the real boss, that he has hidden his office employees. And this time isn't a great drama of those to which we are accustomed to the Danish director, but just the opposite. Laughed I not remember having so much film in a very long time. Von Trier satirises the film process, labour relations and appearances, possibly in a much more autobiographical way so that I can appreciate. And it does so by absurd dialogues, strange characters and disparate situations. A risky bet, that could have given rise to a stupid movie filled with topics and easy jokes and that, however, it turns out to be a hilarious comedy with many unexpected twists. Between the obsession of the actor to make each of his sentences in a historical interpretation, Chief cocoon with pint of good-natured (and Peter, "Family guy" voice in the Spanish dub), the cries of the Icelandic entrepreneur and the rarities of the Office as a whole, "The Chief of all this" not too has to envy to the Coen brothers or Woody Allen comedies. Of course, Lars Von Trier does not remain quiet if you do not experience. What she has already made clear with the dogma "Idiots" or the scenarios of "Dogville" and "Manderlay", among other things. On this occasion, there are who can bother you that the director has dared to interrupt the action with their explanations on the narrative structure of the comedy in voice-over, or forget voluntarily camera, giving rise to those curious frames. To me, personally, I like these jueguecitos that break the monotony of the image and give a more fresh air to the final result. It is very likely that "The Chief of all this" is not valued and deserves to go down in history as one minor in the Filmography of the director works, lost among its large, deep dramones. It is not that they look me bad movies, but when I saw Emily Watson, Björk and Nicole Kidman play the same role of "poor defenseless individual before cruel and powerful society", I cannot help but start thinking that Von Trier is a little tiresome, who knows only shoot the same over and over again and that its main objective is to demonstrate his mastery when it comes to suffering the Viewer. Work such as this do not lose hope that is capable of much more.</body>
</review>
