<review author="Dragon negro" title="Premonition (Siete días)" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film full of inconsistencies and temporary failures to sing a lot, see it without giving many laps which tells you can entertain you, but find their faults you entertain even more.</summary>
	<body>Sandra Bullock stars in this film with supernatural overtones where a wonderful life in principle with her husband and their two daughters troncará after receiving the news of the death of her husband in an accident of traffic, the next day wakes up and is that her husband is alive, thinking that all been a bad dream. But the next day he wakes up and her husband returns to be dead, with resulting everything more real than she thought.From the outset, a paranormal thriller starring Sandra Bullock already claims some aversion to the couple that warns that we are facing a very conventional and shot product in the face of the showcasing of the star. What happens is that the star looks rather little as it happens with the same face of disgusted during all the footage and also the character that plays just becoming more pathetic than anything else. And is that when one already it makes time given has that what happens is that the protagonist is living the days in a disorderly way, she seems to discover it and also tells it you out loud until doing a sketch so that we understand well and we do not lose, as if we were stupid.After all this the grace of the film is to see if the Bullock will be able to save her husband from imminent death or whether it will fail to do so, but the writers discuss the great failure of portraying her husband as a cocoon, which makes you lose all complicity and emotion by what happens or notrather, what you want is that they kill and already step that takes the woman with him. But this is not the only bug that commit the writers already that the film full of inconsistencies and temporary failures to sing a lot, and is that if you get to play with the time at least keep some consistency, not a puzzle pieces that then do not fit.The film deserves a mention to the scene more jam as seen by a server recently and is how to convert a task daily, as normal as going to collect the clothes lying in a sequence of tension in crescendo stuck with shoehorn to justify another scene. But the jackpot goes to this ridiculous way, touching the joke of how the Bullock tries to save her husband, seriously I was starting me the box and hallucinating, it can become more foolish?As telefilm for the desktop on Sunday has true pass, see it without giving many laps which tells you can entertain you, but find their faults you entertain even more.</body>
</review>
