<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Spiderman 3" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Viewers who see Spider-Man 3 without the blindfold of fanaticism blinding them eyes, will have a bland, boring and excessively long film.</summary>
	<body>Bad us though, there is never two without three, and in the film this maxim is true to letter, except cataclysm box office. And as the Spider-Man franchise has generated huge profits for their producers, already took too devise the third installment of the saga, which will be the last (not for lack of desire but because Tobey Maguire has already said that it will not hesitate to mesh). The invasion that now suffer the Spanish charts only may be comparable to that it suffered for almost 200 years at the hands of Napoleon and his Grande Armée. To that we planted face and we won, but the man spider is difficult to stop him.Sam Raimi gives us the darkest film of the saga, in which the inner hero conflict multiply, at the same time increase in that strange (laugh of the Bermuda) triangle formed by Tobey Maguire, Kirsten Dunst and James Franco. Finally, turn Hollywood fashion, which says that in a pure and simple tape of action and effects must be human and dramatic elements to demonstrate their depth. And since then, with similar arguments, Spider-Man 3 manages to demonstrate that it has the same depth that the flow of the Júcar river. The script has both development and progression as a Communist in Wall Street and all its characters are flat encephalogram. If outside little, to achieve size effect, must be made a film of two hours and a half duration, i.e. 60 minutes more than any human being would be considered rational. It must be said for the tape that has a couple of good sequences, and a really impressive technical deployment, but that despite its spectacular nature, you cannot fill the vacuum resounding plot.Staunch supporters of the Marvel, Spider-Man 3 will love. The rest of the spectators, they see the movie without the bandage of fanaticism blinding them eyes, will have a bland, boring and excessively long film. What a shame that not mount a stall that sells insecticide and mata-moscas, because it would be a true pitch, and a relief for more than one disconsolate Viewer next to the box office of each film.</body>
</review>
