<review author="Jose Contreras" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Said a critic that see "The Da Vinci Code" is so exciting as see your grandfather solving a Sudoku puzzle</summary>
	<body>After embracing Christianity, Constantine convened a Council at Nicaea to unite all the positions and point out heresies. One of the most important discussions was that raised the Arianism. The official position was that Christ was God, had not been created, like the rest of mortals. ARIUS, on the other hand argued that Christ was a creature. What importance can have Christ to be one thing or another? Mucha.SI Christ was human, his sacrifice has value, but not more than the many other people who have suffered. If Christ was God, and defends the Church, humiliation and torment of the cross is not an example of suffering, his sacrifice is the central point in history. This Act also, justifies the salvation. This whole issue was at stake at Nicaea, and also it is in "The Da Vinci Code".The film is the battle between a secret sect, the Priory of Sion, which has a proof that Christ was human, and the most conservative branch of the Church, Opus Dei, who fight to death to preserve orthodoxy.The story of this discussion has allowed Dan Brown to do with record sales of all time with his novel. However Ron Howard is maybe not him to go so well the accounts when you see the box office. That brings me to the difference between seeking a reader that passes the pages of an avid book for a reply and seeking a viewer intrigued by a mystery: slightly different things.The film is faithful to the book for his disgrace. It begins to pose questions and advances at the expense of more questions and turns. But the role of the protagonists is not cinematic, is rather intellectual. It is not a film characters, but enigmas. A critic said that see "The Da Vinci Code" is so exciting as see your grandfather solving a Sudoku puzzle. The film does not work if the characters do not imply to the bottom; they have to play it all. The novel, on the other hand, functioned as a puzzle as an intrigue affecting the religion, to culture, to the reader. The problem is not that chemistry between Tatou and Hanks there is no, the problem is that none of his characters live the movie.</body>
</review>
