<review author="Berto" title="Sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good bet of science fiction, quite interesting and entertaining, that without being a great film fulfills its mission, and although to see it always left with the question of in that could have been converted into the hands of a different director, not disappoint to stalwarts of this kind of movies.</summary>
	<body>Danny Boyle is a fairly irregular director throughout his career has tested different genres and has had mixed luck both critics and audiences with his films. He started strong with Trainspotting more afternoon was followed by films like A different story, La Playa, that excessive video clip for showcasing DiCaprio that should not be considered a film and then the very interesting 28 days later, twist back to the mythical films of zombies in the 1980s, that my personally I liked a lot, and millions, atypical family history and also has good detail. After all this embarks on a movie of science fiction in which a hypothetical future Sun this extinguishing is. The land, plunged into an ice age decides to send a first spacecraft toward the Sun with a nuclear charge to see if they can return to reactivate it. After 7 years without news of the first ship, sent a second with another nuclear charge and their last hopes in order to revitalize it and avoiding the annihilation of the human species.This point of departure, so stark original serves Boyle to tell a quite sober and entertaining film and although it's a science fiction more than the style of Deep Impact film, contains certain elements that make you stand out from the film more current popcorn maker. There are some sorpresilla when the second ship crew are the first, which reminded me greatly horizon end, film also ships in deep space, but with a distinctly psychological horror. That's why that begins as a science film fiction, pure and simple, to then gradually go moving by fears of a single crew and carried behind the future of all mankind and to be found with many more problems than people had thought at the beginning. Obviously, if everything was perfect, the film would end the half an hour to start, so the problems do not take to arrive, flavouring with a little mystery associated with the first spacecraft launched seven years ago and that gradually becomes the leitmotif of the film, leaving a bit of the main crew mission side.The characters, to be a movie of his style, are quite worked well, and little by little will be making us insight into the motivations and fears of each one of them. Not removed are the typical archetypal characters, with the typical scientist dedicated to the mission, the hormonado handles to find the success of the mission above all things, or typical captain that manages to get along with the entire crew and get the best out of each one, but no this is an innovative film, not going to win any nomination for the Oscarsits mission is to entertain and more than meets its mission. Much of this is by the actors, pretty good in their roles, including Cillian Murphy, Chris Evans, actors on which rests the entire weight of the film.In short a good bet for science fiction, quite interesting and entertaining, that without being a great film fulfills its mission, and although to see it always left with the question of in that could have been converted into the hands of a different director, not disappoint to stalwarts of this kind of movies.</body>
</review>
