<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Tu la letra, yo la música" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film like this not should have been dubbed. Perhaps even should have been exported. I've seen in Spanish and it just works.</summary>
	<body>Hugh Grant plays a star of the pop fall in disgrace. The actor lacks little to put a face to that ineffable thing that Oscar Wilde wanted to catch in their sentences, the charm ("It is absurd to divide people into good and bad.") ("People are either charming or tedious.") Drew Barrimore makes dead woolly. Since the left dress faralai helpless aliens has specialized in the role of neurotic girl that is so easy to take care.I understand that we tired a bit pedantic commentator that recommends us to see the film in English, when what they want is not that we see it in English but we know that he knows English. But it is that a film like this not should have been dubbed. Perhaps even should have been exported. I've seen in Spanish and it just works. The singer and the regadora of plants have five days to compose a song, and nothing else in the world than a les. Things are little by little known, and every detail is adding in a small crimping to the lyrics of the song. What is between them has to do with its past, but also with this poem. For this reason, when they begin to launch the same in the Spanish version, the Viewer cannot otherwise shy away. And when Hugh Grant sings his song one can not be thrill with the verse: "I love you despised the fact, that you? ve killed all of my plants," because hardly has time to read in passing under the leg of the piano.I would like to explain me with this rodeo criticism, a little harsh I read everywhere. The film is not worse than other fun of Hugh Grant comedy "Big kid" or "Notting Hill" for example. The film is intended as a climax that the characters come after Polish verses. The viewer of a dubbed copy sees them reach that moment like a pair of automatons who must comply with the producer, and give a kiss to hastily before the fall of the iron curtain.</body>
</review>
