<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Sunshine" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film innovative, eccentric, irregular, masterly in its last two minutes and really surprising.</summary>
	<body>We have a film innovative, eccentric, irregular, masterly in its last two minutes and really surprising. Sunshine, directed by the always original Danny Boyle (Trainspotting, 28 days later, etc) is, above all, a kind of experiment, formulated with safety, curious, above all, perhaps, if we talk about its theme, not us may seem the height of originality. Yes, so far nobody (that I know) had directed a film from a trip to the Sun to make it explode and, thus, produce light for a humanity that is running out, but isn't that what is, so to speak, less innovative, but its plot structure, full of clichés and innovations at the same time, igualadamente. Although it can resemble incredibly, at certain moments, this masterpiece of Ridley Scott, all and this drawback, the film in question get get with it and ultimately prove spectacular.Think bold orally communicate, more poetic that commercial, more strange and minimalist which, for example, that of Scott film, thing that does not mean it, Sunshine, better than Alien. Am not going to go into comparisons, but did make it very clear that both films have several points in common, as for example some of the relations between the crew (here are nine and not seven, or eight?) or the transformation of one of them in something extremely unpleasant (here occurs at the end and at the other by principle. great Ian Holm!). As I said, the film of Boyle is something less commercial, although perhaps I'm wrong, because many scenes are really worked with computer and when the film opts towards the end, its simple and poetic aspect is burned by the very light of the Sun and becomes, suddenly, a horror film style more gore. Perhaps this is its main fault, the pass, no reason, one gender to another. The rest is, as I said, great.Let's start with his elaborate script, carried out by Alex Garland. Leaving band detail that I have just mentioned, the beginning of the footage is appalling and when it ends is when the work is more exciting, exhausting and intense (impressive frozen Syndey image). It has a clear, precise structure, a topical hair, perhaps, although it never presents considerable pace slippages or plot flaws that highlight. Perhaps it is not a great script, those that impact by the master are, by its perfection, but nor is it for those who do not say nothing, completely lacking personality. But personality here have Danny Boyle, the director of the film, Sunshine, which manipulates and move all the threads, which, unfortunately, is wrong in some cases, but who knows how to rectify some of the scenes showing us more beautiful ever views, such as the already mentioned located in Sydney, Cillian Murphy's viewing of very, very close, the light of the Sun or when Rose Byrne and latter maintain a delicate dialogue. I will not forget, either, the scene of the death of one of the main characters, which suffers from a "slight" damage to her leg. That Yes, sometimes the film loses quality, or rather originality, since special effects appear, and in abundance, which worsens, mainly, the acting showcasing.Another aspect very important film, totally remarkable, would be their interpretations. Say that Cillian Murphy is not so well (say OK, so of Oscar) as in breakfast on Pluto, but which however gets that credible and to some extent their interpretation is moving. His role is one of those who are alienated from the outside world and seeking a way out, a hope. Also note Rose Byrne, in the most exciting interpretation of all. It is as if say, the melancholy of the group. Then there are others that make more than good work, as Cliff Curtis (which will become the worst enemy of the Group), Michelle Yeoh (along with Gong Li, the Eastern actress more listed in the United States, and not so, worst actress) or Chris Evans (perhaps this the best role of her career, good, if we can say career).And not to forget me some spectacular special effects that help and at the same time prevent make the film look with regard to artistic quality and not a splendid picture and really good frames, except these "slightly" recuperated appearing at the end of the film, when it becomes an absurd adventure of terror. The music of Alwin Kuchler is also notable. As you can see, what stands out in Sunshine is its ability to tell the story, rather than the technical sections.A good film, able to satisfy both young people and adults and that, above all, not disappoint lovers of science fiction. That Yes, those who expect a sort of adventure in a spaceship without any moral background or social criticism, better that they move away, because the film from Danny Boyle is not appropriate, then. The film from Danny Boyle, in some way, is a contrast between the original and topical, being majority first thing.</body>
</review>
