<review author="Dragon negro" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We have the weaker of the saga film, Raimi, seeing it come that this would be his last delivery, has decided to cook us a plate with too many ingredients and seasoned in excess that one is you just indigestando.</summary>
	<body>Excessive, this was the word that could not stop repeating me while watching the new installment of the saga of trepamuros, excessive. And it is that Raimi, seeing it come that this would be his last installment of the saga, has decided to cook us a plate with too many ingredients and seasoned in excess to one just indigestando. The large number of plots and characters not allow to taste each one of them as it should be and everything just forming a potingue did not finish digesting very well.Loving conflicts between Peter Parker and Mary Jane just does not work, the evolution of the character of Harry Osborn is more than little credibility, the transformation of Peter Parker in a dark being is ridiculous and the man of sand and its involvement in the life of Parker almost better not talk because he is loaded the essence of the character and virtually all the saga. Somewhat better resolved this aversion of Eddie Brock to Parker, perhaps better conducted plot of all the more believable.One of the weaknesses of the film lies in the humorous part which so well had managed to take the previous installments, these small touches of humor that this time are too child, these dances on the street and the bar scene are Palm. Although the opening scene of j. j. Jameson this pretty well and the emergence of the great Bruce Campbell is one of the best moments of the film. Something that has failed me here is also the music, for example when Peter and Harry fight sounds like a horrible music that does not fit at all with the scene.Surely tell that the spectacular nature of this very successful film, but you want to tell you, found me much better resolved and worked against Octopus fights than any of these, which are solved too quickly, the camera moves at such speed that barely enough time to see much and end up becoming somewhat repetitive, we return to the excessivemany fights but as a whole they know little and are wanting to taste with a little more detail the scenes against the man of sand or poison. And return again to repeat the same pattern of the previous films already, turning again to Mary Jane in victim of the villains and has again be saved already bored and he tired, one expected something more original this time, besides being the worse to straighten the situation of the three.The question I am asking me then is because no film has split in two, each with a different villain and leading the new Green Goblin during these changing and developing everything a little better and not so hasty way, the two way shot simultaneously, gave what they want us to be here for this and more, because it not do then well and not this way that surely not settle many.The result is that we we have the film weaker of the saga, which has more concessions with regard to the merchantability, that the excess of characters is a burden that is not resolved well because it does not give for more. Dress him seen more than one because you will not see so bad that for a future delivery, that is sure that it will, I opted for a different creative team and with a new character's vision, that perhaps for better and perhaps worse, at this point would be appreciated.</body>
</review>
