<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One is going to see the most expensive movie in the history of the cinema and he dislikes to meet with a surfeit of French Existentialism poorly digested and passed through the Blender of the Disney style. I do not know whether to Raimi &amp; Co. It has risen them arácnida fever at the head, but these ravings of Kierkegaard for children are pretentious, stupid and nonsense.</summary>
	<body>What boredom: Spiderman 3 a dramatic thing. Children yawned between plúmbeas scenes of conversations of adults and elders desesperaban before the childishness of the characters. From time to time came the action, but it was like awakening to the TV and see some goal with sopor loose, light years from the emotions. So disappointing has been "Spiderman 3".I have already said on other occasions that I love the direct, forceful and passionate style of Inigo Domínguez, correspondent in Italy Ideal. Actually, wanted to Inigo: bread, bread and Spiderman, boredom. In a few petados theaters as ever, with LF tails that sold out the taquillaje to see Spider-man, at the end of the film, the most widespread comment was: "Vin compae longest movie". And immediately, talks trufaran a damn Word when speaking of a film, especially when it involves pure entertainment: boredom.Because who cares about the metafísico-sentimentales sorrows of Spider-man? One thing is the Lair by the dark side of Batman, his fears and fears; and quite another this babbling arácnida telenovela: you want-no te quiero; I envy you - I admire; you understand-you-no step are when you need; I love - I hate you. By God! That already have to Diego de la Vega and india for clamoring Yumalai.El case is that "Spiderman 3" lasts two hours and media that seem to five, makes you remove you in the armchair, looking at the clock continuously, consult the phone looking for an SMS that you lift it out of the tedium and of having flight attendants in the room, wanting to give ask a pillow and some earplugs and take a NAP until leaving the titles of credit.Okay, okay. I'm going through. I have exaggerated somewhat. Nor is it you feel irrepressible desire to open up veins or something. It must be recognized that the special effects are milk, which Spider-man flies beautifully, black suit mola mazo and, above all, the Sandman is amazing. Vale.Pero one is going to see the most expensive movie in the history of the cinema and he dislikes to meet with a surfeit of French Existentialism poorly digested and passed through the Blender of the Disney style. I do not know whether to Raimi &amp; Co. It has risen them arácnida fever at the head, but these ravings of Kierkegaard for children are pretentious, stupid and nonsense.With good, complex and stimulating was the last "Batman", often blunder have led us to this "Spiderman" complacent, ombligista and jamaipanese. To see if the action film directors/producers learn to make films with message, committed and such and such is not necessary to bore up to the sheep, with endless discursitos loaded with morals. So now I have the Bucay and Coelho's turn.</body>
</review>
