<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="¿Quién dice que es fácil?" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Who says that it is easy? It is another resounding example of funny comedy that could become, but who stays in a sad sentimental comedy funny at times.</summary>
	<body>There are many things that give life to salt and pepper that needed, and one of those elements is the irony that sometimes spends the destination. Although sometimes it seems more than irony, pure and true bad milk. When you need to pass one thing, convert the other, and sometimes, when you need to pass the other, passes one. All this small philosophical gibberish is beside the point of irony that Spanish films succeed in Argentina and here pass more punishable than glory (not, isn't a nod to Víctor García León), and to the Argentine films pass them exactly opposite, who succeed in Spain and their country pass with indifference.After the great success of No Sos Vos, Soy Yo, reaches the Spanish charts the new work of its Director, Juan Taratuto. Who said it was easy? It's an unconventional romantic comedy, whose protagonists are Aldo (Diego Peretti), an insecure and obsessive man, and Andrea (Carolina Peleritti), a graphical one reporter who has traveled around the world, pregnant without knowing who is the father. The first half of the film has the best qualities of a romantic comedy, is fun, enjoyable, and possesses a great pace; However, the second half has all the defects of the romantic comedies, leaves humor aside to focus on the sentimental level, get the usual conflicts, and finally becomes slow and heavy. Today, there are very few comedies from beginning to end intending unique and healthy to laugh to the Viewer, that most just hiding intentions moralistic or sentimentaloides. For its part, Diego Peretti (luckily has not known it Quevedo, because if not laugh of the "there is a man in a nose glued") does a good job interpretive, more content and less histrionic than in previous works. Carolina Peleritti also offers a good job, and surely finally ends with the former model stuck to actress sambenito.Anyway, who says that is easy? It is another resounding example of funny comedy that could become, but who stays in a sad sentimental comedy funny at times.</body>
</review>
