<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The 3rd sequel of this series Marvel is a real disappointment. There is no where take it.</summary>
	<body>Good friends we are facing a hodgepodge of incomparable stature. The 3rd sequel of this series Marvel is a real disappointment. There is no where take it.First of all the writers have emphasised, what is the comic itself is what they have gone through the ass and have remodeled the history as it has given the win and above bad, without imagination and fabulously pathetic moments.When working with a production of that caliber, with these budgets lunatics and above all with a solid idea and hook of base since that is adapting a comic book, it is unforgivable that the end result provokes laughter. Of course that it is by not mourn, laugh because I assure you that if it is to laugh, then id to see because you will not lose your time. On the other hand if you expect to see something "as a minimum" at the height of the previous Spider-man, I advise you what you to think twice.All this disaster involving Spiderman3, would like to highlight the following unforgettable moments:-time boy Genial: is the beginning of the film, a real horror, seems a Latin soap opera of series Z-time Chepa Wonderful:pero let's see, what happens to my beloved Kristen?, is desmejoradísima, with an extreme thinness, goodbye to the brand-new Mª Jane of the previous films. Not be who will be told that it is beautiful, because it is horrible, anyone could give him a pucherito?. Fuck on top of more than 45 people at least were on the set of filming when she sings "Wonderful", pussy and recoño there was nobody able to yell "Kristen my life, get straight to the chepa is horrible". Fuck. someone tell that it put straight, is in the pass of equal Madrid press, lost chepuda and as a noodle, with wonderful, not the entiendo.esperemos to go back to his time dorée-time flag American "because I'm worth it": bone that above, I have to endure with the American imperative, seeing the superhero in a moment of maximum glory by art of magic is a U.S. flag. There by God, I laughed, absolutely pathetic. A nationalist claim unnecessary.-time I get the orquilla: nobody has given account, that when Parker grandmother is giving the engagement ring to his grandson, he begins to leave a huge orquilla of the bow, jajajaja, momentazo gentlemen, click Pause and laugh non-stop. To where it looked the script at that time?.-Time moral: and if there was no little, above, over, fuck, rising me sugar reminded at the time final pelt us with the patriotic moral idealist. ANDA, Anda that go the pedo.meteos writers la moraleja where more pleasure you for-now I like the pepper: I forgot this, is very good. When James Franco (this man has me in love with as a quinceañera, can not with him, is the most) and Kristen Chepa are in the kitchen and he tells her "You like peppers," as saying "that you mmm same". Ay! James control you son that you are clearly very sexual, I then had told him: "sisi with rubber or without rubber?."Ultimately all a horror show.</body>
</review>
