<review author="Victor Omar" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Underestimate the intelligence of the public is the worst sin of the film</summary>
	<body>Over the years we have been devoting full time to the world of cinema, we have learned many unwritten rules. One of them has to do with the tapes that have caused much excitement before reaching Billboard. If that film in question, the time of the premiere, the Distributor chooses to hide it in the press, it is almost certain that they do that the media do not have opportunity to speak ill of her. Reasons: the long-awaited film in the end is not at all good, but if the public does not know, attendance at cinemas will not be diminished.And unfortunately this premise is fulfilled in "code Da Vinci". Too solemn, too cold, too politically correct. Much ado about nothing about a too conventional thriller. "Code Da Vinci" is in good measure, with the exception of its final part, a sort of almost literal figurative representation of the book that inspired him. As if it were a graphical version of the text, which includes literal transcriptions of some dialogue or key expressions and refers strictly to the description of actions, in the recurring flashbacks and adjusted description of his characters, perhaps visible except for the Manager banking André Vernet.Howard leverages the privilege to have been able to shoot the opening sequence in Louvre himself to handle from the go with strong pulse and sobrado tanning craft Narrator the suggestive atmosphere of intrigue that seems to accentuate it while more grows the hieroglyph - tired known by the disclosure that claimed the book - raised before the noses of the expert simbologista Robert Langdon (Tom Hanks) and the young full of French police Sophie Neveu (Audrey Tautou): the death of the curator of the Louvre - and grandfather of the girl old man revives a secret deployed around the work of Leonardo da Vinci and which might call into question the foundations of Christianity and the power of the Iglesia.Es no doubt that, if the Brown book had not existed, no Hollywood studio would have put money to convert in film so thick script built almost exclusively on explanations and (somewhat) fanciful speculations about symbols, codes, secret cults, history of religion and messages disguised as art, presumed by the unique appeal of putting into question the fundamental principles of Christianity.Conspiracy theories lose value and credibility for the manner in which they are presented.The explanation that makes the last supper, the box of Da Vinci, Sir Teabing (Ian McKellen) is suitable for minds trained by Barney the dinosaur. Underestimate the intelligence of the public is the worst sin of the film. History, thus moving through solving puzzles, detection of codes and the display of historical knowledge but not the construction of characters, designed more with idiosyncrasies that personalities of flesh and blood.A generous director of actors, Howard is usually not able here to provide an identity to its partner lead, which remains false, pale, rigid and deadpan. In a movie so full of hot air, there is no room for that, or emotion or style. Film is the most impersonal of Ron Howard, a filmmaker with ex officio but not talented, which although it has sent some skids career always was you could trust a couple of hours with total confidence. "No longer.""Code Da Vinci" (version film and book) is a sign of the eternal conflict between historians and novelists. If the novel or the film accurately reflect reality, then is her accused of not being a novel because it contains no fiction. And sometimes plagiarism, because logically the novelist has to be based on the study of historical sources. "And if it disfigures the facts in fiction, then charged that he is not saying the truth, he distorted what happened.""Code Da Vinci" is not intended to be history, history is not, and therefore may ficcionar the facts, inventing a new reality, although some facts are taken from history. What is true and what is fiction a novel is a privilege of the novelist. If you write a pasted argument of historical reality, perhaps would be rather a chronicle. And yet, in the Chronicles there is also a large part of imagination by who writes.Regardless of everything, it is ridiculous that in 21st century, hierarchs of various Christian doctrines as the Catholic Church and Governments such as the Philippines, Thailand or the India forbid the display of the Ribbon, for things while they are not entirely true, somehow threatening to think people, which would lead to that also reach sooner or later question your realitywhich is very dangerous for those who wish to have the masses under control.</body>
</review>
