<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Those who believed that after the House of flying daggers, we weren't going to enjoy an orgy plastic and an explosion of similar senses were wrong.</summary>
	<body>While history may be less attractive than the narrated in his previous titles, Zhang Yimou gives an aura of distinction Supreme to his, forgive the term, folletín set in the china of the Tang dynasty, which is like our middle ages but with much more glamour and brightness, to the less seen by historians adecentan and makeup the truthful story in its film adaptation.If it has been pejorative novelistic reference read, because here is a strong supporter of a filmmaker that has more than two decades the gap. Remove the maximum performance to films that are more than a simple deployment of well managed media and experiments, and proof of this is the delight that see the curse. on the big screen despite its weak points more distressed that on other occasions.Far is already the intimate tone of their first productions or the last, the way home, before its 'wuxia' stage, initiated by Hero. Although this is not entirely true, because if we remove the packaging, i.e., great choreography, slowed struggles, plastic binge, is that, the history. Behind all epic, the manifestation of power and ostentation, there are feelings which are responsible of embodying the interpreters that give life to the indulgent little emperor and the strange character linking this story with the great tragedies of the Shakespeare Theatre, in the same way as the backdrop of the House. It reminded the world of thieves that steal from the rich to help the poor.Honourable is the reunion of the exceptional Gong Li with the film of his country from the hands of its discoverer. The maturity and the imprint make you worthy of this character of flashy than not would have been able to take advantage, by age and his physical, the also Muse of Yimou, Zhang Ziyi. Li moves with ease by Palace but, and this is more inherent to the plot that the characters, sees as his soul and his heart are lost among so much magnificence, which also affects the rate of the tape.Despite this final point, Zhang Yimou has already shown that he is a master of the cinema, able to satisfy his creative ego and leave others speechless. Now, after this superb and elegant epic parentheses, should rethink return to the crossroads and take the other abandoned road, that if not the weed that the hidden will prevent you from following him.</body>
</review>
