<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Tuya Siempre" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The director of in arms of mature women becomes Flora Martínez one of its tourist cicerones: delving into the lower depths of the city and see what does not appear in travel guides.</summary>
	<body>If there is a classification of film by colors, this film would have a greyish tone, intense Mallard and very close to the black brown tones. Chromatic curiosities to one side, yours is always an example of film noir whose employers have been reviewed by an interesting filmmaker by bold, a priori.Correct thriller with a right and social conscience is the portrait of this another Barcelona, away from the stately neighborhoods, tourist and safe from the modernist air centers and modernilla whirlwind. The scenario where there are two outcasts (played by Martinez and Ruben Ochandiano) serves as a meeting point for beings that hold dangerous balance, always with the threat of falling into the void.Well outlined the players, remained to define (s) plot (s) and it is here where weakens this tape, which suffers the excesses of a somewhat unbalanced pace and the idea of puzzle in the Assembly. This new vision of the 'other side', portrayed through an accurate setting, a prominent musical support and a very correct picture of teacher José Luis Alcaine is still very interesting. Where also confirms Lombardero is in the direction of actors: Nancho Novo takes two of two very soon, because we don't forget Pudor.Es one of these unfortunate beings that populate these islands dominated by drug dealers, prostitutes, gangsters of little rides but able to do much damage and criminals with dreams. There is the need to distinguish between good and bad: all have reason to be there and do what they do. Without wishing to influence their judgement and despite the fact that these pieces of non-life are left to see, Manuel Lombardero could have driving the tooth with more force. But maybe, that of not doing too much blood.</body>
</review>
