<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The sacrifice is here presented as a form of suicide. We don't talk history, nor the characters, but the director to venture into a film that anything upstream.</summary>
	<body>There are surreal films that have where grab them. This visual poem is that, an elegy, a sort of swan song, so its leaders expect an overwork on our part.Imagine a box that contains metaphors, related philosophical and cultural memories, sensations, errors, images of great beauty, cuts, tears. So is this movie, that fascinate, catches our attention, albeit relying on our waiting to see what route will continue. Perhaps to strengthen this linkage, its argument say that love gives strength for everything, that it is an act of faith, dedication and selflessness and, as such, it has also its victims.After deploying the ideas, here the victim may be public. We are spectators accustomed to a cinematic prose with their spelling and grammatical rules, with their meanings and their interpretations. We we have educated in a 'normal' cinema, with a specific narrative and therefore before anything current proposals, we tend to show us reluctant.The close-ups of Rachel Weisz, the hard background of the relationship between his character and played by Hugh Jackman, plastic's good intentions and rhetoric employed and in some respects sweetened counteracting with predictable of a narrative that not being atypical is more seductive and sins of excessive plastic pedantry. The script, far from surprising, stands out for its simplicity, downside that looking at it favourably, just become curious virtue to emphasize the aesthetic imprint.I would like to make it clear that the third tape from Darren Aronofsky (after Pi and Requiem) by a dream led to me, me picó. They are verbs that I use when I do not know if something convinced me or not: is like watching an abstract painting in a museum. The formal courage is almost always at odds with our own liking, supported on the cultural heritage seized. Therefore it is constructive to remain not airtight to different bets that extracted the most critical side of us.</body>
</review>
