<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Dios o demonio (I love Miami)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film about the life of Fidel Castro in Miami? What laziness! It was the first thing I thought, although sometimes, even of the most absurd draws interesting conclusions.</summary>
	<body>Castro is sick. That is what they say from their Government in Havana. Indeed that it has disappeared and that is the news that have been known to earn time to prepare for the transition to another representative. On this premise, which could well be true, reached approaches, these Yes, far removed from reality.Avowed my initial reluctance I must tell you that it was not for both. That her endured and not only that, that also, at times, I entretuve, although without reaching become an adherent to the proposal. Much of it lies with situations surreal, impossible to reproduce if not with the help of a good actor, which squeezed a crazy script and gives courage, because this have the drama of the balseros from the most illustrious of them have crumbs.Juan Luis Galiardo I think is one of the great live performers, but I sometimes too intoxicated to be confused person with character. Cadiz has my sympathy, but this is not enough because sometimes I do not see anything on the screen than him (despite his good characterization), so appreciated the sway of the plots, that dot the comic story to other characters, as interpreted by the child, a methodical actor already was in the fiction of Antonio Banderas and Catherine Zeta-Jones in the second installment of the adventures of the Zorro.Deof the nod to the supposed news, it going to the movies with a social conscience. The new Fidel aventurilla helps us to know other Cubas and other Cubans forced (envelope) live off the island. It is here where give rein to our concern at the prospect of seeing what has generated the Castro regime outside its boundaries.It is true that there is a histrionic and pamplinoso veil that blurs the reality, but also the political debate may arise from the irony and farce. Credibility is another matter to leave them to you. A note in conclusion: I had opportunity to see her in the Festival de Málaga, free; This leads me to believe objectively using the rule of 6 euros per entry so, certainly, reconsidered me this review.</body>
</review>
