<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Mi hijo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Public, critics and jury festivalero often go through different paths. Irrefutable proof of this is found in the winning the Golden shell at San Sebastian 2006 tape.</summary>
	<body>By the time that has been slow to see the light, it feels that distributors were afraid to teach us this claustrophobic and bitter story about the sense of maternal possession. Without going into plot reiterations, sanity has prevailed and in the end has come to our screens with little hype that Yes, this funny portrait of despair and selfishness, fed by the excess of authority, for which his main actress won also the silver shell at the San Sebastian festival.A mother's love can be unbearable for the suffering. Behind this claim there is no second that worth, but a sentence that feeds the essence of a short but intense and somewhat predictable feature film about the maternal Authority carried to extremes. Psychological violence is less tangible than Physics: no bruises, no visible damage to the naked eye, but who endures carries with it their traumatizing brands of for life. From this premise, Martial Fougeron describes a myriad of sour situations outlined in dry and austere but with realization way and, at times, excessive point of reiteration that could have led to his downfall.But there she was to sustain this descent to the abyss: few actresses convince me both as a Frenchwoman Nathalie Baye. I have not ignored any title starring her since I met her flirting in bed with Sergi López and verborréica lost in A private relationship. In this decade? she does in the gap much longer - I've seen as Matthieu, Venus, beauty salon, the flower of evil? more or less interesting films, jumbles and wonders, but all with one common denominator: which was François Truffaut Muse always was splendid. The same is true here, where in addition to being the main attraction, acts as a Savior of a tape that could well have been mitigated and neither had suffered a great deal.</body>
</review>
