<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Respectable Office of science fiction with more claims that substance. This is this compendium of horror, metaphysical speculation and heroic survivors covered by a precious gift paper.</summary>
	<body>If so we developed, i.e., if we remove the excellent technical invoice, we have a paquete-bomba of reflections can explode at the time that the ideology is diluted by the application of the standards of the thriller.Rather than keep reading him I have to confess that Danny Boyle has my sympathy: seems to me an atypical and thanks to that type, a filmmaker who does disgusted to nothing: it recreates in a fable with children with Angel and obsessed with the Saints (million) that it decimated the British population (28 days later) and us into social subworlds with Trainspotting. He has talent and pretensions of greatness in equal parts, a blend that balances the balance in this curious puzzle, strange within the genre are going-to-save-the-world, so interesting and uneven with regard to strictly narrative, and it is here where weakens the thing.Its excellent ability to telling stories led him to narrate the Chronicle of the last days of the life on Earth from a point of view more realistic, unlike the triumphalism which we are accustomed of Hollywood. That does not mean that the film is positive, just the opposite: the Sun dies and there is no trap or cardboard. Foreseeable of your argument is diluted as soon as they take runout the pace and tension that we submit, supported? it must be said, in certain episodes more typical of a sort of titles framed in terror tacky and cheap catastrophism.Sunshine is what you would get if we substantiate 2001: an Odyssey in space and Solaris (both in plot issues such as formal), Armageddon and the Wes Craven factory titles. It shows the influence of classics like the above first and the jewel of the space horror, Alien, the eighth passenger. Initial approaches are very attractive, but lose consistency at the time that advances the footage and is carried away by the sensationalism of most commercial productions.Still worth it, by similes - Icarus is the name of his ship - and the psychological background of characters very well interpreted by devoted but little recognizable actors by the spectator: Cillian Murphy, seen drag in breakfast on Pluto and hero force in the epidemic 28 days later, Michelle Yeoh (Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon, memoirs of a geisha)Chris Evans (the human torch in the fantastic four) and Cliff Curtis (the source of life, River Queen), among others.Let us spread by physical claustrophobia and spiritual distress of these beings destined to a sad end for the good continuation of our life. His experience is illustrated with a cocktail of special effects, picture of high quality plastic and impeccable sound? if so be that we arrived in space abroad--drawn up in what had to be a gruelling stage of post-production. With their errors, Sunshine suggests a priori to entertain then, which is not little.</body>
</review>
