<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="River Queen" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The director of the curious beyond the dreams of experiences, without much success, in this exotic drama linking warlike peoples who seek to impose on others with interior of any searches.</summary>
	<body>If Australia is far indeed that its history find us something more known for the film than its neighbour New Zealand, although not much more. Vincent Ward, who is originally from the country become Tolkien's Middle Earth, by Peter Jackson tries to put his two cents to the cause making a historical, not very contextualized approach the truth, to the colonial past of these islands.Surely the actress Samantha Morton conquered them in code 46, of futuristic Court, and the tremendous in America, which gave life to an Irish emigrated with his family to United States. Here back century and a half to arrive, also as a foreign, to a strange land will wake up suddenly because of colonialism. Do do do surrounded by other prestigious performers such as Cliff Curtis? to which we see in Sunshine-Stephen Rea? that is lavished here shortly - and Kiefer Sutherland? few know die like him-, succumbs to the claims made by a director who is descompensa the play.This journey upriver is curious and we start from an idea: is irregular in terms of its story, equidistant between the tedium and the frenetic pace, i.e. wrong level. Sometimes catch us the action, draws us what is narrated, and almost of instantly, we evadimos because of an abuse of the voiceover and locations of unsurpassed beauty. They will think I am exaggerating, but sometimes I would mind to the Piano and he believed he saw Holly Hunter moving with difficulty with her dress between the weeds and mud but detonations were calling me back to the scene of a woman fight (and partly fraticida) between the Army (English and Maori aboriginal tribes.The idea of search dominates all the footage: find the true identity, persecuting those who took away you the life, search for a better than the stormy present. While this mix of desires to meet may be interesting, the rhythm to which the director submitted to us arrives at touching the extreme boredom, not to mention the lack of depth profiles of certain key characters in the story.Without entering in repeatable turns and little credible history of love to be built with just data, River Queen, neocelandesa fate of the African Queen, is only right to put a different historical episode in his sights, but suspended to not give it plot fortitude and dress with beautiful and exotic landscapes and childish thoughts about beings condemned to live divided between two cultures.</body>
</review>
