<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="La vida en rosa" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Away from the biography to the use, convinced by the 'real' profile which outlined about the artist Edith Piaf, whose songs became anthems for different generations.</summary>
	<body>The problem of approaching a myth is that many of their fans? although this would not be the correct term - can return against you. That was the risk that ran Olivier Dahan with this portrait of a sacred legend for our neighbours to the North. How can win so difficult to penetrate audiences? The answer is simple: with an actress that transform tearing the skin and looking for from within the personality of a character which have references to bore. It has done so Marion Piaf, forgiveness, Cotillard, unrecognizable in its transformation: scratching found the actress took justice into their own hands in long courtship Sunday and entered the universe of Tim Burton with Big Fish.Si a song evokes a State of mind, a film must do the same: provoke emotions and stir the sleeping feelings. What was considered responsible for this audiovisual biography supported in scars and triumphs biased to consciousness in order to serve as a vehicle to a time past and recreated not only by the fragrances decorators, but also by sharing Excel where Gerard Depardieu and Emmanuelle Seigner.Igual that occurs when one reads a book and recreates it in his minda character of legend comes to life in our minds after having received countless information impacts. In this way, La Vie en Rose (the film, not the song) is an idealization of a star from a compilation of cuts in press, hearings of his discography, official biographies and personal perceptions? these are the greater part of the cake.Popular fundamentalism and destructive minds of some critics can condition the future of this laudable work, similar to the of the recent Lola, the film, with a glorious Gala Évora. After this Iberian chauvinist comment? to make parallels between two artists, two myths — we can only emphasize that their footage which, though compensated by an excellent soundtrack, partly undermines the capacity of impact that holds this portrait of La Môme since their first frame, which initiates a passionate and exciting life may seem excessive.</body>
</review>
