<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Moscow Zero" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entertainment is often incompatible with the cinematic perfection. It is what is happening with this new notch in the race of moon, filmmaker so atypical as criticized.</summary>
	<body>Dispar. This is the work of María Lidón, best known in the industry for his space nickname which gives idea of orbits in other parts. His gaze daring cinema today makes him worthy of praise and ridicule.Do the latter we will arrive soon, only allow me to recall the Moon filmography: began with castaways, an adventure on Mars incredible and worse told to follow later with Yo, puta, where combined with Sham documentary tone, with Daryl Hannah and Denise Richards.¿De where gets funding for their projects? What are your contacts in the scene? They must be interesting to count performers renowned as Val Kilmer and others listed by their worth, case of Joaquim de Almeida, which here does show her. That get so much money, the question that arises is why its oversights in the script and inconsistent interpretations of their actores-estrella, that border the pathos.The bowels of Moscow can generate one and dozens of worthy of reaching the film stories is something that does not take us suddenly. Why not get catch this descent to hell taking as input the Muscovite metropolitan transport? The dark, claustrophobic atmosphere spreads of a formal apathy resulting in repetitive levels, recurring music and a rough script that baby of two references already classics: the spine of the devil, by Guillermo del Toro, and the resounding 7337 film, about a group of children to 'hide' in a school during the Spanish civil war and. Up there we can count.Giving him the benefit of the doubt even? can be that Moon will not see many productions Spanish-, Moscow zero must trace the pre-críticas which usually generate this Director. It costs much to believe us that the depths of Moscow are controlled by urban tribes that appear and disappear by magic and attend the delusions of a kind obsessed with legends dating back to narrated 1920.Mal perplexed, this tale is much more acrid, if it is garnished with absurd winks: a priest kissing with a peculiar Guide to the underworld, the eternal struggle between the living and the dead by one place in the world (live, clear) and fast camera movements following stelae and shadows, the same as all bad horror film.By the way, directors friends of cinema, some of the best stories of the genus occur in full light of day, the case of who can kill a child? Hence there is no darkness that camufle the imperfections.</body>
</review>
