<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Pudor" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without kind wink and with great courage, the brothers Tristan and David Ulloa made their debut in the direction with an interesting intimate look at the tumultuous relationship between castaways of the same family.</summary>
	<body>With honesty and modesty come into the stronghold of emotional decay and bad odor. Forgive me this play on words with meanings of the term that gives title to the tape, but is that it summarizes rightly the expedition carried out these debutantes? if forget the short cycle - the territory of intimate and individual.They say that actors that are passed to the address have a special optics, a different way of tackling a project. Although many risk with an own story (Laura Mañá and sex) by compassion; Federico Luppi and steps; Carlos Iglesias and Un Franco, 14 pesetas) others are supported by outside texts that endorse. It is the case of Tristán Ulloa that taps into the novel by Santiago Roncangliolo and the technical expertise of his brother David to lift the variegated and claustrophobic microuniverso of Pudor.La camera becomes our peephole to pry on the Habitat of some lost beings naked before our eyes. In the transition from paper to screen not fleeing of the drama, but also fall into the tedium of those who rejoice in the misfortunes of others, digging into wounds. Do (common) sense and sensibility (Special), in a way nothing subtle but not bleeding too much, giving glimpses of hope.Between the clouds sneaks some ray of sunshine along with simile, we open the umbrella and we took refuge under the shower of movies on the family, that object of research which have experienced so many filmmakers: Ettore Scola (family), Sam Mendes (American beauty), Ang Lee (the ice storm). They seem to inspire the Ulloa brothers to get a side of voyeur combined with a performance supported on the pillars of the suspense and lightweight surrealism separating them from the more typical costumbrismo.As the naturalist who observes the beasts, we are approaching a wounded family on which flutter vultures waiting for one fail. Elvira Mínguez, Nancho Novo and the young Natalia Rodriguez are backed by a well-chosen cast: Celso Bugallo, Joaquin Climent and Nuria González. And turning to the pair of responsible, one runs while the other performs, why is as well the direction of actors not found errors in photography, music and the Assembly. In other words, the perfect tandem that we hope more movies.We reserve a final point and they are devoted to the stage: Gijón. It's a necessary flight of the foci of shooting usual, Madrid and Barcelona. Beings who, despite living together, are alone and are airtight roam its streets. Fable or reality?</body>
</review>
