<review author="Javier Moreno" title="Hard candy" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>David Slade has composed one of the best thrillers of all time, able to provoke tachycardia to sensitive people or with heart problems</summary>
	<body>That complicated speak from Hard Candy!, after seeing the film, I do not know if the Spanish title is a subtle irony about what awaits us in the next 100 minutes of footage, because Hard Candy is a caramel very difficult to digest, very difficult and distressing.Pederasty is a very complicated issue deal with film, very complicated because the simple act is already scary thinking.The film begins with a conversation in a chat between Hayley, a teenager of 14 years and Jeff, a 32 man who hides a dark secret. A conversation laden with a tremendous sexual chemistry who never had to have doubled as well indicates my good friend Alazne cinefila. They decide to stay and from the first moment laying down a few roles, Jeff is a Wolf, a sexual predator, a pederast in power, and Hayley a innocent girl, a kind of little Red Riding Hood to the mouth of the Wolf. Jeff her engatusa and her takes her home, Hayley is left to do, and even begins to prepare a few cocktails and alcohol to pave the way for the leon. What you do not know the lion, is that under the small lamb hides a real Wolf. Hayley drug to Jeff, and in a tense plot twist, the roles are exchanged, the pederast is the victim, and she is the executioner who seeks vengeance.And it is here where begins the real film. A tense thriller, psychological, that without blood, without sex, without Visual effects, only with the interpretation of the two actors, make Hard Candy in a movie perverse, oppressive, uncomfortable and difficult digestion. We're talking probably about one of the movies most unhealthy arrived from Hollywood. The game that the young Ellen Page submits to the child molester is distressing, as says Alazne new online film from Haneke, impossible to keep quiet five minutes in the armchair.What most stands out of the film, in addition to a solid script seamless and that time of bucólicamente disturbing environment, is without a doubt the lead actress: Ellen Page. Her performance as sweet girl turned into a psychopath is not great, it is ANTOLOGICA. She alone is capable of making the film, she alone in each of levels overshadows the rest of the footage, literally eats actor, mixing malevolence and macabre humour that causes nervous laughter in the cinema. Ellen Page is the movie Hard Candy, she is in a superb debut actress presents his letters to be called to become a major film, and is only 19 years old, it is the best debut that server has been in a movie in years.I do not follow destripandola, the end is simply shocking. David Slade has composed one of the best thrillers of all time, able to provoke tachycardia to sensitive people or with heart problems. Refrain squeamish, Hard Candy is not poisoned, but sweet candy that you eat the entrails to such an extent that halfway through movie do not know where put in the film. An authentic jewel.</body>
</review>
