<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Spiderman 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Accompanied by popcorn fun and any refreshing drink what more you can ask?</summary>
	<body>Sam Raimi spoke in the presentation tape that this third installment of adventures of man spider would be "More" in all aspects, most villains, more history, more action, more screen presence of Peter Parker, more brides for Spidey, more headaches for the same, and much more budget (today the most expensive Hollywood sector), and somehow not us has defraduado to all those fans of the trepamuros, which we have almost grown seeing playing Peter Parker, as Spider-man, stories like the black suit (black Spider-man was called in my time), poison, one of the favorite villains of the undersigned, or always bland man of sand ("Sandman" in the comic), it has been a pleasure to meet with them in the armchair of the filmthe film though with a quite excessive duration at any time one realizes that you seated nearly 2 and a half hours, believe me that for an ass of bad seat like this, also a difficult challenge overcome, being so long sitting. Tobey Mcguire, reconciles with the character that has made him world famous, giving Spider-man a completely unknown dimension, much more dark, thuggish and bastard of what we had used in previous tapes, is true in comics, usually quite "vacilón" with opponents, which here is not the case; on the other hand, and looking again cast protagonist we find ourselves again with Kirsten Dunst as platonic love, with less elevation of screen than in the previous films, and much more discreetly dressed in the first tapes (I believe I took less that pink dress of the first film) James Franco, now as the Green Goblin 2nd that, want to tell you, to my reminded me a skier of snowboarding, rather than even villain of the comic, by Thomas Haden Church, we have the man of sand, bland, and adds little to the character, and where the only delight of the screen is in the sensational CGI effects that make him therein, sand pure and simple; Topher Grace is poison, I like most of the comic, it neither chicha nor another; He didn't forget about Bryce Dallas Howard that already I fell in love with in "The bosqué", I idolatré in "The girl in the water" Shyamalan and now as Gwen Stacy has re-entered a forced walk in the Olympus of my goddesses on screen, I do not know why but her blue eyes and such as Candida and fragile beauty dazzles me. I can not forget 2 important faces in the Spider-man saga, by a part of Stan Lee, once again dares with a cameo appearance by another Bruce Campbell's and is the ineffable actor of the saga of "Infernal possession" is present in all the tapes of the man spider. Sam Raimi composed a superhero to use tape, fraught with action, that does not go down of pace at any time (in almost 140 minutes of footage not stop things happen), and one is first to the Goblin then before the man of sand and finally waiting to poison Spider-man them of "candir" much better, I bet it will be one of the taquillazos of the year 2007 and will come back in a couple of years back to the cinema with a 4th delivery. Accompanied by popcorn fun and any refreshing drink what more you can ask?</body>
</review>
