<review author="Jose Contreras" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The message is an ode to conformism and frustration, a hymn to the contempt of the rebellion, and the individual. The film, in short, is not more than a defence of the submission against the power, worse, against any power.</summary>
	<body>The Empress desperately weaves flowers of Chrysanthemum. The Chrysanthemum is a symbol of the rebellion. The soldiers of the Emperor wear all the same spotless red, the adversaries are golden, moving in unison in a dance and fill the immense courtyard of the forbidden city. Yimou film is littered with symbols, and I think this is the first time that scored it as a default. The idea of a plague defines the aesthetics of this Yimou, abuse of the colors of the myths of the armies. Each element is there to crush the viewer with the excess.It runs the 10th century c.e. in the Court of the Chinese imperial family. The Empress has to hurry the medicine to the bottom. The Emperor puts his honor at stake in enforcement of rules down to the last detail. The Viewer does not take to discover that the Empress is being poisoned. Three children have to choose between his ambition, his love for his mother, not always convinced, and blind obedience to a wicked father.The approach of Yimou bothers me deeply, and is not the first time. Behind the sumptuous sets until the Vertigo of the costumes Carnival of the indecent pageantry of the pneumatic courtesans of the warlike choreography of the macedonia of Greek myths and Venezuelan clamoring, Oedipus and a restored Macbeth, Palace intrigue and paternal tyranny, there is a monstrous message behind the veils. The message is suitable, only for viewers alienated, able to make pants for five euros and grow economically to eleven per cent per annum without making a Holy strike. The message is an ode to conformism and frustration, a hymn to the contempt of the rebellion, and the individual. The film, in short, is not more than a defence of the submission against the power, worse, against any power.</body>
</review>
