<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It occurs as an option for lovers of Zhang Yimou, Gong Li and the visual spectacle. The best rest abstaining.</summary>
	<body>Disillusioned and bored. So could define me after seeing the new film by the great Zhang Yimou. The truth is that I was eager to see this new work, and virtues that has "The curse of the Golden Flower", continues to be an excessively long and heavy work.The virtues jump at the sight, and never better: photography, the art direction, design production and Gong Li, stand out and show the talent in this production. I can not forget me also of Chow Yun Fat, although not noted especially.Anyone who sees this film at a cinema, will be amazed by the images so spectacular and ornate so distant and ancestral, culture that combines the different chromatic values, in an exceptionally beautiful manner.See these flat General of the exterior of the Palace, the different suits are the characters, the official dwelling in which the Emperor stays before reaching the Palace, these rocky landscapes where there is a battle. In short, a visual spectacle that almost worth going to cinema, and I say almost, because the biggest mistake or problem of this film, is that it is eternal.With a home in which they give us information, but not just happened "nothing", history is becoming increasingly denser, while introduce us new mysteries and family dramas, attempting to alleviate with small too choreographed action sequences, and that long lost his grace. I think that in the first half hour of the film, many people wondered what the hell was in the room, and if it would be better to try to sneak in another or failing spend the time on something more productive. Yes, this assessment is very strong, but the picture did.I could elaborate more, but even the final part, which begin to great things happen does not leave us with good taste. Battles reminiscent at times to the of "the Lord of the rings", but without the magic of these, to finish with a slightly bitter finish (which isn't bad) but does not cause any feeling in the viewer away already for many minutes, the spirit and the feeling of this peculiar Royal family. In short, "The curse of the Golden Flower" is presented as an option for lovers of Zhang Yimou, Gong Li and the visual spectacle. The best rest abstaining.</body>
</review>
