<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Spiderman 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Okay to spend a ratillo (a little long for what counts, the truth), but left quite indifferent. So that, as it ends, it gives a little as if there will be a fourth part...</summary>
	<body>Entertaining third part of the adventures of Spider-man 3, directed by Sam Raimi.y the least good of the three.I'm not saying that it is the worst by the consideo which is not bad. Of course, what is clear is that it isn't as bad as many critics and bloggers are commenting out there, is not even bad. Only that it is the least fortunate of the three for different reasons.The first is that the formula is exhausted. It shows in a script where the fortunate situations not abound, there are somewhat repetitive dialogue that do not contribute anything to the action and the employee rate is very irregular, the final result being a mere hobby, forgettable shortly see. In this sense, does not seem nothing to the brilliant second part of Spider-man, where the character is offered us in a fascinating manner in their duality super-héroe - normal person, with all your questions, desires and human pain.Here we again offer this duality, but already without this patina epic just emotion, Yes with humorous notes, some good achieved, others a both streams.And is the best of this film are scenes where humor makes presencia.sin to provide an the protagonist. For example, the very funny character embodied by the likeable actor fetish of the director, Bruce Campbell, in the role of the maître of the restaurant where that left the protagonist with his girlfriend, with the pupils asking in marriage.And also, the descacharrante moment in which the Secretary of the head of the protagonist sends acústico-vibratorias to your table shaking to do what his wife he has entrusted to not be nervous.With regard to the action scenes, so irregular, with a first confrontation between Spider-man and his friend, excessively long and embarullado ex-mejor, and others better, with the "sand man" in liza.In short, I do not think that it would be worthwhile talking much more of this film. Okay to spend a ratillo (a little long for what counts, the truth), but left quite indifferent. So that, as it ends, gives a little as if there will be a fourth part (only signed three Raimi) or not. This is perhaps the worst thing that can be said about it.</body>
</review>
