<review author="Taliesin" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Respect that Sam Raimi was approached by Spider-man in the first delivery has been diluted in the ego of a director become accustomed to doing things in their own way. The result is an excessive film in many respects, that entertains in the boot and makes you ask the hour at the end.</summary>
	<body>I'm not a connoisseur to bottom of Spider-man, but enough as to knowing that a character with 45 years of history has passed through many hands and that each one of them has shaped to suit. This means that a Spider-man, there is but many and very different, but all share a profile that Yes belongs to the character and not for the writer or artist turn. And I say this because Sam Raimi has led to film his vision of Spider-man and, like it or not its adaptation, fidelity to the comic is not what most despite the hour to talk about Spider-Man 3. What happens is that if Spider-man fans were quite satisfied with the first installment, I fear that many will be they trinan with the third.The main problem of Spiderman 3 is the respect with which Raimi approached the character has faded after three films in the ego of a director become accustomed to doing things in their own way. The result is an excessive film in almost every aspect: the footage (140 minutes), the amount of enemies, the maniqueismo of the very eighties superheroes, fighting impossible and Tobey Maguire making the clown for longer than necessary. All of this confirms that Raimi has opted for a movie with lots of action and a simple one plot, rather than by an approach to more adult themes, to which a character like Spider-man is very used. It gives the impression that the director has already tired of the spider and says goodbye with a final Fireworks that hides a big empty plot.Presented in this film venom and the Sandman, this character to be the most interesting difference. It is left wanting the lizard, sure we'll see in Spider-man 4, and Gwen Stacy begins to flirt with Parker. But the worst is the change that suffers from Peter Parker when he wears the symbiote. Usually alelado reporter turns an as Nicks Rivers of Val Kilmer in Top Secret. Grace would have been nice if it had lasted five minutes and so we would leave in acceptable if the thing had reached ten. The problem is that if the thing reaches the quarter of an hour, including a number of dance of our friend and neighbor, we have already arrived at the ridiculous more absolute. Yes, we learned that the black suit makes a redomado bastard, do not need to insist.In short, Spiderman 3 is a film starts being entertaining and at the end the hour just asking. Like the South Park movie, is larger, longer and, unfortunately, uncut. Sam Raimi gives us everything and in large quantities, except moderation and a really interesting script. In the end, everything is a succession of scenes without a glue clear between them, it does not mean him missing footage, but quite the opposite. It is true that there are flashes of what could have been an interesting film, but tried to please all audiences, I am afraid that he has angered some and left cold to others. In short, to see and forget.</body>
</review>
