<review author="Dover157" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Simple, entertaining and palomitera movie made to become the taquillazo of the season</summary>
	<body>It is difficult to understand this film and its criticism without having previously read the book. But I will try to analyze it from the point of view film. But I have to say that except for some licenses not be you can brand not be faithful to the book.A film without more pretenciones than the sell and entertain the mass avida político-religiosas conspiracies that raise blisters between the more conservative. why this story is so controversial still fiction?, why the churches of the world are tear vestments with a history of many that stain the name of these institutions? Here is this very popular saying "When the River sounds, water bears" while the story is completely fictional, may that its historical context is not so much.So apart from the raised controversy, to my personally has degraded me nor I am pleased to a masterpiece. A simple, entertaining and palomitera movie made to become the taquillazo of the season. The director, Ron Howard, plasma with quite master pages of the book by Dan Brown. showing much of the scenarios where it develops the plot, some of which like the louvre Museum with great clarity and fidelity.Who is read the book can be seen with MIME and detail to managed to capture the essence of these places, the real protagonists of the film.And speaking of protagonists, one of the black spots of the film are precisely these, intoxicated by the charisma of the side. We have a deadpan Tom Hanks who has failed to capture the essence of his character, a Audrey Taotou remembered by all as the fragile "Amelie", which is its role in excess, Jean Reno in the role of Benzu Fache totally correct and credible, Ian Mckellen in the role of Sir Teabing highly rewarding but something jester and especially Paul Bettany in the role of Silas where demonstrates his talents of actor for one of the roles more difficult to film.The narrative action, the metric and the pulse of the film is chord in the 131 minutes that lasts for mixing between if flashbacks, both historical and personal, in order to better understand the context in which develops all the story. But sinning a script caught with tweezers and adapted, as far as possible, the phrases most famous book. Although there is to thank him that he has respected the different languages spoken in the history, in post of an adaptation more reliable of the book, but reassured because all have subtitles.On the other hand we have the band sound, wonderful as all compositions of Hans Zimmer, although it does not reach the height of previous scores of this great composer.</body>
</review>
