<review author="JLO" title="Luces de la ciudad" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>At first glance, and also taking into account the the gold rush and the circus, city lights would be the definitive work in that refers to the character and life of the silent tramp.</summary>
	<body>Overwhelmed by the talkies - who already had two long years of success - Chaplin decides to do a "talkie". but without dialogues. Lights of the city - against all odds - turned out to be a solid film, almost without gaps, with the excellent interpretation of Charles always, but adding, one jot more subtlety and again incorporating the melodrama, or perhaps in a more serious way; as did already successfully on the famous El Pibe. The only criticism - as it was the case in almost all of his silent shorts - is a poor Assembly and a camera too static, being everything generally reduced to a single plane, where all the action takes place. Content in detreimiento of aesthetics.The discovery of the opening scene - commented until the tired-in which the florist mistaken you for a millionaire, is the basis and the fundamental pillar of the film (along with the struggle to do the "right" the unknown hitherto actress). The final sentimentality never becomes excessive as in other cases of his filmography.The final moments are an unpublished ambiguity in his film so far, aside from the happy endings - sometimes introduced to the force, betting on a beautiful, bittersweet and logical culmination.This is also the scene - along with the now blind florist and a more ragged Hobo than ever--of a poetry and feelings, only comparable to the one maintained in the reunion in the police van down by little Jackie Coogan in the kid. An exact conjunction between the naif of short and imminent and forthcoming "seriousness" view first Charles.A, and also taking into account the the gold rush and the circus, city lights would be the definitive work in that refers to the character and life of the silent tramp.Summary: Charlie saves the life of a drunken millionaire, this locks friendship, but it is totally unknown when he is sober. Earlier, he falls for a blind florist, who ends up paying his operation to return to view, confusing it with a millionaire man. He is accused of theft and to release from prison, reunited to the florist that only recognizes - and was disappointed - to play the hand.</body>
</review>
