<review author="JLO" title="Tiempos Modernos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Modern times contains one of their best--or perhaps the best - start of any of his films. Chaplin shows in a few minutes, the alienation that plunges man industrialization and the wasteful use of own machines.</summary>
	<body>Modern times contains one of their best--or perhaps the best - start of any of his films. Chaplin shows in a few minutes, the alienation that plunges man industrialization and the wasteful use of own machines (up is "eaten" literally by one of them).All part of an idea of the clown after his visit and meeting with Mahatma Gandhi, a fervent advocate of the rights of man and of one of the most important crisis of the U.S. (1929), effects which lasted several years. A great moment of the film is the confusion as a leader at the head of a manifestation, along with several and achieved prison scenes (the use of drugs in the salt shaker is unpublished so far).Then Chaplin is lost in an incessant repetition of their own jokes, as providing a dignified farewell to his silent and eternal character, condensing the most successful sketches of some of his past films. Here again are the adventures in skates, drunkenness, the escalator, the smacks, etc; that so famous he did in his shorts at the beginning. At the end, he relents to pressure and messengers for the first time the tramp, making it non-existent - and with the horrible pre-recorded laughter of fund-another mockery to sound words. Thing to do already and with much better tino in city lights, in the opening scene of the speech. The typical end chapliniano starting to a destination of freedom and without end, does not provide anything more. It just leaves us the nod of the nostalgia of the repetition and his trademark.Summary: Carlitos suffers various setbacks with a factory machinery. He later protects a thief, they pass through together a strike, prison, setbacks in a large store and finally, acting together in a cabaret.</body>
</review>
