<review author="JLO" title="El Gran Dictador" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If it is not his best film, it is without doubt the most risky just by embarking on a production - with all United States in an ambiguous abstention-during the time of greater domain and influence German, making it so much more valuable. Without a doubt, a classic film of a classical artist.</summary>
	<body>The great dictator was created as a joke by the appropriation of Hitler in the mask of Charlie and his universal and famous mustache. Then it becomes in anger by the growth and popularity of this nefarious character, almost a vendetta made by an artist who at that time declares not to have the honor of being a real Jew.The remembered scene of the globe, with its infinite poetry and determination to portray the pathetic obsession of the dictator Hinkel (Hitler) and their longing for power; It is both a blunt weapon and an unforgettable film testimony, both its lyricism and their stay in the memory.It widens even more, to be linked to the rhythm of the scene at the hairdressers, in charge of the Charlie Barber and are of the Hungarian March by Brahms and his baile-fantasía, shaving a customer and prove unparalleled skill. Nor Chaplin in talkies break away altogether from the tramp, evidenced by several times played by the Barber.Only these two moments and their ten minutes of duration, would suffice to justify the name of this artist in letters of mold. A not happy scene played by Paulette Goddart limited - to declaim in the door of the ghetto-the final speech that some sounds pedantic, and some that another disjointed scene; they do not obscure the greatness and courage of a great film.If it is not his best film, it is without doubt the most risky just by embarking on a production - with all United States in an ambiguous abstention-during the time of greater domain and influence German, making it so much more valuable. Without a doubt, a classic film of a classical artist. Pure history.Summary: Chaplin made here two roles. As Hynkel, dictator of Tomania, orders to harass the Jewish population and planned the invasion of the neighboring country of Austerlich. As a Jewish Barber Charlie sees suffer their colleagues of the ghetto. The physical similarity of both characters leads to confusion, where the Barber coincidentally usurps the position of Hynkel, and finally delivers a speech in favour of peace, equality, democracy and brotherhood among men.This final speech turned the world.</body>
</review>
