<review author="JLO" title="Monsieur Verdoux" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The end is one of the most beautiful of his filmography, as lucidly defined great analyst André Bazin: Chaplin makes us witnesses and participants in the death of the great Charlie, at the hands of a society already uninterested about the fate of the erstwhile, Idol of the masses.</summary>
	<body>To continue hitting strong after a controversial predecessor film, also still hurt by the advance of the talkies, stripped of the character of the tramp, Chaplin plays being washed face on this occasion a murderer of women. Of course that with style and good taste expected. A kind of cynical blue beard modern, skillful and seductive. One original idea by another big as Orson Welles Chaplin birlara you with your consent.Using the ellipsis as simple and beautifully as possible as in the successive murders, and sometimes with only a subtle opening and closing of doors. That happened up to his own family?. only Verdoux knows this. Politics provides the inclusion of true - then - fall of the stock market, and as a mere malefactor is judged with the force of law when a mass - Hitler by case - murderer is completely ignored. The end is one of the most beautiful of his filmography, as lucidly defined great analyst André Bazin: Chaplin makes us witnesses and participants in the death of the great Charlie, at the hands of a society already uninterested about the fate of the erstwhile, Idol of the masses.OK, Chaplin "kills" the Tramp and all fall on him is by far his most criticized and rejected - film, but there are no account which now ceases to be shielded in the myth, entering other "reality"; making this a much more personal and risky work. Perhaps the best film of Charles Spencer Chaplin? In my opinion it is, followed closely by the great dictator. In other words, safety pin.Summary: Verdoux successively marries a rich women who then kills her to stay with their money, thereby helping to his son and invalid wife. Their false names and their mock culminate when it is recognized by relatives of his victims, and decides to surrender. "Black" film, ahead of several years to his time.</body>
</review>
