<review author="JLO" title="300" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The political intention also mixes a little many, in a story that shows the values of the Spartan, militaristic, authoritarian society exalted. Beyond you with true intentions Yanks and the same film. Or is it spun too thin?</summary>
	<body>Move jewelry comiqueras of Frank Miller to the big screen, both by his large, flamboyant graphic style your Rodez and his good scripts is always a challenge. 300 is a comic of the 98', after his famous Sin City of the 91'. To productions that do not name?Daredevil, Batman - have their mark. But one thing is the adaptation of a comic book and quite another the language of cinema. Already demonstrated in the irregular Sin City (Rodriguez, 2005).300 is faithful to the original Miller (there are modelled paintings), but is mammoth by their rigidity cause of being filmed almost entirely with blue screen wallpaper, for his oral heaviness, carry slow matrix unsuspected (believe it would last 30 minutes less without it). Up the sex scene is in slow motion! The picture is as impressive as the of Sin City, luxurious and monochromatic, but ends up being anecdotal by the weight of a script with "epic" phrases to repeat.The battle of the Thermopylae and his veracity are not in discussion (is a version of the comic, not about the real story), but Snyder does not deprive put the Frankster so famous were after the Lord of the rings. Let's say that within its genre, it would be more honest to Gladiator (2000) and less passionate than the Alexander by Oliver Stone (2004).The political intention also mixes a little many, in a story that shows the values of the Spartan, militaristic, authoritarian society exalted. Beyond you with true intentions Yanks and the same film. Or is it spun too thin?The criticism in the North the try fascist, of the film more gay history, bloodshed to the cuete. It is not for both. The people became the most-watched in the United States. I.e., the same old story. We agree that it is not a lead either. 300 can be seen, has the necessary action and also monocordes actions, clothing and unrealistic male bodies, endless battles in idling and is cheerful and cartoon at times.Finally, the subject is the film after his vision, becomes a real shame for what could have been.</body>
</review>
