<review author="JLO" title="3000 millas al infierno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Some winks make it fun, touching the parody for performances with a touch Tarantinezcos. Precisely the actors - all good - make credible the incredible script. The old twists of the plot and stereotypical characters something down the score.</summary>
	<body>Strange and enjoyable film. Since the titles of beginning, where in a futuristic scene where two Cyber Scorpions beat duel do?, is the analogy of what is going to happen with the two main protagonists: Michael (Kurt Russell) and Murphy (Kevin Costner).In a tone of comedy enter the other two important characters, Cybil (Courtney Cox) and her son, then shifting to action with a spectacular robbery at a casino in Las Vegas (machine guns to fire on fire simile full). Continues as a road movie - with duel in the western style and everything! - to culminate with a fast-paced police scene of suspense. Variada.A despite the varied mix of styles and genres, the film becomes interesting because they have no claims whatsoever and by a rhythm and furious editing, without falling for this reason in the Vertigo of video clip although debutant Lichtensein, is justly recognized by them.Some winks make it fun, touching the parody for performances with a touch Tarantinezcos. Precisely the actors - all good - make credible the incredible script. The old twists of the plot and stereotypical characters something down the score.Theft from casino, five former convicts and their different problems, intrigues, betrayals, persecutions and deaths in bulk. All the actors said in good shape, protruding Cox (Ace Ventura, Friends) for an unexpected ease and known beauty. We agree that Kevin Costner dressed in brightness and wig and broomrape Elvis-style, is not very common, both by their seriousness and put in the shoes of a repetable and achieved villain. Pin the clip that accompanies the end credits with Russell playing in playback to Elvis Presley - with all the cast making midair and dancing - in a clear auto-parodia of his old role in the telefilm "Elvis" (1979) by John Carpenter.</body>
</review>
