<review author="JLO" title="Fuimos soldados" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film false, hypocritical and sanctimonious you will need much the people of the North after 11/09 but here makes it they lengthen the minutes and be shortened more patience, with an unbearable war movie.</summary>
	<body>War film describes based on real events, the leadership of Colonel Hal Moore (Mel Gibson) at the head of his troops, sent to Viet Nam to meet a kamikaze mission, interspersed with family relations of these and their regret.Its director, Randall Wallace (brave heart, Pearl Harbor) is showing us the side of more humane war - if any - next to the relations between the soldiers and their environment without depriving yourself of the bloody scenes of combat (which they are not bad but they are not much), and countless cheap shots that have more than two hours of this film.All are brave, they are all good, all are great soldiers; all stereotypes and characters already displayed a thousand times too much, these past years (the soldier Ryan, the fall of the Black Hawk, codes of war).The most successful is the gaze of the Vietnamese Colonel, parallel to Colonel Moore, reflecting their similarities knowing that they are the two side of the same coin. Although really, if one does memory and recalls the portrait and human profile of recruits of born to kill shown by Kubrick, or below, the lyricism of Terrence Mallick's La Delgada line red, it ceases to be original to become a school manual look.Another case is that of Mel Gibson. Being a conservative Puritan fan in real life, choose (or imposes?) roles with a strong religious connotation (signals) that already in these times begins to tire.With all the elements trodden the gender and exaggerated until the exasperation: dies first the black, then the recent father, Yankee flying in the foreground every twenty minutes, flag with final obvious, chato and corny, phrases of the style: "Tell my wife that I love her" - of course, one second before you die-, make this, a film false, hypocritical and sanctimonious you will need much the people of the North after 11/09, but here does is they lengthen the minutes and be shortened more patience, with an unbearable war movie.</body>
</review>
