<review author="JLO" title="El aviador" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With the pedigree that supports Scorsese in their espaldasor is difficult not to compare and judge it. Only you can add that the Aviator, is another example that we have one of the great film.</summary>
	<body>Howard Hughes, Aviator/director/entrepreneur eccentric and insane megalomania, could not find a better vehicle than a biopic done by another passionate as Martin Scorsese today. Also shares it the same excess of Hughes director in the almost three-hour, lavish scenarios, and arduous follow-up during twenty years of character and its rare psyche. Another success is focusing almost exclusively on his facet of Aviator rather than the obvious as a filmmaker.It is not true as it is judged, the be a film too impersonal. Throughout his extensive footage, note the hand of its director, both in him editing as in the treatment of color at different stages, with the inevitable grand scenes in his filmography.The Aviator is Scorsese his staff Ed Wood. The affection shown by its "creature", this conscious tribute car, makes it akin to the affection shown by Tim Burton in this film with his also alter ego. Howard Hughes during the Golden Hollywood, was a key figure both by his facet as director (the angels of hell, the outlaw), producer (Scarface) and the largest aviation pioneer. His obsessive disorder, the visceral fear of germs, and relations with its famous women, did the rest to be attractive to Martin.Su verbosity and violence, New York Gangsters visible flaws, not repeated them here Scorsese. The Aviator is stronger than its predecessor. If they are the fact of telling with passion - and stubbornness - American history. Di Caprio continues to pursue his acting growth, even if this is not the best of his career, but more than meets. It seems to stay halfway with regard to the interpretation of the old age of Hughes, problem of his eternal face of nene not aging or with the scruff and a thick beard. Katherine Hepburn, found in the skin, voice, claw and up the affectation of Cate Blanchett, a living synonym. The end is revealed as a debtor of Citizen Kane scene. Seems that our mothers and their memories, are a hard to beat in our psyche hurdle and could even replace the final phrase of the future, with the small and great word Rosebud.Con the pedigree that supports Scorsese on their backs (Taxi driver, raging bull, the last temptation of Christ, Casino) is difficult not to compare and judge it. Only you can add that the Aviator, is another example that we have one of the great film.</body>
</review>
