<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Hana-bi ( Flores de fuego )" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is a brutal poem, an excessive and also beautiful singing about destiny and life from very few materials and filmed with an extreme tenderness</summary>
	<body>There are honor codes requiring a rugged calligraphy, an epic background to justify the deployment of violence. No violence to the way in which Tarantino filmed her: oversized, master for your visual enjoyment, but totally Rome in dramatic profiles. I prefer Sam Peckinpah or Samuel Fuller, who are (perhaps) the relating two immediate about exerting this unnecessary, although movie fan Mania (the cinephiles of idle fancy) of being Westernized Asian film. Hana-bi (fire flower) is the portrait of a man driven by circumstances exceeding you - who does not? -: terminal illness of his wife, partner which has been paraplegic in a RAID and the clan of mobsters who pursues him with funeral and evil intentions. And it is death () which dictates the script. Death accompanied by tenderness or beauty or melancholy. The brief, almost fragile, outline explodes when necessary in a powerful visual stream, hypnotic action scenes that are flanked by beautiful and unexpected recesses in which the characters, to which we dedicated to a fatal destiny, stop to contemplate the sea not a landscape snowy with the delicacy with which would make it a character in a film of Bergman or Kurosawa. This tottering thriller (does not appear it in his boot) is a funeral poem, a kind of hymn to life since the consent of his escape. Perhaps despiste profane spectators in the Filmography of Takeshi Kitano or which consider only the frames for content to that biased public and the American, who exude violence, blood and adrenaline, GLUGs, there's all this and in adequate doses. But Kitano cannot contain his poetic breath and upload your camera to the sky or let it rest on the sea: us Tames in the Tempest, leads as you want to the ground that most pleases to ultimately make us descarrillar in the abrupt drama of a pressing destination, fabulously orchestrated from the shadows of the sky or the neural crests of the infinite sea. This lyrical breathing is also possible to appreciate the various drawings that appear throughout the film and that they are the work of the director (and actor Beat Takeshi) was awarded the Golden Lion at the Venice Festival in 1997 and brought international recognition to the work of a man who has a very peculiar sense of violence and how to narratematrimoniando minimalism and spectacle, making their Yakuza, these gangsters of the rising sun, hechizados by some spell ancestral, expressionless and lethal, hieratic and thinks, constitute a caste of loyal Archetypes of his dramatic universe, who comes to these mimbres, the spell, the plot and the paucity of gestures to make explicit an enormity of resources and an almost unfathomable array of messages.</body>
</review>
