<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Brick" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Brick is a desinflada by its budgetary scarcity and its teenage cast, which gives the film a sense of artifice that (to me at least) distracted and bored.</summary>
	<body>Why are the protagonists of the film noir of the 1940s characters such talluditos? Why not be reverted its directors by youngsters hairless chest, facial acne and easy laughter, or girls of smooth skin, size without cracks and Karasu experience? I guess that the essential reason is that the audience that filled the rooms at that time was equally mature and interested to find beings that could identify. Clear that those were other times, and the film noir was in charge of exorcise fears and hopes of a skeptical generation marked by the war.Thanks to this we can today enjoy a mythical genre that has had more than worthy followers, especially in the Nouvelle Vague and the American neo-noir of the nineties. The Nouvelle Vague gives the film noir narrative fluency and spontaneity and freshness and everyday life in its staging. Dialogues and scenarios are street, and his youth characters, faced with an aging society do not understand nor want. The skepticism of the generation between wars item is the rebellious Existentialism of a generation seeking their place in the world away from the map provided by their adult conservatives. Today times have changed. Cinemas populate teenagers looking for their dose of tits, romance and good special effects. And already do not seek outside their environment places where grow (advertising that avasalla them prefer them always young).Brick (in reference to the bricks of heroin that manufactures The Pin) inspires us the memory of the evolution of the black genre (and the hard-boiled Asia, with its urban gangs) who tries to always with effort reinvented in more or less successful formulas but without remission us back to their sources, making us resoplar: again will be!, well then! or I liked most of Bogart or Tarantino! Do is that? say the promoters and admirers of so-called independent cinema - the greatest success of this masterpiece of the young filmmaker Rian Johnson resides in having placed a genus designed for adult characters in a context of Californian teenagers playing terrible mafiosi, fatal girls or astute detectives. Everything seems very postmodern, but seasoned with a rather classic script: (occasional) detective in search of (his) lost girl, sensual fatal femme de dark intentions (crazy to throw to the detective), fearsome bully and eccentric mafia Chief). The characters are caricatures of cartoon, that only in brief instants manage to take a more solid form. Almost always when appear in scene the duo starred by a solvent and content Joseph Gordon-Levitt (how much I reminded Fele Martínez in thesis!) and this expressive eyes and conspirators doll called Nora Zehetner (seen by the heroes series). The others are to take them to sharks.I guess that it was precisely this amateurism what you caught the fancy of Sundance (special jury prize) and to the Sitges (Citizen Kane Award for best novel director). And is that Johnson manages to create feeling of closeness and freshness at the expense of a prepared script with MIME, but accentuated by the lack of budget (scenarios are scarce and repetitive). What we have (sure we will soon know) is to think that it would have done this filmmaker with a larger budget and a more adult story (in all senses).Brick is a desinflada by its budgetary scarcity and its teenage cast, which gives the film a sense of artifice that (to me at least) distracted and bored. A pity, because their intimate scenes (the discovery of the corpse in the tunnel, calls to his girlfriend, encounters with Nora Zehetner) promised that eventually becomes as a seasoned puzzle of endless punches. Even so is a success (own all postmodern product) offer an unusual collage that combines film noir with characters that populate even by the Institute (in fact Johnson filmed at the school attended by small), despite seem so theatrical and forced. Discover teenager roles that not fluctúen between coarse humor, precast terror, or the romance pastry chef, is almost a miracle that should be protected by UNESCO.I guess everyone who see Brick will be hoping that Johnson will make us enjoy soon a force stronger and darker than this (and perhaps without so much testosterone derrochada). Apparently it has more than proven resources. In process is which seems that The Brothers Bloom, a triangular noir, with two brothers (Adrien Brody and Mark Buffalo) and an unreliable partner (Rinko Kikuchi, the excellent sordomuda of Babel) will be called. Complete the cast always great Rachel Weisz.</body>
</review>
