<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El gigante de hierro" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Best animation film for the whole family. That is much? Lol It is the truth. And it should be scheduled usually in schools. I've done it on my behalf on several occasions.</summary>
	<body>The spirit of classic animation, the profiled by Disney and now exploited sensibly by Dreamworks or Pixar, often falling into clichés that encourage the infant public's imagination, but despistan wishful adult (other, not talk) and force you to reconsider its natural vocation as cartoon Viewer. The iron giant flees from these commercial stunts, lacks musical numbers, obvious sentimental side, does not include animals that talk. Doesn't even have to Sting and Elton John on the central issue that will occupy a few minutes at the next Oscars in Hollywood. Therefore, by not appear animated film, I saw the iron giant. And I discovered a much more intelligent script works for adult of recognized signature and contrasting aparententemente dramatic pulse. The story told is the story of all the world's children: of dreams made reality, the fantasy that takes a piece of reality, without denying her, without supplanting his evidence. The story of the boy who discovers in the forest near his home to the iron giant (a bloating E.T.) was not originally written for the times in which the film is set (the cold war, the fear of Russian invasion, terror to the paranormal, the belief that beings from another world may at any time to sit down with us and eat our lunch). Is based on a child text written by Ted Hughes at the end of the sixties to comfort their children by the death of his mother, recounts the friendship between the child and the robot in the placid English countryside, but Brad Bird (then famous for the Incredibles) change in a hallucination produced by the unprovable imminence of the Red armies and poso pulp of B series of film of summer that illustrated the porous imagination of all those kids who now have 50 years.Taken directly from the comic, drawn with MIME, mirror of the Sci-Fi of the time, alien to the clichés of the formal art of Walt Disney, the iron giant is a tale for children explains the greater wrong that are weapons. A metaphor pretty and playful, is also plastically beautiful on the anti-Communist psychosis of an entire people, the American, who was educated to hold the breath to the stirring beat of the patriotic anthem to the flag of the stars and bars. People that took several decades to understand that the enemy is at home, although now the thing ande bundled and the ceremony of terror does not write the Soviet enemy but Arab fundamentalism. This will also produce a film less as this tone in the not too distant future. The story is written much better last battle. Don't want his story is permeated too much hatred which always promotes today, everyday, the hectic pace of news and the insane complicity of the television cameras, which recorded the infamy of a soldier devastated by a bomb at the time that stored in its bovine morbid and resounding carnality of a miss in an empty throne. And at the end, it is not thing of gutting the more than commendable feelings that drive the plot, everything is resolved in mansa, tiny, necessary happiness after the debacle. And I imagine, cinema, gets standing to applause because the language of tenderness is universal and here is superbly unspoken. A masterpiece of animation.</body>
</review>
