<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Spiderman 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We have a film one hundred by hundred popcorn maker, without hardly personal añadimientos, with doses of action at raduales, a couple of really painful scenes and it relies on a really light script.</summary>
	<body>"We all need help ever," says Mary Jane Watson Peter Parker in one of the multiple discussions closer to a saga that the most expensive film in history. The sentence, perhaps the best of the film, concludes: "? inclsuo Spider-man". So yes, even Spider-man (Peter Parker) and even own Yes, Spider-man 3 movie. We are certainly some, before a film palomitero one hundred per cent, without añadimientos just personal (perhaps saving the history of Sandman, the best of the movie), with doses of action at raduales, a couple of really painful scenes, which feels embarrassed, and based on a really light script.All the bad welcome that took the film once you surprised is preestrenó, even to me, but is that they were right. Yes, some her admired for his spectacular (no doubt, that Yes), but others, the more ready, her KTP not treat well the characters and lack the magic of two previous deliveries, which for me are much better than this. Spider - Man 3 not only lacks magic, but also maintains. A film can be designed completely to the public (in this case, to a rather silly public), but man, need to know what is done, and more, with Sam Raimi. Here, more than doomed to a certain audience, youth theory, is made without personality, with economic intentions, above all. The action scenes, for example, are not as of the previous deliveries, with that touch of intensity high, tension one hundred per cent and intrigue. Here the emotion is not so great. Yes, all of them are very well done (except the final battle, with a lousy editing and repeat, without a minimum of maintains and intrigue). I would stress above all the brief but interesting fight between Spider-man and Sandman in the truck, what is perhaps the best made and the most intriguing. And better not to mention the small battle have Harry Osborne and Peter Parker in the first House. I that call you the sum of Los Angeles of Charlie more Mr. &amp; Mrs. Smith, with exemplary music, of course. So we could say that the third part of this series, hope that finalized up to this release, there is no point on many occasions and magic is virtually non-existent.The screenplay for Spider-man 3 would be envious. I mean that it would have to be envy of others. Actually, the number of sequences which could have left for the deleted scenes of the dvd are many, not to mention that with them feels embarrassed. For the former, highlighting many of the dialogues between Peter and Mary Jane left over completely, by not say that threat of Harry Mary Jane, to that extent sorry, because it makes no sense. Also highlight the phase transformation of Spider-man in a bad and rebellious, man because of the poison that is goes to the body. In my opinion, this idea of the change of personality, good man and bad man, her was, at first, original and innovative. But it is when you see the film you see there that the transformation is painful, totally painful. It could have been care much more personal change of Peter Parker, also the physical (to what comes this hairstyle to the rebellious?), because many (Yes, many) dances which gives us during the movie (especially on the street, because even I am laughing of pathos that results) are completely dispensable. That Yes, the black suit is great. Also talk about the lack of sense that has the anger that you are corroded journalist Eddie Brock then formulate the alter-ego of Venom. I, at least, would like not to cold-blooded murdering the man who I left without work and kissed my girlfriend, or is there need to be very crazy. Well, in any case I would have read the comic before I say what I say. In short, that if it would have worked and cared more aesthetics and personality of Mr Parker had been, Spider-man 3, a really good film, with its other small errors, but that Yes.And to not be so critical this criticism, I speak on the points in favour that I find the Raimi film. It is true that has some gags really successful and funny, as the French restaurant, very well coordinated and nothing cansino. The love triangle, despite being affected by too many unnecessary turns, remains attractive. I believe that the end should have been another, more than anything because SPOLIER that slow and romantic dance which is melting black scene not paste or glue in a Spider-man movie. Because it could have been stopped nonsense and end as they ended the previous two, with the man spider flying happy through the streets of New York. END OF THE SPOLIER. But as I say, the love story between Parker and Watson affected by the friend of both, Harry Osborne, does not become too heavy, although it isn't anything original. Another aspect to be highlighted is the story of Sandman. I will not tell, because it makes more grace follow her watching the movie, but yes I will comment on that you except the formation of alter-ego, everything has its meaning and is, its history, the most attractive, credible and dramatic. And not to forget the last dialogue maintained with Peter Parker, with a few very well introduced flash-backs.Cast it would highlight nothing more and nothing less than to Thomas Haden Church, in the role of the above-mentioned earlier Sandman, alter-ego of Flint Marko. Within the extensive group of performers, he is the most believed his role and that, to be brief, makes it better, much better. It is also necessary to stress the other new addition Star: Bryce Dallas Howard. She plays Gwen Stacy, the girlfriend of Eddie Brok and the daughter of a police captain. Her role is so much untapped and gotten a little with a shoehorn, but along with the Sandman, is the most interesting and fresh, as it is which breaks the relationship of the protagonists. Rosemary Harris neither does anything wrong, although it was already expected. Their interventions are more sense give the love story between Peter and Mary Jane, like Kirsten Dunst, which is more than correct in his role, very confusing (personally) on several occasions. And to end the good, highlight the interventions by j. k. Simmons and James Cronwell wasted two veteran actors that make his brief role, as best they can. Tobey Maguire is a case apart. Has it been the alien black which has become a very bad actor? Or what the budget has made him move from his charisma and act without dash and then collect? I do not know why will be, but it is clear that his interpretation is pathetic. And not only by the dances, but by all false expressions that transmits, the face of pasmarote throughout the film. For me, only okay when it takes place costume. It's really incredible that an actor like him, who had given us good performances in the two previous installments, now, don't know why, has morphed into this. So as you can see, the cast itself isn't at all bad, but what in theory is the most important thing, the protagonist, is really painful.As you would expect, the digital effects are of excellent quality. To see the transformation in Flint Marko Sandman in this kind of experiment and their subsequent attacks or the final battle, already we can only clear that money has been much greater than in your script. Although this already no one could doubt, so I I contendré with respect to the comments of each of the scenes of action, which, as I have said before, are all spectacular, but without too much emotion. As always, the picture is correct, no personality (multiple planes, just highlight on Spider-man dressed in black at the top of the city climbing up the crystals of a building). The Assembly by another band is simple, to become, at times, quite bad (sometimes resembles the of the television series, with those fades to black between). And music, this time not composed by Danny Elfman, but Christopher Young, still in his score for film commercial, correct line and with many hisses. That Yes, the main theme of the first composer is still, which most attracts.In short, a film irregular, rather disappointing, although incredibly spectacular in the action scenes, despite not having the same excitement and intrigue that the of the first and second installment. Spider-man 3 is what it is, a palomitero blockbuster without the intention of being a cult film or anything like that, which could have been reduced its lengthy duration (156 minutes). Boring is not, but there are plenty amount of scenes, some of them painful. I recommend it to the unconditional fans of Spider-man, which they are interested, rather than as film, in its contents regarding the comics, which in this case is well managed. Those seeking the magic of the first two deliveries, which is not ilusionen with this third. It will disappoint them.</body>
</review>
