<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Megavixens up!" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apotheosis of film of female despendoladas, ubérrimas, designed to be pin-up poster of box office of soldier, but personal, care, worthwhile film when it was checked and how he battled towards his corner in the history of the seventh art.</summary>
	<body>This is not a fairy tale and there are at least a couple of good reasons to confirm it. The voice of Greek chorus (Kitten Natividad) who is narrating the vicissitudes of the film desataviada of textile prejudices, rotunda in charms that disgustarían not a Botero to diet to your models or a Rubbens aware in the aerobic power, announces that this is not a porn voyeurism of the three to the fourth. Russ Meyer is the King of the nude: not one. Their carnal demands are always by the same thread: mammary exuberance. Don't need no other dramaturgical preparation. Their actresses are females of the common people have been blessed by a runaway hormonamiento. Already. And they are out there, by deserts, fields of wheat, for short rental apartment motel smell sweat, and nicotine by coniferous forest, running without decorum. Because running, that knows well Meyer, breasts rise and fall and that monotone choreography (although hypnotic) raises the interest of the male spectator, prototype of the viciosillo movie buff, delighted you brighten eyes with this recital of bodies ubérrimos, unbound, accomplices in a lust soft, stubborn in his lack of shame to tell us that the world is full of problems and probably sex desastaca the brain of the Earwax of stress.Megavixens Up! It is the quintessence of the genius of Meyer. Overwhelming meat, surreal delusions as a perfect instrument of Adolf Hitler (later killed by a Piranha) looking for orgasm with a multidotado ephebe in a mansion of Empress Sissi or exotic ladies of tremebundo chest and pubis ogres company service. The film runs through predictable places: lumberjacks brutotes in search of beer, and while, corrupt sheriffs who see any bend in the way occasion for the wild fornication, genital links filmed with playful and unprejudiced morality and, above all, generous portions of glossy bodies, grown by mother nature without the modern competition the silicone. Let us not forget that we are in the early 1970s.It will not find the gentle reader is inherent to this incendiary context pornography. We will not see any sexual intercourse: everything is unspoken (and how) but this detail is not subject to its sweep of field. Icon of the film underground or nuddie, Meyer is an author with an absolute mastery of the medium of film. In this it differs from ordinary commercial eroticism or porn white workers or hard that feeds the shelves of the video shops or extreme content of certain channels of payment programs. Meyer is a perfectionist, an author with a language immediately detectable. And I am not referring to the curves of his heroines: in all his films are very serious portraits of the always call profound America which already in force to be so told machaconamente, has ceased to be. Slums of road, on the edge of the cartoon characters or invariably caricatured features soundtracks...Author total, was not only responsible for directing: was also writer, cinematographer and producer of his daydreams. He died at the age of 82, proud of his humour, oblivious to who ninguneó for life have been making the same film (and rolled 30). Kitten Natividad, Babette Bardot, Lori Williams, Haji, Uschi Digart or Erica Gavin were his body of dance, his army of females, the pin-ups in the back of the Playboy (whom was eventual photographer in his youth) recruited and that was usually rejected by excessive. The public was content with minor monumentalidades and wasn't well regarded this maximalism unless had a worthwhile piece of paper (of Fund) (example: Jane Mansfield).The colourful film desparpajo, its lust almost naïve, still resists the passage of time. Pulling more two tits than two carts, reads the Hispanic adagio, but these here described are not normal tits: the proposal is subversive. The malairado group of feminist women in one or another occasion have whipped his film have not warned the bellicose, independent, strong and radical nature of its protagonists, who are never mere inflatable dolls. Anything, are less submissive to the way in which are women porn, or in one lower tone, which have built the erotic film since that Hedy Lamarr leaving weaned of the Lake in black and white.The Edition retains this scribe is on vhs, although her now I've restored to dvd so the years not mistreat. Her issued a decade ago a regional television in very late hours and with adult film fanfare. It is, of course, but not usually mistakenly go escorting insignificant film interest zafiedades, aimed only at encabritar the noble bruising parties, film jamaipanese urgent kleenex. There are movies, cult film, if you prefer. And future generations will laugh or looked or discussed, as here now, the legitimacy of a single author (there is No other: Tinto Brass is crude, but it shares a very similar icons prontuario with Meyer and both have a recognizable language).</body>
</review>
