<review author="Kahzrrak" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film that I recommend to anyone who wants to have a fun time</summary>
	<body>And here comes one of the most eagerly awaited deliveries for this year, starring Tom Hanks and Audrey Tatou (that she is gorgeous, everything must be said), with secondary appearance of some fantastic Jean Reno, Paul Bettany and Ian McKellen.I am one of those who has seen the film but has not read the book. If you don't have time to read all what I want to!. Because, despite this, I must say that I really liked and felt me very entertaining. Seems to be based on real historical studies (although the data appearing in the movie whether or not truthful, is not for me me judge it) and draw much attention how fits perfectly in works written by other authors (that famous head of woman that the Templars worshiped and that helped it were accused of heresy, for example) if it is true that discerning it in other data (for example the reason why French Crown) (it helped its extermination, which seems to be that it was indeed political or, better still, economic: a reading that could you this a little further clarification could be "Beltrán, the last Templar", although it's a little suckling pig, heh, heh).It is a film that I as detective encuadradía: the protagonistan are caught up in problems without eating or drinking and are forced to solve all the puzzles that are them are raised while they flee from various enemies. The performance of the actors is fantastic (well is true that many of the actors are not exactly beginners) and history is very well framed, without flaws in the plot, you hooked and is not slow in no time. In addition, which interested the topic of the Templars, of the secrets of the Church and similar things I suppose that he will be happy if you are going to see her. In fact, upon seeing her very clear why the Church has not given credit to this work. They appear in the story characters from the Church of Opus Dei, the supposed are the heirs of the Temple, etc., making that the Viewer does not know well who is the "bad" nor what relationship are interrelated with each other until the end, thus keeping the mystery until the end of the film.In short, it mixes mythology with religion, history and fiction, is a film that I recommend to anyone who wants to have a fun time.</body>
</review>
