<review author="José A. Peig" title="Spiderman 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>At the end, and bearing in mind that this is the peak of a trilogy about one human being rather than a superhero, the style and profile of Peter Parker is ennobles and plays its role in the area for which it has been created.</summary>
	<body>A man of sand, a sticky poison, a photographer, the old aunt who gives good advice (what good woman, what mantra so requetesobada), love, jealousy, hatred. And at the epicenter, the hero, Peter Parker, who will come to sustain and suffer the weight of the plot in this new installment filmed the man spider, which most rummages (or intends to dig) in the emotional world of the main characters. After its two predecessors (brilliant, though never perfect), and time to complete a trilogy, Sam Raimi meets the problem common to all the sagas in lathe to superheroes. The main defect of "Spiderman 2" consisted of stretch and squeeze too about same issues: the vulnerability of the hero, the waiver by love, sacrifice the dreams in pursuit of heroism. On that occasion, in broad terms, the result was more than acceptable, and Spider-man began to become a soap opera, not the masked hero but about human responsibility to embody the exploits of a superhero that drag on his conscience. In Spider-Man 3, the saga is amplified and rises to one octave higher, stretching and returning to stretch the same topics, the inevitable when a study does persist in turning into saga material that would only give to a couple of good movies. Therefore, in the third step, and following the canon, Raimi, to avoid the repetition brazen and bland, was left to explore the dark side of the hero, without be able to avoid remember "Superman II" and "Superman III", in which Donner and Lester marked the steps to follow (see Superman renouncing heroism by love, II, and III)(, facing his dark side, in one of the most remembered by the older generation geek scenes, although the film as a whole is pretty mediocre, but bad to nausea).Therefore, Spiderman III insists and is repeated in the above but adding a touch of darkness, situándo the hero in fight with itself. And at this point in the film, as that is quite difficult to surprise the average viewer. And you know what happens when they tell us the same story all too often; that all comes down to a Manichaean, pamphilus and apathetic, empty product of creative values, predictable.The "technical" narrative of Raimi (quoting comes with sorna and nasty) is reduced in the television soap opera style: love scenes, so clear of facile lie down on his back: "no longer I want-lagrimita - what you've done? - lagrimita - is there another person-lagrimita - is mi-lagrimita raisins - that kiss that you've given to the other was our Kiss-lagrimita". We are not malicious, but because they are going to tell us a little bit original, the only thing that could save the product is how tell you us.Spectacular battles, vengeance as destructive impulse that moves the characters, the rencor.y to the end even the need to forgive!. A true film about good and evil in which the decisive battle being waged in the depth of the hearts. The true, and in this layer the film succeeds almost in unexpected ways, is that each piece and character takes his load motivaciónal justified as the story progresses. The man of sand peca por amor (to daughter), Parker, who in turn is love and rancor to the memory of his uncle killed by the man of sand, Harry, sinner out of love for his father, redeems in love to the friend, and after learning the truth of the facts. In this film, the tormented hearts are cured when the truth comes to light: Parker knows the circumstances of the murder of his uncle, which motivates his forgiveness, and Harry forgives Parker when he meets the true circumstances of the death of the father.In short, although in a few years no one will remember this movie, although it is not a great movie, all justified in the final stretch and Spider-Man 3 sees the light that compensates for excessive footage, probable inconsistencies argue them or the treatment of helpings which gives to relations between and the construction of characters. There is a network of relationships that, at least, follows a scheme defined and organized according to an idea. Idea loaded moralina, even some religion. But in the end, and bearing in mind that this is the peak of a trilogy about one human being rather than a superhero, the style and profile of Peter Parker is ennobles and plays its role in the area for which it has been created. Scholars of the comic can say many true things. But here we talk about movies, we are not interested in the comic.</body>
</review>
