<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="H6 Diario de un asesino" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>During good part of the footage and only I could breathe calm when appeared the final credit titles. Pathetic, not it can be summarized more in less...</summary>
	<body>I had not sat to read any criticizes the movie that brings us today, after seeing their pathetic way to promote themselves, I said, come hard with her sére not and given that this week I'm going to see some Spanish to another tape, let's give him a chance...Before entering field (little, so we are going to cheat) and after investigating a little by the network, I will say that after the painful promotion of the tape is the advertising agency Kanzaman, "expert" (see quotes) in advertising American tapes shot in Spain, and has the dubious honour of turn into shit everything he touches (go)(, as a King midas in reverse), his or rather, our, are the promotion of tapes so pathetic and painful as "The Kingdom of heaven", "Basic instinct II", "Sexy Beast", "Sahara". so no wonder up his screenwriter has repudiated the same indent of the tape.Finally, as they say in "yellow humour" new programmes to the nougat!!! The tape already begins badly, and is that, I do not know you, but when I see an assault a woman, but know that it is false, I get very bad host, I can not, and although I know that I usually have an acid humor and which ever kidding on the subject, believe me, everything is façade. As well, the tape already begins evil, but not only that, but that the stupid pint of telefilm starring 2 familiar faces of the small screen, without hardly decorated, so dark that I had to change more than once lit the hire of the monitor to appreciate something, trying to lay chair where there, with unnecessary and lacking planes of meaningless, both cinematic and narrative, and thousand and one experpetos, turn this film into a pathetic spectacle that should not be seen more than a few minutes, in honor of the truth I will say that I click the arrow keys on my remote control &gt; during much of the footage and I could only breathe calm when appeared the final credit titles.Honestly, not I see the logic to spend money to do this shit of film, and then we complain that the Spanish film is in crisis.</body>
</review>
