<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Garganta profunda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Legendary porn movie of a woman who has the clitoris in the throat. Hilarious situations and dialogues, takes us back to that absurd atmosphere of the 1970s. Recommended to have a good time, or even to be able to say "I have seen deep throat".</summary>
	<body>A few days ago we mentioned the documentary "Inside Deep Throat" that left me with the intrigue of seeing the film. Obviously a serious and formal man like I did not possess a copy, so I had to ask my usual pornographer I got me a copy. The copy I got in no more than six seconds. Thank God I asked him a digital version, if leave me DVD may that it had not been able to draw the movie of the apparatus, je, je.The film is a girl that does not reach orgasm. In his words, it has taste, but do not see rockets, not hear trumpets, or anything at all. So it gets in the hands of a psychiatrist rabigordo who discovers what his problem, which has the clitoris in the throat. That is why you have to reach orgasm through fellatio deep.My mother what I've been able to laugh. As porn movie the truth that is not worth a pepper, but it has sentences and scenes that are great. I swear that great. In addition to this, you can say that you have seen the most profitable movie in the history of cinema, and quedais as God. We could say that this film opened a genus, named with the same name, where currently there are true artists.In short, legendary porn movie of a woman who has the clitoris in the throat. Hilarious situations and dialogues, takes us back to that absurd atmosphere of the 1970s. Recommended to have a good time, or even to be able to say "I have seen deep throat".Besitos.Escenas and dialogues (more or less). ** "Do you mind if I smoke while I eat?" says one in what eat you the pipitilla.* "Do want to run you or mount a berbena?" in reference to the rockets that you want to see women protegonista.* "Imaginasé have the balls in the ears" and responds "well, oiré well as I run!".** The doctor said "It's amazing" and said it "Would have been someone the clock inside?"responds the doctor "has No!" and she says "women don't have badajo" ** mounted a party so that the girl can achieve orgasm. And how come so many are giving number at the entrance.As I said, great.</body>
</review>
