<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Dame 10 razones" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without being no wonder, and thanks also to their very short duration, he recalled with sympathy and appreciation.</summary>
	<body>Brad Silberling is a curious director able to make films of fantasy genre ("Casper", "A series of unfortunate events by Lemony Snicket"), almibarados commercial products ("City of Angels") or an intimate story on their own traumas ("the compromise")."This time he comes to our screens with smaller jewel-minded film that fails to meet all those expectations.""Give me 10 reasons" (Ten Items or Less) tells the story of a famous actor (Morgan Freeman) low hours, in preparation for a new role, visiting a supermarket in a working class district of Los Angeles. There you will learn to Scarlet, a vigorous cashier (Paz Vega) that will engage a peculiar relationship.It was perhaps predictable by the synopsis but the argument is somewhat forced and not very credible, but not get the feeling that it intends to. It is more a mere plot excuse to create a fresh, simple and nice film interpretations of Morgan Freeman and Paz Vega, full of naturalness and spontaneity that has as strong points.Both note them comfortable and thanks to that develops between them a certain chemistry in which, I feel, there has been room for improvisation. Perhaps the fact that Freeman is also the Executive producer has given them more freedom than usual but the fact is that it shows that all have spent it big during the filming.This relaxed atmosphere seems to have moved even to a fun soundtrack, whose original songs have been composed by Antonio Pinto.De such way that we have a film that can remember for his approach to tape as "before the dawn" or "before sunset", with funny, tender moments, even, emotionally intense, without being no wonder, and thanks also to their very short durationHe is remembered with sympathy and appreciation.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 6.5 out of 10</body>
</review>
