<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La flauta mágica" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Its flaws are forgotten due to interpretations, wonderful music and the brilliant direction of Kenneth Branagh.</summary>
	<body>Those who know me know that I try to follow me in my comments to purely cinematic. "However there are occasions, like this one, in which a few preliminary clarifications are essential.""The magic flute" (The Magic Flute) is not a film for everyone. I would like to say that if you hate Opera or classical music is not your movie. We have an adaptation of an opera by Mozart and, therefore, most of the time the players are singing opera. Surprised, or feel disappointed by this, would be ridiculous.Now if you like Opera, or without being a lover of Opera or classical, you have the Mint open to enjoy new artistic experiences, then, and only then?Let's talk about film."Because movies, so in capital letters, is what distill each and every one of the films of Kenneth Branagh to date (even the less good).""The magic flute" starts with a (false) up prodigious sequence, which make time, in which we move from soldiers in the trenches until the aircraft in the sky. With such brilliant start, Branagh creates a visual equivalent to the Overture to the Opera, introducing with mastery in the context in which the story will move.Before an impressive beginning, it is very difficult to maintain the level during the footage, but without reaching the genius of this script, the movie succeeds and Branagh demonstrates thereby having lost none of his narrative claw. His work as a director is one of the strong points of the film.Since the beginning of the project, everyone has had its (logical) doubts about the work of the actors. The risk of that to employ professional singers (something inevitable in a project of this type) lost in acting ability. I have to say that not only is not the case but people like Benjamin Jay Davis (Papageno), Joseph Kaiser (Tamino), René Pape (Sarastro), Tom Randle (Monostatos) or Lyubov Petrova (Queen of the night) are really good and some, such as the aforementioned Jay Davis, show a great comic vis. More loose in that paragraph perhaps Amy Carson is a little bland.But the movie is not perfect. Indeed, it has a major inherited defect, I believe, of the original libretto: certain lack of consistency. If in the original script these small inconsistencies can apologize for being a text full of references and Masonic in the film and already devoid of that reading keys, it is not so Mann. In this way there are jumps in the history that are strange, as see appear or disappear certain characters without any explanation.There are also some scene that Branagh has resolved with inserts fast to try to explain parts of history that would not be otherwise clear. The result in this case is not entirely satisfactory and could understand her any Hackney of videoclipera. This happens, in any case, in a scene or two.What happens is that these defects, any important stress, are for me almost forgotten thanks to performances and, above all, the wonderful score of (very accessible in addition to the profane public like me) Mozart and the brilliant direction of a Kenneth Branagh showing that it remains one of the visually most exciting conductors on the international scene.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 8 out of 10.</body>
</review>
