<review author="José A. Peig" title="Piratas del caribe" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bathed in sinister dyes as well as bufonescos, transports us to a world in which the sea and those who populate give life to a universe which dream. As in a book of Stevenson, in good cinema of adventures, importantly give spectacle, a show with a soul.</summary>
	<body>When the curse of the Black Pearl reached the charts around the world, a certain mental state had already set in the minds of lovers. The Decade of the nineties, bland in what film show is concerned, it left us a bitter feeling (for some alleged Vanguards of high intellectual Crest, with Lars Von Trier, heading the new moves) and the eighties began to establish itself as the golden age to which a worship of nostalgia. In the 1980s the big three Trilogies which, since then, were and will be the model to follow, the canon for a well done entertainment film saw the light: Indiana Jones (Steven Spielberg), back to the future (Robert Zemeckis) and the original trilogy of Star Wars (George Lucas, Irvin Keshner and Richard Marquand, more the invaluable work of Lawrence Kasdan and star Bracket in writing). In 2003, the film by Gore Verbinski put an end to a wait. In General, the comments of a large part of the public came to say that "by end, a film adventures in conditions". In conditions, I would stress. The conditions are the canon. And the adventure genre has a few golden rules that never fail: you don't have to be original, gives life to the characters, encouragement epic plot as a whole and the camera translates into an absorbing visual style (pace, mounting, framing). Fun is served. On the basis of an immortal icon, the figure of the pirate, of great importance in the history of cinema as literature, the industrial giant Jerry Bruckheimer produced a product planned and designed to become one of the biggest taquillazos of the story (it is on its way be). The fact that this icon has a fascinating power that tune in a special way with the adolescent and youth audience is not a question of tastes or trends. The pirate, as icon, idealized figure and archetype, brings together the concepts of rebellion (understood, for the youth sensitivity of our times, wild life, anarchy, "hooliganism"), freedom and adventure. Not in vain, in one of the scenes, Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp) runs in verbiage that reminds us of the famous "the pirate song" of Espronceda. Pirate remains a hallmark of romanticism, that magic, that mystery and worship a mixture of admiration and contempt for an immoral and adventurous life, well tuned with the assiduous popcorn young public and the hobby without adversity with people of all ages, all including, those who grew up in the heat of the sword of Errol Flyn and those who did empuñándo the lightsaber Luke Skywalker. The smell of Bruckheimer made no mistake: Jack Sparrow, as well as the remaining cast, es-son a strong embodiment of the romantic archetype of the pirate. but a new varnish, to undergo more pulp, more Kitsch, banalizando - is only an assumption - the figure of the pirate for a consumption faster and easier serving the commercial structure of cinema today. It is nothing new: the key to the success of the original Star Wars trilogy was a play, based on talent, heart and enthusiasm with Archetypes of the tale and universal legends but "putting them in crates" to the taste of the consumer on the basis of a socio-cultural moment very concrete. By Verbinski we cannot say too: shows know the scope in which it moves and is a correct executor of the idea made by Bruckheimer, inspired by a Disneyland attraction and a video game, "Monkey island". History: between the legend and the folletín pseudo historical, it tells a tale of pirates and pirates. Little Elizabeth Swann (Keira Kinghtley) opens the function while he recites a chant of exaltation to the pirate life. It is the sign that announces what will be the end of the narrative, in which the same representatives of royalty and the order assigned to the charm of a pirate on the run, a maid and a blacksmith apprentices in the life of the sword, the freedom, the Buccaneers and the lost treasures. As we have pointed out, romanticism involves the narration in order to squeeze the maximum this charming aura of the pirate. The argument is based on historical facts which are revealing as the action progresses: a group of pirates in search of the Aztec treasure. There was a mutiny to banish Captain Sparrow, who will be left to their own devices on a remote island. William Turner, known as "Bill the boots", decides to be faithful to the pirate code and disobeys the orders of Barbosa, acting against the mutiny against Sparrow. Barbosa sent to "boots" into the depths of the Ocean as punishment for his disloyalty. When the greed of the Barbosa group leads them to steal the gold, the Aztec curse falls upon them. The only way to undo the spell is to return the gold and the blood of Turner, whose son was abandoned on the high seas with the piece of gold that will serve as a connection to the past and the present narrative engine. As we see, the story has all the ingredients of a pirate legend that could have existed in the popular folklore of the time. Verbinski introduces us not only in a mere history of pirates, goes beyond that and forge a pirate legend in which the two worlds of fantasy and reality, seem to live together following rules: Will and Elizabeth are the reality of the present. Barbosa, Captain Sparrow and other crew of the Black Pearl are entities slaves of the past, a past of betrayal, mysteries and enchantments: the curse of barbosa and his, which prevents them to taste the rum (expressive and grotesque the scene in which the rum drink slips between the skeletal Barbosa tripe) or the perennial madness of Sparrow. However, the film always keeps a humorous tone which refers to the pure entertainment unpretentious excessively dramatic: there is something of desolation in these pirates sentenced to an eternal death, history runs smooth, but without wanting to take too seriously to itself, in which raw the show by the show, the dramatic nod, witty dialogue and gesture spoof auto. Spectacular visual energy looks all the iconic elements of the piracy at frenetic pace: fantasmagoric and ships with sails to the wind, the waves of the sea beat on the mast and the bow, the anchor at the bottom of the sea, the buzz in the duels between swordsmen, the rumbling, and the artillery of the guns, the paradisiacal beaches of the Caribbean, the cave of treasure. The appropriate orchestration of all of them - in a montage certainly irregular, because the slippages of pace was quite noticeable in some sections - translates into a mesmerizing spectacle in which the viewer almost can smell the gunpowder, felt the violence of the battles between Buccaneers or evoke the magic of a Navy legend. The cinema show, more solid and mature content from an intellectual point of view, consisting of sensations and evocations. Obviously, every viewer lives this pirate adventure in images in their own way, and some can even be bored on the way. But Verbinski film has enough elements to evoke sensations (which are at a good adventure movie) and represented with a visual style history, as a minimum, striking, and a structure, as a minimum, acceptable, that is something unquestionable. Tastes, as we say, have nothing to do. They are characteristics and inherent to the own film creation textures which focus our discourse and our assessment of the House according to standard. The film also bears a romance between Will Turner and Elizabeth Swann, and settled in the purest classical style, with a final kiss after tension sustained throughout the 150 minutes, which is a virtue, eliminates any excess sweetener so prevalent in this type of production (you want to-kiss-you want to-kiss-you want to-kiss.). In the film adventures, the characters can not fail. The authenticity, freshness, sharp dialogues. In that regard, perhaps the results are somewhat unbalanced. There are two actors (and two characters) that, without a hint of doubt, fill the screen and give character to the story: Captain Jack Sparrow and Barbosa (Geoffrey Rush). Seems that Jack Sparrow, over time, is becoming an icon of cinema of current entertainment and is one of the most original characters now in its scope (come on, a character that cannot be said to be a plagiarism or rehash of topics, to possess his genuine style). Johnny Depp's eccentric and enigmatic personality comes as ring finger to configure a héroe-antihéroe which stands at a neutral point between the interests of each other, giving the character of an ambiguity that well complements your bufonesco profile and your intentional self parody (Sparrow is a pirate of volume and spine, but, moreover, he derides his own condition of pirate.) Note the reader what does Sparrow is a parody of Errol Flyn. In her personality embodies the spirit of the film: a story of epic legend which, at the time, does not take seriously itself. ). Part of who's captain Sparrow?. We will not know until the final minutes of the film. Taking into account that cinema adventures does not need complex characters to work and meet their target, a character like Sparrow is a luxury and a puntazo the franchise. The characterization adds an attractive, some ways and a physical appearance that combines the masculine and the feminine, and gives it a certain air of androgynous. Barbosa did not say much more: simply a wrong with claw, sense of humor and nasty, antithesis of Sparrow, what is bufonería and parody, Barbosa contrasts the seriousness and the traditional pirate conduct. Keira Knightley makes a correct work, but their records and his physical are overly stereotyped, with which the character loses much freshness, and it shows in the overall result. The other major problem with the tape has to do with the Assembly work. The footage is excessive. If instead of 150 minutes lasted a few 125 I would save some slippages in the pace and the feeling of adventure would be more emphasized by winning in fluidity and interest. As we see, it does not reach a perfect finish, but "The curse of the Black Pearl" is an achievement for the recent film adventures, the best discovery in the last 20 years (which is not to say much taking into account the almost total absence of productions in this genre, and the garbage to which we are accustomed). And for his detractors, want to say very clearly: beyond each with its gustos, but it is hypocritical to not recognize the virtues of this adventure film when nobody question the merits, the quality and the myth of in Raiders of the Lost Ark. We are not saying that one is going to have the significance and the depth that had and has the Indiana Jones trilogy (time will tell), but if we look exclusively at the properties and intrinsic characteristics of each of them, if we want to see defects in one, them can also be found in the other. Idem for the qualities. The curse of the Black Pearl, an adventure on pirates and the iconography of his legend, bathed in sinister dyes us while bufonescos, transports to a world in which the sea and those who populate give life to a universe which dream. As in a book of Stevenson, in good cinema of adventures, importantly give spectacle, a show with a soul. </body>
</review>
