<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Raimi has confused the complexity with the excess. Instead of an hour and a half has shot more than two, rather than a villain has brought together three.</summary>
	<body>A friend tells me that reads the cartoons depicting, in the universe of superheroes, Spider-man the hero complex. That brings me to two conclusions, first, that the inconvenience of the movie are probably more available to Stan Lee, Sam Raimi, and the second, if intended to be complex, only stays in the attempt. Peter Parker is as complex as a sausage sandwich.Raimi has confused the complexity with the excess. Instead of an hour and a half has shot more than two, rather than a villain has brought together three. Sandman chases Spider-man because it is an outraged father. His friend Harry Osborn is a son in search of revenge which cannot comply with the will of his father. Venom is a photographer who competes with Peter Parker and hates Spider-man because he believes that he took the bride and the post. Almost all the bad guys are victims of some confusion, as the girl. That gives them the possibility of awakening of his self-deception but never before doing any dirty trick to Spider-man that feed their endless self-pity and justifies an action scene.Spider-man is a series where the transit between good and evil is not particularly complicated. Apart from the mistakes that everyone strives to commit, are external forces. The bad guys invent things that end up dominating them, as the Green Goblin, or Doc Oc. In this third installment appears a black clay which adheres to the victim and takes the worst that has inside. The Fund of "Spider-man" is that no one is bad, what happens is that a black hand, either in the form of chemical formula, or in the form of sticky engl is to blame that evil is habit. Young children they are worth those explanations to go pulling; politicians would love to have them to justify their blunders (who doubts that Aznar was abducted, either narcotizado by the pure of Bush when he signed the Pact of the Azores?); but would-be creators of complex heroes should be squeezing a little more brains.When the stellar engl takes over Spider-man and black dyed his suit, and his soul, the hero is transformed into a bad type. Which entails explaining to readers/viewers is a bad type. Evil is, according to Lee / Raimi in a provocative fringe and a casquivano, walk to the style of Travolta. It consists of paraded by a local fashion hugging the vampires and dance with frenzy as a flirt that leads his life in these slums. The property consists of the distressed look of Peter Parker, faithful as a lamb. Jerry Lewis was suffering the same dichotomy in "The Nutty Professor", when the ducks insecure teacher transformed into Buddy Love. Jim Carrey her suffering, either her enjoyed, in "The mask". All three share the same revulsion for this type of heroes in other theaters, a couple of streets below, will delight everyone.</body>
</review>
