<review author="Torbe" title="La guerra de los mundos" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Until the balls of the Yankees</summary>
	<body>Each time I least like cinema of masses. The movies they see everyone seem increasingly more pain in the ass and jerks. Not be why but the prota is always stupid ass is lucky, and at the end of the movie, when it succeeded in defeating evil, it becomes ready, and the crap that to at the beginning of the movie disappear as if by magic. It becomes mature and intelligent.This movie from Spielberg is more of the same, escape and flee and do not give a shot. In addition the bastard has got a couple of actors which is to lend them to eat separately. The girl, an old stuck in the body of a girl, because you just have to see him speak (in original version of course) to realize is that we we have one of the great film freaks. Is CTS makes grace the baby when he speaks like su puta madre, but my cause me fear. See a cria who speaks as a mature person is something awful. Children are children and see them outside their role scares.Then this the teenage son who has the Cruise. Another moron that is to give of slaps on the face until see you the bone to the hand. Faithful reflection of what is called military manipulation, the boy wants to kill the bugs without any weapon, hale, crazy and without thinking, come on, a sack.You want to tell you, but to me that I think fanaticism and madness. Someone wants to go to fight without means is to go to a certain death, why fuck me greatly which at the end of the movie appears this the mongo and his grandparents and all the family. All God is saved, and above the old appears in suit on Sundays and all maquillada.¿Pero sinsorgada is this? Just need to Cruise again with his ex-wife and that the world is much better. Quiet, I tell you the end of the movie but nothing, happens all the movies end up in the same way, and say that not remains mystery to the crappy this. I not be will Spielberg, but this step will only become a director who is good doing special effects, because what is telling stories? not you account you gave that Americans do not know to keep their composure? All say it screaming. In difficult moments it more sensible is to chill out and not be discussed by jets, and in all the fucking movie don't stop shouting and paste among them.It makes me laugh at the beginning of the movie, when the soil begins to crumble, people stop there to watch what happens. Damn, not be them, but I would be running like a bitch for some time, and hiding me. If I see that a bug is launching rays and crushing to God, I hide.Anyway, that to continue talking about this shit, if what they wanted have already done, which is to pagasemos the entry, why I believe that it is going to film his cousin, now me it it down all Internet, that so you can see, the quality of the movies is acceptable, and I can pass palante. Nowadays not be commanded with the forward hand is to die.</body>
</review>
