<review author="Raccord" title="Encadenados" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nazis, intrigue and passion in one of the films that occupies a place in my particular podium from maestro Hitchcock filmography. A delight.</summary>
	<body>A spy film unconventional, with outstanding performances by Cary Grant and Ingrid Bergman. And I am surprised that I like, because I know I'm a declared fan of his style can not find too many similarities to other films of his own. Audiovisual aspect is the same to which we are accustomed always; but in the script it introduces innovations. Here there is a Byzantine plot or farfetched situations; the suspense is created with the minimum number of elements (a key and a bottle) as if he had chosen to do the "harder still" when it comes to get us the heart in a fist. Also introduces very well the loving component in the film, using his enormous creativity: mocking censorship, which prevented then several seconds on screen kisses, makes that Cary Grant and Ingrid Bergman talk one to one centimeter of the other and giving peaks constantly. This produces a much more "dirty" effect on screen than a kiss of screw. At the same time, in this torrid scene the protagonists speak completely inconsequential subjects, what makes it stand out more. Hitchcock here proves that apart from the genius of intrigue, it was also an away series in the romantic scenes.The character of "the bad" is portrayed much more psychological depth than thrillers of conspiracies and spies to use. As data fun, "Chained" in reality it is the only film with science fiction overtones in entire Filmography of Hitchcock that he spent something really funny. In the famous talks with Truffaut, the master of Suspense reveals wore seeking money from 1944 to make the film, but no Studio wanted to produce it because contained in his script, an atomic bomb, something that nobody believed that it came to invent. Only a year later the Manhattan project was made public and the Americans unleashed massacres of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. Only then the savvy producers, already convinced that it was plausible to manufacture nuclear weapons, decided to finance "Chained".</body>
</review>
