<review author="JLO" title="Crimen ferpecto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The problem of crime Ferpecto isn't in his steady pace - and fluid - or the characters - all stereotypical-, but that is always the feeling of little strength.</summary>
	<body>There is something wrong with this comedy by Alex de la Iglesia. Owner of a solid filmography and with its own characteristics (during the triad consisting of the day of the beast (1995), Perdita Durango (1997) and dead of laughter (1999), which made him a specialist in this genre, able to exalt or base "celebrate" the ridiculous human, corrosive, "bizarro" black humor and other powerful.)Crime takes place in a shopping center, far from the recurrent cold and aseptic place, is the place where emerge in living flesh jealousy, the competition at all costs, as also the sex between the protagonists and their following and dire consequences.Rafael - Guillermo Toledo, excellent - is an ambitious materialistic and misogynistic, seller that takes everything to its logical conclusion in wanting to become the head of plant of its section, another clear example of the Gallery of characters "borders" of the director. Power is always present in all his films, both either by leadership, by money or simple excessive ambition. One of the best qualities of the Church, which returns to re-confirmar in this film, is the be a great director of actors. The heterogeneous level of performance - along with the choice of casting - is excellent, even in all secondary. Best sex scene, which gives samples of its cinidad and the timming for comedy, is the one that plays the protagonist couple in dinner at her house: more glowing and bite in his film.The problem of crime Ferpecto isn't in his steady pace - and fluid - or the characters - all stereotypical-, but that is always the feeling of little strength, of a languid exercise almost "taquito" by the director, well as a repetition of style.Its plot is somewhat obvious nor the summation of gags along with references to the films of Buñuel, Hitchcock and Chaplin - the use of the suspense of the surrealism of the film noir, the shopping to closing - manage to get afloat, surmounted by a final weak and too concesivo. Almost of commitment.Both crime Ferpecto and Alex de la Iglesia equal rise the aim then of the failed 800 bullets, albeit only superficially. Directors of weight and with its own characteristics is they always requests a little more and there is nothing wrong with that. Crime is not "ferpecta" or anything, but is what it is.</body>
</review>
