<review author="JLO" title="Sin city" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film that hits in various ways, which does deserve to see but he ends up running out even by their own - and exaggerated-virtues.</summary>
	<body>Filmmaker Robert Rodriguez took as story board the graphic work of Frank Miller's Sin City (a legend in the world comic, responsible of the best Batman, 300 and long etc.) to achieve an impact of action, aesthetic and a real before and after in the history of the genre and its adaptations. We must also highlight the work of the comic in the film today, art always disregarded and that only in this Millennium is real acceptance and its importance.The picture is of a white and black excellent, perhaps unrealistic and insurmountable, with a transfer filedigno frame by frame of the comic and a right direction of actors, are exclusive merit of the Mexican Rodriguez that continues to grow with a filmography a bit despareja but always passionate.Miller is a fair co-director only for having carried out the comic and the screenplay, in addition to oversee the entire process. But not everything is rosy. Perhaps this translation with so much love and loyalty takes away a bit of rhythm and personality so much visual dexterity. There is a clear abuse of the voiceover, easy resource for when there are ideas and the ultraviolence by time - smoothed by the neutral color - reach tire.Becomes a bit tedious, uneven, slow in the third tale starring Clive Owen (the weakest of the protagonists), precisely in which participates Tarantino in a segment in the direction, although it did not clash for nothing with the address or aesthetics of the film, noticing his influence - in addition to the own friendship with director - both in the segmented plot violence pulp and praised and cryptic Assembly.The casting is equally impressive, standing out Bruce Willis always as the scruffy and romantic hero this time fighting against a pedophile, and a surprising and unrecognizable Mickey Rourke its look - behind kilos of latex - both for his good performance. Sin City is a film that hits in various ways, which does deserve to see but he ends up running out even by their own - and exaggerated-virtues.</body>
</review>
