<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fairly loose movie with great special effects and some other things. But with a convoluted storyline with characters that try to be complex, but become ridiculous. Why not they do this? We want to eat popcorn while desenganchamos the brain.</summary>
	<body>It already begins, it starts already. That, which aren't trailers. Papa, when does the bat? That is another, do not you learn. Chissst, that is already beginning. Yum, yum, yum, chup chup chup, rasss, rassss. There goes piderman, there goes, there goes. Give them strong. Pope have pis. Tooomaaa, tooomaaa. Mabuuuurroooo. Is how much it? Are you going to die? Pope, I have dream. Ñiaaaauuuunnnn. (Note from a server, not her see in morning session, which is filled with children, heh, heh)The film is about a boy that has a superpower that makes man Spider (for those who do not know the saga). The plot of this third installment is divided into several stories. On the one hand Spider-man has become popular hero and all is well, with you something external you have to ruin the life. His girlfriend goes from triumphant to the harsh reality. Their enemies are still hating. UM, now that I think about always.I have to admit that I bored as a sleepless bear during hibernation. On the positive side we have that special effects are amazing, but as we are already getting used to these things, therefore not surprise us. Soundtrack says my medium Zucchini which is also fine, but my felt me appropriate in some fight scenes. And some moments of Peter Parker are very funny. In the flat, else negative. The argument is very strange, given that in a film where we hope a frenetic pace, put us much roll. The man of sand is too Mystic. The Spiderman with teeth if that cool, resentful and bad host. The normal Spider-man does rare things that are not understood. Black Spiderman also cool. And the son of the Goblin is bland and even absurd.In short, fairly loose movie with great special effects and some other things. But with a convoluted storyline with characters that try to be complex, but become ridiculous. Why not they do this? We want to eat popcorn while desenganchamos the brain.A roll.Besitos.P.D: The kiss of Spider-man did not believe nobody, is absurd.Pd2: As mola dentudo spidy, shame to leave so little.</body>
</review>
