<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Los Abandonados" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A horror film with all the pictures of the album of stickers of the horror films... Even so: visible, discreetly entertaining, very well done, fantastically photographed...</summary>
	<body>I critique of the abandoned house poetaUn, doors that creak, dolls with a perversely trapping eye, rotten wood, mist in the Woods, the ghosts of the past, the relentless fate who returns to collect its debt, gloomy corridors that amplify the breath of evil, has been ever at Disneyland?II the critique of the film buff not overly agradadoCompetente in its purely technical aspect, simple in its argumentative proposal and, above all, very richly photographed, abandoned may have been the year horror film or the film of this century. At least, made in Spain, although the credits we apabullen with Czech names, búlgares, Russians and it is possible that up to Ukrainians. Who runs is our compatriot, but we're not here to raise the flag and sing the virtues of national products with the shrinking hand on the chest. For that we have programs on television that they still grip the sentimentality and nostalgia and emit Cifesa pestiños and vacuos in love with the Riviera Gigolo folk melodramas, but perhaps I'm going of the matter. Iba by the homeland: the abandoned seems otherwise, an invention foreign or extranjerizante. Good or bad? Fright da: goose bumps across the dark corridors and there are screaming in the room. Who gives more? Then there is the strictly film component: hence Cerdá complies, but we have no awareness that we are witnessing something new. Clichés, again repensados cliches, cliches sieved by the funnel of talent, although clichés within. (Iii) critique of the fan to the géneroQue don't need a libretto of dialogues to the Ivory: Cerdá needs few elements to create unhealthy atmosphere and deliver to the respectable a tape of the highest quality that does not disappoint the true genre fan. Tired as we are of American pastiches where premium flavored gore or al gore decisively crushed by the membrane of the tweeter of a loudspeaker in a concert of Linkin Park. The abandoned is an exceptional demonstration of narrative verve: the two protagonists, that shine at extreme altitudes, copan almost all meters of bovine. The ghosts, the inevitable, not abuse of framing and no (fortunately) children, but the spirit of two of them (not destripemos nothing) pulule by desvencijados furniture of the House, which is one main character. Isn't a masterpiece as The shining of my beloved Kubrick (allow me the anglophile detail: I have today been Recalling my summers of phonetics and dramaturgy type Guinness), but suggests that this author we rejoice with works in the future more daring, with milestones in the bibliography of the horror genre.IV critique of the film lover recalcitranteCaso that this infumable neuronal tracheostomy photographer had caught pneumonia double three days before starting to record, would have a surplus concatenation of scares that do not lead anywhere. As the man went to work, we have a crappy boutique, one of those movies that we get from the video store and call a few chums to lower stress and desparcharnos to taste a few litres of malta and hops with panchitos and French fries non-stop. We left the usual scenographic framework: now we are not in Kentucky or in Wichita Falls, the deep America so enchanted with itself and with its capitalist ghosts barque. The director of foreign has sought an idyllic boscosidad Ukrainian or Hungarian or Bulgarian. I do not know and nor do I care the least. My brain feeds on other vitamins: they left for teenagers with acne in the lack of scruples and a brain yet to be regulated. Had only missed three yo0o0o of good breast perimeter (silicone, not create) to liven up the yawns of the espectadores-macho and (modern times) some convinced and smugly fémina of his sexual orientation. I now lame Murnau Nosferatu and I sew the wounds. I do not chillaré. Not endure me longer neighbors these critical angry rants. V the critical old crípticaMuñecas that mean memories, a crazy truck driver that has not been read to Panero, a mansion which prendarían good fetishists of the Hammer, little more than a hundred minutes of kangaroos jumping over the gut of a broker of feelings.I saw the criticism of the has never written a críticaEsto is an American who comes to Moscow, I think that Moscow is to collect an inheritance which turns out to be a home field or forest which then spend a few terrible things and meets a family who did not know at the end. The two, before the end, go through trouble and more trouble until that finally cease to pass distress because they loaded. At the end of the projection, left the cinema with my softer noble parts completely encogidas and with the feeling that when I would like to spoil the evening to some undesirable would not have any qualms in recommending this movie has scenes of impact. Thus, it says no?VII the critique of the merengueCuatro fan goals he has got Real Madrid to Spanish tonight and that the Spanish has got three. Three great goals of Pandiani Rifle, but my Madrid not daunted and knows getting up from the ground in very fallen seems. Just missing that morning click the neighbouring Catalans and then there are, dear love, path of another League. And gave to this already the away when we were in November. Before the football I saw the abandoned. Do not leave David Beckham or Roberto Carlos, but posts to one of them to make a piece of paper because I prefer the defence Brazilian, which gives more impression in a dark hallway. Ah, if to a horror movie you take away the music is as if to the Bernabéu you take away the grass.</body>
</review>
