<review author="Andrés" title="Flores rotas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Broken flowers" is a hard irony about human relations, vacuum and loneliness, in various forms</summary>
	<body>I was fortunate to see this movie in the presentation of the new issue of the magazine Godard! Definitely there is no better way to present a film magazine that projecting a sensational film (also in quality of pre - premiere in Lima). But at the same time it was very annoying to find, even among film buffs, people with such bad manners when watching a film. Its damn findings aloud, his dialogues to mezza voce and their stupid cell phones. Funny thing is that "the Lady in yellow", was the person who had left to enter without invitation, the same disturbed to the room with their murmurs. But despite these interferences could taste with attention this great movie of Jim Jarmush.Don receives a pink letter the day that his last girlfriend leaves him. In the letter without a name one of her former lovers informs him that he had his son 20 years ago. Add now the supposed son has left in search of his father, a Bachelor all consider a Don Juan. His friend, fond of mysteries, devises a plan to find the author of the letter. Then Don embarks on a journey by United States to locate his former girlfriends and find a track. "These lines that can make us believe that you it's a film about"someone to learn great lessons in life", perhaps it would be if Don would not be portrayed by Bill Murray and, above all, if the person in charge of this story wasn't Jim Jarmush.""Broken Flowers" (2005) is the Odyssey of a Ulysses who would have preferred to stay at his home. After the departure of his girlfriend, Don does not seem interested in nothing more than sitting on the couch in his room. The persistence of his friend Winston, obsessed by playing to unveil the mystery is what in the end forces him to the first plane. Key track is to find a machine of writing among the possessions of the ex-novias and bring her so that Winston verifies if the letter has been written with it. With this objective and trying to disturb as little as possible, Don appears front gates of old girlfriends. In this Odyssey will be not the sirens to try to stay with the traveller.One of the things that surprises in Jim Jarmush, and at the same time enjoy both, is the use of time in his films. What others may seem boring and pretentious, here the fixed flat long and silences in conversations details the viewer discrete and rewarding, content in every small moment. And "God is in the details" say that Santo Tomas. said in "Broken flowers" there is also a hard irony about human relations. The emptiness and loneliness, in various forms, weigh on the lives of the characters. The communication between them is complicated and tense, full of misunderstandings. Don moves as a zombie, for their girlfriends is that: a dead man who returns to an uncertain search. But you can not expect too much from a zombie, except this. Bill Murray is so funny doing almost anything. Swayed from one place in the car, circulating perfect urbanizations, only a punch achieves this awakening.</body>
</review>
