<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sometimes, computers, an excellent Assembly and a director with claw, do wonders. The penalty is that they forget the script. For example, a button.</summary>
	<body>Spider-man and Sam Raimi you have foundered, because the third installment on the newspaper the Marvel hero offers nothing new to the viewer with respect to the previous. Seems that, to deal with Spider-man 3, filmmaker has built a sort of DIY with several of the already exposed concepts in the first two, with which my whole view, seems to me excessively repetitive.What's more: I would say that, apart from repetitive is boring, that, at all times, it puts the melodramatic effect above the spectacular nature of its action scenes. If any, haylas, but with too many times dead (and unnecessary) between them. A curious contradiction, because this happens precisely in the chapter that more attention has been devoted to (perfect) special effects. In fact, at this time, Spider-man 3 is the most expensive film in the history of the cinema.The only notable plot developments are announced that dark side of the hero (very forced and poorly explained) and, above all, in the approach to the relationship between Peter Parker (the alter ego of Spider-man) and his girlfriend, Mary Jane Jackson, after which it discovers his double personality. The rest is more of the same, starting with the rivalry created between the protagonist and the vengeful son of the Green Goblin, Harry Osborn, who, following in the footsteps of his father, will evoke the vicissitudes of this to get rid of the man spider.And as it seems that a single villain film is not enough for the ambitions of the current Hollywood, Raimi load your product with two evil types inks more. One is the man that took the life of his uncle and the other, a resentful photographer who, after being humiliated by Parker, DSAT the latter's death. Too many concepts mixed - and not very well grouped - to make the story good tack.I've always considered a defender (tooth and nail) of the first two titles in the series, first and foremost of the second, which made gala of an excellent script that, in this case, throws less. Perhaps for this reason that this delivery I have disappointed both. Expected much more of one Sam Raimi which, unfortunately, seems to have been accommodated too - and easy way - with the character, forgetting to draw a well-defined story and conforming, only to show, over and over again, the same scenes as always. In the end, one just getting tired of those (very) filmed sequences in which Spider-man as an urbanite Tarzan goes jumping from skyscraper skyscrapers. And more if Tobey Maguire - for the first time since that gave life to the character--gives the impression of not being very comfortable in his role.Anyway, it is undeniable that, despite its flaws, the tape has moments unique and worthy of a filmmaker who (if you want) can put the camera properly. A good example of this is at the moment in which the superhero must save a woman who, because of a crane runaway and placed on top of a large building, is on the verge of falling into the void.Sometimes, computers, an excellent Assembly and a director with claw, do wonders. The penalty is that they forget the script. For example, a button.</body>
</review>
