<review author="Tyler" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is the worst of the trilogy which takes this into cuadrilogía. Do do the box office responds, and someone much smarter than I once said that? never argue you to a success?.</summary>
	<body>Now yes, now I can speak. I've already seen and, as I expected, it is the worst of the trilogy which takes this into cuadrilogía. ERGO, there will be a fourth movie which recur Sony Pictures which is not known to that level of participation will be Raimi, Maguire and Dunst, but I think that Raimi considered this character already yours to and safe returns to the battle, if not as director as producer, but now refers to a screenplay by David Koepp, which suggests that the fourth part of the adventures of "Spiderman" repeated with regard to its team.Not be what would think in the event of a change to this level, would it collapse?, it is risky to say because, dammit, James Bond have done you pretty well their changes throughout the series. What happens is that Spider-man makes a mistake in this sense. James Bond the things have done you well by, among other reasons, its mode of script, i.e. all the stories which told us about Bond are absolutely independent, is a series, and as saga his movies work alone. I do not need me to see before "Only for your eyes" that "The man of the Golden gun" to understand the story. The Spider-Man movies have a fairly risky continuity in that regard. "Spiderman 3" make another big mistake, his excesivisimo footage, on the other hand inevitable that the error comes from further back, and the duration is an error that occurs by carambola of another, that is resent to the entire film and damage its structure at all levels.Raimi knew from the outset that this part Spider-man was going to face the Sandman; also knew that, necessarily, Harry Osborn should continue in the saga and avenge his father, now as a modernized ultra Green Goblin. Avi Arad, responsible for production of all films and coordinator of the Marvel company for all its film adaptations, then told Raimi who should introduce once venom, one of the characters with more popular heat by comics fans. Raimi became convinced only when Arad said that people should see once the dark side of Spiderman and Peter Parker. This convinced Raimi who, with his brother, turned to writing. Venom is a character that does not have the sympathy of Raimi, and it shows a lot. Well, what I wanted to get I is here, if you have cash well Venom makes Spider-man already three enemies in this part. Three enemies! "Any writer with two fingers of lights I'd say that is crazy, because there is no way to structure it well, to give coherence to the skeleton of the story."Spider-Man 3 "has no pace, is going to catch-up and, occasionally, because you don't have to go changing the plot remains stagnant. For this reason Raimi needed more time to close all these frames, something that does not do well.A film can not have more than one plot may have few sub-plots want, but never more than one plot main, and "Spiderman 3" has three because even having been able to turn his confrontation with Harry Osborn into something less important, Raimi and his brother give it too much weight. At a technical level "Spiderman 3" is more an episode of a sitcom than a film. The sit? coms work like that, with more than one plot, but the film is much more closed, you have to take many things into account and not do what comes out of noses, for this reason the films of directors like Lars Von Trier or Julio Medem will never be good movies, because passed the rules of screenplay for the eggs, and this affects their films, making them true tostones.If Raimi would have done what initially wanted, i.e. confronting Spider-man with the man of sand and had become the Green Goblin subplot the movie had worked much better, its structure not be resentiria and his pace would be much more kinetic.The box office responds, and someone much smarter than I (which is not particularly difficult) once said "never will you argue to success". It is true, and in this sense "Spiderman 3" is opinion, something that we all expected. But one well, think it was as this was film, also her we would have gone to see all. The Spider-man franchise works only by his name, and that if there is than giving it.</body>
</review>
