<review author="Tyler" title="El caso Slevin" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tene a script very well, those with plot twists, multiple views, lots of action, good dialogues and, very important, few pretensions. Reinventing film noir.</summary>
	<body>The Slevin case is one of those modern film noir movies post-Tarantino not made by Tarantino. Well, for a server, Tarantino represents something much larger than Ra for the Egyptians. Which does not mean that he decries anyone who mimics him, on the contrary, I am a great admirer of imitators and good imitators.That if. contempt to bad imitators, but happens that this movie is not any imitation of Tarantino. just follow its wake, that verede which opened the right to make movies of this type without actually copying evil to Quentin, is the case of this infumable movie which was "things to do in Denver when these dead".After Quentin came (almost at the same time) Rodriguez, and next came Guy Ritchey. This Paul McGuigan movie follows more the parameters of the English that the Tarantino. "I'm late to this criticism, but I went to see recently and wanted to say something about it.""The case Slevin" has a script very well, those with plot twists, multiple views, lots of action, good dialogues and, very important, few pretensions. From the beginning it keeps you entretenidísimo. A good narrative pulse for a story that required of him, a story that still very confusing you is perfectly clear. He has some these wonders that are "Ocean's Eleven" and "Ocean's 12"; this playful and frenetic, but more violent tone.Interpreters are in State of grace. I have always felt that all actors, once in his life, want portraying a gangster boss, because it must be the role more fun to interpret of all. Sir Ben Kingsley already it had done with great results in that movie so magnificent that it is "Sexy Beast", directed by a man, Jonathan Glazer, which we then disappointed with that pretentious little pain in the ass that was "reincarnation"(con_ese_niño_de_cara_insoportable) Morgan Freeman never thing had made, we do not have "Hard Rain", and it unfolds in a perfect manner within its role.Bruce Willis is still an actor that it consider after his death, most by these roles than for those for which said many people who remember. I prefer John McClaine as the dead of "The sixth sense". I believe that modern cinema owes a lot to this actor. its roles of "Jungle of glass", "The last Boy Scout", "Twelve monkeys" or "Pulp Fiction" (obviemos the tripped corny "Arnaggedon") Genial.La movie has a very good rhythm, is long but not boring, has good story but not memorable, good characters but not epic. It is what it says is a very good film, that they should do more frequently so that spectators move so well.The director, Paul McGuigan, is a Scotsman who made a movie that some people will remember. "The Acid House", a movie neither good nor bad. something rare in the era post "Trainspotting". And also an entretenidilla movie that was filmed in part in Spain called "The Reckoning" and recommend it without any urgency at all.A highly recommended movie of a writer obviously coming from the tv. environment where great writers are finding lately. ask him to Dr. House.</body>
</review>
