<review author="Tyler" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This script is internal action, but physical movement. You should learn from it Spaniards and Argentines, and stop doing so extremely boring movies.</summary>
	<body>"Little Miss Sunshine" has possibly one of the best scripts for the last year. And I don't mean in terms of content, that also, but in terms of his technique.The movies of internal action such as this, are much more difficult to write. In addition to much more boring to do so. A good few times script is entertaining to read it, because it is not made for that, is made to be read. "Little Miss Sunshine" has much work of script, dialogues and characters triangulation, about it works this movie. Use a lot of sub-plots to move a main plot "must lead to this girl in the competition".The screenwriter Michael Arndt, knows this very well. And mounts its structure on these relationships, doing something quite frantic trip. These characters live on the verge of their own lives. The script is to study it, its structure and frames, regardless of the moral content or not having. It is a rounded script, as the of "the Fisher King". Work a script so frantic about family relationships is very difficult, you have to have very good characters to make it work. I imagine that Mr Ardnt had to spend hours writing the lives of each one of them, trying to it were interesting and consistent, and thinking that it was going to put everyone in a van to make a long trip. I had to have much material so that it does not aburriese. And it gets more than. It gives a lesson in how to write.The movie is fun but sometimes something ñoña, which you forget and forgive as the rest.Greg Kinnear is one of his best roles, and Steve Carrell this huge in her role as suicidal mad homosexual.Alan Arkin is another issue. It is a lesson of what it is to act.Abigail Breslin, the girl, makes it great in a role that, contrary to what it seems, is quite difficult. Playing a thousand million times better than the backward mental of Jennifer Hudson in "Dreamgirls".Everything is going to hell, he is very pessimistic, but unlike many movies, it gives a positive vision of pessimism.The directors are two, a couple from the videoclip, which here forget paraphernalia to give us a good story.Then say that here the people will not see Spanish film by the budget of our movies. I don't think that "Little Miss Sunshine" was very expensive. Only esque tien a great script, unlike the vast majority of our movies that are antifísicas.This script is internal action, but physical movement. You should learn from it Spaniards and Argentines, and stop doing so extremely boring movies.</body>
</review>
