<review author="Tyler" title="Una canción del pasado" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a little slow, but not boring, needs attention and accept this leisurely pace to enjoy.</summary>
	<body>A film like this it often happens what happened. Pass something unnoticed when they should not.They belong to this genre drama, something acid, who tries to recover some lost customs of the cinema of yesteryear type "Mas Dura will be the fall". Beware, not ataqueis, not compare them, only say that share that tone or that intend to recover that tone. Several things happen you to "A song of the past". It is a little slow, but not boring, needs attention and accept this leisurely pace to enjoy. On the other hand need to pace dramatic because in part the story goes that nationally. The passage of time and the use we make of it. Waiting.The thing goes a girl, Pursy Will (Scarlett Johansson), which receives a call that his mother has died. The chavalita in question long ago that happens by his native house which, in theory, has received in heritage. Arriving at New Orleans (city film like the most) discover that there are two installed characters that tell that the housing, his mother, also was left to them are two friends in the House, which is nearly sunk. My colleagues are a pair of Alcoholics; a former Professor of literature of dyed hair and an aspiring writer.The best of the movie lies in the character of Travolta, although it sounds cliché is true, that inpregna his role as a pathetic, powerful and overwhelming personality at the same time. You really think that such is the case. as well of worship and so useless, with your fingernail on the verge of rot. We also have the opportunity to see him singing and dancing. Sing a cappella with a guitar to the same plays very well. Travolta remains one of the finest actors of his generation and is still a very young voice.What I wanted to say with the tone of the movie is that it is very Orn, and believe that the only one in the movie that understood that acidity been Travolta, because the rest and interpreters are limited to do something very typical, following his performances you can imagine an end as the one who has, that may be the great failure of the tape. Through the interpretations of others you can imagine that there will be hope at the end, and that's where this script fails think I. If for the character of Travolta and, above all, the tone it gives you; the terminaria of much more dry and cruel movie, as you should be. While pedia looked screaming by my himself that this movie left me bad body. But in the end the "America" is the "America" and they are a family and maybe want to. That makes the story, in my opinion, lose lot of force.The city leaves precious because it is beautiful. I think that New Orleans is one of the cities more kinetic. "JFK" 0 "Human target" attest.A movie something failed in some things, good view, enjoyable. With good dialogues and a very enlarged development. A boot that, that Yes, it portends a movie good and hard.</body>
</review>
