<review author="Tyler" title="La cosecha" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is boring and predictable, and above you eja a final open to a sequel that not is if it will be. The success of the movie was not at all expected.</summary>
	<body>Really expected me a director as Stephen Hopkins, who made movies as great as "Predator 2" or "Fly por los Aires" gave us a movie, although it was somewhat more effective.The theme of the movie is uninteresting, is something that everybody heard talk: Biblical plagues. Above they don't stop repeat it to you in the movie, and this makes get bored, because you are continually saying that it will happen then, and you know that it comes. then you think "well, alomejor is in the as tell it me", but neither, because the realization of Hopkins in this film is absolutely flat. Hillary Swank does not seem to have much éxto despite his two Oscar, gives the impression, perhaps erroneous, for that is not consolidated as "Star". Still, his interpretation is the more notable of the film. He does with his character can, and he gives something of interest. Even the special efecctos work, are of more plastic. The blood is not credible and rare strange visions. It is as if a vague malaise nothing advisable in this kind of films it produce in the Viewer. It's funny, because the make-up of FX are responsible to the genius who made this peliculón is "Abuerto Hasta el Amanecer", Greg Niccotero.Nunca know that really will the movie, if it is about pests or find a lost girl. The horror film uses too much lately on the subject of children. one is tired, embucha of children. Here the girl is that of "A bridge to Terabithia", with the face of "the small premium which announces Plystation makes some años2.." not be if the remember.It is boring and predictable, and above you eja a final open to a sequel that not is if it will be. The success of the movie was not at all expected.A few years ago that reaches us horror movies produced by Joel Silver, who regained his super Empire thanks to the "Matrix" trilogy. Recently he founded a subproductora to finance terror fils. "House on Haunted Hill", "13 ghosts". None of them very successfully with the exception of the pitch which was the first.If there is something that can highlight, is the time in which a number of moths accidentes attacked a House. It is a rather comical moment as how you look. It is a version with the end of "The birds" bugs... most own a comedy than a movie would be. To my me more pegaria that scene in an ochentera movie type "Ghostbusters", that for ICLS, we should wait for the third installment, this time without Bill Murray (shit!) and the magnificent Ben Stiller starting as his son.</body>
</review>
