<review author="Andrés" title="Plan oculto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The director Gets the way: makes a tape of gender while continuing to crush us with four ideas that has had since he took a camera</summary>
	<body>I have the fact of seeing this film at one of those rare occasions where friends are in agreement to go to the movies. In this case it was more strange because, despite having been accompanied by, I had to see the movie only. "The feast of the goat", which I had already seen was winning in the choice of the group. Then chose "The perfect plan" or "Inside man" (2005) as who makes time. It was not very convinced, because the previous "stalk" of the director ("A Spike Lee Joint"), "She hates me" (2004) I was disappointed and the trailer of "The hidden plan" I smelled film commissioned. After five minutes I realized that was completely wrong. To begin "The hidden plan" it is a very entertaining film, this makes any subsequent comments pure rhetoric. This tape will attest to the quality of "make us-forget-of-all" sometimes has the film. Who does not like the suspense? Well well, here the old Spike offers a concentrated stock of suspense from the start. The admirable is that, in addition, the director Gets the way: makes a tape of gender while continuing to crush us with four ideas that has had since he took a camera. The film begins when "the thief more skull of the world" (Clive Owen) tells us that he has the perfect plan to Rob a Bank and that what we hear well because he will not explain it twice. A minute later: he and his band have all customers and staff of the Bank in the face against the floor. However, what starts here is a war of brains. Criminals, police officers and others put in the game to prove who is the most vivid. The first big idea: criminals force all hostages to dress like them and release a few. Police, baffled, believed to be part of the band and spends his life questioning them. Meanwhile the Bank owner call Madeline (Jodie Foster), "the most cunning dog of the city", so it rescue a dirty washcloth hidden in the Bank bobeda. But Keith (Denzel Washington), the detectivo in charge of the case, will not leave any woman come to mandonearlo and begins to put the batteries. Cops and robbers is striving to prove which side are the best neurons. Secret negotiations, hidden microphones, misleading recordings, implausible claims, anything goes to stay as the smart guy. And the most fun, all this sprinkled with fine Street humour of Spike Lee, this ingenuity that would leave without words to any criollazo.In the course of the film, as diluting a syrup in this soup of suspense, Spike makes us we traguemos some spoonfuls of its political message. New York no longer that racist, violent and unscrupulous mishmash. A city, as say Vallejo, populated by "embracing wolves". The tripping, partnerships and the insults that circulate between the protagonists are simply symptoms of their daily struggle to stay with the largest meat piece. Large fish or fish small, black hand or white collar, commit their peccadilloes to progress. And this is what has always been so roast to final Spike.Al of both functions I found with my friends. They also had liked his film. Comments, comparisons and weights on the way to the place where we llenaríamos us the stomach. We both like the film and then welcome is the mayonnaise.</body>
</review>
