<review author="Tyler" title="Los amantes del círculo polar" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film by Medem has no pace, it is corny, amanerado, forced, long, silly and boring. Nobody believed those so stupid characters.</summary>
	<body>Well, consideration for this (sorry) Basque director is well known Spanish in our country.If you look at his filmography will be an absolute obsession is his person for being "different", as that which is called "original". None of his movies is conventional or tries to be, quite the contrary, his filmography is a huge pretentiousness. An intention to draw attention to and talk about the world and change it. By that his movies are like pieces of life and analysis of the human psyche. Pretentious that can reach this director is incredible.The film that we are talking about, "The lovers of the Polar circle" is possibly one of the most boring, pretentious, stupid and pretentious history movies.Without a storyline, it shows different moments in the life of Otto and Ana, since that they are small until they are older. There is no history, only moments. without ningñun kind of plot or momentum. He is and do you interesting with many jumps in time "because it", without any reason. The thing of telling a story in non-chronological order is all very well, but has to be about something. look at Tarantino, Nolan, Ritchey. his movies are jumps in time reasoned by own narrative of the story. It has to be counted as well to have a complete sense. "Perfect robbery", "Countess barefoot". films that do what they do because they have to do. The film by Medem has no pace, it is corny, amanerado, forced, long, silly and boring. Nobody believed those so stupid characters. It's like a movie about "Cool". The movie does not know where to start, has no approach or conclusion, tries to be, by the way, an exercise in novedosidad. Medem is of these managers who believe that being original is the most important thing. In the film there is no rules... breaking them is good, look for new things. No friend, the film is something much more closed. At the time of writing there are things that are going to mass. And this is the case.A script that you can remove and put things and does not change anything. It is as if it weren't on anything. Or you discover anything or not. Medem is believed to be the most important thing tell at the moral level, and fills the tape of quotations, phrases and existential talks that lead nowhere. Anything physical happens.A failed movie. boring and nonsense, I'll take the words of Carlos Boyero (with which I am not always agree) "is a pseudorománica bullshit".</body>
</review>
