<review author="Tyler" title="Dogville" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is a very physical thing... film is Sam Peckimpah, Andy Warhol.... the film isn't so you can see it. Corny metaphors and the dejemoslas aside videocreations.</summary>
	<body>I'm not really very objective to speak of someone like Lars Von Trier. Personally I think that you one of the most terrible filmmakers in the history of the cinema. I think that it makes a film so stupid that even should be no case. "Not even for bad.""Dogville" is not that it will. It is the bullshit elevated to the cube of the pretentiousness. It is the nonsense of a sort of videoartísta who believes Dios.Desde the principle one realizes. This girl comes to this abnormal pa people hide from some gangsters. There they her putean. Listo.Lo of the people is pa to eat separately. Esque thing that there is nothing at all and I I have to imagine seems to me an insult to the Viewer. Making us believe that it is an artistic appeal that look at actors, as has done it to make it as a book (which us us us imagine. buah) and that is a metaphor about the modern world and blah blah blah.Please. We must be serious. The movie cannot be more bad although it tried. Nicole is not of my devotion and here shows his coldness as the puteada Grace.Didn't ever know what happened, and I get nervous everytime I see someone manipulate something that does not exist. When I see these broods painted on the floor without any reason more than save paste to give the Kidman.No any good Von Trier movie I remember. only an argument that was funny... of "Epidemic"... then is a suckling pig.Lars Von Trier also made a second part that I've refused to see, among other things because he made that they killed, really, a burrito during filming. Just as Almodovar when he "Talk with Ella" (another crappy). Von Trier replaced actress claiming that "you want a Grace that is different in each part of the trilogy", because esque is also a trilogy!The film is a very physical thing. the film is Sam Peckimpah, not Andy Warhol... the film is so you can see it. Corny metaphors and the dejemoslas aside videocreations.I am not saying that it is a video creation. what I say esque is not film. It is ottra thing. "Dogville" rejected the film. the film is set of long ago, and if we reduce the film to its minimal essence we have two very simple elements, time and space. Everything comes from there. You play with those two elements. It is the only thing that is. And "Dogville" rejects them both to give a progressive propaganda speech heard a thousand times and that it is boring. The film first and foremost, rather than lecturing or have moral cavities or move or Excite. you would not get bored. Then say what you want, but complies with the rules. "Dogville" does nothing.</body>
</review>
