<review author="Paula Zurita" title="Borrachera de poder" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is too long. It is interesting and entertaining, but there comes a time where you the viewer want to end.</summary>
	<body>This film is perhaps the story of what we are accustomed to read in the press or see in the news. Entrepreneurs and politicians discovered more low and vicious actions. Malaya, in a certain way, would be a version impaired, although real, what you describe Chabrol. Does do, however, the director of the? French new wave?, looking for a film inspired by all and a none. And why in the beginning does not hesitate to emphasize that any resemblance to reality is only a coincidence. But Chabrol transcends the evidence and tries to discover the two parties involved in the game of Justice: the official and the res judicata. Judge Jean Charmant, starring Isabelle Huppert, investigates a case of economic corruption in a major business group. While discover information and will unravel the axes of action of officials, its success and its labour power increase. However, he gradually left his private life.In the 105 minutes lasting film, Claude Chabrol wishes to show the two sides of a reality. The conflict does not end with the accused. Chabrol experiment a little further and analyzes the behavior of an official who is also embedded power. Somehow, the director wants to demonstrate the power to catch anyone that SBI holding it for a few seconds between his hands.Jean Charmant, the judge is a woman of fragile and delicate appearance, qualities that fade with his strong character. Sometimes his attitude rubs with the cruel when he interrogates the poor Humeau, one of the accused. Judge removes up to the last detail: the clothes you saw the lover of the accused, the construction of a swimming pool, expenditures on hotels and fruit trees, in short, the public money used as its own. The judge, however, everytime it delves into his research, losing part of his private life. It only maintains a close relationship with Felix, the nephew of her husband, that, although everything remains an ambiguous relationship. Her husband, for his part, Philippe is relegated relegated from the life of the judge from the beginning, unless it decides to call the attention with a suicide attempt. But Jean Charmant is so blinded by his role and position that behaves in a distant way.In short, Chabrol shines in the relationships between the characters. Each one is so intense that it needs time to describe them. By the same token, the film is too long. It is interesting and entertaining, but there comes a time where you the viewer want to end.</body>
</review>
