<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Cache Escondido" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is deception, the end and Cape. Haneke dominates the medium of film, but mocks a spectator who manipulates with style. The film is at the end, after handling.</summary>
	<body>Intellectuals, in France, are legion, are a few heroes, are admirable, respected. The Gallic intellectual he relieves the mundane with a Stakhanovite work routines and proletarian commitment and he deals in a microphone or gives a column to live free of the beauties of the vulgar and on that altar despotrique with dispassion against the discourse of the social, the political plot and forms of culture. The protagonist of this film, Georges Laurent, superbly played by Daniel Auteil, is that hero: the character that does not construct his life under the avatar of the epic to the classic mode, but escalafona in society as the Warrior of yesteryear and occupies an irreplaceable place, the place of the critic. That, in Spain, is still unthinkable. France, in terms of secularism in these fringes of culture, leads forty years ahead.Haneke, director, is one critic: one that has arrobado the public disclosure of political correctness bass which pulsate, bitter, lies, disasters, miseries and barbaric of varied coat.Haneke is a fable about the hostility of the welfare State, a moral tale about the fragility of this Europe of alliances and pacts fragmented by imperatives too powerful local, represented by a man of letters, a well-known intellectual that warns how something or someone filmed you and sent the tapes of that recording. That feeling of being spied produces a series of foreseeable consequences, but one misses the logic, which is the one that supports the bulk of the plot of the film. Laurent begins to seriously question his life to the point of inquire with calling cuasidetectivesca on its own existence on its own past. Yours is the past of France since the World War II pre-feed wounds of centuries of resignations and social fractures.Incorporated in a flamboyant design of thriller, cache exhibits a more than convincing domain of narrative. The plot is opening new frames and certainly closing others. However, the degree of suspense is abruptly aborted.It is not possible to liven up a film of this political depth without that trade concessions, at times, seem too light. As if Haneke knew that it should reduce the doctrinal and apocalyptic tone and allow scraps of sanity, fresh aires, kites that fly the hope of redemption. Language, overly elliptical, fragmented, as a broken post, forced to take a very active position in the viewing of the film: fiction and reality, the traditional instruments of literary composition, is engarzán here added formidably.The tapes are traps of the real ideological pumps that dinamitan the placid book life of a marriage entirely functional, integrated and, above all, Yorick shielded to the rigors of the reality. When the protection mechanisms are disabled, life becomes thriller, adopts nuances of pure suspense and ends, bound and stubbornly, questioning the true nature of the human soul, which connects the banal with the tragic, the strictly cultural with the pathological.The film closes without closing it: proposes everything without giving valid solutions. There is a sense of deception. The film is deception, the end and Cape. Haneke dominates the medium of film, but mocks a spectator who manipulates with style. The film is at the end, after handling.</body>
</review>
