<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Premonition (Siete días)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good idea, in a very bad result. Sandrita, pretty, dedicate yourself to the romantic comedies of those that so much like my wife, because the truth is that in this type of film sobras.</summary>
	<body>I have almost 20 min. sitting in front of the keyboard to write this criticism, bad is when I feel so, and begin to remolonear, thinking that writing, and is that "Premonition" (not confused with the film of the same name directed by Sam Raimi), is an idea well intended but poorly executed, and is that the opera prima Mennan Yapo, it is rather weaker than one expects to find a priori on screen; I do not know, maybe is that I have so much time thinking about conspiracies "Judeo-Masonic" one when he sees something strange on the screen never think that they will give cat by Hare, for love to take in cats and with those who share life and home for several weeks...But I'm not by the branches, the tape of Sandra Bullock, lacks sense of narrative, and is that, trying to follow a path that already marked tapes "unsorted" as "Memento" or "21 grams", here the only disorder lies in how live the character of "bullock" days, and is that once we learn the rules of the game just the grace of the tapeseparate mention is their tramposidad and little artifice in showing us, again I repeat, an idea embodied in the script was nothing short of brilliant.Bullock makes his character, like Julian Mcmahon little credible (and is that everytime I see this man I remember "The fantastic four" and lose seriously.), to which translate as usual in it, and you join the crusade that not help you nor the mother who gave you birth.It needed a paragraph separately by its end, laughable, little developed and quite helpings, and it is that, (I repeat I), after be throwing meat to the grill during much of the footage, one expects the fireworks at the end, and meets a small firecracker, which tramposamente hidden on screen, just does damage when it explodes.Sandrita, pretty, dedicate yourself to the romantic comedies of those that so much like my wife, because the truth is that in this type of film sobras.</body>
</review>
