<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Domino" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Telefilm loose budget which does not deserve to be included in the Filmography of this man. Finally and after he made the fire of revenge and the great red tide. Love at point-blank range on my altar of weaknesses, occupies a prominent place.</summary>
	<body>It has already opened the Circus: pass, see, sit, enjoy the Vertigo and out conveniently discounted concerns, manumitidos stubborn routine machinery, comfortably installed in the deception. Cinema has always been a fabulous factory of deception. There are films that produce a greater certainty that the lie has occupied our senses and that, in the end, we have swallowed a tremebundo roll, a playful Epiphany of fireworks, a three-dimensional celebration of noise. This is Tony Scott, a magician of the noise. Below late, sharp, the fury, the pulse of a director too often ninguneado, but vigilant jealous of an ancestral form of making films, the show a hypnotic spectacle, a real party of barracks of fair. Its suggestive images Fireworks is still luxurious, but then nothing is left or is so little time, severe judge, just deleting profiles (first) and those dazzling images (later).Scott is a Baroque author, but his hyperbolic warp of concepts and forms not seduces as I would like or as his talent would suspect because the film of this director is a tiresome, very lyrical wit sobreimpregnado, Yes, but become the abuse in a parody in a cartoon not reaching the grotesque, although round it and is not difficult to predict that drowned therein to the satisfaction absolute for the Legion of fans who has eventually.Many shots, the abundant load of adrenaline, light eroticism and the frenetic sense of rhythm make Domino a work one hundred percent Tony Scott. The history of the eventful life of Domino Harvey suits this tsunami of technical tricks, of aesthetic videoclipera of pop resonance. Writes Richard Kelly, writer of the cult of Donnie Darko tape, but what attracts is the psychedelic movement of the camera, that seems touched by the numen of the mescaline put the protagonists. Mickey Rourke wins the admiration of the owner of the seat because it's credible: more by his look of pimp with bad milk that for its efforts to make us see that there is still an actor inside your brain crushed by boxing and narcotic drugs.Christopher Walken is Christopher Walken which is nothing new, but we thank him always. This accelerated biopic should be viewed with complete lack of cinematographic requirements: as a disk of the ear of Van Gogh hear when we have already been in Dark Side of the Moon. I don't know if I can explain. There is time for everything. If not there, should waive the gentle reader of this excessive exercise of ego kept.</body>
</review>
