<review author="José A. Peig" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An irregular film, designed to be a bridge to the next episode, and this is a setback that condemns the project to be a mere transition without greater bellows.</summary>
	<body>It is something that happens in most major productions of cinema of evasion, and here we like to stress it often: create a universe to screen mode or mirror in which the viewer can see reflected, that these fantasy worlds are an idealised projection of our own experience of reality. I.e., that the heroes that live in these fantastic worlds are a reflection of the best that we could become, or what we are, but materialized in the sphere of the idyllic, taking advantage of the playful game of adventure. Evil can be represented in many ways and can point to various obscure aspects of the human condition or the society in which we live. Whether Sauron (the Lord of the rings) or Darth Vader (Star Wars), are equally archetypal representations that we refer to our psyche and our real world. a world in which things are never so simple. We said that "The curse of the Black Pearl" is one of these living spaces for fantasy, both by the brilliant visual embodiment the right configuration of characters and history, creating an atmosphere of myth, legend Buccaneer which justified itself by the own rules implicit in its texture. In dead man's chest, we have a clear attempt to expand that universe with new characters and plot stunts although on this occasion the lush imagery in the design, art direction and intentional shantytowns surrounding to the history and iconography of evil prevail. Unfortunately, in this case it does not reach the right balance between resources plastic and narrative strength, dramatic tones and bufonesco spirit that animates it from its original purpose. Or, in short, you cannot find a point which reconciles the pure evasion drawn with firm and credible hand - always laudable - striving to be original. It is not easy to face the criticism of this second installment of the Pirates of the Caribbean trilogy (trilogy or series?). For their successes in the design and creation of atmospheres and the effort to create a story that goes beyond the predictable "hard" stolen to the classics of the genre (especially Indiana Jones and Star Wars classic trilogy), it's a very strange and fascinating film as failed and disjointed. History: the argument still stressing about historical events that mark the development of the present, and along these lines, the cava history deeper in the expansion of the universe pirate and introduces us to the King of the seas, captain David Jones, a sort of demon who administers and controls the flow of objects and the souls of the pirates. In fact, Jones played the role of the God of this universe configured in the two films filmed and released to date. The design and characterization of the crew of the Flying Dutchman has a power of fascination that connects with old myths of literature and cinema, as Captain Nemo, Dracula, John Silver or Darth Vader himself. That David Jones to mid-way between cruelty and melancholy (the scene in which he is playing the organ with desperate, unforgettable Fury), this ghostly ship which is found in the depths of the sea and that rises to the surface as if from a sea monster is involved. an evocative and sinister atmosphere that surrounds an enigmatic character: he only we know that it controls all the flow of pirate life on the seas, but we cannot say that he is the villain of the piece. Her love blue eyes, in contrast to the cruelty displayed at other times, configured the best romantic representation of what it is and has always been a fascinating profile of the pirate: free, solo, and in this case, a prisoner of his own love story, anchored in the past. and a pulsating heart hidden in a chest. Anyone possessing the casket, will take control of the Sea (will be owner, therefore, of the world created in the film representation). Love and power are part of a continuum of relationships, causes and effects. The lyricism and Poetics on the personality of David Jones and his chest are one of the best advantages of the tape, original, playing with the icons and the theme of the genre with a clear intention already seek something that almost no one remembers and up we think a cursilada: beauty. Yes, beauty. The noble attempt to provide the circus of absurdities and Visual effects of an romántica-onírica epic. It succeeds only halfway, but there it is. David Jones is not the villain of the piece, in the context and intent of the work. Let us not forget that "Pirates of the Caribbean" is an exaltation humorous by the idealized figure of the pirate, the closure of the previous delivery was a tribute to that profile uprooted and immoral. Thus, if in this saga pirates - all without exception - are the "good guys", the bad is to be found in an antagonistic profile, and this profile is Lord Beckett, spokesman representative of the law and the new illustrated order of 18th century (following the game to the pseudo historical pamphlet), which, at any given time, said something very important: that someone like Jack Sparrow has no place in this new order that no region of the world will be free control and the influence of the modern power. And attention to the huge clock that adorns the bottom of the level, which contrasts the mechanistic laws disorganized life of the pirate. Upcoming new times, and not there is place for pirates. Beckett pursues the extinction of the pirates, so need the heart of David Jones "King of the seas". Jack Sparrow need chest to save his own skin because of the old debts, Will Turner to free his father and Commodore to recover the lost prestige. In short, David Jones, as Dios-Demonio of the seas, is the center of a plot too main in wanting to give turns to the same and to create questions that serve as a bridge to the third installment, so the narrative too often becomes thick, but simple stretches unnecessarily and the result is a quite inferior to "The curse of the Black Pearl" product. The poetic personality, attributes, characters and the history of David Jones as profile agglutinating of love, the cruelty, pain and power, multiple evocations profile perfectly vertebrate with the set, because he is the center of gravity (the reason) around which revolve the exploits of the protagonists, this poetic is the aspect-as we pointed out previously-depths of the filmwhich it gives beauty and epic force, and it is also the most unnoticed aspect for most of the public, but you'll gain understanding with future revisions, as David Jones has the flavor of a classic, adding to the list headed by Sparrow in this extravagant saga in charismatic characters. Johny Deep repeats the same ambiguous, extravagant and buffoonish interpretation so good result gave in the previous installment. But if something was disappointed the tape, is non-existent progression from a scheme that is already given. That is, that if you do a sequel or continuation in which you return on the same characters, you must add them to legitimize new dimension, artistically speaking, the existence of the sequel and so allow a progressive character to the saga (eye to the canon of teachers: "the Empire strikes back", perfect example of innovative sequel, with characters that move towards psychological fields just outlined in its predecessor). Sparrow does the same thing that in the previous, the same gestures, the same antics, same situations, same resolution in extreme situation. There is no progression: the nobility arose at the last moment, when he decides to return to the Black Pearl to help his friends. Here it seems that the writers want to highlight their morale over the anarchy, but at that point, as we say, neither surprised nor adds nothing new. Elizabeth Swann, ditto; the maid of blue blood which, at the last moment, becomes a genuine pirate. Orlando Bloom, in classic plan, emulating Errol Flyn, but the poor have less expressiveness that one table. He is the greater burden that has been dragging the saga of pirates. And since a Prism more generally, it should be noted the irregularity as a whole of a film which first and foremost want to be film show. The problem comes when a production of this type you want to add a darker, as in this sequel to Pirates of the Caribbean. The truth is that it is not easy to combine and combine the playful spirit of adventure disneyana that worked so well in "The curse of the Black Pearl" - despite their sinister dyes - with a Baroque style that frames a story that, from now on, longer wants to take too seriously itself. The first delivery was a funny legend of ghosts that flowed in equilibrium with itself, here is an often disproportionate Cirque who tries to live with poetic and far-reaching claims. It is not only a tale of ghosts, is an epic about the struggle for control of the sea, love and hatred, the anarchy of the pirate universe against the enlightened order which Beckett intends to impose. That mixture between circus and dramatic epic ends not curdle the desired effect: Entertainment from beginning to end in a spirit of epic the eternal theme of the struggle for power. The writers complicated life wanting to introduce and explain too much, raise too many enigmas, submitting to too many characters. Result?. You have already said: the narration is not smooth but thick, and "The curse of the Black Pearl" was almost continuous entertainment, here the fluidity and freshness go to catch-up. When Sparrow or David Jones will disappear from the scene, the film loses many points. So there can be a great entertainment without an appropriate structure that expose the history clearly. The plot and the history of "Dead man's chest" are more than interesting, even has implied a genuine poetic (attention to the heart of metal that Jones keeps together with the body of their sorrows, or the compass that indicates the path of the wishes or the ghostly silhouette of a female dress that feeds the superstition of the Buccaneers) but can be quite confusing and unbalanced in its submission. On occasions one poetic, funny and sinister, others show a circus grotesque and excessive, "Dead man's chest" is an uneven film, designed to be a bridge to the next episode, and that's a setback that condemns the project to be a mere transition without greater bellows. Which does not mean that the tape has the sufficient - evocative by the rightness of his characterization - elements so, returning to the thread of the home, the pirate universe of Verbinski and Bruckheimer copper life of its own once more with style and ability to suggestion. </body>
</review>
