<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Xmen3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entretenidilla without more, in part due to its limited duration, but disappointing and far below the previous two series</summary>
	<body>"X-Men 3: the decision Final" (X-Men 3: The Last Stand) proposes an interesting premise: a pharmaceutical company has managed to create a serum that, injected into the blood of a mutant, he is able to make him a normal human. This will trigger a doubt among the mutants around the world: live a normal life or accept as they are.As I say, it is an interesting premise; the problem is that it is just one of the plot lines of the film. They have decided, moreover, address one of the sagas more mythical and complex history of the X-Men: the dark Phoenix saga. All this without forgetting the treatment of a number of parallel stories as the birth of El Ángel (Ben Foster), the relationship ice man-Pícara, the Phoenix-Código-Wolverine relationship, the return of the beast (Kelsey Grammer) or the growing leadership of storm in the team. Too many fronts would require a brilliant script to resolve them all. And unfortunately the script far from being brilliant.Because of this excess of claims we have characters who do not paint anything and arriving to disappear from the action, as by magic, you can to avoid the problem of not knowing what to do with them in the scenes end (still the problem becomes clear). In fact I think that purists will be the hands to the head to see how important characters in the comic are here so blurred that his appearance has no other function which serve for the showcasing of the Department of Visual effects and to be able to say that they appear in the film.It is curious that my great fear during the development process of the film was that the director was Brett Ratner. Once seen the film I have to admit that the blame for the outcome perhaps not theirs at all, but the script. I am sure that a director with more personality clear had been forced to Polish the script until it would be much better. On the other hand the Mise en scene of Ratner is purely functional; correct, Yes, but devoid of brilliance while in some scenes their lack of expertise see makeup on the excellent work of the team of Visual effects that allow us to see storm (Halle Berry), to Fenix (Famke Janssen) or Magneto deploy all its power (especially the latter two).On the side positive note the charisma of Hugh Jackman as Wolverine, who asks shouting a movie for him only (hopefully her lead someone better than Ratner), Patrick Stewart as Professor X and Ian McKellen as Magneto. I do not fail to mention the wonderful soundtrack of John Powell; author which raises points every day.In short, a film entretenidilla without more, in part due to its limited duration, but disappointing and far below the previous two series. As curiosity and notice to potential viewers comment that the movie just after the closing credits (although that scene might have been spared).</body>
</review>
