<review author="Silvia Giner" title="El niño de barro" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a horror film as perhaps he has claimed at some point but rather of suspense and drama. This is the 4th film of Algora and I believe that it is the most effective of all.</summary>
	<body>Jorge Algora from Argentina brings us a story that chronicles the events that happened on the "Petiso Orejón" reached become a legend of terror among children as here could be "The coconut" or "The man in the sack".Inspired in real fact, we enter in Buenos Aires in 1912 when a series of brutal murders children is prpopaga by the city. Mateo (Juan Ciancio), a 10-year-old boy, has a strange quality: sometimes your mind leads him to a dark place of the memory where is witness to the murders.It is not a horror film as perhaps he has claimed at some point but rather of suspense and drama. This is the 4th film of Algora and I think that it is the most effective of all, although I think that some stuff has been left in the dark.For example, if we look at the poster of the film there are two things that call attention powerfully a "Child of clay" is title of the film and the other is the motto "the evil has 10 years", both may resemble a sinsetido simplevista, but it has its explanation (see my story on the press pass), although for my has been rather a poor marketing strategy.Another thing to keep in mind is the more obvious like the character of Maribel Verdú that played in "El laberinto del fauno" Although sicneramente for me are identical and she insists that they are completely different. We must also take into account that the interpretation of the Argentine cast is incredibly good, but my there is something of this film that does not fit me and it does not end by believe me history and pisses me off because I recognize that the work of Chete Lera, Daniel Freire (aka the penis of Lucia and sex) and the indescribably beautiful Juan Ciancio is muyyy goodis perhaps the contrast with Maribel which I don't like. Eye that Maribel itself always liked, but perhaps in this role, it is something contained, lacks it claw.For me there is a great film, but a film you must see (premiered in cinemas on May 18). What is clear is that for Jorge Algora is an important jump and perhaps this is one contribution to eliminate chronic boredom that suffers the Spanish film.</body>
</review>
