<review author="JLO" title="Alejandro Magno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He was accused of too long when the short life of the conqueror would give, at least, for a miniseries.</summary>
	<body>All features always vital Oliver Stone film are delineated in the monumental - in every sense - Alexander the great (only Alexander in the original). That Yes, it is a "anesthetized" Stone. The camera nervous and self-centered that characterizes his style and praising "smaller" films but valuable as killers by nature and way without return, conspicuous by their absence.Alexander is a logical choice for an adept filmmaker to the great biopics: JFK, Nixon, The Doors, Larry Flynt, Commander. If we add to these filmic dating others of the value of platoon and born on July 4, the rejection that generates your film becomes incomprehensible critical. Grandiose? Pedantic? It is not the film that same?It begins in the 323 before Christ, telling the life of the Conqueror of 90% of the then known world. Historians say that Alexander was so great, that the conquests of Julius Caesar or a Napoleón are reduced to "a short walk in the Park". Reading makes Stone is historically correct, but in appearance, is done without passion. They are unusual sensitivity to the time of Alexander and his excessive ambition, but not his gift of command and its animal ferocity. The battles are bland, dull and unclear, seem to be a mere pretext that fail to save a very good montage. American critique her shattered unjustifiable - leaving aside the policy by Oliver on Fidel Castro - still fresh documentary reasons. He was accused of too long when the short life of the conqueror would give, at least, for a miniseries. The voiceover of the Hopkins character is needed by the amount of events narrated, if not everything would lose clarity. I will not refer to the problematic homosexual so much commotion caused in the North, because it would delay twenty years. Beyond them. Of course it has faults. Olympia (does Jolie Farrel MOM?) never aging, the music of Vangelis is unbearable by the cheesy and by highlight "serious" scenes, Val Kilmer seems a whim of the director (what weighs?), the film loses strength at the end and we arrived at his big, big mistake: Alexander is a character too big for the three gestures of Colin Farrel.El human profile of the hero, the scene of his wound next to his horse and an elephant, the inclusion at the wrong time of the death of his father, his photography and visual richness, rescued Alexander of mediocrity and her located in an imaginary space defined by Spartacus in its roof, but higher than the contemporary and subvaloradas Troy, Gladiator and 300.</body>
</review>
