<review author="JLO" title="Star Wars Episodio III" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If one is not a fan of the series, or not wallows with small details of continuity between films, it is difficult to be deliver the enjoyment of a film at times bland, impossible to stand on its own.</summary>
	<body>Star Wars was, and is, a phenomenon like few others in today's world of the film Trilogies (comparable only to Mr. of the rings). Returns the factory of George Lucas (filmmaker if not mediocre, the less uneven) industry go &amp; Magic creator, with the famous sequels (or calls now prequels) of his saga rompe lockers, which generate a legion of fans mas grande at every step.He had to see ingeniaba them Lucas to surprise us, knowing that the storyline of his series was already defined in advance (the step of Anakin to the dark side), the birth of twins Skywalker, etc.. But it does not. Perhaps the achievement of Episode III is the be the mejorcita of prequels them. Too little.Visually stunning, scenes strung from the beginning as a kind of infinite necklace of fights, swath clean and everyone in a new arena ever more spectacular (simile video game), with much color but with little emotion. Hayden Christensen (Anakin) continues to do what they can (which is very little). The omnipresent music of John Williams flooded all of triviality, as well as dialogues (error already quite repeated in the series) and a story of a dramatic simplicity, spent and which taken as a whole, can never be told in six! films. The expected conversion of Anakin in Darth Vader (that Yes, one of the best characters in fiction in the history of the cinema) is resolved only by a fear of dubious taste and pulled their hair. Its presence is also reduced at last - and few - minutes of the film.If one is not a fan of the saga, or not wallows with small details of continuity between films, it is difficult to be deliver the enjoyment of a film at times bland, impossible to stand alone without this Galactic fable which in its first parts (the old), I had a certain poetry and idealism naif. And that in the latter - primarily Episode II - stained political issues, violence and a single value: the so famous "force" is the greed of power at all costs, both the "good" and "bad". Too similar to the real world.</body>
</review>
