<review author="JLO" title="Hable con ella" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mañosa, passionate, provocative, delirious, sentimental, brilliant, excessive, emotional, cheesy, all descriptions that fit you and define it this both entire Filmography of Pedro Almodóvar.</summary>
	<body>Films of Almodovar - mainly from Attalus I (1989) this part - is always the same and leaves no room for doubt: he loves or hates it. The loas sometimes exaggerated his work, make more widen that gap and siding with one or another option. Today we are facing one of their very good movies, the best meat Trémula, having in common with this male roles and physical impediments of the same and Matador. Talk to her is one of the melodramas to which we are accustomed, although this time with less touches of comedy but with the same characteristics of his film, a recognizable world in which live the sexual with the mundane, the kitsch with random. It's about the birth of the friendship of two men United by the convalescence from his two loves. A journalist (Darío Grandinetti, content) and his ill-fated Bullfighter (Rosario Flores) and on the other hand, a bisexual (Javier Cámara) nurse caring for her ballerina neighbor and platonic love, character in which Almodóvar focused all their phobias and feelings into almost his alter-ego. Intersect other stories love, loneliness, not correspondidos love, all dyeing of a constant and ever-present sexual patina, with backward and forward temporary routes that make fear for continuity but coming afloat with elegance. What the difference of his recent films is that it does not under a strictly feminine look, or guide you its strong female leading, but the aforementioned male. The route - with few low blows but that limits - is entertaining despite its confrontational theme (rape, vegetative life) but without explicit scenes or in bad taste, with something of which to critics of his film will not be able to deny any of his films: well directed, well acted and very emotionally charged from beginning to end.Only in an Almodóvar film (or in one of Woody Allen) can coexist and intermingle without risk of dementia, a collage of diverse more namely: a Spanish singer (Rosario), an Argentine actor, the daughter of Chaplin, Caetano Veloso, dance body (at the beginning and end, that remind you both powerful Aphrodite and Greek choir) etc., etc. Mañosa, passionate, provocative, delirious, sentimental, brilliant, excessive, emotional, cheesy, all descriptions that fit you and define it this both entire Filmography of Pedro Almodóvar. In the should we mention the end, which is ambiguous optimism continued in his later works, closer to hollywood and further away from the same film.</body>
</review>
