<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Tu la letra, yo la música" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Simple but effective comedy that will delight, especially those who still, today, we continue enjoying with the music of the 1970s and 1980s. A fresh degreaser that deserves to be enjoyed without complexes or cultural hampered false.</summary>
	<body>You the lyrics, I music opens with a video-clip in the style of those that were done in the 1980s. In fact, thanks to this funny music video, its Director and screenwriter, Marc Lawrence, recalls and satirizes, unconfessed way and in unison, the universe of Wham!, a British duo of short-lived career and which the popular George Michael was one of its members. The truth is training disbanded when he decided to start his solo career, ruining the future musical of his partner, a such Andrew Ridgeley.Aquellos they lived - as well as a server - explosion pop of the 80s through the television mass in part of them - by that time-are newly born vídeo-clips, will discover in Alex Fletcher - the character played by Hugh Grant — to the unsuccessful Ridgeley of Wham!. In the film, the actor gives life to the aforementioned Fletcher, a singer and songwriter frustrated, which, after live their moments of glory, two decades earlier and as a member of the Pop group dismembered!, will have to swallow quina before the unstoppable success achieved by his old partner of fatigue. Currently, Fletcher earn the living acting, solo, in small teatrillos and amusement parks, places in which offers the four forties captivated in her day, a small repertoire of songs that launched the Pop duo! to fame.From this pathetic character, Marc Lawrence develops a plot simple but effective; a plot that will bring closer the rickety musician the possibility to achieve the success that lost for more than 20 years. And that possibility, will come in the form of musical challenge. A challenged atypical in that involved a couple of women: a young and insecure writer and a provocative and eccentric fashion in full effervescence singer; a character, the latter, to which the viewer will identify with more than one of the female stars of the current Top 10: these clone girls that, always showing his muslamen and suggesting her smooth buttocks, sing similar songs with the same tonality and rhythm.Did not expect much of you the lyrics, I music and, however, succeeded in making me disconnect from the outside world during his footage. His proposal is linear, without surprises or plot twists, but pleasantly enjoyable to follow. As a sentimental comedy works perfectly, despite not contribute anything new to the genre. His dialogues are nice, sparkling, and the chemistry that develops between Hugh Grant and Drew Barrymore exudes true surround tone. He fulfills his role to perfection: the role of Idol dropped, covered even in the 1980s, will of pearls and Moreover, if little, outside shows her good and unexpected gifts as vocalist. And she, Barrymore, is more charming than ever: breaks a bit with his usual roles and through the funny character of the writer Sophie Fisher, transforms into a sort of endearing alter ego of Diane Keaton; but a Keaton of ancient times, just when was funny clown in first-time follies of Woody Allen.Una comedy simple but effective it will delight, especially those who still, today, we continue enjoying with the music of the 1970s and 1980s. A fresh degreaser that deserves to be enjoyed without complexes or cultural hampered false. The ideal product to slow down a little, the demoralizing effect that causes the tiresome and unstoppable invasion of acids and sharp melodramas in the Billboard. I, at least, let me carry and spent a while certainly delicious. And even during their slide, up came to believe (dreamer from me) that, maybe someday, Hugh Grant would be a good actor.</body>
</review>
