<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Yet in order to spend time entertaining, and nothing else, I would cost recommend. But I'm going to do. That Yes, atenganse the consequences. More than one can leave the angry film.</summary>
	<body>I notice from the outset: I am not a fan of the comic or Spidey geek or anything of the sort. You had a lot of sympathy to this saga, I liked the television series when it was small and little else. If you have not seen the film yet, keep not reading. And if you expect a "serious" criticism, either.Spider-Man 3 has been released on records at the box office worldwide. Trailers and the previous films were big incentives for viewers come en masse during the first weekend. In addition, it is the most expensive film in history, so expectations were high.But the end result is, without a doubt, DISAPPOINTING. Thus, in uppercase. The film does not make any sense, the presentation of characters is not only regrettable, but that do not complete fit in history (if it exists). The reactions of the characters are totally unrealistic, the dialogues are almost comedy romantic (that end with the dawn of Fund, by God, only missing a kiss.), and if outside little, visual paragraph offers nothing new, and although it is not bad, the truth is that there are quite a few scenes that note too that the actors are in front of the famous screen green. does what good then? Little. Very very little. Ignoring special effects, only he managed to do it enjoy a comic scene from the movie. Nothing else: no Venom (with the amount of hope that had been deposited in the bad malísimo par excellence), or Sandman (but what crap is that that was who killed the uncle and wants forgiveness from Parker?), or anything. Harry plays a quite stupid (in the line of the second part of the trilogy), Mary Jane behaves like a real bitter selfish, and Peter Parker outbursts that are not kept by any lado.¿Pero who believed what you enter? Let's see. might start with a thousand things. But I'm going to do with the end. A man of sand of thousands of tons of weight is destroying what is its paso.pero there is a girl with his camera, next to his "Mommy", photographing the moment.-"look MOM!" A black bug and a mountain of sand are crushing to our dear Spidey! And all before mine!In addition, on TV you have live, as if it were the most normal thing in the world. And what about Mary Jane? What faces are those when you're trapped in a car, to 80 stories tall, in a giant spider web? If it seems that when they focus it is watching TV on the couch of his home!It seems incredible that it is the same team than in the predecessor films. Why the script does a downturn in quality so brutal? How they intend to us we traguemos phrases such as: "My best friend", "Forgive you", or scenes like the kiss between Spider-man and Gwen Stacy, the bailecito in the kitchen, the club.? And the story of Sandman? Wants the money to his daughter but. There goes! The girl does not appear but the principle! What is doing the rest of the time? Can to feed the pigeons?The problem of Spider-Man 3 is that you not think nothing of what you are telling. And Yes, what I know, it is a movie about a hero of comic and blabla. But you already know that it can find some kind of things, but never a series of nonsense, a film without storyline any. In short, there is no where catch her, and that I love the previous two.Yet in order to spend time entertaining, and nothing else, I would cost recommend. But I'm going to do. That Yes, atenganse the consequences. More than one can leave the angry film, without going into the inconsistencies with the comic, which already gives me equal.PS: Feel Me bad writing this in a series that had predilection. Perhaps it had not been for both. Or Yes?</body>
</review>
