<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Diarios de la calle" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Films of charismatic teacher happens to them as well as passionate lovers. One believes, but at the same time knows that it is better not to return ten years later, with the camera so it could find.</summary>
	<body>"Diaries of the street" is like watching Jack Nicholson taking my kids of HD in a sailboat while Dr. Ratched werecat shouts that it is time to take the medicine. Since the Sydney Poitier taught his dwarves to make a salad at the Institute, the world of cinema has flooded of charismatic teachers who dream of conquering the Immaculate minds of our tender teens. Antonio Banderas it was trying to modestly with the ballroom dancing. Mr Kitting went too far in the club of dead poets. The Forrester of Forrester discovering taught nothing, but served to the kid to hesitation of famous author. Dangerous minds Pfeiffer Michelle is the most similar to the protagonist of this film, because the guys are all about desmelenados offenders, and resolves the issue involved with them. "The least similar to Erin Gruwel Professor is the Mr Chips of Goodbye Mr Chips, because it does not arise as a"pitch"educational, but also as managing a whole life devoted to teaching.""Diaries of the street" is essentially true. Teachers sometimes live situations in occurs them something special, oasis of understanding. Erin Gruwel narrated your oasis in a book which was a collection of the diaries of their students and what we now have in film. He ran the year 94. The revolt of Los Angeles was still alive. Police clubbed to Rodney King and an excessively clemente judge left out in freedom those responsible. The country erupted in flames during a week. This all happened in the same country that wanted to set an example to the world of peaceful coexistence.Erin Gruwel has at that time 23 years old and doesn't know do with a multiracial class that either screams, fights, either or makes pellas when it wants to impose on them where have to sit. There is no communication until a student ridicules a black of the class. Erin responds hablandoles of the nazis and the course starts to listen to. I don't know about that would talk about the American film industry if Hitler would have lost the elections of the 33.La teacher works extra hours to buy them new books. The students are stunned. One smells like yours, smells like new. The topic could be is necessary spend more that pupils be involved? As all the teachers that connect with their students, she has to contend with the conservative sectors who want to do the same as always. His head of language Department opposes: that is doing is not exportable, does not serve as program, is a special relationship that can not be repeated each year. And it is partly right, the relationship with a group can live as something unique and special. But a career means a line of work, a habit which can be repeated every year. The film lives of certain mirages. The films of love always speak of eternal love. It is easy to love forever during one hour and a half. Films of charismatic teacher happens to them as well as passionate lovers. One believes, but at the same time knows that it is better not to return ten years later, with the camera so it could find.</body>
</review>
