<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El niño de barro" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The child of clay is an acceptable product of entertainment, who stays away from the fast-paced and intense psychological thriller that promises publicity.</summary>
	<body>What is it that terror and suspense Spanish that Captivate viewers around the world? Well, it is not really so, since national genre cinema still resisting a very important market, the Spanish. It is ironic that while in United States praise Spanish terror (and no, do not refer to politics or the world of the heart), in Spain the public attends mass see the bloody nonsense of Hollywood.Jorge Algora made his debut in the feature-length fiction with the child of clay, an approach to the figure of El Petiso Orejudo, Argentine serial killer who lived at the beginning of the last century. The figure of the serial killer is very recurring in the film, but Algora discusses history from a new perspective: rather than from the point of view of the criminal, does so from the point of view of one of their victims, tormented with visions of the murders. From the outset, the tape immerses the viewer in a disturbing atmosphere, very well achieved thanks to the work of Algora, as well as the excellent photography of Suso Bello. However, as the plot develops, the film loses bellows and intensity at the same pace that decays the attention of the respectable. Note that Algora still not fluent narrative fiction, that prints a rhythm excessively slow and contemplative, which is more suitable for a supposed psychological thriller. Another deficiency of the child of clay is becomes something quite predictable and monotonous. The characters initially interesting and juicy, also transformed, leaving behind their development and becoming flat. But not everything is bad news, because all performers doing good work, especially Daniel Freire and Chete child Lera.El of mud is an acceptable product of entertainment, that stays away from the fast-paced and intense psychological thriller that promises the advertising, but can be seen and is forgotten when it comes out of the film.</body>
</review>
