<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La soga" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It has been for history as one of the most radical experiments of its director and he has not lost an iota of his audacity with the passage of time</summary>
	<body>Hitchcock bet strong which was his first film in color and the first of his Trasatlantic Pictures company, founded with Sidney Bersntein British film magnate. He decided to adapt "Rope", a play by Patrick Hamilton whose action happens entirely in a Manhattan penthouse in real time. The story is slightly based on the real murder committed by two students of the University of Chicago Nathan Leopold and Richard Loeb, inspiration also film of Richard Fleischer momentum Criminal (Compulsion, 1959).That, no doubt, was a great risk decided to shoot the story in shots long (plano-secuencia) about eight minutes each. To pass a character in front of the camera the back of the character would darken the image and do the junction there. The duration of shots is because eight minutes is the time that lasted a loadable film in the camera roll at the time. Despite this (and what many fans and critics mentioned) there are some sharp cuts not hidden. For example there is a cut after the opening credits and the plane gives a turn of 180 degrees. There are some more such cuts during the film.Anecdotally tell that although the film lasts 80 minutes and it is assumed that it takes place in real time, in fact action covers about 100 minutes. This was accomplished by accelerating action: dinner takes only 20 minutes, the Sun gets too fast, etc. The number of September 2002 of Scientific American contains a complete analysis of this technique (and the effect on the onlookers who really feel as if they were watching a film of 100 minutes).It is easy to imagine the tremendous difficulty which was filming. The furniture and the walls were fully mobile so that the camera could move through the decorated with freedom and, due to the length of the shots, the floor was full of marks where should pass the actors or deposit the furniture.Through the window of the living room is the line of buildings in New York. To simulate a massive Cyclorama was built (three times the size of the attic) reproduced almost 70 kilometers from the scene of the city. That of cyclorama with 6000 incandescent light bulbs and neon tubes 200 was lit. The lights in the Windows are lit and apagaban to simulate the normal life of a city (the lighting and color are really important in the film, see in this respect the final scene where the lighting accentuates the tension of the moment). Built clouds of fiberglass that were moving to go moving the filming and the hue of the sky was changing to go bringing overnight. In short, a very complicated shoot.Another added difficulty was linked to what has already been said. Hitchcock was a director of montage, which considered that the fragmentation of planes in a movie served to enhance the story (in the popular imagination is well recorded the scene of the shower of psychosis as a perfect example).It therefore had before it an enormous challenge against himself: adapt his style to the shooting in a single plane. And it is certainly interesting to note how does. There are moments in which one movement from a character to another makes the same function that acts as a plano-contraplano, an overview of insert (so typical yours.) or relates a look with the object of such a look without having to cut the plane. A certainly fun and interesting exercise for a fan is watching the film to pay attention to these and other details.Hitchcock always mentioned that suspense is to make the viewer knows more than the protagonist. For example, to know that there is a bomb under the desktop of the protagonist and suffer seeing like this do not leave the room. As well, here master Hitchcock carries its definition of suspense until the end to do that throughout the film there is a corpse in the room without the protagonists know it and we know how they will find out the truth.It is this tension that makes advance action and it gradually increases from the first moment of the film. Every detail is designed to keep the attention of the Viewer. As a small example I would say that the character of James Stewart takes 20 minutes to appear for the first time but when it does have spoken so many times he and have drawn their character with such clarity and interest that we are eager to meet him. Entering the scene is really impressive.In the opening credits to the end of the film the characters appear referenced in function to its relationship with the murdered boy (David). The only person who is not mentioned as well as the character of James Stewart.La film was banned in many cities in the USA due to the implicit homosexuality of the characters of Farley Granger and John Dall (unfortunately not improved too much since then). The film has been for history as one of the most radical experiments of its director and has not lost an iota of his audacity with the passage of time.The small problem comes precisely from its main virtue: the shooting in a continuous plano-secuencia a little encorseta the Mise en scène. Nevertheless it's an excellent film that will keep viewers stuck in the seat since the beginning until its resolution.</body>
</review>
