<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Zodiac" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This turn of Fincher is not stylistic. It is not containment, but rigour. I am collecting, as always, the abuse of pampered managers of the industry, which owned the system, sent on producers and refuse to accept the necessary scissors.</summary>
	<body>«The time has taught me some tricks: avoid synonyms, which have the disadvantage of suggest imaginary differences;» prefer the usual words to the amazing; Insert in a story circumstantial traits; simulate small uncertainties, that if reality is accurate memory is not; telling the facts (this I learned of Kipling and Iceland sagas) as if not understand them at all; Remember that the previous rules are not obligations and that the time will abolirlas.» Borges is in his foreword to "Praise of folly".The prose of Borges is full of hesitation. They serve as he says, to simulate the memory which is imprecise. But not the reality that is accurate, but to the imagination that is always assertive.I quote Borges to inform Fincher. After Seven, Fight Club, panic room, wheel a documentary about the impossibility of knowing who was a serial killer of the 1970s. Away from the Symmetries of Seven Fincher consists a circular work where the same subject of the impossible of a killer search returns over and over again throughout a life which, in a background, is composing stages of a story: courtship, marriage, separation, and in the Centre, the case.I guess that this turn of Fincher is not stylistic. Was it imposed its material: years of research, suspects who could never sit on the bench. Fincher does not give the Viewer none the agrados promises to fiction, punishment, the solution of an enigma, the culmination of a search, because you can not give them. It is not containment, but rigour. Not find, however, mastery of which I speak. I am collecting, as always, the abuse of pampered managers of the industry, which owned the system, sent on producers and refuse to accept the necessary scissors. 170 minutes had also done dent in Casablanca.</body>
</review>
