<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Retrato de una obsesión" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ambiguous, desvaido, sad and honest, at the time, portrait of an obsession, Yes, but filmed with icy breath documentalist, unattractive as film entertainment.</summary>
	<body>Gradually detached from the initial charm, portrait of an obsession is positioned in this very slippery limbo of unclassifiable movies that don't deserve applause, but not the neglect, disinterest. It is of a more than free photographer Diane Arbus biopic, there are licenses that do not conform to the linearity of the forms (the whole movie is an estomagante flashback) as well as disproportionate allegories on the freedom of expression, decision making and the will on changing the course of our lives for more than a supraterreno or invisible fate seem stubbornly strive give us. In this, the film is exemplary, in what is subversive of transgressive. We must understand this love strange between the beautiful Kidman and the ugly Robert Downey Jr. as the real subject of the film, although he then desbarre in occasional demonstrations of what not worked enough script can cause to the general impression that causes us a film. To Cocteau's beauty and the beast you should not be imported sign the relationship of these characters.The relevant label of fictionalized biography which opens the title of the film suggests to us that the director, Steven Shainberg, offender of the also eccentric Secretary, going to sneak us a sobrevitaminado story about human relationships. And indeed, this happens, but Shainberg prefers to dive into fantastic, in the Ethereal part of the soul, in that in which abnormal attracts and beauty, unsettled or not, as I said Breton, happens to occupy a necessarily secondary level.The progressive process of afeamiento of the diva Kidman in the role of photographer suddenly illuminated by the freak is worthy to be included in the private collection of any fan to the kitsch. Special mention to the neighbor disturbing, amoral, incorporated in his suit of solitude and compassion, which introduces the world of celebrity without make any circus of people props to this crucial transformation.Sadly burdened by their unequivocally unconscious title in Spanish, Fur (skin) is a curious work, a punto y aparte in the inventory of movies that we see on a daily basis. This is not going to swell our particular altar of jewels, it won't be highly recommended to our friends when we talk about film (Yes, still is great to talk about cinema around some reeds in a bar), but is not possible, in an act sincere, her crush, impose the dubious "capricious" epithet.This tale about the fascination of the rare evidence forced as the kind, gentle and always correct Diane Arbus matrimonia not with the indomitable spirit, an accomplice with deviant from the norm, the film wants to show us and already its actual photographs were commissioned to do. You can see some wonderful here. Copy this curious mind disturbed by the infinite beauty of ugliness is suicide in 1971 and the urban legend circulating in the gossip of the Guild of the culture cotillas is that he photographed while he was losing in the more beyond. We are not here to deny this rumor.</body>
</review>
