<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good movie, very estimable, need to see quiet and calm, unhurried. Otherwise it might seem overly long and somewhat tedious at times.</summary>
	<body>Very interesting film of intrigue, based on notorious facts, adaptation of the book who wrote one of its protagonists, the cartoonist of the newspaper of San Francisco who became obsessed with the case.Because that is one of the real issues of the film: the obsession.An obsession that led to a human being to unravel one of the greatest mysteries of modern criminal research, of the mysterious serial killer who terrorized San Francisco in late 1960s and first half of the 1970s.Obsession, as shown on the tape, led him to lose family stability and his work as a cartoonist.But he could not stop to know the truth. Up, as he says and is checked at the end of the film: be in front of the murderer, staring him in the eyes. The film is quite good, although it is not, in any way, the masterpiece that is saying there. Fail you and spare you so some things.The best is undoubtedly its beginning and its end. The first half hour, where are three murders (terrible of the Lake), and not only one as recently said an acquaintance, and I suppose, respected national critic (once again spoke a critic in a newspaper without having seen the film, and they go.).And the last is also great half an hour, with the artist as absolute protagonist in his terrifying visit to the former film projectionist, the defendant in prison, and the policeman who led for years the case (here is used, with intelligence, humor).However, there in the middle are many, I would say that too many dialogues, fact that denotes a comprehensive, rigorous and very careful script. A work of impeccable research, however, much longer film. Well, maybe not much, because it is possible to have the appropriate duration which is exposed, but could well be out of history a large number of spectators who action like more than the explanation.Good performances, especially in charge of Robert Downey Jr, which leaves less than what I would have liked to me, I am a fan of him, and John Carroll Lynch as the more than possible suspect. Exquisite setting, acrisolada photography and a wise Assembly, especially in the first and last quarter of the film.In short, a good movie, very estimable, that need to see quiet and calm, unhurried. Otherwise it might seem overly long and somewhat tedious at times.</body>
</review>
