<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="El retorno de los malditos" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A sequel that not only throw overboard all the virtues of the tape of Aja, but is also strong candidate for more bland and infumable we had to swallow in so far this year.</summary>
	<body>Wes Craven, the man who had the opportunity to do the same movie twice, charged along with his son to write the screenplay for the sequel the hills have eyes (2006), the successful remake directed Alexandre Aja one of their classic setenteros. Under normal circumstances, the hand of Uncle Wes would be a reason to trust in the quality of a movie, and if I say "under normal circumstances" is because we all know very well that Wes Craven today is light years of the of thirty years ago. Man we have today is someone who is in franca decline and has given to the fret with our hopes on more than one occasion, either as director, producer and screenwriter. Said this should go to the point: the return of the damned (2007) is a sequel not only throwing overboard all the virtues of the tape of Aja, but it also is a strong candidate to more bland and infumable we had to swallow in so far this year.And worst of all is that Wes it was easy, as much that it attempted to, this sequel (in an incomprehensible marketing move has been named Spain as the return of the damned when the easiest thing would have been placed a "2" to the title already had) could not be worse than that which he himself directed in 1985famous not only for being one of the most solid jumbles of 1980s, but also for being the only tape of history (as far I know) in which a dog has a flashback (!). There's nothing that, as from the outset aims to emulate the intense and frenzied style of Aja and take it to the next level. Charge of the address is the German Martin Weisz (best director of Sitges film Grimm Love (2006), which I have not seen), shadowed the visual style of the film predecessor to looking for addition a claustrophobic atmosphere very in line with The Descent (2005). Unfortunately, the results can not be more disastrous.Instead of a family of bystanders unawares, the protagonists of this film are a group of novice recruits of the National Guard panels to provide supplies to a group of scientists who lived in the hills of New Mexico. What are, in contrast, is massacred scientists and themselves prey to another family of mutant cannibals, who will face if they wish to survive. From the outset, this is already the first error: by making the protagonists a group of soldiers with weapons and training to kill, the sequel strips to the history of its human component, moving any empathy that can feel the viewer towards the characters. If we add to that the mutants are represented as real giants who lack little to have superpowers, we find that interesting primitive confrontation of the first part is here reduced to a typical monster movie, only that badly made. The face to face between the beasts and soldiers going through each and every one of the clichés of this type of films during an desganada address and a plot that moves almost by inertia. To make matters worse, the soldiers are so frankly stupid that fifteen minutes not only don't we feel pity for them, but we wish them openly the worst of luck. I am not exaggerating when I say that these bogus soldiers pose a greater danger for themselves than the savage cannibals that are hidden in the caves.As a good representative of his time, the movie nor spared in the offal and rugged situations. Only the first scene is quite hard to bear (which, not deny it, look good at the beginning,) but after seeing all of the tape one could not but admit that you it's a shock therapy quite clear that attempts to cover the countless shortcomings of the film by appealing to the easy impact. There is also here a bloody rape scene, of course much more explicit in the first part and with a greater emphasis on the pleasure of the attacking beast, which he even hangs very calculated thread of baba from the mouth.The question I have is if really (as I have read in some places) the film tries to sneak an anti-war message to us about the invasion on hostile ground at the hands of American troops always lists, reading that not only I have heard about this film but also about other next premiere, 28 weeks later (2007). If so, I think a message quite poor and the exploitation of the deaths of the soldiers through the childish method show them as a band of rednecks who deserve the fate falls on them seems to me not only ineffective, but also somewhat miserable. The return of the damned is, in this sense and any other an absurdly forgettable, mediocre and surplus film that can happen without any charge of consciousness. It seems to me that Wes Craven will take a long time to return to lift head.</body>
</review>
