<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>As science fiction film is correct, entertaining at times, but becomes soon what it is: a thoughtful metaphor, poetic times.</summary>
	<body>Cuarón and Iñárritu share in his two recent works that look bitter (do Mexican?), penetrating and thoughtful on the contemporary world and its contradictions, as well as a perspective without concessions on the pain and loneliness. Children of men this picture is drawn through a future and apocalyptic, London mired in terror and despair, whose state releja in a bleak apartheid (which recalls Auschwitz) their migrants, and leads to its citizens to suicide or neglect (as of the own character played soberly by almost always great Clive Owen).But - as in Babel - it will be precisely from the womb of these immigrants where escape the last hope for an opulent society, tech, but sterile and nihilist, condemned to disappear. The political claim of Cuarón is explicit. Yet his speech - and that of his friend Iñárritu - does not close there. Both investigate the psychological drama of his characters, extracting from him a perfect metaphor of our civilization, but at the same time a personal reflection that shoots straight to the Viewer, unsettling him and forcing him to think.The script works as a metaphor intended is not warning about what could happen to our civilization, but that rather distorts the reality in which we are already installed to ensure that every spectator performed his own map of the world and its paradoxes. The immigrant is taken in children of men as archetype of the other, to the opulent world fears but need as cheap labour and increase in its birth statistics. Europe did not want to have children, or any a meager number of retirees pace that thicken the Imserso.Pero infertility which talks about the film is more extensible to the climax that according to Cuarón breathes in a first world tired although abundantly surrounded by amenities. The scene in which thousands of dozens of citizens discover with grief - in front of their televisions extra-shallow - the news of the death of the youngest of their fellow citizens is insightful. Acceptance of death and the need of hope can only reach of countries with a biography tinged of pain and poverty. A self-satisfied society does not accept death and is intended to deceive living the dream of eternal happy present.Do already in Y tu mamá also? and his first work, Sólo con tu pareja, or as Assistant Director in Gaby: a true story - see the concern of this filmmaker by exposing the cuts that we did flee from death and pain. And does it so ruthlessly, but always leaving room for hope of reborn feel touched by the misery and deadly.In children of men, Theo receives a timely visit of Julian, with whom he had a son, died of a fever shortly after. Julian encourages Theo to go a journey of redemption which will save his dreary existence because of the memory of his dead son. As the character of Richard (Brad Pitt)? or of Chieko (Rinko Kikuchi), in his desperate search for love - in Babel, Theo learns that pain only healthy with the help of the other. In fact, before appeared Julian, Theo only had friends locked up in their ivory towers, bearable by the music and drugs (Michael Caine) or the enjoyment by the beautiful (Danny Huston). Julian (Julianne Moore) returns to reality, as the Matrix Morpheus. You will even have to impersonate one immigrant, discovered the treatment they receive and the conditions in which they live.In turn, human project is suited as a nothing subtle metaphor for this utopian space (away from the city, on the high seas, no fixed port) where the differences are highlighted as only as a means to protect fundamental rights and not to segregate, exclude or exploit, and where all are treated only as they are human. Hope cannot come either from terrorism that says defend rights of minorities against the totalitarianism of an oppressive State. Why the girl by birth does not have more room than this boat has no more owner that you want it to, outside the city, that London, symbol of progress and democracy.Children of men enjoy more leaving you suggest beyond shown (which is not little). As science fiction film is correct, entertaining at times, but becomes soon what it is: a thoughtful metaphor, occasionally poetic (as that final scene shot dead building, with some soldiers petrified to hear the cries of the baby). To highlight the start-up scene, the setting of an unrecognizable London, flat hairpin sequence, rather than good actors. But it is not a film that meets the stomach of a good lover of action cinema, it is not even a science fiction to use film, although this genus end easily skirting the border of ethical and political discourse.Among the most remarkable moments that empty, almost crumbling school visit.You can read in the works of p. D. James in which this film is based: "We have departed from us, as parents in mourning, all the painful memories of our lost." Games for children have been withdrawn from the squares.They burned all the toys, except dolls that some women not all strings used as substitutes for children. Schools were closed for a long time until they shut down them or turned them in educational establishments for adult people.The voices of children heard only on cassettes and disks."It is unbearable for some, but for the majority of people work as a drug."</body>
</review>
