<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Zodiac" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An intelligent story about the frustration of a group of researchers, but is also a wonderful portrait about EE epochal.UU. about to leave the exciting and non-conformist spirit of the 1960s.</summary>
	<body>David Fincher has shown in his career ample capacity to handle the springs of the thriller (Seven or the panic room) but at the same time, also has exhibited traces more understanding in innovative and least conventional films (the club of the fight or The Game). But his film has always been tack by the same line of continuity: its well cared aesthetics and its detailed mise en scene. Each level seems to obey a studied planning and, when it comes to recreate environments in this Zodiac, his films get as few transport the Viewer to the environment, time and places of his short stories (in this case, shines the splendid recreation of the 1970s).Zodiac, Fincher seems to have wanted to combine his job as Rapporteur of thrillers with a drift towards a dramatic film which does not seem to function as comfortable. With a scrupulous respect for the research data (police and journalistic) of this famous case of serial killer of the 1970s, the tape loses at times emotion to promote its determined commitment by verismo. In addition to narrating the investigation continued for hunting the Zodiac killer, the film is, above all, a story about how the lives of police officers and investigators involved in the case by this puzzle dilated for thirty years was marked.And probably this greater deepening in his characters, unusual in thrillers, which has lengthened the footage from the tape up some questionable 158 minutes. Because, despite the prominence of Jake Gyllenhaal in the role of the journalist author of the novel on which the film itself (Robert Graysmith) is based, the other characters receive an I extend treatment and are not subject to the coarse brush so characteristic of the genus. So roles side as of Paul Avery, brilliant journalist of the San Francisco Chronicle, mayor charged packing mercy, also, to the splendid interpretation of Robert Downey Jr. Similarly, the detectives Dave Toschi (Mark Ruffalo) and William Armstrong (a great Anthony Edwards recovered for the film after the television effervescence) appear described with more shades of the usual.Zodiac is a clever story about the frustration of a group of researchers, but is also a wonderful portrait about EE epochal.UU. about to leave the exciting and non-conformist spirit of the 1960s. Only the character of Gyllenhaal, who treated dismissively as 'boy scout', refuses to be overcome by the carelessness. And somehow, despite the Lees bitter and impotence deja Zodiac in its final, at least worth staying with the small tribute pays to a young Illustrator, the last monkey of the drafting of the Chronicle, in its tenacious perseverance to find some truth in a tragic fact forgotten by the vortex of the years.</body>
</review>
