<review author="Txapulin" title="Zodiac" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The last film by David Fincher, director excited Seven promises what is not, and that is his major problem.</summary>
	<body>The last film by David Fincher, director excited Seven promises what is not, and that is his major problem. Both his trailer, as its synopsis, and the background of the director (basically the aforementioned Seven), as the first hour of footage, they argue that we we have a whodunit, a film in which that some cops try to discover the identity of a mysterious killer.Seven was amazing at the time by its solid script in relation to the seven deadly sins and the sordid deaths appearing therein, but neither was a classic whodunit, the murderer appears quite before the end of the film, which surprisingly, ends not with the discovery of the identity of the murderer, but by solid rounding of the structure of the script.But Zodiac is not surprising. Moreover, does not want to surprise or it pretends. To make matters worse lasts nearly three hours when I already half guess the murderer and we know that that's not going to be the important thing, not strange to the people in the film end sick of the last hour of footage. Go warned, I think, therefore, to see this movie. It is not a movie for police to catch a murderer, they tend more to be a kind of pseudodocumental, or a dramatization of an actual police investigation. From one point in the movie the important thing is not who is the killer, but the obsession of (certain) police and (some) journalists to discover it, and that is what us portrays here. We have therefore a film of characterizations, both setting and interpretations.The historical setting is very successful. It can be more or less easy to find costumes and hairstyles of the 1960s and 1970s, but the flat broad of a changing San Francisco over the past two decades are incredible. The interpretations are more adjusted, they are well Mark Ruffalo as the COP responsible for the research, and Robert Downey Jr., that although lately it makes similar roles (see A Scanner Darkly), and something will be, is not bad. Jack Gyllenhaal, on the other hand, I think that is the most complex character and does not give the size.Total for a three-hour movie set in the 1970s, is now Spielberg Munich, which, besides the fact that it is also very well done, relates facts of much greater significance, both historical for the characters. In any case, for those who go warned, Zodiac is not any bad film.</body>
</review>
