<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Un franco, 14 pesetas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very correct directorial debut with a careful invoice technique and election of the cast</summary>
	<body>By tag will say that we we have a tragicomedy, and another hanging one more, say to a vision of the past style tell me. A formula that seems to give good results and not only by loyalty to members of a generation specific.Bittersweet printing that not everything is going to be a showcase of topics: the tender gaze of Carlos Iglesias to the past of many Spaniards as migrants, from a grey Spain, is dulcificada through a dose of sentimentality and humor, but raised and distributed by a calm, but not without rhythm and hook footage.Very round has left him this title, the first which writes, performs and leads in 90% of their sequences. A very correct directorial debut with a careful invoice technique and election of the cast becomes their card as a filmmaker. Without forgetting AzulOscuroCasiNegro, Un Franco, 14 pesetas was one of the most interesting proposals of the past Festival de Málaga, being receipt recognize the good wishes of the author to recall and anchor a forgotten of our recent history chapter.The Spanish landing in Europe during the 1950s and 1960s, which should establish as many comparisons with our present, has not enjoyed much impact film, except manners comedy style see you to Germany, Pepe, who once played a correct role according to the political intentions of the regime. Churches play with the real fact but also suggests ways to strike a balance maintained between the tears and laughter without that it almibarado to the dessert. Author of the screenplay, has rescued part of their memories and has mixed them with of as many emigrants returning that you narrated their stories. It was a long process, not expensive. Note to see the small tables that dot the action: winks to the culture shock upon arrival in a more developed country, the exaggeration of the passage through customs, the return to a strange country where the priests punished children for their misdemeanours of spelling and Franco (from the title, capitalized) was theirs as good feudal Lord. Do do the chorus of actors that accompanies the director acts supportive: Javier Gutiérrez, snow of Medina and Isabel Blanco? for more details, the young Swiss owner hotel - counteracting the prominence of the Iglesias-actor, excellent in his role? something tormented, put some glue. The fact that its interpretation tics had round-the-clock eliminated all burden of arrogance, that many players bring with them when it comes to being on both sides of the camera.</body>
</review>
