<review author="Luna" title="Zodiac" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It would be glad to the stalwarts of the director and all those interested in detective films. Despite all I I miss the aesthetics and rhythm that gave that to me remains his masterpiece, the fight club.</summary>
	<body>The lights of the room finally shut down and I wonder with what David Fincher we're going to meet again at 24 frames per second after five long years of silence and absence of the seventh art (or Vice,) as you want to look at. It will be the Seven David Fincher, fight club or the fanfare with the camera of the panic room?From the first frame we note that Fincher has decided to abandon the aesthetic line that in the panic room he would put the camera through the loop of coffeemaker to show a visual approach more rested, suitable for telling this story that "notes" the entire process of a criminal investigation over almost twenty years. Do not leave Fincher, however, this trend to merge computer graphics with the celluloid as only he knows how to do brilliantly (there is nothing more to remember those opening credits to the room of panic or "the House ikea" of the fight club) and there are times that merges the essential element of the research, the writing of the murderer, with images in a very original way.It is not the first time that David Fincher discusses serial killers. He already did with Seven. On this occasion an actual research, to create fiction, part of a real event. From my point of view in this case Fincher speaks, rather than of murder, of the inevitability of the obsessions, because all that is involved with the case and are obsessed with him end up destroying their lives, just like the murderer killed their victims.An impeccable realization that perhaps is sometimes too many jumps spatio-temporal lose a little to the Viewer as to the continuity of the events in the narrative. Despite all I I miss the aesthetics and rhythm that gave that to me remains his masterpiece, the fight club.Currently David Fincher is competing in Cannes with this film, that criticism seems to have quite applauded.The film will like to the stalwarts of the director and all those interested in detective films. He will not like those who hate the stories with jumps in time.Final anecdote: for all those film buffs a perlite which reveals this film, Dirty Harry is based on the same case of EE serial murders.UU, only that the murderer for Dirty Harry signed as Scorpio and not as Zodiac.</body>
</review>
