<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Zodiac" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film more complete and mature of David Fincher. He broke with his usual excessive slope and, despite resorting again to the figure of a serial-killer, distances itself totally from the style used in the brilliant Seven.</summary>
	<body>Zodiac is, by far, the film more complete and mature of David Fincher, one of the most interesting and controversial today's filmmakers. A title that breaks with the usual excessive slope and that, despite resorting again to the figure of a serial-killer, distances itself entirely from the style used in the brilliant Seven. Behind Zodiac lies another way of dealing with the genre, where austerity and thoroughness are paid a special role.Indeed he has not invented anything new. He has simply sought other narrative resources had never used so far in their cinema. And, in doing so, takes as ideal models sobriety retailer that Alan j. Pakula reflected the journalistic investigation into the Watergate in all the men of the Chair and tone, aesthetic and documentary filmmaker, with which Richard Fleischer orchestrated his wonderful the Boston strangler. Like their referents, Fincher attends truthful otherwise marked to American Society of the 1970s; that of a serial killer who caused panic and anxiety among the inhabitants of a large area of the San Francisco Bay. There, just in the County of Vallejo, a type without scruples, nicknamed Zodiac, started their evil actions in the summer of 1969 and, with their multiple crimes, kept in check to the police and the press for many years. Today, the identity of the murderer is still unknown.Elegant, intelligent and meticulous; in a Word, masterful. Film classicism emerges in each of the scenes of Zodiac. There is not an only detail that has no waste. Everything is controlled until the last millimetre. Taking into account that the story takes place during two long decades, their forced numerous narrative ellipsis are an example of the perfectionist manner with which the director has raised its product. These temporary jumps (, sometimes encompassing several years at a single stroke), never is an out loose along the way. Even, at all times and in a subtle way, the socio-political in a country description is present at different stages. A wonder.And, unlike other similar tapes, instead of focusing mainly on the personality of the killer, he explores the psychological effects that marked the life of those who, during this lengthy period, were the footsteps of the elusive Zodiac. Is why the objective of the Chamber of Fincher rests on the figures of David Toschi - the Royal inspector of police that inspired Peter Yates for Bullitt-, Robert Graysmith and Paul Avery?, a young cartoonist and a journalist for The San Francisco Chronicle, respectively-, three individuals that are more involved in the pursuit of the criminalAn excellent way to demonstrate that, apart from those who murdered, Zodiac - with their provocations and encrypted games - also got other types of victims.More than a thriller to use is a film that, at two different levels, analyzes the causing effects of an obsession; one born in all Hunter Díez to get to their prey at the price which is making such efforts in the sole aim of his life. And I say this on two levels because it apart from the self-destructive portrait of the personality of the researchers and their direct environment also explores? but with less depth - in the mind of a killer ready to kill for the pure pleasure of killing. The difference is that Zodiac always managed their purposes, while their crawlers only knew the powerlessness of confronting a real ghost. It is not surprising that, with these constants, the evil Zarov is a title cited several times in the film. And is that, in addition to being preferred film the killer (as counted, a film buff in every rule), defines perfectly the relationship established between the hunters and their prey.More than 2 hours and 40 minutes of film in its purest form; Cinema of this that can be enjoyed on very few occasions. And is that, in this calibration (and anything heavy) footage, is a bit of everything. When faced with intimate moments, Fincher takes his time and relame (somewhat sadistically) with the coldness and distance which handles its protagonists. It faces the scenes of tension with a majestic correction; therein, is conspicuous by its absence the artifice employed on other occasions by the director. At no time looking for cheap tricks and spectacular effects, even when plasma on-screen killings by Zodiac, these are reflected so very realistic with which caused the viewer impact is even greater.Everything is perfectly embedded in the film, starting with performances contained, among which deserve special attention the creations of Jake Gyllenhaal and Robert Downey Jr., two men of the drafting of The San Francisco Chronical who, with that case, radically changed his existence; the artist and reporter, both trapped by the same obsession, but affected physically and mentally different magnitudes. And this without diminishing the sobriety with which a chameleonic Mark Ruffalo gives life to the own Bullitt in person.A model work which, without a doubt, opens wide to the classroom teachers to a new David Fincher. A superior and intelligent, work whose maximum charge, from now on, already can go tuteando is with the great classics of the seventh art. Finally, the clear successor to Clint Eastwood already has name and surname. Not in vain, Dirty Harry, as well as being inspired by one of the constants of Zodiac, is the subject in the film of a well-deserved tribute.As final figure, I quote the other day I saw The Zodiac, an American film, produced a couple of years (not released in Spain) and based on the same story picked up by Fincher. I know that comparisons are odious, but in this case, inevitable. It is curious to discover how, with an identical material on the table, the director of the Club of the fight manages to break molds with an unsurpassed exercise in style, while another filmmaker, a such Alexander Bulkley, not beyond a simple thriller riddled with lots of television connotations.</body>
</review>
