<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Spiderman 3" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The story is quite simple, and despite its excessive length, fails to close all the sub-plots that creates, so successfully?Spider-Man 3? an irregular product that achieves its mission, is fill the screens of viewers...</summary>
	<body>Sam Raimi returns to place behind the scenes to "close" this trilogy starring the man spider. After the previous successes of critics and the public, "Spiderman 3" returns to achieve a sobrado triumph in what regards to spectators, but the criticism is another story. Most branded the film's child, excessively long, pantomime and other descriptions, that lower the bar of an interesting trilogy. "The truth is that they are right."Spider-Man 3 "is presented as a story noña, in which the character of Peter Parker/Spiderman shows on many occasions as a caricature, which does not present anything new, nor does the film more interesting. On this occasion, we have new faces to help increase the expectations of this third party, such as the case of: Thomas Haden Church, Thoper Grace and Bryce Dallas Howard. Of these three, the best standing is without doubt Thomas Haden Church ("sideways"), who made up a character like the sand man, full of humanity in the sobriety and coldness of a convict as which interprets. Thoper Grace also shows two expensive, much more differentiated, as photographer are the metete Eddie Brock, who will make competition to Peter in the newspaper, and the expected Venom, character that should have been given more game.If in "El Bosque" Bryce Dallas Howard has already demonstrated his talent, is checked here not what it has lost, despite the fact that his character does not go beyond the typical blonde beauty, dumb and rica. Bruce Campbell returns to his cameo in one of the jokes more funny all the footage.Focusing on the protagonists, Tobey Maguire has the opportunity to nominate a Peter Parker more self-assured, bordering the caricature, and dares to make everything you had never done before. Kirsten Dunst plays a fairly bland, who does not deserve too many qualifiers, and finally, James Franco more of the same.In short, "Spiderman 3" is presented as a film entertainment, in which Visual effects take the leading role, and that in many moments are outstanding (see the man of sand), but in many others they sing to the League. The story is quite simple, and despite its excessive length, fails to close successfully all the sub-plots that creates, so "Spiderman 3" is an irregular product that achieves its mission, fill the screens of viewers (dissatisfied).</body>
</review>
