<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Daunting romantic manifesto between science fiction and romantic melodrama. He loses because it is very ambitious and WINS our hearts because it is very ambitious.</summary>
	<body>Although it contains some of the most brilliant scenes lately I have seen in a movie theater, the source of life is a spectacular hodgepodge of metaphysics, melodrama and science fiction, may, in the effort to please in all three, not content at all in any. The love story between Izzy and Tom (splendid Rachel Weisz and Hugh Jackman) is a masterful portrait of love beyond death, beyond of adversity and over time. Conqueror, scientist and astronaut conspire to reach the source of life, the tree, pre-Columbian, telluric and transcendental. The Visual excesses escorting the fantasy of Aranofsky excuse: is not possible to be as ambitious and not fall into the ridiculous. And the film has ruborosos moments, you pictures too naïve that lowered the admirable precision of a montage and arriesgadísima narrative proposed: three times, three arguments, three looks towards a single point: the dance of death and the dazzling impulse of life. Death is a disease, says Tom / Hugh Jackman when he sees his beloved dying. Death is an act of creation, says Izzy / Rachel Weisz elsewhere apart from the film. On these two ideas flows the source of life, film that appreciates its excessive not footage (hour and a half) and his firmness in the plastic reconstruction of an obsession. Aronofsky has been eight years after this project. Us, even demanding, not can withdraw the point of wit and talent, vocation rupture, built-up megalomania so the viewer attends a different function, where raw the fragility of feelings, the unrestrained romantic love story which is last of the film Foundation, because this source of life is above all a tragic love storya monument plastically irreproachable passion over time and space. As the film it is a factory of dreams, the tape itself, once finished and lit the lights, turns into a dream. One runs the corridor lit, machine-gunned of kids who shout the points that vomit the Martians killed, capping, embebecido, troubled, simply overwhelmed. No matter that the movie is a good movie: is not, at all, a masterpiece. It doesn't matter that reasoned, repensada cold, as he likes to this passionate scribe, is report them avoidable, broken fractures that could have been amended with less majestic seams. Because if this freak is guilty of something, it's Majesty. I, back home, I think the tree of life, in the Maya, a dark laboratory where three exegetes of the faith have been converted in scientists and interstellar space. It will that: the film is an oratorio, a piece about love and his escape, death and the efforts of the soul Symphony human understand it or deny it. None of this is feasible. At the end, as in the film, we asentimos, we let ourselves be crucified by the wind.</body>
</review>
