<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story that, in a perfect exercise in cinematic wisdom, keeps you imantado to the armchair, embedded in the screen. And, then, to come out, when you mention the movie... so what has really happened in the two and a half hours of projection? Anything.</summary>
	<body>For me, what has surprised me most of "Zodiac", is that in his two and a half hours of footage, by removing the principle, absolutely nothing happens. And, taking into account that the film you hypnotizes you key the view on the screen, providing you with the five senses, there can be no better criticism.Advertising, and more taking into account that David Fincher also directed "Seven", this "Zodiac" has sold us as one movie, another one of assassins in series, it is a genre with its own entity in the USA film. But it is not that. Or Yes, but not only that.Because "Zodiac", is actually based on the crimes committed by a disturbed, on the West coast of the United States.UU., in the 1970s, but that the film is much more than the research carried out to capture him. Through his long, and yet, precise and need footage, "Zodiac" speaks of many more things than serial crimes and police investigations.It speaks to us of obsession, paranoia, the commitment and the madness. Makes us reflect on the role of the media and their responsibility to society on the success media, the desire for notoriety and the compulsive need to be (re) known.And all this without large pirotecnias with a containment of media and a rigurosismo formal as long we saw not on a screen. Cinema in its purest form in which everything is at the service of a complex, complicated and contradictory story as life itself. The music, an exceptional soundtrack that perfectly contextualizes you the history, production design, costumes, those characters who smoke as desperate and crowd of food garbage. all the details and all the elements in the service of the story, as always should be.A story that, in a perfect exercise in cinematic wisdom, keeps you imantado to the armchair, embedded in the screen. And then to come out, when you mention the film. What has happened really in the two and a half hours of projection? Anything. Or almost. There has been tension in the style of "24", there has been persecution, violent interrogations, no explosions.In the 1970s and San Francisco should not have forensic as neither medical Grissom as House. The experts calligraphers are so human that they drink, doubt and they are wrong. As well as police officers and journalists. And even own murderer.And so goes on a story that extends over more than thirty years, that comes to an end apotheosis? that no pyrotechnic - and let you open-mouthed that rarely lets you film a sediment to truth so sincere.And, of course, that hitchcockiana sequence in the obsessed artist goes to the House of a witness and, as in "Suspicion", neither he nor the viewer know what is going to bring that mysterious basement. An exercise in suspense to the surface that results from more enriching and informative.David Fincher confirms, therefore, as one of the biggest and best contemporary film directors. One of the few Directors that, today, you can trust to do feet.</body>
</review>
