<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great film that perhaps disappoint to those who seek a thriller like the others but would be glad, I hope much, that seeking the good film.</summary>
	<body>I have that thank, once again, the Warner Bros. Spain and muchocine.net the invitation to the press pass, already two weeks ago, of "Zodiac", the new film that already consiero one of the best directors of the present: David Fincher.La film tells the Zodiac killer crimes and the subsequent investigation by the police and journalists.A cursory look at the synopsis comes to understand the reasons that led Fincher to make this your next project. Crime, the unhealthy atmosphere, the macabre are present in the story and are reflected on screen effectively. Especially shocking and desasosegantes are the scenes of crimes, able to put in tension the Viewer as only Fincher and a few more can do. An oppressive atmosphere the director also transferred to other moments of the story.But that nobody expected of "Zodiac" a new "Seven" because it's two movies with few elements in common. It is clear that Fincher not likes repeated and advocates here more for the epic of the research, by the inner journey experience character, rather than thrillers of suspense to the use.It is assisted in its work by the millimeter screenplay by James Vanderbilt, based on the book by Robert Graysmith, which is able not to let up loose ends in a very extensive history and that lasts many years. This gives the film an air of "biopic" which is his biggest problem because it can cause a certain distance between the viewer and the story. In any case, the writer should be aware of this problem because it adds a couple of subtle touches to the history that make be more round.A great script again, that brilliantly drawn characters of flesh and blood, not flat and are beautifully interpreted. Jake Gyllenhaal is a good actor who perhaps lack a tad of charisma (this side of pasmarote not help much) but in this case fit you his character. Also Anthony Edwards and Mark Ruffalo offer good performances but are perhaps overshadowed by the talent and charisma of a Robert Downey Jr. is experiencing one of its best moments. In more supporting roles, but seeing also solid performances, can see Brian Cox (in a role initially awarded to Gary Oldman), John Carroll Lynch, Elias Koteas or Chloë Sevigny.Pero if else weren't enough, the element that I liked most, which the rises above many other films, is its pace. Few times two hours and forty minutes I have moved so quickly. The narrative moves so naturally, in a manner so fluid and you catch in such a way that when you realize you are watching the end credits.This detail demonstrates, to me, the brilliance of the work of direction and mounting (Angus Wall) of a film of which I would highlight also the soundtrack of David Shire and the musical selection.In short, a great film that perhaps disappoint to those who seek a thriller like the others but would be glad, I hope much, that seeking the good film.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 8.5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
