<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="El color del crimen" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Awkward, long and tedious movie devoid of its rhythm and hook</summary>
	<body>This film starts well. A priori reconciles a mystery plot? a child abduction - and drama of racism in the ghettos of the large urban United States framed. If to this we add the participation of two almost always solvents Samuel l. Jackson and Julianne Moore as head of distribution, the cocktail seems interesting. What happens to that thwarts the essence of this cheap copy of television series about criminal investigations involving social background? The couple of the year and A crazy Christmas director wanted to make the jump to the thriller and so focused on a novel by Richard Price, who in turn adapted to screenplay format. An ugly incident joins the ways of a woman with feelings of guilt and irrationality and a police officer struggling to control the security of a neighborhood of imprisonment separated from the "white areas" of the city.As the story progresses, it starts to divest certain whiff to C.S.I (in any of its variants: New York, Las Vegas and Miami), saving also a similar reasonable with Crash and Grand Canyon, the soul of the city, by its racial connotations, but with crime of through, something which most rooted if fits the sense of discrimination based on the blame for acts. And the story follows its course, jumping from plot to plot and anticipating the end but does not stop when it should. The director is recreated in the oppressive atmosphere where take place the inconsistent actions of the protagonists, comings and goings that attract attention to all but are mostly jerks for one that you already imagine the outcome. When it seems that the argument be straighten and we see the light at the end of the tunnel, dialogues begin to extend without the need for and, no kidding, emerges a beautiful and tender love story. The question we is. from where? Yet by analyzing the moral of this awkward, long and tedious movie. Her leave on hold if still you want to see a bland title heir of the police plots of television, although lacking in its rhythm and hook products.</body>
</review>
