<review author="Patri" title="Trainspotting" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>His merit is that shows the drug world in a way that had never seen before</summary>
	<body>Trainspotting basically consists of a group of heroin passed almost the entire film hanging. Tells the story is unimportant, what draws attention is how account you, that this same story another way would have lacked entirely interest, because it is not much.It has memorable moments as the dirtiest Scottish toilet, must have stomach to see, as well as other scenes from the movie, but even by the "surreal" touch is worth the trouble to see it, it is not the only touch of surrealist film, because to show us how the protagonist feels to be hung, Danny Boyle gives us some other time as when it dives into the carpet and ends up in the hospital.Trainspotting is one of these movies that they become icons of a generation and thousands of followers worship them, as the Club of the struggle or Clockwork Orange that will later influence later films, all of them cult films. His merit is that shows the drug world in a way that had never seen before.Ewan McGregor was announced with this role, then his career has done a u-turn and no longer this kind of films, but it seems that it is going to shoot the second part of Trainspotting and will be the protagonist, but Danny Boyle is waiting for players age more. He is good actor, has great versatility, has shown that it can interpret a drug addict to a normal type, to a gallant and can even sing (in Moulin Rouge) and work with Tim Burton (Big Fish).Are you has blamed to Trainspotting seem too to Clockwork Orange, may have some influence, but the only thing that appear is that tells the story of a group of young people who do not follow established standards, Trainspotting his life governed her heroin and in Clockwork Orange is violence, but it has a history much more interesting and best screenplay, but of course, are not going to compare to Stanley Kubrick with Danny Boyle.</body>
</review>
