<review author="Patri" title="El hundimiento" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In general it is a good movie, perfectly recreates those last days of Hitler and his faithful in the bunker and what we believe, is what really matters.</summary>
	<body>The collapse shows the last days of life of Hitler and Nazism in Germany from the point of view of the Secretariat that the dictator had during his last years, is a vision close and human in one of the most bloody rulers of history, although no time seeks to justify their actions, simply teaches us that the bloody are also human beings, although cost us to believe it.The pace of the movie is slow and at times becomes something tedious, and more when you're trying to remember as many names of German officers to not miss. The duration (2 and a half hours) helps create that feeling of slowness, but in the second half the film becomes more interesting, although without causing either excessive interest.At the time he spoke much of the interpretation of Bruno Ganz, it is always difficult to play a real character, and the more well-known is that character more complicated it is to recreate it in a realistic manner, but the actor gets to know a more humane Hitler what have always imagined that it is with a personality full of contrasts, something that is very well expressed in a conversation with Secretary Eva Braun, women married Hitler, the Secretary tells him that he is a very kind man, but that sometimes it is able to tell real atrocities to which Eva Braun responds: "If, when it is the Führer", thereby expressing the "dual personality".The character of Eva Braun, is which is more nuanced, and the better interpreted, is a vital and optimistic person full of joy, even in the toughest moments, but this behaviour is only a mask to hide his true feelings.While the story is told from the point of view of the Secretariat, (even at the end get a picture of the real Secretary speaking) the character it is not well developed, we do not know almost nothing of it, and this is something that is missing.There are several secondary stories that are themselves, something that enhances the film, which sometimes lacks drama. Despite these failures, in general it is a good movie, perfectly recreates those last days of Hitler and his faithful in the bunker and what we believe, is what really matters.</body>
</review>
