<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A relevant movie, a visual spectacle of first order which made me remember, at times, the hue between the circus and the transcendent of Cirque Soleil. Pure gold: a unique visual entertainment, a remarkable finding.</summary>
	<body>Zhang Yimou is no longer the poet intimate, Chinese director who signed / filmed the Red Lantern, back in the early nineties: now is the dazzling artifice of visual pirotecnica rare, stunning and beautiful. Yimou is a master whose talent is to seek us beauty, give us an exercise in low plastic affectation the that fascinating, flows a way of understanding the film to which we were not accustomed. The brittle, weak and melodramatic hisatoria of this Chinese dynasty enfangada betrayals, deceit and passions to the purest style SOAP Televisa accurate so overwhelming wrap, incorporated in a suit, so rich and expensive, so hypnotic that there comes a time in which the story not have her characters nor are his dialogues that explicit plot developments but the costumes, the apotheosis of mass movements in battles, choreographed with a sense of the detail cuasipornográfico had already wanted to Yes Zack Snyder in his wonderful 300. The bombastic staging not abotarga the viewer's attention: it adrenaliza, subjected her to an iconic overload that comes out unscathed, although crippled, fascinated. That the story is leaden seal, plumbate and plañidera? Delighted to agree who thus intends to lower the film and aesthetic - pictorial magnificence which are three different issues although vectorized into a same essence, pleasure, knowledge, art - this film? Even the reduced set of scenes of martial arts has seemed competent, not being me - whatsoever - fervent fan of such excesses. There are characters to middle ride, stories that come from old and placed on the story before the film and are not convincingly told, there are actors that are not at the height (the children, in general), there are aspects that did not go unnoticed by very trudge we have the experience to chromatic level, their textures in his admirable and more than fluid mounting: all apologized, everything that I excuse. The curse of the Golden Flower is a relevant film, a visual spectacle of first order which made me remember, at times, the hue between the circus and the transcendent of Cirque Soleil, which I could see and enjoy this summer in Malaga. And that it seems by the enthusiasm on the iconic plan the narrative thing has been neglected: the script, with a few very fragile mimbres, with a simple story worthy of cthat a NAP with TV humming an archetypal SOAP, is worn with care, bringing the essence that suits each level (when custom debieramos think that the level is which goes to look at each tab of the script of the film).</body>
</review>
