<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Infiel" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Found me an excellent, brilliant film and even for a long time that it did not enjoy anything as good on the small screen of television.</summary>
	<body>Said Pedro Ruiz in his book "Think I." which "horns, not hurt when you leave, but when you look them in the mirror" nothing more true and under this premise tour the plot plot of this film. Provided that I have spoken of Diane Lane I have cited this film and as I went with Colin Farrell and "Tigerland" I have finished watching her to see if that nomination Oscar which took Diane was for something or just mere coincidence, it is also true that after this movie has been able to do what has been given the real WINSas a sign things as "Under the Sun of the Tuscan" tape for his own showcasing. But I roll not it up more and let's what leads us, for those who ever have suffered from these ugly and unsightly bultitos on both sides of the head (called horns) this film serves to feel identified with what it shown, if I put the hand on the heart and I must say that in the past I have had horns (or "billets" as they say in my neighborhood) and since then it had acted as acts have Richard Gere in the tape, on the other hand, need to be "hang" to the Sr.Gere husband and go out there to look for another. Found me an excellent, brilliant film and even for a long time that it did not enjoy anything as good on the small screen of television, has been of those movies that I paladeaba and I reveled in myself putting me rather than the characters. You can already see, one who gets fast task. I am of those who like to "suffer at home"; It is what is cinema, for a couple of short hours those who suffer are others. Diane Lane!Explendida! (I understand and accept his nomination), Richard Gere as I said and Olivier Martinez although he is an actor that I do not like especially nice (what I've seen of him I am not convinced too) the kid meets and does not entirely bad. The direction of Adrian Lane is also sobervia and music helps to lead the story where it should. I imagine that I will be the last people who has seen this movie so that too many recommendations, right? That you have not seen it like me?Then another pal' boat!</body>
</review>
