<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Remake" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Characters brought to the end and that is not torture with the enough rawness to this pessimistic fresco shot with digital camera</summary>
	<body>Roger Gual made his first feature film solo - a project that flees of cinematographic standards to use - moving to nine players to a micro-universo away from civilization, anchored to Earth by the idea that young people we are heirs of the failures of our film on parents.History repeats itself, in this case the yearnings and betrayals to oneself. The title alludes to it, a new version of those films of personal search, with same stray if characters. If these belong to two different generations, the emotional shock may be greater. But however much proposed it Gual, his film does not cause the impressions that cause other choral drama.Do the touch of authenticity supported in the naturalism of the actors? constitute the real wealth - and scarcity of technical resources has just become modus operating both helpings. While the initial idea has strength, the development is carried out with ups and downs, full of questions without answers or resolved hastily, as the escape of the sector is young as an alleged act of rebellion, wasting such a good dramatic material.Tragic comedy about what are the ideals that one day were persecuted far is clear on the script but the result on screen is not much: imagine a terrarium with bugs or Simulator with virtual beings managed to our own liking and that they leave you live; but make that no mistake, his paltry existence depends on the above. Gives the impression that the auction is unfortunate and Gual is resting on its laurels to relying too heavily on his dialogues: eccentric, funny, curious, but without the claw of the writings with July Wallovitz for Smoking room. Yet the proposal does its component of originality, although it also deceives easily? as it is known, in the country of the blind. It is not a title whose wake go to shine with great force but nevertheless serves as a double touch of attention: industry notifies necessary renewal formal and plot; the creators to Gual in this case, that not be must abused with this type of formulas although of course, they say that there is no two without three.</body>
</review>
