<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Trainspotting" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tape of cult, pending for more than one... Perhaps one of my favorite movies, this second film from Danny Boyle, starring an unknown (at the time) Ewan Mcgregor, role that you throw fame, both to him as Robert Carlyle.</summary>
	<body>First of all wanted to start with: choose life, choose a job, choose a career, choose a family, choose a big television that you cagas, choose washing machines, cars, compact disc and can opener electric equipment. Choose the salt, low cholesterol and dental insurance, choose to pay mortgages to fixed interest, choose a flat, you choose your friends. Choose sports clothing and suitcases to game, choose to pay in installments a suit brand in a wide range of fucking fabrics, choose DIY and wondering who pussy you are on Sunday morning, choose to sit on the couch to see tele-concursos that dull the mind and crush the spirit while you filled your mouth fucking junk food, choose rot you oldcagando you and pissing you above, in a miserable asylum, remain a burden for the Brats selfish and made dust that you've created to replace you, choose your future, choose life.Perhaps one of my favorite movies, this second film from Danny Boyle, starring an unknown (at the time) Ewan Mcgregor, role that you throw fame, both to him as Robert Carlyle. Perhaps this film, although it has an air gamberrete and rebel, along with "Requiem for a dream" along with "Diary of a rebel" would be the trilogy should see many Brats that begin to flirt with the joints a day, another day with the "tripis" and at the end just falling into the "jaco". Personally, find me a movie that starts awesome to see how everything goes twisting, with quite hard scenes (won't reveal anything although I guess that 90% of you the you have seen) and with some hilarious scenes. Now there is a very good DVD release for the movie lovers, only has one catch!He says comes a poster and a lie! (so you walk with eye). Anyway, that if to this we add an acojonante soundtrack, with themes of Brian Eno, Iggy Pop, Lou Reed, Underworld, New Order and even Damon Albarn can say that we we have a movie!ALMOST PERFECT!</body>
</review>
