<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Flores rotas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Commendable for its insightful portrayal of the loneliness of a wealthy, retired, donjuan who returns to the past to find a meaning to life.</summary>
	<body>Broken flowers is an existential road movie, an intimate catalogue of emotional adventures of an autobiographical languid, deep, conscious of their marginality (such as the own Jim Jarmursch) and embarked in the very noble and worthy task to seek a child who does not know and who has news for a letter pink that it makes you remember the women he loved and who will return to find it. This mild mcguffin encourages a zany neighbor fond of detective investigations, which just convincing him to leave the ostracism of his idyllic life encapullada and perfect, except because the last girlfriend has left him, which only is altered by the missive fuse of the plot.Very few acting records of Murray, for whom the director wrote the screenplay, favor the delinquencies of the trip: its introspective decline, its ability to exasperate our wishes for action be speeded up, Jarmusch is not interested in classical patterns but it feels more comfortable (Night on earth, what more splendid film) in small episodes that are assembling so, in the end, complete a unit that turns out to be the film that we are watching. Murray makes a Mimetic extension of its work in Lost in translation. His solitude is reflected in the kitsch of his home, in his retirement, in a peculiar way to understand their relationship with the world. Don Johnston, as away of romances, living lover placid retirement donjuanesca, makes the journey back to its past with the perspective that nothing of what it finds should be amended in excess its natural habitats, its sophisticated hi-fi, his large home for solo usufruct. Except the neighbour with pretensions of Sam Spade, all the characters in these broken flowers are individuals defeated by routine, adocenados, romantically immature, as the own Johnston, whose girlfriend (Julie Delphy) he has made precisely for this reason. Other brides, the old ones, are evidence that the world revolves and that no was better last time especially because already autumn Heartthrob who has returned ever found traces of what was a love of youth but sad, when not pathetic, women to the same edge of the vital disenchantment. Gives equally whatever widow sexy with his Lolita Haze to lap (great and little exploited Sharon Stone), the ex-hippy now happily inserted in the job chain, the ill-tempered repellent or, finally, lesbian concerned about animal rights (my always beloved Jessica Lange). Oh, forgot the girlfriend spread.Broken flowers is independent film, although I still am not sure what is this to say. About the independence I say this because it viscerally away from another film worked in its commercial representation, his need to please over other artistic considerations. It is also literary film, and that they have very clear what is: forged from the word cinema, written with the caress of a goldsmith who reinvent the nineteenth-century novel once a terrifying fire her would have deleted all libraries, private funds and the wide and always alien world libraries. Goldsmith is Jarmusch: their material is not entirely linguistic. As a good filmmaker, knows to suggest with a travelling (in the beginning) that coming as well as use glances, minimalist records of their actors and actresses to achieve what, on occasions, the Word does not reach. That is the magic of cinema. This is a charm. By this miracle life is always beautiful, but all have from time to time to navigate murky waters and the days are left herrumbrar by the stale air of the routine and the tedium. I do not speak in the first person. Necessarily.</body>
</review>
