<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Keane" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Intimate Chronicle of a mental imbalance growing dramatic intensity and aureolada of a fluid style suspense plot. A tiny masterpiece that will give that talk.</summary>
	<body>Anguish: this is the word. We can, in any case, find nouns that say the same thing, but otherwise. Despair. Impotence. Keane also is schizophrenia. We can, in any case, find nouns that say the same thing, but otherwise. Paranoia. Madness. Life can be wonderful, as vocingla the repetitive and weary commentator of football in the sixth, but life can be a mess, impossible to endure suffering. This is what Lodge H. Kerrigan has done: filming the suffering, give visual content to an idea that has bothered to any creator in the wide and long history of human feelings and emotions. Dispenses with all accessory for printing the story the necessary fluidity and the Viewer is not distracted in reasoning about how it happened or disquisition on the relevance of go to this or another method that illuminate the research: what is what happens? Keane, the troubled protagonist, has lost his daughter in the metro station. Everything else is the titanic effort to find it, but the pessimism lastra any option of success. During much of the footage, it seems that the task is impossible. That the girl will not be found. Keane is also mentally ill, a being that we can not always ask to act with exemplary; a being of which we are not even sure that have clear what really is happening. In this sense, Kerrigan elevates the status of the subjective work of art because there are moments in the film that we feel Keane and lose the North of reality wanting to (albeit mentally, fictitiously) convince us that it is not true. Desolation, disappointment, sadness of Keane make fatigue the city, contaminate your dirty supply of drugs, sex and confusion. This is the price to pay for the mistake he has made. Because nothing of what Keane is it is fun or is nowhere near that can lead you to the hardly imaginable happy ending that, ultimately, we all want.Not all is madness and Vertigo. The hell of the search consent meek breaks: places for the abandonment, backwaters where Keane finds himself as never never thought to find. Then reality scraped ROAR this soft surface of pure feelings. The noise returns it to the infamous territory of blame.The glory is for Damian Lewis, an actor in State of grace, which makes plausible his risky role, which do not have any time to break and where camera rummages in his emotional intimacy as a fine scalpel which diseccionase with cumbersome neatness stretch marks of mind, his go map of feelings.He also mentioned the meritorious performance of Abigail Breslin, the girl of little Miss Sunshine, which gives a counterpoint of verisimilitude to a story that's so simple, produces the feeling of being false. Nothing of the sort: Keane have a formidable exploration of the troubled soul, but also traces (and of very high quality) film of the most genuine suspense that obvious not the usual apparatus of enigmas capable of changing the course of history and do work out in several places. I insist on recommending this movie in this tsunami of film sequels that leave the viewer completely stranded on the tedium. A small masterpiece.</body>
</review>
