<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite its flaws, Pirates of the Caribbean: in the end of the world is an acceptable adventure film, which entertains more that bored, and it will delight fans of this popular series.</summary>
	<body>The day in which unveiled one of the most anticipated outcomes of recent times has finally come. No, we are not referring to who will be the next champion of League, but the outcome of one of the most blockbuster trilogies of all time, Pirates of the Caribbean. Do the most famous Buccaneers of the contemporary cinema landed finally on the Bank of Spanish theaters to offer us what will be their last adventure? or not? This third adventure begins where stayed the previous one, with the death of Jack Sparrow and the Dutch Errante in the hands of the East India Company. Captain Barbossa (Geoffrey Rush), Will Turner (Orlando Bloom) and Elizabeth Swann (Keira Knightley) depart until the end of the world to rescue the intrepid Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp) of the Kingdom of Davy Jones (Bill Nighy). With the help of Jack Sparrow, pirates around the world can deal with Lord Cutler Becker (Tom Hollander) and dreaded the Dutch Errante. First and foremost, it must be said that Pirates of the Caribbean: in the end of the world is more in line with the first delivery of the second (hodgepodge of biblical proportions), which is very welcome. This film has a more leisurely pace, there are fewer visual maremagnum and the script and the characters are more polished on the chest of the dead man. But not pears at del olmo, we may ask that the freshness and innovation of the original film (and which it should not have done, at least in the artistic sense) are conspicuous by their absence. To show us the script given new depth, Gore Verbinski gives us a tape that it touches three hours, which leads to moments of sovereign boredom among the respectable, especially in its central part. In history there are many twists and turns of the screw forced and unnecessary plot loopholes and pseudo-dramáticos moments that border the ludicrous. Not to mention some really ridiculous and infumables sequences of its last minute, starting with their own outcome. To speak of the end, a notice to Mariners: after the closing credits, there is a "surprise scene", if there are any brave hold until then. The technical section is very well covered, although still screeching the crew of the Dutch Errante, and the latest is worthy of praise, technically speaking. From here, we welcome the decision to restore the character of Barbossa, which gives us the opportunity to delight us with the great Geoffrey Rush and their confrontations with the no less brilliant Johnny Depp. Orlando Bloom is as boring as always, while Keira Knightley meets perfectly to take forward with total dignity increasingly impaired and less graceful character (both interpretative and physically). Despite its numerous and important judgments, Pirates of the Caribbean: in the end of the world is an acceptable adventure film, which entertains more that bored, and it will delight fans of this popular series.</body>
</review>
