<review author="Patri" title="La ciencia del sueño" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Michel Gondry shows that not all the merit of forget you me it was in the script of Kaufman that he also has an impressive inner world.</summary>
	<body>In this film Gondry teaches us the two worlds in which the protagonist lives: that of dreams and the real, mixing them with a clever mounting which causes that the Viewer is at many times, as confused as the protagonist, played by Gael Garcia Bernal, to which I did not see in this role, perhaps because I'm used to see him in dramas and more "serious" films (Babel)(Do, amores Perros, bad education?), Gondry has discovered his comic vein but I noticed that can be a much more versatile interpreter than I imagined.The director, Michel Gondry, writes his own script, proving their worth as an artist and as the author of film. For the first time not so has written Charlie Kaufman, who had worked with in his two previous films, Human Nature and forget about me. I expected much of the science of sleep and I was disappointed, though not to be at the height of the previous Gondry film; also has a history of love as the main axis of the story, but unlike in forget me, here do not see the end of this story but the beginning; fears of Stephane, the protagonist, and so great insecurity that has him causing strange dreams and nightmares that confuses with reality.Best thing about this film for me, is the dreams in the World immerses us and which at times reminds me of the surrealism of Dalí, almost I see in this film a work of art, when that city paper houses and cars of cardboard, this water cellophane and paper bird, I feel as if you were in front of a painting charged life with the charm of the stop motionwho left to use because of the digital effects.I think that it is better to see it in the original version (although it is always better), as in the original it is spoken in French and English and is important because it also helps to increase the confusion of the protagonist, and the dubbing are lost some important things.The science of sleep makes people laugh and makes you dream of impossible things. Michel Gondry shows that not all the merit of forget you me was in the Kaufman screenplay but he also has an impressive inner world, I hope to make us enjoy with movies like this for a long time.</body>
</review>
