<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Sunshine" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie very dignified and above the average of its kind.</summary>
	<body>Admittedly you Danny Boyle (director of "Trainspotting", "The beach" and "28 days later" among others) his willingness to do something different everytime it gets after the cameras.This time he dares with science fiction, difficult genus that has, as I said once, with a very demanding public. "I have to say, without being a wonder, yes it has made a film very dignified and above the average of its kind.""Sunshine" puts us in the year 2057. The Sun is dying and mankind is facing extinction. The last hope for the Earth lies in the Icarus II, a spaceship with eight crew members. His mission: transporting a nuclear device designed to re-activate our dying star.Beyond the incredible plot premise conceived by screenwriter Alex Garland, must assess the effort to make something credible mission thanks to some details: the use of plants to generate oxygen and food, the plates protective of solar heat, sense of isolation, the cooling of the central computer (a kind of Hal9000), etc. Of course the remarkable work of the art direction team it is helpful to do so.Bet Danny Boyle for the serious and credible, science fiction, based more on its atmosphere than in the spectacular (there that is, in certain doses). A result of this have a history whose tension is increasing and reaches have some really accomplished suspense scene.There are those who detect in the movie "2001" echoes of Kubrick and I, personally, think that they are not wrong at all. The problem arises when Boyle forgets its own approach and jumping of a style "2001 &#8243;-style" final horizon, abandons the verismo and atmosphere to finish 20 minutes quite confusing, something efectistas function." I could not help thinking, during this final, that Boyle "had left you the pot".I see another default to the film (it seems that today I only speak of defects) and is that the tempo of the mission is not clear to the Viewer. In a film of these characteristics the viewer should have been warned, with some time, which is the next step to feel adequate tension when the time comes. We must prepare it. To the not happen, in my opinion, we are suddenly and almost without any notice in a risky situation. Part of the excitement is lost in this way.Fortunately, the strong leadership of Danny Boyle and the solvency of the cast always come to the rescue of a film that is, finally, a very decent entertainment. A small shame because I think that it could have been much more.Final evaluation moonfleet.es: 6 out of 10.</body>
</review>
