<review author="Nisuyaves" title="Volver" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film basic best friend Almodovar, but with these actresses piece any...</summary>
	<body>Returns to its birthplace "La Mancha", and is in this film you recognize what you see (I do that I'm from La Mancha parents more), since the houses with its courtyard, the gates, wafers, bring you doughnuts to Madrid, the way of speaking of its inhabitants, etc. A commissioning scene very carefully, and a wise take people to shoot any other scene. Nosé if my feeling but the dialogues sometimes seemed (especially in the beginning) with too many breaks between a phrase from an actress and the reply, did me something weird.Once again reunited with Carmen Maura, who had already long, and is that she is one of the best actresses in our country without doubt, succeeding abroad, especially in France Sergi López (and speaking in French? if someone can confirm what to do). Anyway despite being one of the main protagonists not highlight much, rather seems that you deja show off to others, which caught the witness quickly.As this is a film of actors (rather only 4 women and the small role of Chus Lampreave) Let's talk about them.Let's start with the youngest (to finish with the best taste) Yohana Cobo that although the that more footage has, does not add much, I think that it lacks more expressiveness, in fact she has the scene with more dramatic charge which kills the "father" and not just transmitted.Lola Dueñas with the most "expendable" role and without much to show off, but we already know that to her need you little, his presence makes it more essential, perfect really. Also, for me, the best (well are several times) point of the film, is when the door opens, look at her sister, pauses and says screaming: "good morning RAIMUNDA!" hahaha madremía to laughter by God!Blanca Portillo, the eternal Charlotte (their loss in 7 vidas, is comparable to the Paco), which makes the best role of the film, the accent and the way they talk, their form of dress and walk, treat the family front. His voice on the phone saying to Raimunda what happens, is bestial. And her final scenes are excellent, congratulations! I much upset his departure of 7 lives, but if there will be performances like these, I am glad.For the end we left the great Penelope Cruz, because if it seems that Almodóvar is underpaid, she is very underestimated (could be its relationship with the mission impossible?). The truth is that it outboard its role, but it is that it is no longer that interpret well, do you think the character, etc. Is that when it is on screen and do you a foreground, you can't be aware of another thing, especially when you have watery eyes, I think another of those actresses (such as Meryl Streep) who with his mere presence filled her fill the screen and leave you astonished. By the way, there is a moment in which Carmen Maura says that Penelope was the girl of his dreams, remember that already was "The girl your eyes" Fernando Trueba, do coincidences?, good just curiosities.As for the plot stands very well, with the surprise that all we know, but without being a big surprise, because it would not come to tell the film depended on if there is someone is dead or not. The film focuses on the relationship mother-daughter, that makes good and relations in general, be a nearest movie and you enjoy it. So we have before us a basic film, best friend Almodóvar, and it does not leave any transsexual! Back to succeed (although with these actresses piece any!).</body>
</review>
