<review author="JLO" title="Reservoir dogs" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>From his opera prima Tarantino you can like it or not, but you never will leave indifferent. In Reservoir Dogs clearly already marked his particular and personal style that later made him famous.</summary>
	<body>The irruption of Quentin Tarantino film was a breath of fresh air as a slap to the anesthetized mainstream cinema. From his first film you may like or not, but you never will leave indifferent. In Reservoir Dogs clearly already marked his particular and personal style that later made him famous. A film that begins with the phrase: "Like a virgin is about a girl that he met a guy with a big cock"? It is a serious thing. The robberies or the so-called "homages" not distract the narration, but derived in new situations, in the known hyper anecdote of their passage by the video club, but unlike that steals for stealing, they enrich their film to the point of to his ceaseless parade of taste class B (Madonna, Japanese gangsters films, music and 70's series)not bother us and on the contrary, we are charming tastes.The breakdown of time which would later make famous Pulp Fiction is already present with the plus that is about a robbery that never looks (noblesse oblige: this was already in the great The Killing of Stanley Kubrick). Quentin takes forward its stories through banal dialogues become irresistible, crossed by a rare freedom? as the total absence of women - and with much wave by her seduction constant even in insignificant details, as these black suits parodied and appropriate style. But the base which supports Reservoir Dogs and the own Quentin - is in cash and his tremendous mounting. Assembly which shines the same way here that in Pulp Fiction and even, in the two parts of Kill Bill failed. Do as an example, the sequence of the false story of Tim Roth, far the best role for his fetish of this first stage actor, who then call for the Four Room episode is also which opens and closes Pulp Fiction.Los frenetic flashbacks never? or few times - were better used both by your information agility that gives the story tale. Reservoir Dogs is their vision of how should re - make movies so often seen in the beloved video club as a teenager. Not to mention its soundtrack, today already a classic total. His subsequent to Pulp Fiction film is as irregular as any child of neighbour. Rumors of their future projects do not show any improvement. To enjoy this new classic, re-read that review seemed so pleasant as the first time. Equally and with what has been already done, Quentin belongs forever to the Pantheon of the elect.</body>
</review>
