<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Oldboy" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Oldboy is one of the reasons why the film makes our lives happier. Masterpiece of cinema. It does lack something more?</summary>
	<body>I saw Oldboy lift me. For some time it was not beginning a day as well. I finished her ten minutes ago and I have the impression that it is not the best time to write something, but can't handle me at will in these matters and I've finished here, at my computer, ypacarai to express my absolute fascination for one of the best films I've seen in my life. I'm not sugestionado about anything that you have not read nor moves me as special circumstances that have contributed to who can see it (I'm at home, low, I'm not alone, there is no noise, the world seems that it has ceased to exist for two hours). It may be something that I can not reason I has moved to overestimate this time perfect film I have. Oldboy is one of the reasons why the film makes our lives happier, even better seeing it, I've detached from movie fan contamination that has been able to bring having enough films. At times, it seems that it was the first film. The Asian cinema is taking the reins Western film (American or European) makes time that were leaving, turning them over to some law that makes the quality with the box. To higher-quality, lower-income. I understand that Oldboy is not consumable dish easily. It contains scenes that may hurt the cacareaa sensitivity of the Viewer. Which does not stop being a solemn bullshit: can hurt you the sensitivity the wanderings of Pajares and Esteso by Franco bingos and therefore not going to put any label to their fantasmadas. Oldboy has reminded me to Almodóvar and Tarantino. By some or other causes. It has also made me think of hackneyed Greek tragedy that accompanies us through the bizarre history of literature because the arguments were designed in Greece and then the only thing we have done has been adapted to the times and modify them so that they appear to unpublished. The story tells us is that of Oh Dae Su: a type that enclose fifteen years to release with some minor clues that they will lead you to the reason of his captivity. Does not require the reader who has not seen the film more data. The embrutecido hero of the story, as a modern count of Monte Cristo, submits his revenge to the revelation of the truth of their confinement. This plot, very skillfully threaded, acquires, at the end, in the attic scene, lyric, Shakespeare dyes... If only by reaching the final and understand it, it's worth attending everything tells what us before. And Park Chan-Wook counts for a lot and does so with a crushing trade: lateral close-ups, wide angle to highlight the State of mind of the disturbed protagonist... And now I'm going to breakfast, although not live Octopus. Some already know.</body>
</review>
