<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Una mujer invisible" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An Invisible woman denounces a reality which many take back, but as a film proposal, the truth is that it leaves something to be desired.</summary>
	<body>There are few so prolific filmmakers on the scene today, both nationally and internationally, as Gerardo Herrero. For several years, Madrid filmmaker has caught the pace of making a film per season, as Woody Allen, and in addition, via Tornasol Films serves as producer in almost a dozen of titles per year. It's a true lover of cinema in the dimension of the word, although paradoxically, his film is not the most loved by the undersigned these lines. An Invisible woman is considered the successor of the reasons for my friends and the principle of Archimedes. To do so, Herrero has Belén Gopegui, screenwriter of the Archimedes principle, to tell us the story of a woman who feels invisible. Luisa (María Bouzas) is 44 years old, and feels invisible in his work for both men. To recover their self-esteem, decides to seduce George (Adolfo Fernández), co-worker, which maintains a relationship with a young girl, Marina (Nuria Gago). With A women Invisible, Gerardo Herrero explores the female universe with a sensitive look, which is not intended to judge his characters neither nor justify their actions: only the muesra as they are for that value judgements are in the hands of every viewer. The main virtue of the Belén Gopegui script is the great feeling of verisimilitude that transmits, with characters that any viewer can recognize and identify with them. However, despite this remarkable virtue, the text also has flaws, such as its lack of originality in many aspects, as well as predictable which is its final. Blacksmith does not end to find the appropriate pace for the film, sometimes too slow, and in other too fast. A point in favor of Herrero is the well that fits everything about the character of Cuca scribe (which outboard), as well as the dialogues of the dangerous friendships. The best of the film are their interpretations, stressing its protagonist Maria Bouzas that unlocked a fine work full of subtleties. Adolfo Fernandez also signed a good interpretation which could be his year, as well as Nuria Gago. An Invisible woman is a film denouncing a reality which many take back, the problems faced by many women from 40 years to be recognized in our society. As a film proposal, the truth is that it leaves something to be desired, and is not the best work of Gerrado Herrero.</body>
</review>
