<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Zodiac" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do a masterpiece calculated from beginning to end and above all very, but very? fincheriana?.</summary>
	<body>Some people believe that there are no geniuses. I include myself in this group, although sometimes I hesitate to pass to the side of those who think that David Fincher is a genius, and therefore that there are geniuses. Se7en director a genius or not, the issue is that its new and highly anticipated film is chilling, is practically perfect. Perhaps its best aspect is the Mise en scène, deserving of the recognition and awareness of many directors. Zodiac, so called, in way so suggestive and minimalist, the movie, is absolutmante puzzling, brilliant in all its aspects, obsessive, milimetrada and round.In Se7en, two very different cops penetrated to a dark world full of sins and obsessions with tremendous end. As we all know, having seen the movie or not, its end is at the moment already legendary, one of the most chilling and demolition of the last years, due to the surprise factor. In Zodiac, everything is different. The other film is somehow, dedicated to the Viewer, it was more commercial (and that does not mean bad! I think Se7en is a masterpiece!), and his last film, to somehow put it, is more intimate, obsessive and dense. It is unquestionable that two works are insurmountable, breathtaking from beginning to end, but there is a very clear difference between them, and is the first dedicated to all kinds of audiences, whether Fincher fans or not, and the second is exclusively directed to these. I do, that I think that having seen four of its six films is necessary as to assess whether catch me a director or not, I find that Zodiac is absolute, a masterpiece calculated from beginning to end and, above all, very, but very "fincheriana".As well as in the great, but not great, The Game a character introduced its own and empty mind to realize, at the end, than the life he has done has been both useless, in the film in question, in its third "chapter" specifically, the character played by Jake Gylenhaal undergoes an excessive obsession about the Zodiac killer. And it is, like the other film, which haunts not only the protagonist but also us. More that become obsessed, what I think we are to see Zodiac (or generalizing, any film director) is a feeling of adentramiento, of moral entrapment. Or I at least left with this impression of the film, and still persists me. Its end is not more than a conclusion unfinished everything what we have just submit, an eternal, but not heavy, mental torture filled with unknown symbols and characters as complex as in real life. It is said that the film is inexhaustible, with scenes of violence, perhaps not as extreme as the Se7en, but deeper. I must highlight, first and foremost, all sequences of the murders, because two of them are perhaps two of the best ever shot murders. The film begins with an air of San Francisco at night image. The camera then enter inside a car while you see very blurred and dark streets. In this same car is travelling where a young couple, which will influence the outcome of the film. From there begins the murder scene, filmed with a never before seen accuracy and a really impressive tension. Later, appears the second murder, also devastating and chilling. Pay attention to the disturbing scene of the killer behind the tree?The film's screenplay is based on the novel by Robert Graysmith, the main character of the film, also. Actually, thinking that it was he who became obsessed to leave apart his family, who was the writer of a later novel (which apreço in one of the last scenes of the movie) is strange. Fortunately or not, who has written the film is called James Vanderbilt, and we could describe as to his writing as a true masterpiece. There is a small fissure, little everything is perfect, everything is calculated up to the thousandth. Incredible is the experience of observing during the footage there is no a single one drop rhythm. Moreover, the pace of the film is frantic, claustrophobic and oppressive. From beginning to end, you feel a sense of immediacy absolutely heartbreaking. Zodiac, as a whole, is even more intense and intriguing (namely despite its outcome) than many other films with surprise ending. It is eviente that the direction of the master David Fincher is the best, or even the best of the film, with a start-up milimetrada scene and a general tension is appreciated once you left cinema, with eyes still the screen if something more happens. I will never forget the scene of the car and the woman with the baby. It is own of Fincher, own of a genius with a mind so perverse as disconcerting.The acting work is simply stunning. Stress, above all, to Robert Downey Jr. on custom made paper, complex until its outcome and with some very realistic thoughts. Your interpretation is that most told me, which most I was interested, but he would not fail to mention Mark Ruffalo and Anthony Edwards, a real pair of policemen totally peculiar and very, but very well compinchada. Do not miss the scene where fire, simple but effective. That I not just convince, then, is the protagonist (the last part), Jake Gyllenhaal, who encunetro a magnificent actor and not doubt here is wrong. On the contrary, in Zodiac its interpretation is almost prodigious, but I believe that the role is not very well drawn, or it seems to me. I hate obsessive people, and I guess that why you caught craze to his character in the most conclusive part of the film. Even and thus the cast, including the brief but very good performances of Brian Cox and Chloë Sevigny.Y Finally, highlight the paragraph técncio, where everything is absolutmanete arrogant. Photography, insurmountable. All levels and sequences are cleverly shot too. Assembly, original and calucladísimo (look at that kind of collage in motion where mixed research with the signs of the zodiac). And the music by David Shire inspiradísimo, incredible at all times (I love the songs belonging to different ages).So in short, we have a brilliant, terrifying, chilling, film catcher oppressive. Everything about Zodiac is magnificent, everything comes out from the darkness of the movie, with a calculated staging and a superb script. Do not miss, and even more, if they are fans of Mr. Fincher, now already an absolute genius. I have changed my opinion: there are geniuses.</body>
</review>
