<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Calvaire" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sickening, suffocating, timidly attached to the horror film, but it could also be an unhealthy love story. Isn't love insane?</summary>
	<body>Bordering topical, indisimuladamente fagocitando patterns exploited until the tedium, made wonderful films. Some, even accepting that dubious origin, agreeing in that they are the product of a little creative time and continuously going to sources rigorously classics drawn from where his artistic breath, achieve more than acceptable levels of quality and the spectator, foreign perhaps to these reflections of goer idle, enjoy with new readings of ancient books. We have the latest and most fabulous example of the hills have eyes in the version of Aja, which far exceeds the ajado and already passed of the multifaceted Craven model. Cult directors as Tobe Hopper again by suit, retake his works and rewrite them in the musculuso tone and modern that they mark these times of high technologies. There will also be who see echoes of Misery, the wonderful Stephen King novel and notable version filmed by Rob Reiner in 1990. Calvary is one lesser film, a new sunset Boorman film length (inevitable the memory of the great Deliverance) or the best Peckinpah and his straw dogs. In any case, Fabrice du Welz dominates the cinematographic language and makes it a very original and self-sufficient way that we overlooked that the film is literally modeled four or five masterpieces of horror movies. We have already mentioned two. We could add the dam and perhaps up to psychosis, much racing movie fan look. Unlike these, Calvary not rummages in the visual sensationalism. There is, with few exceptions, really shocking images of those who create a tension that already then it is not possible to break off. Du Welz adopts a limp, introspective ways. There are few dialogs and the plot is gaining the Gothic, terrifying and estimable suspense tone already very at the end of the footage. In its initial stretch we have no accurate record of the genus to which admits the film. I've read that influences from Haneke had. So very well. If one wants to see influences of someone, just wanting to see them. I have no doubt. The universe of taradas creatures that populate the geography of Calvary has nothing to envy to the atrocious amorales beings and mentally crippled inventory that make up the view that Haneke has of the world.We are in the deep France: is not Ohio and Minnesota. If it is the same. Fear and anxiety are universal. A crappy singer (Marc Stevens) leaves a home of the pensioner after having entertained female staff with his French song and her Gigolo to grandmothers yeyés winks. The van leaves lying in the middle of nowhere. Trees, fog, rain, a man stubbornly looking for her lost dog, a hostel in the forest run by a retired comedian. From here open the gates of hell, being here smell cow and mud. Nor Dante could have written better. This sickly, conventionally rural and folk, hell is brilliantly filmed.Shy in the management of fear, Du Welz leaves the resource of music ad hoc, pranced in house following the victim for these paths of God. Prefer a more quiet speech: you just go dropping strokes of terror. The entry in the Bartel bar, the owner of the hostel and the zombies dance to the syncopated rhythm of a worthy of the more Tom Waits drunk piano seems outstanding. Or the scene where four porters of the place benefit from a heifer in rigorous shifts. Or overhead making the room where intruders (not desvelemos nothing relevant) are trying to mount the party in their own way. Calvary not excited as it should because perhaps its tone is too gray. Confined to draw an atmosphere, to put on the table the existential void of beings absolutely grillados, oblivious to the world. There is not a single scene in which a character, except the protagonist, the injured Marc, display sanity. Even in the horrifying by kitsch, corner where he sings in the opening scenes. Perhaps the best of this film is its grandiose drawing of solitude. Or how an experience like that relates can completely change the personality who suffers from. Thus confirm the abrupt end, that formidable scene in which a few words solve hour and a half of atrocities.</body>
</review>
