<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Moscow Zero" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I don't know if this moon will continue in the film business for many years or if it will make us change your mind when it undertaken a project of greater fortune. Perhaps. Meanwhile, zero.</summary>
	<body>There must be a program type crypt 2.0 to generate arguments type Moscow Zero. I have no doubt after having wrecked my leisure in this unbearable demonstration that cinema can also a factory of scams.The laughable and regrettable guignol of catacombs, shadows moving, Bible verses and pre-pubescent ghosts fails to rescue us from the printing to be attending something awful, absolutely pathetic. One of those rare times in which one wishes to have the courage to give the stop of the player (in this case the Windows media 10 beloved). As I have not had, I have endured as a brave Eastern folly of tunnels infinities and beings marginal living, i.e. a non-mortals daily routine, i.e. shopping, tender clothes, go with their children to the school, walk through the parks, coffee with friends or moved with a melody of Joni Mitchellfor example. Perhaps what happens is we are tired of this already exhausted trend of resorting to the stocked warehouse of religion, hell and salvation by prayer. Even Val Kilmer, who should be taking gut at his California mansion rather than going cold in these European gimmicks, get Eaglets as a whole to a decent standard. Or Vincent Gallo, another actor of bells which crashes into a simplistic plot, reduced to a sleepy underground rescue children from the beginning of the century and stuffed theories about hell and the sulfur from the wicked. Already the voiceover of the Orthodox boot, a view of the monumentality of the Russian churches, a notice that everything is going to turn around its mysteries and its spell, puts a halt to the skeptical Viewer: who speaks, tells how the underworld has opened because of the sins of humans. That God and the devil touch: that bla bla bla to what Dan Brown, which should ask copyright by the extremely rich vein that have opened their shadows and archangels, his diving interested in myths of Christianity. Anthropologists, priests, mercenaries make up the absurd fauna of this silly story that will only settle for the bland public that does not stop, nor lack that makes you, in the background, to think what pigswill optical via le is inoculando. I don't know if this moon will continue in the film business for many years or if it will make us change your mind when it undertaken a project of greater fortune. Perhaps. Meanwhile, zero.</body>
</review>
