<review author="Nisuyaves" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story that hooks without introductions of any kind, with an impressive principle that does not let you remove the view a moment</summary>
	<body>As it could not be otherwise, forced me to go to the premiere that had read the book, but this time not put many impediments because I knew that day I was special, why? very simple, was the only one of the six that had not read me the book, and more importantly I had remained on the sidelines of comments on this (something like with the Lord of the rings, although there was much more difficult), so that no ideas movie and book, that if this was not in the bookIf have counted you wrong, etc. So I just watch a movie. And I came across a story that hooks without introductions of any kind, with an impressive principle that does not let you remove the view a moment, and try to find out what happens with the old dead.There was Audrey Tautou that according to reported 20 minutes even was presented to audition for the film because she was convinced her would not take, only after insisting did the test and there is now. With it I also remember that I read in a newspaper that the President of the French Republic when negotiating the shootings in the interior of the Louvre, suggested for the role of Tautou to his daughter's best friend (if colaba) what a mug.The case is that the actress portraying Sophie Neveu pretty well to my taste too pronounced French accent, there were times that not her it was understood well. To its dismay stars in the scene which I liked less, and I guess it would be something imposed from above (that we speak of Hollywood), when fleeing from the police with the car backwards and is between two trucks I think, that she is ridiculous and out of sync, they could flee in a more normal way, he moved forward and advancing cars. But good also starred in two of my favorite scenes, in which suddenly drops "Cuá?" haha I could laugh. Another scene is at the end when puts the foot in the water and says something similar to "will be that not", terrific.Tom Hanks has been criticized for his performance which I think of as normal, nothing wrong to claim, and support him to not Kiss Sophie, although you have to be in their shoes to retain impulses. So the script is right in that, to my taste, and succeeds in the pace of the film that fails to get bored at any time. Ian McKellen (Gandalf for friends) appears to explain one of the most important things in the plot which is the table of the last supper, and does spectacularly well, I take my hat off with this Mr. It is a very important moment and without getting his character, appears on screen and steals all the protagonism to the two Portas, with a magnetism to the important spectator.Among the cast meeting an actor I like Alfred Molina, with plenty of movies to their backs that I have seen many less that they would like to (remember now the piece of Coffee and Cigarettes, or Chocolat), it always does a buenísmia action, becomes his character of the feet to the head, in the Da Vinci Code and always. Jean Reno is a film that comes that you no hair, a French policeman, could not fail. And Paul Bettany gives you a tremendous tirri, which is what he has to do, so perfect, when he castigates hurts even me.The theme of this film hooked to believers and non-believers because it is an issue that is always on everyone's lips, and interest. I remember a quote from Hanks that I liked and that I use in my conversations (very occasionally) about religion, spoke of when he fell in the well and the only thing that calmed him was thinking in the afterlife or pray (not port well what), and it is that religion is truth or lie, makes people who have nothing or in limit situations cling to something that gives him strength. Highly recommended for all types of public, and for the people who say it makes many historical mistakes with the Church and others, and notice that novels are fiction and is the author invents a story, so do not say nonsense.I forgot to comment on the scene in which Shopie and Robert Langdon are directed at the Church where at the end stop to Sir Leigh Teabing, director mix on the same ground that happened long time ago and our protagonists walk, tremendous scene I really liked.After so much thinking I like the end, is that another, other possibilities create too many questions there is, there will be second part?</body>
</review>
