<review author="José A. Peig" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do not know if future generations will discover any beauty or innovation worthy of worship in this medley of styles Kitsch, immortal classics and typical universes of the pop era, but for now it seems that it is not.</summary>
	<body>Now it is fashionable do Trilogies, which does not have why be neither good nor bad, but at least we have clear that the third is the key and it will depend on the value to be attributing to this trilogy. Even more so when the episode that remains in the middle (the chest of the dead man) does much more than the being a bridge between the first and third part, depicting the true knot of history and that already showed us that the freshness and simplicity of the first installment could degenerate into a deslavazado, unbalanced and irregular "show" Baroque. "Pirates of the Caribbean", as a trilogy, is really a trilogy about the pirates, seeing the result?. Do not we think also a strange mix between the romantic figure of the pirate and the buffoonish cartoon of the pirate? Exaltation or ridicule on the archetype of the pirate? And care when it is said that Verbinski trilogy "has revived the genre of pirates" (to begin with, the "gender of pirates" don't exist as such), as shantytowns, the phantasmagoria, quirky humor and not always lucky, epic drama and other dyes, are taken to such extremes in his third installment to be to start thinking in different and varied approaches. Calls powerfully the attention the neglect and the ease with which many critics and commentators are eligible to the franchise as "palomitero film", or "film for all audiences". Entertaining film?. That was worth for "The curse of the Black Pearl". From "Dead man's chest" this has become another thing. And now, at the end of the world, attending the "movements" of the plot - which is twisted to the mind of the Viewer by the abuse of "movements" in the history of the characters, not because the plot is complex-. really someone could believe that 168 minutes you can be "entertained" the Viewer, especially teenagers who are supposed is directed the product?. Lol At first glance, the pirates trilogy becomes an unclassifiable expression of the more gross masses film industry operation, a desperate attempt to find the genuine and original in a time where it seems that everything is already invented, especially in the area of family movies, entertainment, adventures. But the result is unclassifiable does not mean that it is original, can mask a product deeply failed in its latest claims. Most importantly, the problem is the mixture of textures, blend does not respond to the needs and attributes of the adventure film. Also responds to the needs and attributes of the public. Or is that we are satisfied with four antics of the jester Sparrow and the visual in the battles delight with the suggestive power of some passages thanks to the successes in the artistic design?. Mixture that lacks a reason beyond a claim to be very specific. Along the 168 minutes we encounter frames that almost referred to the minimalist art, gestures and Dreamscapes, Daliniano surrealism at times seems an experimental film. The schizophrenia which looks doomed Sparrow in the hell of David Jones is puzzling, especially because it is not entirely located in the inherent in the character context. Of course, that a free pirate little or nothing can do with a boat settled in the desert, with horizons and to go to any part. But we all know that Sparrow is a solo adventurer and his schizophrenia cannot be justified by isolation, because that is their natural condition. Every geek can justify the scene to your tastes, but - intuitively - critic detects easily to the scenes of Sparrow in the hell of David Jones (and why is supposed to be the hell of David Jones of that form and not another? does have something to do, in fact, with the character?) are a capricious "hard" with the pretension of originality in flag. In addition, Jack Sparrow has always been a jester, what we have been saying since the first installment, but in these scenes derides the character maybe already excessive degree. The Phantasmagoria is still present in the mythical motives of the world represented, in this case, we see some suggestive pictures of the dead souls wandering under the surface of the sea or visit on the boats, towards a hell of Dante who here has the name of David Jones. The father of Elizabeth is one of the pilgrims to the death, and his farewell - the way in which disappears from the story - may be shocking. The world of the Pirates of the Caribbean is dark and sinister, is no longer a fantasy film, but a sequence of oneiric passages in which, at times, reappears the disneyano spirit. True the dreamlike texture was already in its predecessor, but it accumulates here almost scene after scene, including that battle final in a sea that is no longer the sea, is a nightmare in the form of aquatic spiral that makes shooting ships supporting the feuding sea adventurers, and the issue is not trivial as the strange feeling spread by the circle movement breaks with the conventional schemes at the time of film epic battles. Not lacking imagination nor in the scene in which the Black Pearl and its crew go of the world of the dead to the "real" world. When the Sun falls on the world of the dead, the boat is placed upside down, beneath the surface, to put right on the surface of the real world, when leaving the Sun this (is a scene so original that it can not be defined in writing, we must see it.) Point. ). As simple and evocative as suggestive and striking in the visual embodiment of Verbinski. Never be could benefit both film of a Disneyland attraction. Then appears such goddess Calypso, caught in a mortal body because of a pact between the members of the pirate Guild, which turns out to be the lost love of David Jones. Baroque, accompanied mythologies, circus humor, poetry, surrealism, tales from the underworld, oniric dreams. Movie Pirates in classic plan?. If Michael Curtiz lift head. The plot of "In the end of the world" is that already intuíamos: the final battle in which the pirates play the survival against the new order of Lord Beckett. But it is not so simple; on several occasions the characters go from one side to another, and not attentive spectator can lose with much movement. And what is worse, it is a movement not sustained on plot bases (or, if there are, are poorly developed and therefore the Viewer cannot understand why Will Turner done now and then the other and then about more than. film of entertainment?, bah) but on the need to stretch the product to achieve the 168 minutes. Fashion are the blockbusters of long duration (the fault is Peter Jackson and New Line) and we must put it in the drawer in the size appropriate based on the predominant industrial model. The third had to be the expired and should be given three hours of show. In the end. It was also predictable, we encounter the narrative saturation: too many characters, too many variables, too many themes introduced. There are so many situations and characters to develop not delves into none of them (to be more precise, not end to define its role in the scheme), just an outline fast to go fast and running towards the final half-hour, single space footage endowed with meaning and narrative meaning. The rest are mostly poorly explained vicissitudes that only make the role, as we have already mentioned, of go stretching product. Fortunately, several of these incidents not are exempt of inventiveness and imagination, from time to time we run into powerful images fruit of a splendid scene, and the presence of Jack Sparrow, although perhaps in this third installment since start to be too repetitive in his gestures and its forms, always saves time and recover part of the original freshness. These same defects already existed in "Dead man's chest", and we discussed at the time, but there were a pass due to his condition of episodio-puente. Here the harmful effect of saturation and the hasty narrative ends up stifling much of the content, and the consequences are more serious. However, in his favour, there is to say that successive "betrayals", "movements", "changes of side" of the characters, respond to its nature, or the very nature of the pirate world: the pirate is selfish and seeks to own profit. No one here has scruples if what is to achieve the goal, despite who is. Hence the constant flow of decisions and changes of direction. The idea itself is consistent and fits well with this pirate universe, but the exhibition of motives and emotional tone of the characters is so disjointed that ends by saturate the information that can reach the Viewer. This produces an effect; comes a time in which nothing matters now and can only surrender to the visual spectacle to see how everything ends, but lacks it the dramatic force and a properly exposed human deployment. David Jones was a character that they could have gotten much party, but your profile is blurred between the whirlwind of structural and narrative disruption. Orlando Bloom, which is presumed Resolutive hero, shows that it has no charisma to embody this hero. However, ultimately, the trilogy closes in a correct and logical manner, too much logic perhaps, therefore doesn't glimmer for the surprise (funny is that this product is meant to be so original in its blend of textures and instead is so little innovative in the conclusion of the story). David Jones always represent the eternal alma en pena of melancholy, the hell of the tormented love: in his last moments of life, pronounced the name of his beloved let his body drop and is integrated with the sea, which previously had also integrated the goddess of the sea, Calypso, and so, symbolically, the two lovers meet in the ocean of eternity. Will Turner redeems the crew of the Flying Dutchman and offers his love heart to be the new captain and King of the seas. Elizabeth, solitary heroin next to the seashore, where the heart of Turner and reminded her lover while he otea horizons and dreams of pirate adventures. Jack Sparrow is heading. The flat end where we see him get away in pursuit of the Sun, solo between the immensity of the sea and traveling on a small sailboat, with a map in hand, thinking about his next adventure (does the eternal youth?), is the exact representation of what always has meant and has become it an icon of the current film, beyond of his jester skills. In fact, closes a cycle and returns to the starting point. There will be a fourth installment, who doubts it. In short, more than an unclassifiable product "at the end of the world" is a reflection of the current time within the film industry trade, which aims to innovate modernising old myths and schemes using new formulas. But if not we take care of the structure, the structuring and the sense of narrative, by very good are ideas that we have on the table, the final product, with its bombast of media and elements, stagnates in the undefined, without defining its objectives (George Lucas committed the same sin in his new Galactic trilogy, but that we'll talk another day.). Hence the decline of the trilogy Pirates of the Caribbean, which started very well and might be the current equivalent to what at the time were Star Wars and Indiana Jones. Do not know if future generations will discover any beauty or innovation worthy of worship in this medley of styles Kitsch, immortal classics and typical universes of the pop era, but for now it seems that it is not. </body>
</review>
