<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Las partículas elementales" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The dream of the 68 creates monsters.</summary>
	<body>Elementary particles, with screenplay and direction by the German Oskar Roehler, orbits around the gloomy universe that dominates its literary reference, the controversial writer Michel Houellebecq novel (of the same title). This universe, inevitably condemned to explode into pieces (unless they return to the world his common sense), is a consequence of the unholy legacy received from our fathers of May 1968 - thesis that Sarkozy would he sign with your eyes closed-, that only has left us loneliness, frustration and hypocritical sexual policies. Folk slogan "make love and not war" would be diluted in the advertising claims of suffer on a daily basis on our televisions, selling desire without borders in exchange for the latest model of car. Women is cosificada and doomed to a sex without love, and you will not find this without the prosaic discretion than that. And man, linked to the fateful but for their sexual desire, not more than that, find sex and empty, that will search for camouflage under work, a good table or violence. Now, sooner or later we will have to face the sad but necessary reality of pain, old age and loneliness not deseada.«Aging alone men are much less worthy of compassion than women in the same situation. They drink bad wine, they fall asleep, it smacks them encouragement; they wake up and start again; and they die fairly quickly. Women take painkillers, do yoga, go see a psychologist; they live for many years and suffer much. Their bodies are weak and broken; they know and suffer for it. But they go ahead, because they fail to renounce being loved. They are victims of this illusion until the end. After a certain age, a woman always has the possibility of rubbing against a cock; but it no longer has the slightest chance of being loved. Men are as well, that's todo.» [The particles, p.141]The protagonists: two brothers who in principle do not know that they are, Michael and Bruno. The two in their own way subliman their (sexual, to be more exact) existential anxieties through the intellectual exercise. One as timid scientific geneticist - obsessed with obtaining someday a method of reproduction that does not require contact physical-, unable to express what he feels for a first love of children (played by a deadpan Franka Potente) which still is in love with. The other, Bruno, as depressed and repressed literature professor who dreams to fuck everything that moves, without getting more sex than that which provides the onanism or prostitution, but that soon you will find someone you love (fuck, understand us) without anguish or external claims. The two ends of the desire to illustrate these two brothers: its lack and repression, and their excessive and uncontrolled need. But both are unhappy. Michael wishes to change his life, leaving the University and delivered to an Entelechy; for its part, Bruno leaves his wife, why not already felt the least desire.The two brothers were abandoned by his hippie mother, who saw their children an impediment to express without hindrance their insatiable freedom and their desires. The own writer, Houellebecq, would be abandoned by his parents and raised by his Communist grandmother, of which Museum its simplicity of life and her happiness without more needs to do spend my life and savor (elementary particles, that would say the author). In one scene of the film, the character played by Franka Potente notes with your in love with pusillanimous laborious parents entertained together in their chores of his beautiful country house. She stressed to him the happiness of parents, based on the binomial conservative of "he working, she in the kitchen". This observation contrasts with convulsive anxieties of contemporary man, heir of idealism sexual 68, incapable of being happy and obsessed with give windmills that away it from the elemental.In another scene, a delicious Martina Gedeck reflects smiling at his brand new partner on the miseries of a generation of liberated and revolutionary women of the sixties feminism, which eventually ended up playing what criticized with ferocity. Houellebecq, and with him the director Oskar Roehler, deepen in this paradoxical fracture of the sexual ideals of those years, blaming them? as a triumphant Sarkozy - the current ills of our contemporaries do today. Children of May 1968 official of fine words that insurance is more basic: only labour, the family and respect can make happy and free human beings. The others are progres patochadas are very good on paper, but in reality is showing unable to solve existential problems of men and women of today.The final scene, with all four characters of lying on the beach, smiling happy despite the elementary candor of their joy, says it all. Sex does not give happiness, and even likely that it exists. Just as the naive and sappy dreamers, Bertolucci, trying to uncover the superficiality, snobbery and elitism of the children of father of May 1968, the elementary particles more adult and cane dissects it - without anesthesia or cauterize the lie on which sits that generation and the monsters that has generated. If this thought her read from a political level, implies the need for a revision of the ideals behind one aged (that is what he sees Houellebecq) left, depository so far of values on which settle customs and institutions. But the Viewer is which has to choose whether to read this film as a reflection of psychological about the paradoxes of desire, or as a socio-political critique of the generation of 1968. Or read anything and let go.The best: insurance, Moritz Bleibtreu, winner of the silver bear at the Berlin Festival past. It gives credibility to a character complex, full of nuances and contrary feelings reflected in the same scene without losing quality or depth. Perhaps you remember it for his starring role in disturbing the experiment, or secondary in Munich.Pero the image still I can not remove the head is this goddess called Martina Gedeck, which has matured to the delight of our eyes and neurons. We have enjoyed in the recent life of others or the good Shepherd, or in more distant titles such as delicious Martha or desired man (also committed to desmitologizar humorous social clichés of male sexual desire).The scene: Bruno throwing away your pet. Bruno asking on the street a man what has happened to her partner. The close-up with the face of Martina Gedeck.</body>
</review>
