<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El último escalón" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the best films of recent times fear. The genus has been given so many masterpieces which we must make do with correct products like this, fed from a deep respect to patterns where escarba. Hopefully come many like this. Fans, many of us, Miss them between such pigswill.</summary>
	<body>The last step is based on a short story by Richard Matheson is an absolute guarantee: the incredible shrinking man or I am legend are books of header for any fan to the fantastic of the 20th century. Comparable to the overrated Ray Bradbury, although most contaminated by mass culture industry. David Koepp, screenwriter for Jurassic Park, behind the news, the room of panic or Spider-man, and director of the domino effect or secret window adapts Stir of echoes, a tale about ghosts, although here are not interested in the abrupt effects handled based on loose book blows. Koepp prefers to ask what limits exist between the supernatural and the everyday, what doors connect both world and what people have enough sensitivity to see those doors and perceived interference by one world in another. They come to the head the others or the sixth sense, great tapes that they command similar reflections. Unlike these, the final step prefers a more minimalist, exempt from the usual paraphernalia of the genus tone. It is the terror so spent, there has been so much dementia in the exploitation of well contrasted patterns, machines of make money, which you escaman to a certain arguementos. Escuecen you so many ghosts wandering around there. Mutilated children calling for revenge. Women average rot that fatigue corridors of Gothic mansions on the outskirts of some industrial city. Starts one and not for. The list of films that obey this call fills an encyclopedia. The final step (abominable translation from Stir of echoes, stir of echoes) attends material well known for the genre fan, but respectfully, without squeezing the topics up the same parody of. Fred Murphy photography gives an ocher tone, rusted, very consistent to articulate the madness that Tom (splendid Kevin Bacon) believes brow after leaving make in a session of hypnosis, cause then their terrifying visions.There is scare: fear well filmed, without falling into acuchillantes music that tear the silent veil of air. Own spectrum of the teenager claiming, from limbo, justice, although now the Church ande redefining all this trash words with which it has subjected the will of his fascinated membership for two millennia, was selected in a rigorous casting because they were looking for a girl to walk very slowly or knew walk very slowly with harmony unless it never appeared that it was still. That or save it at six frames per second appearing, in the words of the director himself, "the actress gave a frog like jaunty". The suspense is gradual: murder behind the visions of Tom is settling in the plot with delinquent slowness. One movie more than interesting, well above the average of tapes with arguments sewn to it. Everything is written, everything is published: the viewer has already stopped looking for news in the cinema that sees. You prefer to sell you stories that you already know, but ingenien to them so that they appear, what madness, new. Only this commotion of voices, this echo of dead, is therefore a great film</body>
</review>
