<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In this third, not I've heard almost nothing, what is certainly my problem. I do not deny.</summary>
	<body>Is it over? Hopefully Yes, because I do not think that I able to see me a quarter of the adventures of Sparrow &amp; Co, mostly because I do not understand was anything. Already in the second, to the laughter of the respectable to me not me saying anything, it gave me account that was not in the garlic and I was losing jokes, winks and things.But it is that already, in this third not I've heard almost nothing, what is certainly my problem. I do not deny. If the film was full of kids less that of chest, and they held unabated two hours and average of film without leave, cry or get bored, it is clear that the film has something. But to me I had trouble finding it.I.e. Apart from the undeniable and undisputed power of many images and sequences. And that makes me remember a polemic armed in the Blog of Oti Rodríguez dealers, called precisely one of pirates, on account of a concept so confused as do revolutionary?: the Postcine.Si I I learned fairly well, that of the Postcine would be something as well as Vertigo of the images, the accumulation of sequences as spectacular as overpowering when a Cancel to the previous, without that there is time to store them in the retina. Why the postcine is starred by advertising and video clips, many of whose most famous filmmakers end up directing feature films, that, generally, the protagonists would most the sound and the fury unleashed. would the saga of Sparrow, or Spiderman, me and other franchises for the style, the representatives of this Postcine? Because it is so, they warn. I am under I. I recognize that the spectacle of some sequences of this Pirates of Caribbean is disarmingly beautiful and there are time that you alucinas in big screen movies. But history is heavy, the characters are boring and what have happen to everyone, the truth, I brought without care. I liked the Octopus man. Not be what Jones called. And I like the boats. The design and production. And some sequences of approaches. But do not ask me who are the good guys, who the bad guys, who betray who or why. Not knowing, I do not know who is living and who killed, or who are zombie or undead.I liked the sequence of the ship, the desert and the crabs by the same surreal. So monkey disneyano. The bad milk of some approaches. do but I do not think a round film, half of the jokes do not make me the slightest grace and there thanks sonrojantes, own Ozores movie like el mirón peering the crotch of heroin through some tablas.¿Merece, therefore, going to see the movie? Yes. It is worth because it is one of the pirates, because some sequences are memorable and because it is always worth going to the cinema. But, Hey, if someone was is lost, it would not be to have a trauma either.</body>
</review>
