<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El novio de mi madre" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If there is something that stands out in the film is his cast, everything else is pretty mediocre.</summary>
	<body>Do all the romantic comedies have to be equal? This is the question that should be asked the Director of the boyfriend of my mother before shooting her. According to my theory, it, ready to completely change this habit that all love American stories are very similar or almost identical, decides to shoot a film of the genre, but innovative, smart gags and some interpretations of quality. For now, this, for my taste, only has achieved it, during these years, Director Nancy Meyers (exemplary filmmaker of the wonderful when you least expect). Amy Heckerling, of the movie in question, gets halfway. Initially, the chemistry between the actors and the script seemed to be well coordinated, and I even got to thinking (only at first, again) that this would be an interesting and more than pleasant romantic comedy to the Love actually. Unfortunately, the film dives into the typical clichés of the genre and starts rolling with loves and proverbs, deception and disappointments, obviously not llegana any part. As the film progresses, the script will becoming more simple and stupid, although interpretations never cease to be bad, on the contrary, in general are more than acceptable.From the flower of evil (2002) not saw Michelle Pfeiffer acting on the big screen. If you want to tell you the truth, the waiting was worth it and her has not earned at the same time. Let's see, the boyfriend of my mother is nonsense, but the fact that 49 actress appears in she already is a plus, since not only retain their naturalness and funny faces to the Act but remains under a surgeon, I suppose, an incredible beauty. Amater film speaking on the subject of liposuction and ends up doing it with something else, and that is where is clearly seen that the film, without the contract of Pfeiffer, had not existed. Yes, Paul Rudd can be fun and nice that you like girls, but it is that she eats it live. In addition, Tracey Ullman appears as the "help on love issues" of Pfeiffer, and is really fun. As you will see, if there is something that stands out in the film is his cast, everything else is pretty mediocre.I stretch no more because you can not. We have a simple film, the cast that it filled with some really funny dialogue and situations somewhat less common than usual where only can highlight. Not recommended for those who hate Michelle Pfeiffer (I hope that ye may be few) and those who hate the romantic comedies.</body>
</review>
