<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="¿Quién dice que es fácil?" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Anyway, I join all those who recommend, given that they are, roughly 1 hour and 45 min. very well invested time.</summary>
	<body>In 1988 Sabina reflected accurately "The man in the gray flannel suit", a declaration of intentions of what could well be the character of Diego Peretti, who already knew among others for the excellent "No sos vos, soy yo", with which this film shared director; on the other hand, the tape that accompanies serious moments with others of a sublime comedy, is, broadly, a new bet of Argentine cinema abroad, especially when this tape accompany the protagonists Willy Toledo and Laura Pamplona, the first known for his involvement in "The other side of the bed" (among others) and to it by 1000 appearances in television series.The film, perhaps, can become one of those small pearls of the 7th Art, slip, flat out in the collective memory, and it is that in this case, Word of mouth, helps popularize so magna and fun (that milk) film.Accompanying Peretti, we have Carolina Peleritti, as the character of Aldo antithesis, being someone else, one of these neighboring, so normal, ordinary and peaceful areas of which one, quickly, can fall in / encaprichar be.The argument, curious facilónmente, plasma at a stroke and a thousand references, and it is that we have from the bizarre obsessive Geek, that we have seen in "Virgin at 40", friend (also represented on countless tapes) pervert estupidamente, all this seasoned with a "sauce" of moments estrambóticamente comedians.I can not come to admit that he has haunted me the tape, and that since then and given my Geek-collectibles in DVD, this film will be part of my "Dvd-teca", but if you say that some strange spring has been activated within me, and the I've caught some attachment affection.Anyway, I join all those who recommend, given that they are, roughly 1 hour and 45 min. very well invested time.</body>
</review>
