<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Amazing spectacle for the senses, with a so strange as laughable argument, which is more associated to the clamoring of desktop to a tape of noble invoice.</summary>
	<body>I must admit first thing, my reluctance towards Eastern cinema, and it is that from Kitano until Jet Li, personally "made in Hong Kong" cinema bores me supremely, and while other (more) shell shocked the virtues of this new wave of film, to me, (the less) bored me greatly, while it is true that both told me about this tape, that led I have not very clear for that reason, I have prepared to watch her.It is visually overwhelming, just that soundly, given that if the tape were silent, nor mind too and is that the landscapes are so beautiful and are so well photographed and lit, one with eyes like dishes, and like if were seeing an advertisement for paradisiacos places, it cannot but exclaim over and over again a resounding!OHHHHHH! While at times the tape has a rather theatrical cut, and is that you removing these so perfect scenarios (real or digital?), all its dialogues could have been interpreted in a stall under a patio of armchairs current and because.Disservice makes his argument, more worthy of a Venezuelan soap opera that a tape of these features, a pity that some lances, despite the convoluted plot are so predictable, and it's easy to make in less than an hour of viewing, a Feliz with the genealogical tree of the main protagonists.Zhang Yimou, aimed at a large group of actors (do the extras also count?) among which stands out a superb Chow Yun-Fat, and the beautiful Gong Li, which I fell madly in "Memoirs of a Geisha", one of the few films set in the distant Orient in my DVDteca.Hay that see what they like to Asiansfighting style "Matrix" and it is the school of Yuen Wo-ping, has caused havoc in the country of the rising sun, probably this is not the dancer of the tape, so quiet, does not lack you tiréis all my jugular, one at a time, what neck for everyone, that if, between the flying ninjas and the archers "mora you" one passes as a baby with a caramel.A negative note to his awful dubbing (Yes, I've seen dubbed what? my knowledge of Mandarin, to day, fail for both), and is that a tape of so beautiful Bill (reminds me at times to "perfume" by poetic images), you could have cared a little more voices, and is that which announces the characters in Palace, reminds me with his voice Florentino Fernández in the saga "Austin Powers" so that one little seriousness can put you to the viewing.Every time I see one of the female performers I put one and again the same question do not assume that the Oriental has little chest? Or this film is perhaps an disguised advertisement for Wonder Bra?In short, an amazing spectacle for the senses, with an argument so strange as laughable, that are most associated with the clamoring of desktop than to a tape of noble invoice.</body>
</review>
