<review author="Cp" title="Carretera al infierno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hard, bloody, tense, keeps you glued to the Chair at all times</summary>
	<body>This last night I was enjoying a classic film DVD. Good, or a film which some consider a classic. Valeee, I consider a classic from my personal list. Highway to hell (The Hitcher in original version). The first thing that comes to mind, hours after seeing her, is accustomed to the current cinema, with five consecutive finals and films stretched endlessly, that short and direct made me. Short, because at no time got bored, despite being a film much slower than the current ones, with some scenes where simply the protagonist Jim Halsey (Thomas Howell) is sleeping in the car while they pass the miles. The feeling of being there, get, that the camera does not move to jumps, and scene lasts for more than one minute. The truth is that it can be enjoyed occasionally return to a film as well. Direct, there is no large Grand dialogues and scenes where the bad looks set to kill someone, and threatens, he s'amaga, and no kills. No, here the violence is direct. John Ryder, namely Rutger Hauher in his best role (Yes, I like it better than Roy) is a threat constantly, you do not know by that acts as well, only that makes it. It is dangerous, sadistic, cruel and enjoys especially making suffer to Halsey. Not to mention some scene bright as when it is Tomb in the bed of the motel, next to la dormida Nash (Jennifer Jason Heigh) and begins to caress, unless this wakes up, in a scene that would be the Summit of the film, but were for the next scene, where the police surrounds Ryder in the cockpit of a trailerwith Nash tied to it by the legs, and with arms tied to the trailer, on the verge of being dismembered, if. It lifts the foot of the clutch, what would happen if the police shoots him. Tension by clouds, while Halsey rises to speak with Ryder.Rodada in 1986, shows us the roads deserted of Texas, in the best tradition of the cinema of roads USA, with car chases and perfectly shot accidents, a gallery of characters that we barely got to see, while appear and disappear, but that even so, we imagine perfectly, in just two strokesWhile the story focuses on the three main characters.In short, hard, bloody, tense, keeps you glued to the Chair at all times, both when there is a chase with shots, as in the dialogues between Ryder and Halsey. One of the best assassins in series in the history of cinema, unfairly forgotten in these lists we see constantly of bad movie.</body>
</review>
