<review author="Bruji" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film, in short, that defeats opponents of the filmmaker, who always think that even with a refined style, the director of the Club for the struggle obtained best results in video clips of Madonna to the finished one of his films.</summary>
	<body>Nor, of course, the argument, not even the narrative approach of Zodiac are unknown in film. However, Fincher is the first to rescue the combination; reason worth the recognition of international criticism. The invention is complemented with the improved technical and artistic ability of the director of Seven, to achieve a hypnotic result and, indeed, master.In film, few stories there are both fascinated as those drawn from real facts that make reference to cases opened on murders unsolved. Based on this, "Zodiac" is nothing more than the excuse that uses Fincher to publicize a psychological thriller which owes great part of its narrative structure to the best political thriller in the history of the seventh art, JFK (or, at least, that we hold the followers of Oliver Stone). An idea, certainly brilliant, linking the recurring argument of unpunished crimes (by truthful they are) with an accurate and effective close to the documentary approach. A work of execution precise and perfect, who runs away from the morbid spectacle to support in the austere rigour of a film that has been advised by the main protagonists of the true facts.A film, in short, that defeats opponents of the filmmaker, who always think that, even with a refined style, the director of the Club for the struggle obtained best results in video clips of Madonna to the finished one of his films. Convince those who, wrongly, we are glad that was not witness to the death of Betty Short, the Black Dahlia, who would go on to stop Brian of main attractive Palma.El of Zodiac credited, therefore, lies in the implementation of the "innovative approach" which revolutionizes the gender. If it were not because such an approach already gave him A blood cold Richard Brooks. In any case, this is not the only success in a tape full of them that elevate it to the status of essential.Following the maxim that ensures that there can be a good movie without the livelihood of a solid script, Fincher complete adaptation makes Vanderbilt of the books of Robert Graysmith with the collection of interviews carried out direct witnesses who are involved in the Zodiac case. The result, rich in information, is a saturated plot basis, which is not their own stories of the genre and, out of the film, satisfying even the most demanding of lovers, who sees his curiosity saciada.Gradually, macabre psychotic coming from the murderer, is incorporated the frenetic journalistic efforts to unmask him, which joins the police activity. Do thereafter, in three different frames, the story follows the pace of research, alternating the various scenarios and characters that make up the puzzle by dragging the Viewer to surprising findings and locking him? no rarely - in authentic dead-ends, flowing into the starting point. All this with an excellent measurement of time, a daunting Assembly, and a manipulative, expandable direction to the patio of armchairs. Zodiac becomes, in effect, into a collective obsession. Almost as much as that Fincher shown by the small details, impeccable scene implementations and the creation of an environmental stress that it ratifies the growing alarm at the time.But Zodiac is, above all, the sum of a multitude of cinematographic genius that do not pass unnoticed. The camera that, imperturbable, runs along the path followed by the unusual letter first, event source, since the "U.S. Mail" delivery truck her deposits on the doors of the Chronicle, until it reaches the hands of the Publisher. The scene of the House with basement, where cartoonist interrogates a possible culprit, which reproduces an exact frame of the evil Zaroff, film of 1.932 is mentioned in a cryptogram of the psychopath. The inclusion of a child between the central characters that synthesizes child panic the Zodiac killer raised in a generation (which is Fincher), to being threatened by who said kill them in the school bus. The witticism of the script containing the police investigations, geared towards the premise that remember the silence of the lambs: "he envies and hates is what you see every day", which brings us to the conviction that serial killers are always known his first victim. Later, reportedly killing is easy.With a city visual aesthetics, inspired by the films of the 1970s, which is extracted from Coppola's the conversation; the music of David Shire, author of the best soundtracks of the Decade; unforgettable interpretation of Robert Downey Jr., the laudable art direction, and David Fincher orchestrating the 158 minutes of footage will know shortly after. Therefore, recommends a second viewing, which corroborará this is one of those good movies that movie fan memory always uses as a reference. Welcome is that imaginary sky.</body>
</review>
