<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Apocalypto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Gibson joined this list with dignity and signed a film fresh, direct, without modesty, which enjoy equal that it suggests. Some serve the critical academic about its historicity, nor the attacks of indecent assault against their scenes of explicit violence.</summary>
	<body>The history of the celluloid has given us many films with greater or lesser success, and more or less depth, have addressed the always appetizing affair of the origins, nature and the decline of our civilization. From vindictive films of the goodness of life in captivity without the poison spread of voracious civilizing machinery, as the great emerald jungle (Boorman), the coast of mosquitoes (Weir) or the adventures of Jeremiah Johnson (Pollack), the buttery dancing with wolves or the militant gorillas in the mist, through anthropological studies as the little Savage (Truffaut)Nanook the Eskimo (Flaherty), or that gem called Dersu Uzala (Kurosawa) or films on a unfathomable and devouring nature, which just devouring who try to conquer it (Aguirre, the wrath of God). Not to mention fascinating works on potential natural destroyer of the human being (Apocalypse Now).We also have infinite eschatologies that premonizan bad which will go you to the world if follows depleting natural resources (the day of morning), investigating topics that belong only God or mother nature (Frankenstein, 12 monkeys), or developing artificial intelligence capable of replacing us or even to use as energy (Terminator, Matrix). And if we get tip we will get even some Disney products praising the rousseaunianas greatness of natural, free and carefree life (the book of the forest, Robin Hood, Tarzan), or its approaching dangers (Bambi, the Lion King, Finding Nemo).Gibson joined this list with dignity and signed a film fresh, direct, without modesty, which enjoy equal that it suggests. Some serve the critical academic about its historicity, nor the attacks of indecent assault against their scenes of explicit violence. Gibson has been a wisely seasoned film, with critics of the spicy forgiveness. Anyone who wants to see a fast-paced staging (those final thirty minutes of persecution are as beautiful as exciting). They made me remember much the end of the Emerald forest.Also thank an unknown cast and an original version (in Yucatec Maya language, still spoken in the Yucatán Peninsula) that situate us without crutches in the story you want to tell.On the other hand, who have fun drawing tip to a script with modesty and without fanfare anthropological explores the paradoxes of all civilization, Apocalypto have quite a few cafés of debate and discussion. To my opinion, Gibson? always concerned to preserve the individualistic values of build all American hero (Braveheat, the passion of Christ, when we were soldiers), or stressing the need to protect the family as a bulwark of the whole community (rescue, the Patriot, signals) does not end up choking the pursuit of capitalist achievement or fears that situate abroad (neighboring tribes) as the target of their hatred - he presents the epic of a survivor of this world trip civilized is say, immoral, dominant and complacent - in pursuit of protecting his wife and children of his egotists claws. Happiness is always somewhere else, outside of any Empire, maya or Spanish (more fierce if possible, it will not only attempt to dominate bodies but also souls to save from the eternal hell), but always in family. No wonder the end proposed by Gibson, nothing illogical.As who is not inquire constantly in family relations as a catalyst of the nature of their societies. Thus the Mayan father has two sons who instills fortress with heavy-handed (as told Hobbes, or Machiavelli, societies were founded in fear), front to the protagonist, whose father finds that his son nor topic, but measured against each other as potential enemies, and Yes knowing inside on what that is concerned. As you would say Yoda, fear leads to hatred and hatred of the dark side of the force. Things in the manual of basic psychology made in USA.Why Gibson is concerned in the initial half-hour show us the simple but effective happiness lives all small community in a rural environment (in this case, tropical), occupied in household chores and innocent laughter. Including in the batch to the typical absorbent mother-in-law. This community does not take as its own giving Earth, unable to share it with others; why the head of the clan will allow visiting tribe established there without hostility. Gibson here is American to the core. The values of the old settler? it is already known from westerns - they are love to his family and to the land (if is that there is a difference between the two). In fact, Gibson is the sixth in a family of eleven children, and he currently has seven zagales.</body>
</review>
