<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Dame 10 razones" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A wonderful, small, but for anything simple and underestimated film, it certainly deserves more applause which he had received (well few).</summary>
	<body>I don't know the reason why I have always loved the road movies. And nor is it has seen many, but when I see some of them, it gives me a sense of brutal isolation. Give me 10 reasons (10 items or less, translating the original, much more suggestive title) is not that it is just a road-movie as which they are accustomed to seeing, but somehow, either because the two protagonists (almost absolute) van in a car for quite some time, or because the message of the film is like a journey by car. Whatever it is, seems what may seem, Brad Silberling film achieves what very few get (and very few try to): mix themes and do excellently in just 75 minutes.A surprising review appears in the poster: "You know who". The film, one way or another, been talking about this, precisely. Two rather isolated from the reality people (perhaps not so much as in the great Lost in Translation) they cross the path and, as they pass the hours of the day, van knowing more and more until you reach a mutual love. Thus, at a glance, the basic idea of the film may seem too classical, but I assure that Silberling beyond your own script to images with overflowing originality and sensitivity, so that it sometimes seems that you're with the protagonists living what they are experiencing. It may seem that of so short that it is the tape is less deep. Well gentlemen, not quite the opposite. Look, Spider-man 3 lasted about twice that give me 10 reasons, and this one, however, contains dose of intelligence and morals in abundance. And it is there need to know address, must be knowing how to write. And Brad Silberling, here, is a master (olvidémos their previous works, with the exception of the commitment!). Its fun and sad film has several really wonderful scenes, such as when the two protagonists are asking each other "ten items or less" (those 10 things they like and that not of his life). There, in that wonderful sequence, is you can appreciate the personality of both, their intentions, their fears, their concerns and learn, incidentally, a little about his own life, on their particularities (albeit a toaster). The film is at all times realistic, human, and no longer carried away by the typical winks of American independent films (here are great, but a little topical, little Miss Sunshine, which undoubtedly is, in general, more good film that Slibering, for reasons already described). There are scenes that are not only fun, but they are also masterfully shot, as the Freeman talking with everyone in the hiper-mercado or the same insulting the microphone of the first supermarket.Give me 10 reasons would not give me 10 reasons if not they would have interpreted these two ACEs of the interpretation: Morgan Freeman and Paz Vega. Can it what you expected? Because it's always: melancholic eyes, suggestions that you also affect tí (I mean to the public), and unforgettable phrases as the last. And on the other hand, I at least, it did not expect much. And fortunately, me I brought a pleasant surprise to see that the unbearable niñata of the other side of the bed knows act without scream. The chemistry that develops between them two is formidable, totally unusual to be two players of very different ages and sizes. Stress, above all, the daunting dialogue at the end, where both muestrans its facets more dramatic and romantic at the same time.A wonderful, small, but for anything simple and underestimated film, it certainly deserves more applause which he had received (well few). The two protagonists are undoubtedly superb and the dialogues that maintain should be heard more than once. And is that you give me 10 reasons not only surprised but that also you glad the day.</body>
</review>
