<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Premonition (Siete días)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Premonition is a new and effective return of nut on a fairly recurring theme in the current fantasy film: loops, holes and jumps in time.</summary>
	<body>The routine of this page know of my non-existent devotion by Sandra Bullock. Perhaps this is the primary reason why, until now, had not yet seen Premonition (7 days), a film of fantastic coordinates after that, unexpectedly, hides one of the most compact of the protagonist of Miss agent Especial.Realizada by German Mennan Yapo, tape is - among other things - the intention to relaunch the eclipsed figure of one of the brides of America have been faster than destronadas; a Bullock, willing to put aside his ridiculous collection of mohines, bet to give a more natural interpretation the tormented character who gives life and on which, no doubt, lies most of the weight of its plot: the central axis on which turns his well-structured screenplay. Therefore the maligned actress gets into the skin of Linda, a married woman and with two small daughters that, overnight, you will see radically change its existence when they communicated by the death of her husband because of a car accident. Inexplicable way and the next day of receiving the fatal news, her husband sunset to her vera sleeping in the same bed.Premonition is a new and effective return of nut on a fairly recurring theme in the current fantasy film: loops, holes and jumps in time. The recent (and failed) Déjà Vu or the ingenious trapped in time, are their clearest relating two, while Bill Kelly, its screenwriter, bet by approaching more directly the melodrama of tragic dyes that action or comedy, placing the tormented Linda into a nightmare without output apparent. And it is that that poor woman, who does not know for sure whether her husband is alive or dead, must fight, every day and with his immediate environment, to move from his mind a macabre and devastating ordeal which seems to have no end.The possibility of changing the future anticipation of certain well-known events, is another of the (typical) advantages that plays a film which, despite not offering big surprises along its projection, boasts a very academic narrative, visual and interpretative correction. The ease to create disturbing atmosphere and the courage to dare with The End with some nasty and not as standard as it would be presumed, recoil somewhat to this product from other works of similar characteristics. Sometimes, as evidenced in this case, the well used clichés can work perfectly. Even taking the Bullock as the protagonist.Hope is the last thing that is lost. Maybe in a few years, until Sandra Bullock becomes a good actress. At least, in this film, has been a strong commitment to change its negative image.</body>
</review>
