<review author="Oscar Díez" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>David Fincher makes a good film excellent manufacturing but not surprising nor dazzles, still leaves a good taste.</summary>
	<body>The first thing the viewer should know to choose this film is that little or nothing here relates to the previous tapes of the director, David Fincher, the visual spectacle of the fight club is not seeking, nor leave without Truce to the viewer with a tension in crescendo to discover each new murder in Seven, nor nor pursues an oppressive in the panic room atmosphere. In this film we want to convey the frustration suffered, journalists, police officers and the population of California during the 1970s by the alarm caused by a serial killer, who became one of the most famous and unfinished American criminal history.The second thing that should be noted is that it is an excessively long film, 2 hours and 40 minutes, although they could have been cut in the editing room, are necessary to try to get all the details, evidence and records which are necessary for the explanation of the plot, that is another important aspect to be taken into account, here the viewer has to be attentive to every detail that says that it's a police thriller to the classic American style of that time.That is one of its strengths, the setting of the time is impeccable about 70 years perfectly recreated, as it is the work of acting, featuring Mark Ruffalo and Jake Bonelli, separate deserves mention Robert Downey Jr., an actor who seems to be recovered from their additions though it seems that they going to pigeonhole in roles of precisely addicteddoes not awaken my sympathies but here does a job more than correct.The plot has the years and murders that he committed the serial killer known as Zodiac, and as he could keep in check the police, FBI and CIA, since he used Cryptograms for recognize the authorship of their crimes. It is precisely these Cryptograms that call the attention of the character of Jake Bonelli, who becomes obsessed with the case and is the only one that even spending long years continues investigating and closing the stranglehold on the main suspect of the investigation and almost solving the mystery of the identity of Zodiac. His tenacity in the resolution of the mystery which gives meaning to a life otherwise, submitted to us bland, obsession for solving the mystery is which just destroying the rest of involved in the resolution, except the companion of the Doctor emergency Green, Anthony Edwards and Mark Ruffalo (if someone is bald, his image of recent years is that of a bald?)(do, because putting a pad so impossible that it lays bare the falsity of his character?), that seeing endanger his career and marriage decides to get off the search that would end with the rest.David Fincher makes a good film excellent manufacturing but not surprising nor dazzles, still leaves a good taste. Perhaps their detractors who accuse him of very videoclipero see here a better job of direction, of which for which writes is one of the great directors of the recent film.</body>
</review>
