<review author="Taliesin" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Jack Sparrow returns to command the Black Pearl to conclude the adventure that began with the chest of the dead man. Although a bit long, arriving in a few billboards that usually do not offer anything in the adventure genre is appreciated.</summary>
	<body>It seems that this year is the thing of third parties. After the adventures of the trepamuros, hits theaters the conclusion of the saga of pirates led by Johnny Depp, Pirates of the Caribbean: in the end of the world. The adventure which led to Jack Sparrow and his group in search of the chest with the heart of Davy Jones, that ended with the death of the charismatic pirate and the reappearance of Barbosa, will be resolved after another two hours and a half film with action, adventure, exoticism and some straw to fill.And it is that the story he told us in two installments could have only one. But of course, nothing better than shooting two films at the same time, almost for the price of one, and doing box twice. The problem is that fill in five hours of film of adventures with interesting material, without think the viewer has already seen twice the same scene is almost impossible and, of course, Gore Verbinsky and his team not have succeed. In the previous installment, in the end of the world also has to go forty or fifty minutes of footage. It is ridiculous that they bother to submit an a priori interesting character as the pirate captain Sao Feng (Chow Yun Fat) so then it has no weight in the plot. Neither means that an idea as attractive as the brotherhood of pirates will remain only for a scene.Fortunately, for the conclusion of the series it seems that they have focused more on the characters and, although there are, the scenes of fighting in which can not see anything have been for the start of the story. In fact, the return of Geoffrey Rush with his Captain Barbossa makes upload many integers to the film and the poor Orlando Bloom, protagonist is a priori of the saga, relegated to third Division, behind should Depp and his captain Sparrow. East final, except in a couple of scenes, has lost much of the freshness and the ability to surprise that we caught in the curse of the Black Pearl. In part because the Viewer already knows that it is what is expected of the only pirate that looks like Woody Allen, and partly because it is possible that the own Depp no longer has the goal scored in the first installment, which was not simply to become the true protagonist. Despite everything, Sparrow and Barbossa are a couple that work perfectly on screen and dare with both the action and humor. Keira Knightley outboard his role as Captain monísima Elizabeth Swann and during the film boasts several models of the collection spring-summer of female piracy.There is nothing to discuss at a technical level. There are many digital effects, but all in the service of the plot and with those that have created a compelling mix of the historical epoch in which pirates furrowed the seas and a fantasy in which almost everything is possible. The soundtrack, signed again by Hans Zimmer is perfect for this type of film and differs little from what we have already heard in the past.In summary, Pirates of the Caribbean: in the end of the world is a film to which takes it to boot (does not until that Jack appears) and whose last-minute footage is film adventures of the good: action, excitement and humor in their dose fair, with a pace that keeps you glued to your seat until the end. The penalty is that we have to go through almost an hour and a half of filling to get up there. At least one leaves cinema with best taste that left us the previous delivery, although equally tired of pirates for a season.</body>
</review>
