<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Candy" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Yet another film about the dangers of drugs. Here is portrayed the matter with sincerity, without embellishment. That is appreciated, but as lacks it a pinch of bad milk, acidity.</summary>
	<body>Love is an addiction and who is destroyed by get it, keep it or deny it. Candy portrays the physical and moral decline of two young people hooked to the heroin.As all predictable, Candy can be seen. Don't need that the script of a surprising return. We know at all times when of physical decadence and moral of the couple are. I'm not surprised see them prostitution or steal. Nor do they break all family ties or that sacrificed the love which seemed sincere and deep by the journey without return of the drug. These films are almost always similar: the bar on the Ribbon of Blake Edwards, days of wine and roses, is very high. Leaving Las Vegas raises a different speech: the destructive vocation.Candy and Dan, the couple from the movie, can't be kids who have discovered a deadly toy too soon. There is even a vision the couple naïve at times. When Dan gives a kind of robbery, there is an inevitable tufo comedy fool. When Candy is prostituted, the hidden camera carnal evidence: only the intuímos. Same goes with Dan when he does. It seems as if director wanted not to be overly coarse: borders the ends and precisely that decision lastra the film towards the asepsis, impiendo us involve something more. Days of wine and roses had strong scenes, but it was supplying with an immeasurable dramatic climax here, unfortunately, is not.The three parties comprising the film (heaven, Earth and hell) could be independent. The director (Neil Armfield) not amused at the expense of the viewer and offers a decent show, honored, written with deep respect, caring for the light and the dialogue, which is not abundant. The reciters in off of the poet Dan are peach in syrup: is could have dispensed of this poetic tone. On the other hand, the painter Candy writes on all the walls of the House in which they exposed and in those texts, future palimpsests of some unrelated to the plot tenants, are beautiful and very decently written. Heath Ledger and Abbie Cornish are not Robert Downey Jr. and Courtney Love, but manage to shake with her willful delivery. Geoffrey Rush as talludito friend, gay and drug addict, makes a fabulous role, but leaves shortly and we are eager to see more. Almost deserves a film he alone. It is not a masterpiece, at all. Not a notable film. It is left wanting for mediocrity, perhaps because the theme is very crushed and needed another way to be counted. This us we know. The andazas of the toxic couple is already enough view. Vicente Aleixandre said it better: "everything is apparently enough not surprised". Then that.</body>
</review>
