<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="300" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>awake 300 spectators. Because any brave proposal creates controversy. For now, Snyder is on the right track. A filmmaker of the new century.</summary>
	<body>Zack Snyder with his second film proposes a cinematic experience. It is not a novel experience but, rather, brave. And as often happens in the world of cinema, any type of differential value has to face, fortunately, the controversy. 300 baby of two important references of the last film of the 20th century: Matrix and Gladiator. From the visual, the virtual, the accelerated narrative discourse and music. the Wachowski Brothers film. On the other hand, the recovery of the epic film under the prism of Ridley Scott; talented director that opened new horizons with Alien and Blade Runner. how to tell the same story (we are talking about battles, Gladiator, historical episodes, revenge, heroes.) but from the perspective of the new century, in which the audience has grown with different values and from the visual, it has fueled video game and advertising (not forgetting the music video clip).Matrix was the first formal proposal and revolutionized the scene. Gladiator was the surprise. A classic story from modernity. Followed fashion, exploiting you the boom of the genus, with Troy and Alexander the great. And as often happens, when exploited more than enough coxswain the thing it stalls. These two films provided nothing already met. In any case, they stirred up the interest of those who wanted to relive past experiences. The same happened with without forgiveness, the recovery of the western, or saving private Ryan, new war exploits.The next step gives Snyder with 300. Specialist, to date, update genera. His previous film was one of zombies: the dawn of the dead. Now in 300 revitalizes the epic film through a speech well known for thirtysomethings enthusiasts (ultimately the public of this type of film): the comic. Snyder has drunk from the comic book and moves it to the screen. It does so in the hands of the work of Frank Miller. To bear in mind that the next production of Snyder is another comic, Watchmen's Alan Moore.El cinema, purely commercial, ran out of stories and industry resorted to an inexhaustible source of superheroes of Marvel and Dc. It now remained to delve into this post-modern comic, more well of antiheros, such as that proposed by Miller (remember the adaptation of Sin City). The visual over the speech. Aesthetics as a discourse. Virtual reality becomes the main protagonist. The special effects in the service of the creation of new worlds. The Anatomy of the action goes beyond the screen. The marginalization of any talk of political or ideological. I, at least, do not see. A satire? It may be. awake 300 spectators. Because any brave proposal creates controversy. For now, Snyder is on the right track. A filmmaker of the new century.</body>
</review>
