<review author="Raccord" title="Con la muerte en los talones" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Electric mounting, fast-paced script and the support of the music to create an atmosphere of suspense and speed that no one has been able to match</summary>
	<body>This film is considered by many, others (including not myself) prefer psychosis, as the best work of Hitchcock. There is no doubt what is one of the major and the most representative of his style. We found all the elements that define: electrical installation, a fast-paced script and the support of music to create an atmosphere of suspense and speed, that no one has been able to match. Hitchcock was widely criticized at the time by his "commercialism", but for which we understand that film, as well as a form of artistic expression, is a form of entertainment, filmmaker orondo is an absolute genius that deserves to be claimed.It is one of the films most commented upon by Internet of all his production, so I cannot give you can repeating data. The only thing that surprised me is that nobody mentions the crop-duster plane scene in pursuit of Cary Grant, so I'm going to pay tribute to him my particular analyzing her. Interestingly, perhaps the most famous sequence of the famous film, coolly designed absolutely no sense: do not have the bad guys a way better kill the protagonist shooting from an airplane? They are in the middle of nowhere! Did you egg! Accepting that they are not very intelligent (or very megalomaniacal) and that they have decided to kill him with a machine gun from an aircraft underway, why the first time that pass over the poor Thornill not shoot you? and more so by what noses are so very bad aim? Four times they spend and are not capable of injuring the good or one. And already to culminate the lot of Follies, why crashes the plane into the gasoline truck? Were the pilot and drunken gun? Instead, watching the film you're so mesmerized, that you not notice, and to do so, or you care. Just want to know how will be Cary Grant it. There is the magic of Hitchcock.</body>
</review>
