<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Réquiem por un sueño" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fascinating descent to the underworld of drugs. A fantastic vehicle to operationalize the Visual resources of a formidable director.</summary>
	<body>This it will of ageing in a filthy room only when the children have gone and you only have a television and a refrigerator. It will also of dreams: because nobody wants to die in an ancient building of Coney Island and there are methods to trick the reality and our fantasy to acquire flight and blind us. Requiem for a dream is the toughest loneliness portrait film can give except the closure of Edmundo Dantés in the island of If. In this story Daronofsky does not seek patterns in the ridiculous twists of the bag and passes to Mystic with the phonetics of the names of God to find happiness in the arcane Symphony of mathematics in the world. That made in Pi, the Pearl in black and white that left us halfway between disbelief and fascination. In this case, the author returns to the Holy Grail of the human soul, seeking happiness unstoppable. It gives the same that comes from a chute of heroin or a television program. The characters of the film fatigue shadows in search of light, but not catch up. None is happy and we know that you will not find that happiness in the film. All are addicted to something: drugs or television programming, but both elements are evidence of his solitude, of its abandonment. Aronofsky conceived the film as a compendium fragmented images that matrimonian perfectly with the tortured and also Sub-Division brain of all actors. Some lose sanity by excess of drug. The mother (an absolutely perfect Ellen Burstyn) is placed with television contests and the Pilgrim idea recover the figure that had as a young man to power flush mounted in a red dress which represents the malgastada life, sacrificed time. The music of the genius of the electronic Clint Mansell, attached to asphyxiating strings the Kronos Quartet, is one component of the film. For a long time (Oldboy, very recently) not noticed the physical presence of the soundtrack in a film. The final climax cannot be conceived without the disturbed melody that brush the abrupt ending. It is not easy cinema: not so wishes. Digested with difficulty and leaves a number of appalling images in memory. The frantic camera movement, sudden acceleration of the tempo of the images and, above all, dizzying Visual tics that Arofonofsky comes with excessive and imprudent frequency.Fascinating descent to the underworld of drugs. A fantastic vehicle to operationalize the Visual resources of a formidable director.</body>
</review>
