<review author="Bruji" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Coconut still fail chestnuts. The continuous covenants and betrayals, and the creation of a gay character, constitute undeniable successes of the script. And us continuos with the dog!, cause of my only joy and utmost concern.</summary>
	<body>Almost as an axiom, the thirds in a series often overcome, often the first, and always the latter. There is a nearby landmark in the return of the King. At the end of the world, beheaded the goose that lays the golden eggs, the apparent existing decompensation between a weak script and the technical virtuosity that accompanies it, clearly miserably. In the background, the consolidation of some undefined characters that already have own name in the history of the seventh art.From the depths, emerging / El Hidalgo of the seas / purge its outstanding debt / with the world in her hands, / anchored the helm, presto / already grasping at lontananza / to the mocking feared / his Majesty of the South seas, / by all known as Captain "Bloom".Embarrassed that feel me Espronceda. The same that arrebolaría to Raoul Walsh (he as well measuring times) before the cluster of absurdities sponsored by the "great" craftsman which is repeated after the cameras. Ay if Michael Curtiz reaching up head!. If Robert Siodmak would have had half of technical possibilities in his time. If Jacques Tourneur had approached the Knightley. If Byron Haskin arrives to find with this cake. What waste of special effects and what an absolute lack of imagination. Will have you heard about the writers of Borden Chase?But let's go by parts. Coconut still fail chestnuts. The continuous covenants and betrayals, and the creation of a gay character, constitute undeniable successes of the script. And us continuos with the dog!, cause of my only joy and utmost concern.That fascinate, the curse of the Black Pearl, pleasantly, surprised. The adventures of approach were ransom of the film abyss; their misadventures, returned to conquer, and the impetus given to the fantasy, unconvinced, did not upset. In this way, we are witnessing excited at the opening of the dead man's chest (or was the other way around?), which, basically, was devoted to disappoint. A unforgivable conception of the script placed the action in three different scenarios for the showcasing of its main protagonists and torture of the Viewer. Out of the cinema, with the boiling cerebellum, few recognized Captain Barbossa... nor to the mother who gave birth.The undersigned, refused to drop moorings and in order to avoid a sinking announced, decided to review both the first two parts, not to be missed on the high seas. He lost and was wrecked. Let's say that, in the end of the world, the scripts are not convoluted, but unintelligible. With a deliberate confusion, profusion and dissemination of ideas, Elliott and Rossio only give option to the enjoyment of a purely visual product. The impressive home is diluted in the Singapore nothing more breeze sail, dives into the immensity of his own plot inconsistency, timidly emerges in the awaited Assembly of brothers and marking course towards fruition, is an insurmountable cliff to navigate.The telescope, now allows glimpse an effects spectacular without limits, wrapped in three endless hours of footage, in which we shopping to find only a small escena-tesoro, two beautiful images and three phrases that not I refuse to mention.The first of these, sent to the director: "Do you think that it has everything planned or it will be improvising on the fly?". The second, reserved for the outcome: "the world is still the same, but with less incentives". And the third, which does credit to Depp: "no cause is lost while a foolish willing to fight for it is". Poor Johnny!, main object of the tribute carried out on fantasy. Worse is offered to the Little Mermaid, with that huge goddess Calypso imitating the bubble, I say, the Ursula the sea witch.The scene is none other than the Emersion of the Dutch Errante. and her brand new Admiral. Images, a floating currency and that boat, a cloak of stars which, in absolute silence, crosses the sea. Movie fan memory drags us to the relaxing spacecraft Kubrick Waltz, and a hasty assessment: in the end of the world, do nor spreads the sound?.With regard to the distribution, copy of my previous criticism. Excellent Geoffrey Rush. Orlando, a delicacy. It would not be fair that Jack Sparrow preserve the actor, to the detriment of the magnificent interpretations obtained under the orders of Tim Burton. And Keira Knightley, technically perfect, but with an alarming lack of chloride of sodium in vein. I would add that the hat of china sit very well, and stress the successful performances of Stellan Skarsgard (Goya of Milos Forman) and Keith Richards (of the Rolling Stones guitarist).And no, not I was in the cinema to see the "after from" farewell false final credit titles. This, that every week pirated it the time, refuses to write about a quarter. Clear that, by 9 a real 8... who knows?.</body>
</review>
