<review author="Bruji" title="Retrato de una obsesión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Through a long flashback, creates a fantasy - at times, ridiculous-, on the transformation of the protagonist.</summary>
	<body>It was only a matter of time before an atypical director repair in the strange work of an unusual photographer. As it was expected, the result away from formal biopic, to build one of these cinematic oddities which are much appreciated. "Dignify that others despise, what it is if not"politically correct"?.""I have a secret?"I tell you one. The heart of a woman is full of them. Stanley Kubrick knew it and, in his usual line (i.e., better than anyone else), he explored them in Eyes Wide Shut, his latest work. In reality, are many, "that not they fit in the immensity of the ocean" (Titanic), and many of them derive from the question Ernst Lubitsch made Jennifer Jones in the sin of Cluny Brown: "What is your site?". Does anyone know what is yours? And if it were wrong?At the end of the 1950s, Diane Arbus, wealthy family, decides to change the course of his life. Perhaps because "we only have a heart and we must be faithful" (loving dangerously), perhaps because there is only a life and need to decide how to use.It is precisely in the fictional characters of Rose (Kate Winslet) and Sarah Jordan (Angelina Jolie), in which we find the film references of this real character, a woman who, having everything you may want, drowns in a world which is not compatible. But, as the worst reality always beat the best of the fictions, here there will be a powerful cause to abandon, and itself an exemplary husband prevents it. It is pointless to position itself next to one or the other, because the two will be right. or none.Original way, the film part of one of the photographs of Arbus, a portrait of naked in the living room, this time in movement. And, through a long flashback, creates a fantasy - at times, ridiculous-, on the transformation of the protagonist in Butterfly. It is known that there are two stories that contribute in the jump, Alice in the country of the wonders of Lewis Carroll and the film by Tod Browning La Parada de los Monstruos, to contain the presence of "other worlds". Those are who she is interested, those in which they live "aristocrats" of the unusual. But, above all, know that there is a person that influences his work irreversibly, Lisette Model, which is none other than the mysterious neighbor (bear) who stars in this story; an outstanding success of the script.This new life, as all insecure of their self-worth genius, leads to self-destruction. And it is at this point where the director wins respect for this movie fan, the same he shows by the character that is. The respect with which deals with Olivier Dahan the figure of Edith Piaf in La Vie en Rose. Which Miguel Hermoso in Lola, the film was never given. And it is that our film is different because we are.From this moment, the footage becomes a succession of portraits, predominating the close-ups of the characters, impossible frames and an exquisite photography. Another success of the direction, basically, indicating that this film is not a walk through the life of the photographer, but an accurate overview of their work.The third hit is the artistic direction and the fourth and last, Nicole Kidman.Sin, however, the first three are declared insufficient to save a story which, inevitably, sinks. The subtlety of Wilson to show a Model as the clear reference in the bisexuality of Diane, fades to develop an account of diffuse and directionless technique of rhythm, with the inclusion of an element taken from a film by Cocteau, beauty and the beast, which will only serve to that film critics fill their columns. The director, for his part, always strange and, in other works, brilliant (Secretary), not unify the various pieces of gear, constantly using the main actress who, at any time, fits the character. The character suits the actress. For this reason, the tribute, more than for own photographer, is, in not few occasions, for Nicole. Nicole in jeopardy, the others; Nicole as housewife, Las women perfect; Nicole, tormented, the hours. Nicole has cost us an eye of the face and her we squeeze to a lemon. Nicole, a white combination of straps and a coat of hair (from what part of the hair would be the neck of the coat?) in some unforgettable frames that remind us of Elizabeth Taylor in A marked woman, by Daniel Mann. His partner, Robert Downey Jr, will be most convincing cat than human.The result translates into an abject failure at the box office at United States. In any case, ignoring this fact, they should know that this is a rare movie, similar people. I recommend it.</body>
</review>
