<review author="Bruji" title="El retorno de los malditos" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Never were second parts good?. Not so painful.</summary>
	<body>Never were second parts good?. Not so painful. The new nightmare of Wes Craven - predictable, simple and indigesta - conspicuous by the self-destruction of their dialogues, by the absence of originality and inconsistency in the script, by the inconsistency of their characters. And you make the mistake of doing without the only intelligent elements of the series were not other than dogs.Locate the reader. The return of the damned is the first sequel to the hills have eyes of Alexandre Aja, which, in turn, is a remake of the hills have eyes of Wes Craven, which, to his own, took another sequel, the hills have eyes 2. Too many eyes, so far, totaling four films, three directors and four writers. Come on, the nightmare goes to night terror.Do with the clear influence of the massacre of Texas, in 1977, the Carter family visit some ancient mines of silver in the middle of the desert, to be attacked? it is unknown why - by a repulsivamente repellent things. A wildly original story at that time that, arrival at the moment opportune and censored in several countries, it becomes a cult movie, catapulting to fame to its young director. Eight years later, the survivors of the massacre (the dog and some more) returning to the scene to configure a completely forgettable, improper of the acclaimed master of the horror film. In 2006, Aja, an expert in terrifying remakes? that already prepares for Piranha 1978 - resorted to night of the living dead of 1,968 to explain the repulsivo-repelente phenomenon, and La Noche and La Matanza to realize the presence of the new Carter in New Mexico family. The result satisfies those who are unaware that you it's a remake, the gore soft lovers, to fans of the genre and the critics, which considers it the best film of the year. So far, all happy, nerviosicos perdíos jumping into the seats, screaming with closed eyes and vomiting in the bucket of popcorn.In this way, taking advantage of the good reception of the mutant bugs among new generations of moviegoers, the Craven (father and son) improvise an attractive script for adolescents, which dispenses with the family environment that characterizes the saga and relies on archetypal characters coming out of Scream. Between the clumsy mini platoon of recruits ducks and novices, not miss the boy handsome without brain, Lieutenant Ripley in the Earth, the head of brave Turkish Mission, funny bastard, the friendly goonie and that it is not known what makes in this story. Of course, it would not be a sequel with eyes if not mainstreamed into the cast to the young mother who takes the brunt.Sitting the bases, only there to cause a fire to distract, to try to reach the top of Iwo Jima without Beach and develop an adventure in Fraguel Rock singing the song of the ten Negritos. On this occasion, with nine soldiers who went to explore, one was lost and eight are to remain.Do the "interesting" script, filled with unimaginable bug (remember the timely suicide of the Colonel), gets in the hands of a skilled director at dizzy with the House that AVID of viscera, you forsake the close-ups, los suaves retimes and sound effects for? more than scare - bother. Meanwhile, the torturadora soundtrack not accompanied, but that pursues; the surprise factor is non-existent, the forced touches of humor, ridiculous; and the message issued, americanamente devastating. And it is the largest of the pacifists becomes quarrelsome cruel when the occasion requires. Violence, is (therefore), sometimes justified and they manifest as well.Gone, far behind, was the genius of Wes Craven? director of the last House on the left (based on the spring of the maiden of Bergman), awarded in Sitges, creator of Freddy Krueger - to give way to the orgy of blood and sand that opens the door to all kinds of excursions to the sector 16, Final destination in unwary tourists. The current box-office success you can follow many more hills with eyes to the detriment of the less worthy of quality indication.Definitely, Hollywood is not right to make war on the phantom menace to the already consolidated Japanese horror film. Even with their heaviest artillery.</body>
</review>
