<review author="Bruji" title="Tu la letra, yo la música" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not convinced or lovers of the genre, which does not comply with the fundamental objective of the romantic comedies - which is to fall in love and fall in love with - reaching a fun ending that would be perfect if it had succeeded in create something coherent before the closing credits.</summary>
	<body>Atypical romantic comedy-free narrative pace of bland script and few pretensions, which culminates in a story in which two big stars of the genre operating under its discretion, evidencing the apathy of the director and torturing their detractors. Fortunately, out of the film, the viewer only recalled the music of a catchy song by Adam Schlesinger (The Wonders). The lyrics, as the movie itself, better forgotten.The premise underlying this film is commercially, perfect. It is none other than the meet in the film to two generations through music. To do so, is used to Pop!, an attractive group that had existed, would have caused furore in the charts of "Popularísimo", the mythical Albacete Popular Radio program. While for pre-teens girls claim, creates Cora Corman, a crossroads of Britney Spears Christina Aguilera, that might well belong to the contemporary Top 40. The strategy works, and the nostalgic ochenteros succumb to the video clip of "Pop Goes My Heart", clever way, it combines the dance steps of George Michael with the unmistakable style of Simon Le Bon (the more "Bon" of Duran Duran), the attire of the new Human League romantics with the shirts of parallel botonadura popularized the Soft Cell, and the close-up showing the exotic empty gaze of Spandau Ballet singer with the Chess Board that appeared on the album of Yazoo. Reasons, all of them, more that enough to support two hours to Hugh Grant.Pero, as nothing is forever, the powerful top ends, the musical magic of the 80 is reduced to brief allusions to the poetry of Stevie Wonder and portentous tours of Tears For Fears; and the harsh reality we face "the worst movie of this year and any other". And it is that you, the lyrics and I, the music, he fails the formula of the best romantic comedies, and spare you the main theme of the soundtrack of the history forever playing secret Limal.El if the constant is to prosper?Boy meets girl - sudden infatuation-terrible event that leads to an inevitable break - moments of sadness are recreated with a beautiful song-reconciliation - Happy End - depends on the capacity of those responsible for the footage to elevate the fussiness to romanticism, making credible absurdity. Just have to remember how a glove leads the rapprochement between the characters of Serendípity, the elaborate process of falling in love which fragua in have an E-Mail, the betrayal of a bet which leads to the breakup of somebody as Tú, the melancholy that surrounds the solitude in how to lose a guy in ten days, the spectacular reconciliation of secret admirer. Or what is the same, all those titles where, for very trivial to make the plot basis, the scripts have been worked. It is not the case of history that today we discussed, in which situations are implausible and enforced.The truth is that it is hard to believe that, even the writer of Miss special agent, has been able to conceive a few such regrettable dialogues, that contrast with the depth charge, fleetingly, grasping in the story, and that its failure could be due to translation tasks. In reality, we can only enjoy blur profile of a great woman who, because of a destructive critique, becomes a being of hipocondríaco and insecure, and the interesting comparison between a person and a song in which the music would be the first impression, the physical packaging, sex; and the lyrics, the spiritual content, the soul, love. A real shame that a so beautiful as a direct message is diluted so sloppy as tedious development, framed in painful couplets of fifth of primary papers.Paradoxically, the table of salvation, Grant, become stone that is tied around his neck. A fact that is often the case when consecrated actors are dedicated to "stars" in the shooting, ignoring the directions of the director. Do happened to the selfsame Brando in the disastrous rebellion aboard the 62 to Val Kilmer on so many occasions, and he has not able to resist in a role that? it was - you closer to Ewan McGregor in Moulin Rouge. Nonsense almost as large as that is committed to make sharing history with Drew Barrymore. Those who believed that it could not exist a couple less chemistry on screen that formed by George Clooney and Zeta Jones in Intolerable Cruelty, were wrong. We have seen that it is easier to imagine an "affair" between Fernandez de La Vega and Mariano Rajoy, one starring the four weddings and A Funeral and the Angel of Charlie.El result is a product that does not convince or lovers of the genre, which does not comply with the fundamental objective of the romantic comedies - which is to fall in love and fall in love -reaching a fun ending that would be perfect if it had succeeded in create something coherent before the closing credits.Before size goer chagrin, Relax,-who would say Frankie Goes To Hollywood - Relax.</body>
</review>
