<review author="MrDaine" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is soda, devoid of rhythm, of substance of interest and with the feeling that all the participants in the film are aware of this</summary>
	<body>The history of the cinema has many and varied examples of bad books adapted to major films, some of them so big that they have traded their own context of adaptation. The Godfather, jaws or Jurassic Park, for example come me to memory. Books which, apart from its literary qualities, have reached the screen stomping and making their mark, as the silence of the lambs, or Lo Que El Viento Se led. It was quite obvious that the Da Vinci Code could have entered perfectly in the same group, not the height of certain titles, but have done a worthy role adapting a theme that could have given so much of itself.Well, because not even that. Faced with the film by Ron Howard, fearing to fall into a substantial bluff, nothing more to see the cast. Too many familiar faces, I think, all in poster. Too much interest because we see how many famous people involved in the film. Too many aires of over-production.Let the movie begin commented me that it is calcadita to the book, which I am not surprised too because me has come from other sources that the book only lacking the relevant dimensions to convert it into a screenplay. So me I grabbed to the coke, I open the potatoes and note.After the film, I can only say it is bland, lacking in pace of substance of interest and with the feeling that all the participants in the film are aware of this. It is as if from the director up responsible for styling horribly to Mr. Hanks all knew that the film does not have any chicha and limiting to recite text and move the camera waiting for not much delay in ending the scene. The film is sleeping, and not only blame the book to which suited, but the entire production itself. And why, in my opinion, we are dealing with a subject that could have left a big blockbuster, if only had apetecido them enhance it: when they roll to explain all the stuff of secret societies, historical figures wrapped in a historical conspiracy, and tests that have left behind in their works, only then seems actors to recover a bit of life in their faces and are interested in the subject, doing a little to the respectable part of this (although at that point already are all more than boring). In other words, have a history that like everyone, linking characters and historical sites with dark power plots and secret societies. Something trite, is true, but this are born the blockbusters: of topicazos. And if you know well bring those topicazos, you can at least provide a decent result. However, in the Da Vinci Code all leads with the most absolute unwillingness, worry only in make it mascadito of what will roll with unnecessary flashbacks loaded with budget and continuous references to the same concept as if the public, as well as fool, idiot.So there is little to say of holes of script, of the lack of historical accuracy in more than one fact to release, or the fact that half of the puzzles, supposedly of ancient origin, are subject to modern English. There is little to say of a film whose authors are aware of that are no more than a small part of the huge marketing operation involved in the book by Dan Brown, and that they are not limited to makeup, albeit with a little bit of show. Da Vinci, moreover, it is not even the heart of conspiracies. Only a famous name to bring the masses to the book, screen, or the hundreds of books whose title is composed of a celebrity and a synonym for "code". And with this movie box office data, do not be surprised if in a couple of years we have the box office full of subsequent adaptations?</body>
</review>
