<review author="Bruji" title="Arthur y los Minimoys" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Adaptation to the screen of a tale of four volumes, he wrote in his spare time, and which pays tribute to (or plagiarism) all accounts that are likely to be honored (or plagiarized).</summary>
	<body>The French director Luc Besson writes and produces this story of fantastic Court and good intentions, where the bombers are friendly mosquito and the long-range missiles, tomatazos. A film that has nothing to envy to the American productions in its execution and the outcome of which will be not revealed another thousand years! (from the minimoyco calendar). I am not I get accounts!. Luc Besson not only said, but it also boasted, that shot ten films, but ultimately announced to the French chain RTL this? according to my information, the number nine as director - is the last. The truth is that few things there that I add in the trajectory of the peculiar filmmaker, screenwriter and producer. And it is this man knows how to make all or, at least, has enough money to try it. Come on, that el capricho dizzy with the camera, write scripts without sense, heat the mood with surprising outbursts and teasing the viewer with subsequent unlimited boredom can give. Against what it presupposes, these parameters are unchanged in all of his films, which do not have more than ten minutes of interest. (León, the professional, either). A few licenses that can afford because, in addition, finances and distributes his own works (I am abstaining enclose them an adjective) at the international level. Perhaps, if his film dispenses of the spectacle that has made it famous in the lockers and cared a negligible detail called quality, you could be considered Alexander Korda of the 21st century. account legends about a taxi which is now in the fourth installment, will produce the last work of Jodie Foster as Director. who knows?.In any case, we are left not knowing whether or not the Minimoys is his latest film. If it were, it would be an excellent farewell. A film of perfectly executed, but it employs a cheater script of dubious originality, with possible autobiographical overtones.It's adaptation to the screen of a tale of four volumes, he wrote in his spare time, and which pays tribute to (or plagiarism) all accounts that are likely to be honored (or plagiarized) so far.To begin with, and even at the risk of being no need to comment that the intrigue of finding out what "Al otro lado" already her had a real writer of children's stories, Lewis Carroll, a hundred and forty years ago. We continue to reach the conclusion that "there are other worlds, but they are in this", and admit the existence of "small kind beings who are living with us", in fact, the tiny. will not yet, there is still more!.The initial approach of the script revolves around a problem of eviction, resulting from the imminent abandonment of a home that will fall into the hands of unscrupulous builders. To avoid this, the child protagonist has to resort to the search for a treasure. We are obviously counting the argument of the Goonies. A legendary story in which master Spielberg incorporates flat long linking the world of the sewers with the surface (the scene of the well of wishes), which is exactly what makes Besson, on numerous occasions, in this film.The creation of an adventure that takes place in the own garden of housing, since we already knew it for love miniature is not novel, I have shrunk to children, in which a drop of water causes a flood, or flowers are comfortable dwellings.Selenia - Bell is the daughter of a King good-natured (as all Kings of all the Disney Tales), a Princess of new generation, of those who know take care of themselves and are not afraid to deal with the danger. It is even possible to be friends with some heroin from Shrek. Of course, that alone can not release the magic sword, in the past called Excalibur. For that, it employs the protagonist, which, curiously, is called Arthur. His parents, incidentally, are a few irresponsible as the progenitors of Mathilda and the poor boy is always alone, as the child of the rescuers in pictures. The meeting of dance on a vinyl record, it becomes a hint of Pulp Fiction of Tarantino, (which already had honored at Antz), but soon opts for the paths of Robert Rodriguez, to finish with an unusual sentence: open until dawn. I not forget the stick insect addressing his followers, in a well traced scene of the Lord of the rings, the allusions to Jumanji, with an African tribe that nobody knows where it went or what does in Connecticut. I.e., that that "our story begins in the heart of Africa" is as false as to believe that there is no string to save the waterfall (the minimoy leads more than a thousand in the backpack). It is usual that recent years animated films contain "winks" adult film to be more attractive to parents, only that there are more than wink, nervous tics in Arthur and the Minimoys. Not to mention the Hydrophobia, the mansions built illegally, the problems with the IRS.Nevertheless, I'll be good, him I attach an approved by know mixing, skillfully, the innocence of the fantasy with reality, sometimes unpleasant and not always easy to hide from children.In summary, a film "terribly original", but well done; more than interesting, interested in not stop blinking to kids (by the rapid succession of images), and well-suited for a few dates in which you try to believe how beautiful it is to live!, our House looks like the cabin of the Marx Brothers, and there's always who can afford a breakfast at Tiffany? s (as it must be at the gate).</body>
</review>
