<review author="Bruji" title="Apocalypto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cinema of excellent quality, that captivates from the first frame, does not grant truce, restless and excited.</summary>
	<body>If the provocation personified, he would set his residence in the USA, it would be Catholic of Irish and equipped with a rear nice descent, he would meet Wíinik Ma name? Ki? imakkun óol in Mayan language, (be can translate this for "undesirable"?).Despite everything, Apocalypto belongs to a type of film of excellent quality, that captive from the first frame, does not grant truce, restless and excited, so it should seriously consider the deletion of some scenes requiring to close our eyes. Filmography of Gibson will be perfect when leave of side effects, such as nausea and dizziness in the Viewer.Mel Gibson, that bad actor, that great director that so many things, very interesting, has provided that count.Her armed with the passion of Christ, and when was accused of making a "gore" version of the New Testament and blaming Jews for the death of the Nazarene, the Christian Church (of Rome, also) he looked to his appeal, the Gospel according to St. John gave him the reason and Pontius Pilate continued washing their hands in public event. If I had not forgotten one of the three Marys, of Clopas, yours would have been the fifth Gospel, but as he said Wilder, nobody is perfect.On this occasion, returns to generate controversy by offering what is considered a vision skewed on the Mayan population, by putting his cruelty and ignoring that you it's one of the great civilizations of the pre-Columbian America. Do we are going, it is not likely to get a sa? at if? ipil (pardon) to return to Mexico. in defence of the neoyorquino-australiano film, it can be argued that, by placing the action in the days prior to the arrival of the Spaniards, all that is left of the once thriving Mayan civilization is a virtually extinct culture, who represented no danger to the conquerors. A village, in effect, auto-aniquilado, as shown in the film.In the absence of exact chronological references to specific geographical locations, it can be assumed that an episode of rivalry between independent cities existing at this time is telling (quichés, zutuhiles, MAM), the so-called florid wars that was aimed at the capture of living men to be sacrificed to the gods, as reflected in the Maya stelae and the frescoes of Bonampak. An appalling exercise in which based the reason of its existence the fearsome Aztecs, nightmare of the bearded men.On the other hand, the director also shows the inheritance of their high architectural and astronomical, knowledge that had reached its splendour six centuries ago, in the ancient Mayan Empire. In the 16th century, there are not even the great city-States of the new empire, which has been torn by infighting; still, approaching us to the "city of stone", with its hierarchical political system, its main monuments, religious fanaticism and its mathematical accuracy in the prediction of eclipses.It is not alien to the fascinating legends of the Popol Vuh (written in quiché maya), nor to the millennial prophecy which predicted a new start followed by five hundred years of darkness, which forced them to hide their elderly at the top of the mountains in the interior of the jungles, to preserve a wisdom that has come down to our days. (Not going badly aimed, in the old world burned them more than three hundred codices).I.e., that Gibson movies can spare you explicit images always, but conscientiousness has never lacked.However, they miss least some historical data to close the script and, incidentally, cultivate the respectable. For that reason, out of the film are many doubts that assail the curiosos-ignorantes like me, such as who is the conquistador Francisco de Montejo, year of our Lord 1527?, city of stone is Technotitlán?, "unknown brutal force" which is that of the Aztecs?. A few questions which are not response in the "How was shot", so we return to the starting point, to quote the historian William Durant goes for "almost" all cases (obviously Mr. Gibson, knowing that "A great civilization doesn't it conquer from outside if not has destroyed itself from within" does not justify the permanence of the United States of America in the 21st century Iraq).And little more can be reproached, perhaps (to continue with the controversy of the Yucatán), the hiring of an American Indian that gives life to a Mayan Indian, as Rob Marshall (china rather than Japanese) in memoirs of a Geisha. Moreover, at the cinematographic level, the direction is perfect; production, impeccable; the address artistic, unbeatable; All interpretations, superb; the costume, craft; photography, breathtaking; mounting, particularly distressing, and narrated history, the more courageous legacy that a town could inherit, the only that gives meaning to any life, which encourages, which encouraged to rise up. and to fight.</body>
</review>
