<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Bailar en la oscuridad" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Review of the musical under the Prism more light of the Dogma or, in other words, a peliculón worthy to be included in the bombastic and fascinating history of the seventh art.</summary>
	<body>Turbulent atmospheres from where comes the miracle of the image: dancing in the dark is a dazzling visual poem, a delirious cacophony iconographic where less matter the ride of the characters that the sensations they feel and how explicit them, how capture the viewer's attention and embaucan it (that must be pure cinema or pure literature)(: deception, sleight, fantasy assembled with sanity) that, in the end, entranced by the flow of emotions, let him stricken in the armchair, knocked out.Lars Von Trier closes the Golden Heart trilogy (breaking the waves, the idiots and now this dance in the dark) with this melodrama with contours of this melodramatic musical or musical, fascinating vehicle for an actress rookie although sufficient in a role intended for his histrionic and shameless divismo. Björk is Selma, the Czechoslovak immigrant blind rompe in pain that his son does not suffer his same disability. The greedy neighbor steals the money he saved. Selma murders. And it is judged in an American Court. That it seems that I'm telling the film: nothing has been said. Anything that does not come more extensively developed in the DVD tab or the usual chronicles in magazines or on the Web.What love of this film is its premeditated stripping of all theatrical artifice. Not in the style of Dogville or its logical sequel, Manderlay, but obeying the same visual pattern.The tragic heroines of Von Trier (breaking the waves is an ingenious hybrid between religious and erotic feminist film between Bergman and Dreyer) are angels who aspire to heaven and must travel a true journey on Earth to deserve this award. Selma seduces by its epic nature: Björk employs what better do (compose, sing) for seasoning the dramaturgy of the film with dressings of poetry. The own face of Icelandic singer is the best claim of innocence, goodness and the naivety of Selma. We do not we would understand the tape without the winged, fluid, mystical presence almost of this actress not exploited, who has not returned to the film and that was perhaps only intended to represent Selma, the alter-ego who lives his happiness in their own way, of eyes for inside, fantasy and his pure love of madre-coraje struggling to overcome the convecionalismosthe severity of the society and the injustice of the system. However, there is no political border. This is a musical: an original nauseam.The whiteness of the human, the beauty of the soul and the fragility of the human emocines faced to the tenebrism of fear, darkness written by men for suffering of man.Or life is very sad, in the background, and requires the eye candy of dance numbers and the lyric of the melodies to return it the fugal joy. You only have to see in detail, jubilantly in the detail, the scene of the train with the circus dancers on the road, to us already convince the genre can be rewritten often make is missing and not died in West Side Story or leaden designs for adolescents as Grease.Hay films that don't ever forget you like little or you fascinated. This deserves to go into the chapter of the immortal films in memory. Because of the pain it causes. For the suffering reverberado skin of Selma to the artificial screen of a cinema and hence, in magic acrobatic Pirouette to the more sensitive neuron you have. Or as them it melts you all.</body>
</review>
