<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="El retorno de los malditos" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The make-up and prostheses are the only thing that can save this movie, where everything is fairly simple, repetitive and unoriginal. Or the genre fans will be able to spend an afternoon entertaining with this return of the damned.</summary>
	<body>After the interesting remake of "the hills have eyes", directed by Alexander Aja, we have "The return of the damned", sequel that adds nothing and to take a step back in the genre again.The best without a doubt, is the teaser. Easy, simple and 100% effective, which while a southern music, the camera is supported in the desert. Then it passes one of the damned by dragging one of its victims, then see as another of the murderous strip one of the chains of the soil, and the camera is twisted, realizing that it is a subjective of the other victim.Therefore, which is why I understand that they have managed to "trick" to someone, as the script is quite unfortunate, as well as the start-up scene and other elements. Almost everything that the first part was virtues, Martin Weisz throws him down, with a simple story with some tasteless protagonists, in which ever you find affinity or empathy with monsters that leave a lot to be desired, and a film which is unsupported by any side.Not everything is the fault of the director. Wes Craven and his son Jonathan, are responsible for signing this "script", in which a group of military come to the mountains to deliver material to scientists and colleagues of the army, but upon arrival, are only uninhabited base. The cast is quite unknown, embodying some soldiers are not just very professional and expert, and who will have to manage them if they want to survive. The first flaw is that to be armed and be military, the public does not feel close to them, nor is put in its place. Just in case this was the case, we are presented with a range of characters that represent different aspects of society, including the anti-war soldier, mother, pretty girl, the Hispanic, African-American Sergeant, generous etc. In short, a sad campus, which was not thinking too much to the Craven in creating them. The make-up and prostheses are the only thing that can save this movie, where everything is fairly simple, repetitive and unoriginal. Or the genre fans will be able to spend an afternoon entertaining with this return of the damned.</body>
</review>
