<review author="Taliesin" title="Dungeons & Dragons" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you like the role, the fantasy film and dive into adventure in the style of the Lord of the rings, more better that you keep away from what is insurance one of the 100 worst films of the history.</summary>
	<body>Yesterday I felt a bit masochistic and myself to see a film that, even knowing that it was the worst, I woke up some unhealthy curiosity: Dungeons &amp; Dragons. The film is in the year 2000 and I remember the trailer had no bad paints, prompting many unwary pass through box office, with the consequent later casting. This is one of those occasions where the audiences and critics are agreed and with good reason. And it is that this movie is not bad, but very bad. The surprising thing is to discover Jeremy Irons in the cast and I guess, although it is true that many years ago that not catches a role in conditions, it should be drunk and drugged when he signed to make bad malísimo in this production is that worthless or of telefilm for the hour of the siesta.¿Y what is wrong with Dungeons &amp; Dragons? The first thing that comes to mind is the script, simplistic to the maximum and with zero interest. Scenes will chain is a few other bordering on the ridiculous. And if you thought that it can not stick to the funny black character who dies first in a film like this, you equivocabas. Is like painting sunglasses to the Mona Lisa, but it can. In any case, the problem is not the script. Or, better said, it is not only the script. It is an action-adventure film, but the action is of penalty and the adventure also. The characters, the start-up scene, special effects, the dialogues. everything is laughable for a film that apparently came with pretensions of overproduction. Scenarios, weapons and objects are a mixture of plastic and cardboard stone and the worst is that it shows. The costumes seem to they have taken them from a play of end of course or the nearest town costumes shop. It is as if the entire universe of D &amp; D buy her clothes in the store that the Robin Hood of Errol Flynn.Para make us an idea, the dialogues are at the height of the worst chapter in the fantastic car. Come on, that neither in a fantasy world of D &amp; d so bows can be. Bad, very bad and cruel, are idiots. And the good, apart from being idiots, are courageous and slaughtered. As already awning (feel annoy you a great movie like this), the funny black dies and it is assumed that it should be a penalty. In fact, want to applaud and all you ask is that, please, anyone know a spell of resurrection. By the way, that there is a magician in the Group and I think that it makes three different spells throughout the film. In fact, even dares with combat melee (should have gone the way of the funny thief).In summary, Dungeons &amp; Dragons is a set of nonsense at all levels and what should be an entertaining film more unpretentious turns into an hour and half unbearable without feet or head. Since then, little has this to do with D &amp; D and does not work or as a production of adventures. For the moment, we will have to make do with the animated series which is what more has come to what may be a game of role, and that it was not big deal.</body>
</review>
