<review author="Taliesin" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Zodiac puts the viewer in the skin of the researchers who worked in the case of the multiple murderer who performed in San Francisco at the end of the 1960s. And he does it with such luxury of details that is overwhelming.</summary>
	<body>Hits theaters the last tape of the director of jewels like Se7en, The Game and the Club of the fight. In the light of these three films, it is clear that David Fincher likes the complex plots, with turns and in which nothing is what it seems. It also seems that in his film the characters are above everything else, though without neglecting an artistic direction that provides lot of realism to his works. With this in mind, we can say that Zodiac is the sublimation of his way of understanding the film, Zodiac is based on the true story of the multiple murderer. It is not the first time that a film is inspired in this particular killer series, Dirty Harry or the Exorcist III already approached the character, although they did so with a very cinematographic language, while Fincher to bet on a near approach to the documentary.And this is Zodiac remains with scrupulous fidelity events and research surrounding this mysterious character at the end of the 1960s and during the 1970s. And this is the main attractive and shock of the film. Since that you see on screen credits well-established await us two and a half hours of police investigation that in many moments reminded me to JFK or the dilemma, which possibly will deter many viewers. No matter whatever you sell it: Zodiac isn't a thriller. Those who accept this last and approach the film will find a great movie, a lovingly placed in the characters and the setting as we rarely see.The film is based on real events and as real life is brutal at times, but without recreating in easy blood. In fact, Fincher bet by the psychology of the assassin, putting the spectator on the side of those who seek to unravel the mind of the psychopath. There are no spectacular findings, miracle resolutions, nor incredible twists. The director has not given or a bit of margin to the usual cinematographic resources and has followed police investigations and the book by Robert Graysmith. Of course, in a movie as based on the characters needed some outstanding performances and so are those of Jake Gyllenhaal, Mark Ruffalo and Robert Downey Jr., with a role that comes as a ring to the finger. To highlight the artistic direction that the passage of nearly two decades in the city of San Francisco has captured brilliantly and allowing the viewer travel thirty years ago, when mobile phones and computer files were thing of science fiction. The appearance of almost documentary is accentuated with a full picture flat media and without too many tricks.In short, Zodiac is a film with a comprehensive and complex plot, as it is the reality. Its main virtue and at the same time default, depending on the Viewer, is the zero concession to entertainment film, it does not mean that it is not entertaining. That Yes, to enjoy everything what offers requires us great attention and yet is not easy follow everything that happens on the screen. Nevertheless, if we are not losing the thread too will succeed understand why Zodiac crimes have become the obsession of many in the last forty years.</body>
</review>
