<review author="Jose Luis" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tape that is intended to be serious and realistic, but forget altogether that the novel original is a novel entertainment</summary>
	<body>A couple of years ago a film unwittingly I take hair to many of the viewers and it is not that you have lied them, but that if it presented the plot in a realistic way, almost like a documentary, what caused that many people be her projected asking, inquiring and browsing the newly emerging internet trying to discover if the plot of the film had happened really. The film is called the project of the Blair Witch, and the phenomenon apparently is about to derepetirse the code Da Vinci.Y film is that all we like stories of mystery and conspiracy and more if a tape like this, "reveals" more or less credibly a "secret" jealously guarded for centuries, with the "potential" to change our history, because the truth does not need us much on our side to create a realistic fantasy.I must confess that I am one of the millions of readers who have been seduced by the "Developer" book and that I remained until the wee hours of the morning reading and reading trying to figure out what the next track, which is the next key to be resolved, so entertaining and intriguing was that on more than one occasion reached exclaim: "one chapter and I sleep."Change the tape, on the other hand, rather than take advantage of the exciting and fun book, aspect focuses on creating a drama, a tape that claims to be serious and realistic, forgets completely that the novel is a novel entertainment. So intense persecution, threats and fights are replaced by scenes quenarran the "true story" of Mary Magdalene, with two separate produced Flash backsque go back to two thousand years ago.The long minutes and even hours that Robert Langdon and company spend trying to decipher the intricate mysteries and codes, in the tape are resolved instantly with a photographic memory and other more characteristic of a X-Men.Y skills although it seems impossible, writer failed to copy the plot as is and in its attempts to "improve" became a long experiencetedious and cold flooded abusively flashbacks trying to tell the past of some of the characters, but forgetting altogether give growth during the plot, blurring them only as one ingredient, to make complete the gimmick and not as true drivers of history.And fails, in addition, to the portray with more strength the relationship between the two protagonists, which in the book is very important and in the beginning of the tape her force, so a few minutes both are fleeing.But perhaps the most unforgivable mistake, to my point of view, is that production achievement strain to the Museum of Louvre, filming in the Grand Hall, managed to have access to the most famous painting in the world, to waste a couple of simple shots. A great failure for all involved, except for Sir Ian McKellen, printing charm to his character and now one of my favorite actors.</body>
</review>
