<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El infierno" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Incisive, cold, nothing commercial: demonstrates that there is European cinema of moviegoers dyes, although the script and ideas are provided....</summary>
	<body>Krzysztof Kieslowski left three scripts for titles of biblical reminiscences. Tanović Bosnian retrieves the author of the trilogy humanist views / three colors. The story of three sisters to vivien the suffering of a devastating child episode: the newly come from prison father, rejected by the mother and committed suicide. Broken innocence, vital disillusion and pain as a backdrop of a life led by a secret that will slowly twisting the existence of these sisters. The vision of Tanović is sad: there is no hope in the world drawing. The family exists to catch-up or does not and the circumstances, routine or random lead to that I think that there is life within these women and that the feelings that explicit will unite at the end and all. Chromatic formulas of Kieslowski uses Tanović to reflect the intimacy of each sister (blue, red and white/green) and also uses the symbolism on the passage of time. Some excess verbiage lastra the fluidity of some images that already have by themselves. The consent of solitary confinement is not reflected in a tiresome theatrical speech, occasionally. Perhaps that is why the tape I was cold, far removed from any passionate. One of those uncomfortable movies that catch you, but want to drop because you not agree what he says.Life is beautiful and sometimes choked with bad drinks, said crudely, but hell should not be family. And that, after all, is what Tanović comes to tell. His gaze toward the fundamental issues of human existence (paternity, incommunicado detention, family, love, desire, suicide, fraternity even..) is an academic pessimism varnished.Lack of burning. Are not dealing with a genuine work, written from the heart: is peek echoes of the cinematography of Bergman and the own Kieslowski, clear, but for those who have not seen anything about these two prodigious filmmakers, hell is a snooty work that comes from a man hardened in war (in no man's land) and in another kind of clearer hellmore carnal. Ultimately, this is the origin of the other. Perhaps the evils of this world come from the silence of the family. Tanović was drawn this universe of women so pleasure to our Almodovar after having triumphed with a film of men, war and nothing intimate which received even an Academy Award for best film from non-English speaking. The female cast is masterful: Emmanuel Beart and an avejentada Carole Bouquet are splendid. As said the own Tanović in any press conference: who the hell was at home, were not going to Afghanistan or to the streets of Baghdad to see it closely. Absolutely right.</body>
</review>
