<review author="Txapulin" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This third part is slightly better than the second. The argument is still not take anywhere, but at least is something more linear and less convoluted. Action scenes are well resolved and others are pathetic.</summary>
	<body>I must admit that this third part is slightly better than the second. The argument is still not take anywhere, but at least is something more linear and less convoluted. Action scenes are well resolved and others are pathetic, like "wedding" in the midst of the battle of swords, and three hours of film is still excessive duration, though not to bore.It is appreciated that the character of Jack Sparrow recovers the charisma of the first part, starring a couple of excellent and surreal scenes with a multitude of Sparrows on stage simultaneously. The scene of the ship in the desert with rocks and crabs is precisely the best of the movie. Also the recovery of Barbossa, one of the best characters of the first part is a success. Of who I was expecting much more is of Chow Yun-Fat, who plays the captain Sao Feng, and in addition to having little charisma, in the movie looks rather little. And on the gracienta to put Keith Richards, then find something surplus, but it clashes not as much as I thought. What is stupid is the scene where appear nine big Pirates of the seas, not so much for the scene itself, which is grace by the characterization of each one of the pirates, his ships and his crew, but by its consequences: a supposedly incredibly big by the number of boats in disputed naval battle is nothing because the battlewithout ceasing to be spectacular, it waged only between the two main boats and others are pure comparsa. This kind of things, in addition to the main characters change sides as the wind blows and without any logical explanation is what makes the absurd argument.Moreover, it is a movie, just like its predecessors, of great plastic beauty, and here I include from the sets, makeup and costumes to the photography, special effects and the music. total, if like the two previous ones and want them to see three spectacular hours below: go and see without remorse, will be equal. By the way, they have, as in the first, there a nod at the end of the closing credits, if they want to wait ten minutes to leave the room, which does not come from here.</body>
</review>
