<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Half Nelson" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do Half Nelson seems a film Professor, as the of?Newspapers of the street?, but in reality is a film junkies, as?Trainspotting??Days of wine and roses?,?Long trip of the day into night?,?Days lost weekend?. Deeply subversive.</summary>
	<body>Half Nelson seems a film Professor, as the of "diaries of the street", but in reality is a film junkies, like "Trainspotting", "Days of wine and roses", "Long journey of the day into night", "Days without trace". The difference between film made by drug addicts and the no-adictos, is that we always dreamed to improve something: conquer the girl, upload post, fix any problem. The dream of the drug addict is to stop him continue as it is, his dream is one dose. The tranquility that we pay the letter of the Bank is the same with which they are facing the threat of desaucio. Abusers of the film approaching death, physical degradation, with the same concern that the sober arrive late to an appointment.Dunne gives some great classes in a multiracial school. The day that is animated suggests children forces that cause major transformations in history. The day which has hangover falls asleep in front of them. The first half of the film is shot to insist on something that we already know, Dunne is an imperfect man. The explanation of his life seem shot by someone so hung as the protagonist. Some ability to synthesis would have been more than welcome. Instead of so many hangovers have been enough one, instead of so many characters have been enough any conversation.The preambles to prepare us for a retrospective scene. The Professor decides to save one of her students, but when they are we don't know who is the Saviour and who the victim. In her classes explains that the reality is complex, there is a good and an evil, but a dialectic of forces. The entire scene, perhaps throughout the film, is a series of variations on that theme. Teacher and his pupil, the drug addict and the camel, the hero and the girl. All the lines function as a deeply subversive melody within the vital staff of these two stocks to the limit. That penalty that musicians spend one hour tweaking instruments before starting to play.</body>
</review>
