<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La matanza de Texas: el origen" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Recital of viscera orchestrated by a mechanical saw, a deranged brain.</summary>
	<body>Sometimes it is possible to separate the film as an artistic expression, regulated under the Government of beauty or critical thinking and supervised by sensitive creators of cinema as mere trade, subject to the laws of the market and supervised by merchants. Financial gluttony, your WINS do box can match the artistic ambition. There are many examples to demonstrate this assertion so blunt. The reader can think some. There are hundreds. As there are thousands of absolutely reprehensible clunkers who only appeal to the metallic sound of the dollar or the euro and supplying the curiosity and the need of human beings of spiritual food frivolous, thin and perishable. In view of the rapidly deteriorating of the inventive and original resources, film - company - threw contrasted hits, advised by advertisers and sociologists and found the goose that lays the golden egg by with the happy idea add a number to a profitable film. Whatever its year of production, an argument not just in the "the end" classic but requests a continuation, a second part that, if you give substantial dividends, would generate a third and so ad vomitum. The film - as art - lost his aura of innocence and earned as company unprejudiced basing rights in the international port of gold and silver. Honest sequels save this fascination with little think and live income more in tune with the philosophy of television and its fragmented programming than with a sense of closed unit and work finished, which is inherent to the traditional and accepted concept of cinema.Here not just this little story: the last treasure of these filibusters of frames has been the prequel it, which is a term of dubious acceptance by our ínclita and Vinto SAR, but that is already playing us all. It's search for the past of what worked in the future. Assassins in series with a childhood to discover. Galactic sagas which require a solid narrative explanatory to appreciate the context of what we already know more peering. This Vertigo disturbs the viewer puduroso, which should be providing level and lantern so not to lose in the bare-faced rocambola of flashbacks, memories, and stories lost in limbo for the time you need to know to avoid losing the plot of what the designer is going to plug it.The film rises and redo these skin operations that leave the skin more smooth, but most chemically polluted. Guilt or some of the blame has it the magician Lucas, whose monumental history of galaxies has opened a path inconceivable a few years ago, but hardly erasable and that any filmmaker in distress or any greedy producer of pasta goes because cinema, no mistake, it is not always art and sometimes leaves Assualt by these matters unrelated to the real cause of their existencethat what can be leave annotated in another letter.The issue before us, have a prequel of a remake or what amounts to the same thing, an ancient history in a modern history which is a copy of an intermediate history. And no joke: here than it is to watch the movie and think little or even think about nothing. And enjoy, if you can. We enjoy the massacre of Texas, the origin? Half. That give a child to a psychopath is like find the point G to a pack of hungry Lions. Here take the classic Tobe Hopper of 1974 is an abuse. There has already been enough versions and all have an impact on what the first avoided: the trail of blood, the pornographic gore, intergubernamental massacre with viscera, amputations and other savagery sketches by the mind of a beast without a brain with the disfigured face and a stinking leather mask covering it. The animal will we wear with a mechanical saw, we release it in deep America (Texas, what does the State, all have basements and morons reventonas lost roads) and already just need the cattle to decapitated, which tends to be a fresh herd of beautiful females with hormones to explode them tits and bruisers of proven effectiveness in the revelry. All we know, they are going to die and we sat comfortably in the armchair to attend cutting. The proposal of this novelty of video store (it is not another thing, it should not be) is a scam because not says nothing of what's on offer with sanity and rational sense of the plot. Leatherface, the bichaco, the bloody murderer, was born in a slaughterhouse and grew up on the edge of some guys that educated him in the tenebrism of a weak society, isolated and converted into a parade of cripples mental trying by all means do not suffer in this world and, above all, do not go hungry. In the grapes of wrath, when they passed by hunger, not roamed the dusty roads of second looking for bait to accompany the soup in the pot from noon. Because here the family eats guests and they santiguan and call upon God, as in the famous scene of Tara, that will never go hungry. So very well. Lately I can not think of Freud when I see film. I can imagine how frotaría hands with the Barque mindless American society, portrayed in his film, has given to the world. Or Korean. Or Danish. The cabronazo of the moto-sierra should pass them on straws in his early childhood school. They will laugh him the greatest thing. That then it was hired as a slaughterer in a meat company already gives the pattern that is going to develop its bloody existence. Already. There just the origins mentioned in the title. Then there is action and brutality until the paroxysm: all young people who randomly threw the tragedy end up pitted, open channel, all cash shamelessly, exhibiting a more direct contemplation of the crimes. I have not been I never lover or even friend or known of that genre called gore.It has repelled me the abundance of white blood cells and the pure vision of the viscera to eye level, but this touches the "X" classification and me I have seriously promised never again fall into these lapses. There film good to deal with a life watching a movie after another without another concern that go to the service between pass and pass and eat, perhaps, and drink or stop suddenly to assimilate apparently and return clean heart and avid stories. Movie buff, there is one fact: r. Lee Emery, an actor of great and little seen, is the Sergeant porculero of the metal jacket of Kubrick and here is the man his moment of glory when it assesses on the back of one of the youngsters trapped his speech of discipline, authority and value.Jonathan Liesban, who directs this massacre, never better said, has classic material and shoots it with ex officio. I do not go to consider the efficiency of a director or compliance with a technical equipment or sharing. I do not go because maybe there are no ridiculous pieces or beginner errors. Until I read Liesban was a craftsman and that has been able to do more than I did. Everything is subordinated to the rigour of history: at the marathon of gruesomeness that will delight the genre fan, that have no doubt. Anyway, I am now preparing some of Fritz Lang for after dinner. Or I go to the original Hopper, so beleaguered in his day, as delivered to the ferocity of criticism, that did not understand the lack of psychology of the characters or the sadistic brutality of the spot. That was the beginning, and by starting there all the original tape - covered at least - a worthy share in the history of cinema. This return of the screw is unnecessary, but this strikes me as I have already said.</body>
</review>
