<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Definitely, I was delighted, although I'm still preferring the curse of the Black Pearl. Definitely, I was delighted, although I'm still preferring the curse of the Black Pearl.</summary>
	<body>Pirates of the Caribbean saga already had me captivated since the release of the first installment, the curse of the Black Pearl, which I consider one of the most exciting, entertaining and fun of the current decade fantastic adventure films.The second installment, dead man's chest, do not disappoint me, but could not overcome the bar very enjoyable part. The charm was no longer the same, and was not what they expected and wished for this saga: autoconclusivos chapters to Indiana third Jones.La Awards, the end of the world, which premiered worldwide on Thursday, means a dignísima continuation of the adventures of Jack Sparrow and the troupe around him, and the consecration of the saga of Caribbean pirates as one of the best (and most profitable) that has given birth to the industry the film. Riza curl until exhaustion, but what Earth, how well does it. And also it doesn't fool anyone.It's a film of fantastic adventure as the top of a pine. In this occasion, unlike its predecessors, more fantastic that adventure. This breaks a bit with the general tone that was taking the saga until this third party, but the pure spectacle which means all she justifies everything.Pirates of the Caribbean: At the end of the world is long. It lasts nearly three hours, but however to me is I have not nor long or heavy. You have not found me a nearly three-hour film. He has kept me encandilado, stuck in the seat from the beginning until the end. And how I appreciate that!Made me laugh most of the gags, which are not few (large cameo by Keith Richards!); It has made me enjoy scenes of action and of all the perfect technical Bill that has the movie (wonderful soundtrack and prodigious design art, accompanied by the best and most spectacular special effects that were able to see on the big screen during this decade); In addition to excite me with the sequences intended to do so.A moment of embarrassment. a I only bostezo. It has not left me a moment of respite.Definitely, I was delighted, although I'm still preferring the curse of the Negra.Defraudan Pearl their ballasts: total wastage of some characters and situations, and its excessive length, totally unnecessary, taking into account that the argument is so little thing, although it has seemed more complex than what might appear.Turns out to be less sympathetic, more serious and dark saga film, but however has the largest number of gags and extremely hilarious and surreal situations (multiple Jacks! the wedding in full battle!) of the trilogy.In short, gentlemen, entertainment and spectacle in its purest form. It is true that the script is nothing out of this world (in my opinion is not very well written: halfway through the film multiple frames are entrevesan so that one can be a liar), but when one have remained encandilado in this way for almost three hours, what the hell, a tomar por culo script and other tiquismisqueces we always take into account.If cinema is entertainment, the film was created (sagas) movies like this.</body>
</review>
