<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Days of glory" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I do not think that the intentions of the director have been directed to adjudicate a historical thesis. It rather seems to have had the intention of make think the French on the paradoxes of its history.</summary>
	<body>As I already did the diptych of Eastwood with the double look Japanese and American on the siege of the island of Iwo Jima, (hollywoodizada with the stupid title of Days of Glory) indigenous reveals - language with a more direct and close, unprotected from the dramatic tension, the visual weight and the epistolary poetry of those - the participation of Arabs (disparagingly called bougnoules) of the French colonies in North Africa (Algeria)(, Morocco, Tunisia) in the campaigns of the army of French liberation during World War II, through the eyes of four goumiers (Abdelkader, Saïd, Messaoud and Yassir).The army of Africa participated from 1942 very actively in the liberation of France. The second division of general Leclerc consists of a mixture of the French city of pies-negros, of Lebanese, Algerians, Moroccans, of Equatorial Africa blacks and Indians of the counters. In the end, the balance will be enormous: 60,000 soldiers (African and Western) of the army of Africa die in 1945, i.e., the fourth of the French losses during the conflict.This Rachid Bouchareb (known for his previous work, A small, equally vengeful of the memory of the forgotten history of Senegal) intended to compensate not only the historical injustice committed with the thousands of soldiers from African, especially North African origin, who still expect public recognition and comparable pension (today are a pittance) to the rest of veterans, but also challenges us on racial prejudice that beyond the private sphere infect the military institution itself.Thus the character of Abdelkader see dashed their hopes of ascending rank in the rigid and nationalist military. Saïd will discover the shame that feels his Sergeant at the prospect of is to discover that he is married to an Arab woman. Messaoud will never receive the letters that his beloved writes, and theirs will be the censorship of an army which sees racial Exchange with bad eyes. All will be used by France and only receive in return the back of their compatriots. It says everything that scene with the car of Colonel away in silence.Among the interesting scenes of this honest film noteworthy that in which Sergeant responds to the Abdelkader stops on the lack of training of the soldiers (obligation imposed by the French army itself to their hosts). «Saïd, do you want to learn how to read?» «And Saïd responds: why would I serve?» Sobran comments on the intimate relationship between ignorance and wars.Therefore, indigenous is not only a classic anti-war film (there is the unsurpassed paths of glory as a reference). Also provides, in addition to their vindictive suitability, a political plea against racism which reproduces without reservation the military and calla with clear complicity the own director Estado.El had to silence the many voices against this film, leaving clear in some scenes than the Group of goumiers - famous (do not know if unfairly) for its cruelty and plunder in the strife - was nothing more than a group of people afflicted of the terrible evil of poverty and the despair. The army promised to be a hope for its famine, and turned out to be, if not his tomb, a lived example of his supporting role in the protection and construction of his alleged country.It is a good idea closer to European citizens today issues make us remixed our map of the world, although they occur in formats and stories of the old. Indigenous is a honest film (in its social commitment), with natural interpretations (as of that small great actor called Jamel Debbouze), and with a few foreign and an austere staging which situate us naturally in the sterile and empty means that all conflict is manufactured. Their actors are all in place, giving us simple interpretations, without egocentrismos Hollywood.Why not has been indigenous devoid of one fertilizes controversy (widespread in all current films of true historical significance) on what it may be truth or partisan advocacy of the Arab cause. Some branded her as opportunistic and partial, other liar and insulting for all French to give merit that name. Some reinforced the theory that in reality the goumiers, Moroccan, divided into more or less irregular bands, fighting without rules, taking as trophy heads enemy, living of the sack and devoted himself to all kinds of savagery. The truth is that in France this film has raised blisters still not cured (in Spain happens so everytime we talk about recover the historical memory of the Civil War).However, I do not think that the intentions of the director have been directed to adjudicate a historical thesis. Rather seems to have had the intention to make think the French (and by extension to all enlightened Europe of political correctness) on the paradoxes of its history. The France of human rights, the encyclopedia and respect for cultural diversity is at odds with facts as that has this movie, good little we serve whether they were or not truth, and Yes serve as a perfect metaphor for the nearest present.In the same direction, although sharp and distant fires remorseless excellent cache, Michael Haneke. I recommend it to anyone who has not seen. A joya.«Bougnoule, noun appearing in 1890, means black in language Wolof (Senegal dialect). Used by some white of Senegal to refer familiarly to black native, in the 20th century this noun will become an injurious nickname given by the Europeans in the North of Africa to Africans. Synonymous with "bicot" and "mouse" [the term "bicot", commonly used to designate a goat, and the term "mouse", which normally appoints the raccoon, are also used in France to refer disparagingly to Arab immigrants.] «[Translator's note.]»Dictionnaire alphabétique et analogique la langue française. Le Petit Robert / Tome 1, Société du nouveau Littré. 1979.</body>
</review>
