<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="El número 23" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Aburridísima, heavy and predictable. Quite silly, where at the end you can glimpse in the distance intentions to go back a tad flight, but fails miserably. The 'Scary Movie' psychological thrillers.</summary>
	<body>Battery of questions: in 'The number 23', what is the key? What it gives meaning to the tape? The obsession of the character of Jim Carrey, is not it? Well then - horrific - script fails miserably when it comes to portray with a minimum of realism and seriousness the obsession of the protagonist, and the story in general. All exaggerates and takes it too seriously, so much that just becoming quite laughable and looking like a parody 'Scary Movie' type of Fincher or Lynch, and other psychological thrillers films. It also lengthens it too much, to the point that last an hour has not gone absolutely nothing on screen.Scenes such as those of the dog in the middle of the road (and the halt!), the suicide of a woman and Jim Carrey Crouching on the spot of an old degollando are (by why are executing?) or of a thousand conversations, dialogues and situations nonsense, incoherent, with too much moralina and verbiage child and empty, not to mention the hundreds of super nonsense badly treated and taken to the limit on the number 23already part of the honorable and legendary range of comic and/or stuffed sequences in the history of cinema.It consists in the databases that this film is thriller, but it seems being on vacation in the hundred tedious minutes that lasts the film. If the main mystery of the film were well created and well resolved, because it would have been a more or less decent entertainment, but not even that, because suspense is more decaffeinated (of truth that someone felt really in suspense?) and topic and, moreover, the rhythm is almost non-existent. And then there is ultimately that of those who are so fashionable now, the "finales-recapitulación", that return to review all the details of the plot, not going to be that we not pillemos in its entirety the byways of this script taaan worked and polished. Screenplay that seems to have been written by Iker Jiménez or, if I hurry, by Pete Doherty.Las - more than nothing anecdotal - shares of my goddess Virginia Madsen and Jim Carrey (sorry, it is that this woman has me madly in love), which I thought smarter to accept some papers as undesirable as those who interpret 'The number 23', do not help anything.Aburridísima, heavy and predictable. Quite silly, where at the end you can glimpse in the distance intentions to go back a tad flight, but fails miserably. It would have been a funny short film. but not. With the permission of 'Ghost Rider' (how great!), one of the worst films in what have been in 2007.</body>
</review>
