<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Descubriendo a los Robinsons" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A breath of fresh air in the meantime green ogre, easy joke computer generated, and so much sequel unnecessary Disney direct to DVD market.</summary>
	<body>Since a few years ago, Disney does not lift head. Their latest products non-Pixar, as 'Wild' or 'Chicken Little', left much to be desired, in addition to not create any expectation, as did their traditional animated films during their golden ages.Among so much frustration and so many unnecessary sequels direct to DVD market, little, little good product there has been ("Lilo and Stitch").The incorporation of Pixar Animation Studios to the factory of dreams of the tito Walt was the salvation of this, and the first result of this Union has been 'Discovering the Robinsons', which is not a Pixar film, but that it has teamed up with very grateful of Dios John Lasseter (creator of 'Toy Story') as an executive producer.Something that has been noticed much in the final result.I had no expectation with this film. Call me not care at all, in addition to beginning to loathe the kind of movies animated entirely by computer (which began with 'Shrek') which are detestably overblown and that contain only fools jokes and absurd, repetitive situations to "fail well".But, fortunately, in this case I was wrong, and I I have brought a very pleasant and unexpected surprise (and, who want to deceive, a breath of fresh air bienvenidísimo).'Discovering the Robinsons' can be many things: being too crazy at times (especially during the half, where he'll literally by the hills of Ubeda. see the episode of the Tyrannosaurus, passage that only serves to make children laugh), have some - few - gags do not pinch of grace, of some small up loose ends in the plot, and if even parochial (to what is the reference to Raphael?). However, all the above is clouded by its admirable and intelligent script (despite the small lagoons, perdonables to be a child title), for the fun and entertaining that comes to be, and to recover during the magnificent final minutes the best and most nostalgic spirit Disney (with the characteristic style of John Lasseter, who despite being an executive producer)(note his hand that has gone into the project).Technically it is not big deal. Okay, but it adds nothing new. or lack that makes you. The soundtrack, a delight.It's a great time, very well done and very enjoyable travel adventure: these plot twists in a certain point completely changes the impression which is given during the first half of the film. 100% recommended for the whole family, although the kids can that they Lien with so much (well, not many) temporary pradoja.Since then, Disney has given a great - and very grateful - step from the arduousness of 'Chicken Little'.</body>
</review>
