<review author="Cp" title="Xmen3" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There to bother a little to adapt it, here the screenwriter read five comics at random and remove a few ideas, nothing more</summary>
	<body>If you're an aficionado of good action cinema, fantasy, or you just like a good entertainment film, although you have not read the comics, either published or only one loose, then. don't go to see her. If you are a true fan to the x-men and vibrabas only emotion thinking in seeing the dark Phoenix saga in film, then... don't go to see her. If these boring, and not have absolutely nothing to do, then... rent the first part or the second DVD, and Miss Bryan Singer, but do not go to see!.An exaggeration? It may be. But it is critical that it occurs to me do now that I have come home, and I get to write about the film. Worst thing is that already occurred to me type it while saw the film, disconnected which was what was happening on the screen.As film, you don't have rhythm, it is completely impossible to find a common thread that interests you, which bring in aloft to the Viewer, a good against evil, or a save the world. Something that is essential in this type of film. We will not see these films to hear intelligent dialogues or large arguments. We want to give us an excuse to risk the life, forget the girl that love to run to fight or at least a reason to get our life in the estate. We forget that we are sitting in a movie theater, and continue to maximum or William Wallace with a sword in his hand. And no, that nothing.The truth, X-Men 3 has nothing of the sort. Above, if you wanted a few characters to make you vibrate for them, although you think not more than eat popcorn, then either. A woodpecker you care what happens to them (especially since the mystical her depart from the film in a scene stupid and I if not this mystical, do not want to know anything, hala) or let go. So, a disaster.And if you're a surrendered and unconditional fan of the X-Men, better not read sipnosis from the entrance of the cinema. Stupid history and destroy the dark Phoenix Saga, become one. As the lack of blood (film for children and breast, that go with them to monitor that their children see) that Wolverine lose the grace. How to remove characters that the director does not like, stupid ways. Like putting free fights that make no sense. Get a scene with A Sentinel, only to appear in the trailer and entice fans (I swear I think that is why this that scene, to bring it into the trailer and nothing else). How to change the personalities of the characters of the comic, in all the cases for the worse. Come on, that is a horrible adaptation. That if even a comic and not a worthy of a Nobel novel, there to bother to adapt it, not transcribe her exactly, which is impossible, but if a little bother to adapt it, and here the screenwriter read five comics at random and remove a few ideas, nothing more.Summary: The worst of the three films. As Miss a story, having no clear things. It seems to me watching a famous Conference of Kevin Smith, explaining that the producer wanted to appear Mystica in balls without painting, who had to have many evil mutants dressed as punks, and the bridge of San Francisco had to float in the air. This has left the film.</body>
</review>
