<review author="Patri" title="Adaptation (El ladron de orquideas)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the movie itself we are witnessing the process of creation of the same script, a script impressively well tied and built in a very intelligent way.</summary>
	<body>Adaptation is directed by Spike Jonze, but the true star of this film is the screenwriter, something unusual, but it's not any screenwriter, is Charlie Kaufman, screenwriter known for movies and forget about me, as being John Malkovich or Human Nature, all of them uniquely original.Kaufman commissioned to do an adaptation of the book "The thief of orchids", and from there begins the film, we see all the difficulties that happens to make that script, until he decides to seek help from his brother, and included himself and the aforementioned brother in the script, then, will we see narrating the beginning of the filmwhich has been the beginning of the film that we're seeing, so we see him write the screenplay for the film that we are watching and is a real crazy! Therein lies the genius of this film.This is much more than cinema within cinema, is a stunning twist back, impressed by the ability to tell different stories: the Kaufman and his brother writing the script, of the writer Susan Orlean writing the book and that of John Laroche is the writer in his book account, could have been an authentic gibberish, but get that the Viewer is not lost.Nicholas Cage makes its best performance since Leaving Las Vegas, portraying Charlie Kaufman and Donald Kaufman, his brother, are two opposing characters, and it must not be easy to interpret two very different characters in the same film, pity that Cage be devoted to do anything interesting films such as the phantom rider, or other easily notable action films.Meryl Streep always is fantastic, and here is not less, portraying the writer Susan Orlean, whose character takes a turn along with the story, going from being a writer in love with the flowers, to be an adulteress, killer and drug addict! It seems that the author seemed very original as they had adapted his book and it did not bother her at all to submit it in this way because all of this did not happen in reality.Chris Cooper, who took an Oscar for this performance, is also another pretty good actor and often choose films in which works very well, in American Beauty was really impressive, here plays the Orchid thief who gives title to the book, a character in my opinion very interesting and that is much better understood when explained certain aspects of its past.A true privilege is put us in mind of Charlie Kaufman and attend his ramblings and thoughts when confronted with a script. And what about the script? In the movie itself we are witnessing the process of creation of the same script, a script impressively well tied and built in a very intelligent way.</body>
</review>
