<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Entre mujeres" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The directorial debut of Jonathan Kasdan is not a waste of imagination, but rather otherwise, that it is a story full of clichés and worn-out clichés.</summary>
	<body>There are surnames which will always remain linked to the history of cinema, some stronger than others, some with good reason and others by bad. One of them is Kasdan, Lawrence Kasdan, which have been able to be some of the most important films of recent decades, such as Indiana Jones, the Empire strikes back and return of the Jedi. Now it is the turn to his son Jonathan Kasdan, who assumes responsibility for his first feature film, produced by his father, between women. Among women is a complex place, which is a mix of genres, although most resembles the romantic drama. Carter Webb (Adam Brody) is a young writer who just leave his girlfriend Sofia (Elena Anaya), and decides to take care of his grandmother (Olympia Dukakis). There he meets Sarah (Meg Ryan) and her daughter Lucy (Kristen Stewart), and initiates a peculiar relationship with both of them, while the inspiration to write the story you have in mind for eleven years. At first glance, the directorial debut of Jonathan Kasdan is not a waste of imagination, but rather otherwise, that it is a story full of clichés and worn-out clichés. In that regard, the viewer takes the first on the front with the character of Elena Anaya, who plays a popular Spanish actress in a binge of originality have named Buñuel. The script is a sequence of common and recurring, places exploited endlessly. More than a linear plot we have a deslabazada narrative, as if they were independent sequences without any link in common. Just as monumental hodgepodge by exaggerated to the painted, and the viewer enters a deep trance, in which mixed the most unbearable boredom and a deep anger by being forced to see such jewel. If were not enough the torpor that in itself causes the plot in the stalls, it must be said that this is extremely predictable in all its aspects, and that there is not a single positive surprise in its final stretch. The characters are mere stereotypical caricatures, although that takes the cake is Elena Anaya (the phone call from the party scene is shameful), do not know who framed it to join the cast, despite getting an indefensible character. Adam Brody plays in his role as the young Kristen Stewart, while Meg Ryan is dangerously to the histrionics and the overacting. Among women is four movies in one: on the one hand, a story of a twenties intelligent you not find his place in life; a history of troubled adolescents anymore with the world because their parents did not make them case; a tear melodrama about life and death; and a story of impossible love. But instead of bringing together its virtues, get together all their failures.</body>
</review>
