<review author="JLO" title="Atrápame si puedes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A round, pleasant, film with ambiguous end and a mild taste a little - with a small wink to Forrest Gump in the middle and all-. Spielberg is to much, much more. Fast digestion and an oversight at the same pace.</summary>
	<body>Spielberg promptly delivers us what it promises, always. Movies/Fables with reminiscences of his own childhood, full of fantasy and rhythm, agile, not exempt of the customary moral and also, it cannot be perfect, late reloaded to the best Disney way. After two more serious attempts and kubrickianos A.I. and SMinority Report, with the same faults and features described above, we have a comedy of light tone, Yes, but finally achieved one production lower in the Filmography of a director who becomes a more serious tone to let us see his best film, such as the splendid the Empire of the Sun and Schindler's listtwo of his finest works. This comedy-drama - more the former than the latter - begins to the family of Frank Jr., from rich to poor in one second, loading with the separation of their parents (analogy with the director himself) and the difficult decision to opt for one or the other. The only way out seems to be the flight and take various personalities - pilot, doctor, lawyer - forging checks by four million dollars and try to avoid, as far as possible, the emotional problems, as it is made clear by the encounters poachers with his father (a this time only correct Christhoper Walken). All sustained under the well-known label of based on a true story, adaptation of a book of the 80' of the real Abagnale, fraudster sentenced by the FBI and now become star. The characters are expensive in the style of the director, queribles beings, both the con man Frank Abagnale jr. (Leonardo Di Caprio) as detective who pursues Carl Hanratty (a numb Tom Hanks). This "overrides" the paternal relationship of the protagonist, reaching the limit of needing him despite their differences in repeated Christmas calls. Both catch me if you can as gangs of New York confirms the sudden maturity of Di Caprio, becoming already a good dramatic actor but it would be just stress, already good previous work and who loves Gilbert Grape?, reunion, Celebrity and even in the ill-fated Titanic. A round, pleasant, film with ambiguous end and a mild taste a little - with a small wink to Forrest Gump in the middle and all-. Spielberg is to much, much more. Fast digestion and an oversight at the same pace.</body>
</review>
