<review author="JLO" title="Batman begins" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The end result is overwhelming: lots of action, pretty emotion, a careful music, the best possible Batman, best costume and an excellent script.</summary>
	<body>Christhoper Nolan Batman leaves the previous versions as mere sketches, or only weak close-ups of the essence of the bat man and his dream-like world.It is not that the two Tim Burton are now badly - came with vitality to the real Batman away from the clown television-but that his lauded darkness and vision are superseded by this new version (and safely) years light of the latest Queers who managed to Schumacher with the character, considered - along with Superman and Mickey Mouse - as the best fictional story creations.Nor does one have to be a fan of the comic or the character in order to enjoy this entertaining film. Nolan (capable of imaginative Memento and the bureaucratic white nights), demonstrates versatility, good management of the action and the Assembly and correct insight into both Visual and the script together together to David Goyer (lover of comics as he demonstrated with interventions in the scripts of the three Blade (addressing the last), The Crow)(, Nick Fury and the impending Flash and Ghost Rider), that make possible a first time without the gloomy, without that diminished with this interest or the end result. The introduction is agile and explanatory, and lays groundwork for a Batman more mature in its conception. This influenced by the eighties comics by Frank Miller (mainly by "Batman: year one"), author who established an image more it lasts and raw of the hero, as well as revitalize it.Much has to do with the result the excellent choice - and performance - the Welsh Christian Bale, stage actor little known despite his extensive career, that becomes here the point of reference. The earlier child protagonist of the Empire of the Sun, where also lost in her childhood her parents (and more here of the failed reign of fire, Shaft and American psycho), puts the body and the face to become - without discussion - the definitive Batman by presence and performance. Only with the first time acted more and better than all other Batman together. Gotham is dark, night, daytime and sharp, without clash. The Gallery of side actors of renown (Neeson, Freeman, Caine, Oldman, Hauer) intimidated by his interpretive quality, achieving not be only filled with a super production of this type. Performances couples, confirming the Irish Cillian Murphy (extermination leading actor), here in the role of the villain named scarecrow. Both the origin and various accessories - car, batcomputer, gadgets and the famous and reviled costume - are based on a credible and well-founded basis. Difficult to find weak points, perhaps an excessive - but spectacular - car chase on ceilings. More can not ask you one such Hollywood adaptation.The end result is overwhelming: lots of action, pretty emotion, a careful music, the best possible Batman, best costume, an excellent script. Ah, you want to! to return the Joker also!</body>
</review>
