<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>?The island of the Treasury? He sat the rules of the genre of pirates; Gore Verbinski has found his inspiration in the multiplication of the characters and the sides.</summary>
	<body>"The treasure island" set the rules of the genre of pirates. Jim Hawkins and his friends had the treasure, but John Silver and the pirates had the ship. Each had something I wanted to the other and they arranged themselves with a treatment. But it was a deal with pirates, and the pirates sometimes fulfil his word and sometimes do honor to his fame. The "Pirates of the Caribbean" by Gore Verbinski found his inspiration in the multiplication of the characters and the sides: the Royal Navy, Sparrow, the girl, the boy, Captain Barbossa, the Dutch Errante, and the exponential increase in treatment and cambalaches, which are countless.So we create incredible, i.e. that a pirate will respect their word, the film uses the legendary. The pirate has to fulfill his word because, otherwise, a curse will fall on him. Curses and the rules are rampant as fungi to drive an endless plot without the spectator fail.Jack Sparrow is the second engine of history. Their gestures harmless and amanerados, whose influence on Keira Knightley undermine the principle character of Keira Knightley, mean that we must not take it seriously. In a universe of covenants, he is the pill, in a drama of ideals, he is the selfish. He is also the captain without authority and the negotiator without power. And, however, it is the only one that gets away with. Participates in the complicated weaves - drive with many moves in advance, as a Kasparov in a chess game that changes of rules in each turn.The two protagonists fight marred by the absence of malice, and are tripping each other only on behalf of their parents. His final Union or his tragedy depend on the confidence that (every day more United in the solid business of celluloid) creators and public have in the triumph of eternal love, or proven disbelief that experience has taught them.Long executions of the principle that child that defies the scaffold with his song, the Lair of Sao Feng who composed a complete story in the style of the prologues of Indiana Jones, the multiplication of Jack Sparrows and crabs in the dream of the land of Davy Jones universe, the brotherhood of pirates, and that crazy swirl are exemplary of the battle end. I do not understand the obstinacy of the critics to defend his indifference towards one more than remarkable work.</body>
</review>
