<review author="Luna" title="Tideland" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will please all those stalwarts of Terry Gilliam. Those who do not have a stomach bomb-proof are going to go really wrong...</summary>
	<body>With two years of delay leads to our screens on June 8 "Tideland", the latest film by Terry Gilliam. Neither the prize FIPRESCI he got at the San Sebastian Film Festival in 2005 have managed to make a hole in the Spanish chart to this film, hard to digest, and it provokes reactions found in the spectators who have opportunity to see him.For a sample button. When the film became Donostia more than half of the spectators left the room. Even critics left the projection with the scrambled eggs with stomach. Gilliam also gained appreciation of journalists when in the press conference after the film described as stupid to viewers who had left the room for not be able to endure more avatars of the girl and the corpse.Freely inspired by the novel by Mitch Cullin, the film tells the story of a girl whose parents are junkies in the city and by avatars of fate left orphaned in the field. However this time the director of films as emblematic as "12 monkeys" or "Brazil" gets almost to sadism more gore and macabre to narrate this story he says have to do with "eyes of a child" and where the line between reality and fiction is very close.Despite its passage by Donostia and the award he received there, this film has not enjoyed critical acclaim and supposes a point and separate in the career of this filmmaker. From my point of view there are too gruesome moments that they border on sadism and they provide nor really anything to history (as everything that happens to the cadaver) and also convinces me the interpretation of Jodelle Ferland, who by then had 10 years old, and that sometimes seems too exaggerated. Perhaps like all those unconditional (but really unconditional) of Terry Gilliam.Sin however, all those who do not have a stomach bomb-proof are going to go really wrong because there are really macabre moments in the film.</body>
</review>
