<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Más extraño que la ficción" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Marc Forster in his latest film proposes an interesting experiment: what would happen if the character in a novel were aware of being forming part of it?</summary>
	<body>Marc Forster (finding never ever Monster's Ball) proposed in his latest film premiered in Spain (stranger than fiction) an interesting experiment: what would happen if the character in a novel were aware of being forming part of it; and even more: what would try to make to avoid its sure death advanced by the voice of a narrator describing what is happening in his life and how much thought throughout the day with millimetric precision? This is the original knot of an enmarcable tape in the best version of American independent cinema. A splendid and content Will Ferrell is Harold Crick, the last character of the successful author Karen Eiffel (perfect Emma Thompson in the role of this eccentric character). In the work, Eiffel describes him as an official of Hacienda de Grey and methodical life until the day that meets the rebellious pastry Ana Pascal (magnificent Maggie Gyllenhaal). You must audit the young Pascal that, in his statement, it has ceased to pay some taxes arguing refusing to finance the wars of the bellicose American administration. Terrified by the end brought you the author of his book life, Harold will come to the aid of different professionals with mixed success. Psychologist Dr. Carly ('cameo' of luxury of the vanished Tom Hulce) recommends a holiday period, but little serves the Council to Harold, who voice him seems more plausible. Literature professor Jules Hilbert (Dustin Hoffman) will give the key to a solution: must guess if the story of his life is a comedy or a tragedy. In the first case is it saved, in the second, his death will be the sure epilogue. Fortunately for Harold, the novelist walks with some problems of creative block is solve an editorial assistant Penny Escher (Queen Latifah). While she elucidate how to kill him, Harold happen you events that will make you cling to life with an unsuspected force in someone like him.</body>
</review>
