<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="El sonido del trueno" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nice series B, pulling to (c) (crappy) in his dialogues and, above all, absurd (and therefore to joke) funds and effects.</summary>
	<body>Nice series B, pulling to (c) (crappy) in his dialogues and, above all, absurd (and therefore to joke) funds and effects. The argument is based on a tiny but very interesting narrative of Ray Bradbury, however its development is not round, finishing by entertain, but forgotten with the same ease that view.There are some moments of filling, with, again, stupid dialogues, and more hot air towards the middle of the tape, than I would have liked. Situations occur without passionate and one covers everything with a bit of confusion, not knowing if the story that unfolds is taken from a serious tone or overtly comic, so it seems sometimes taken it a joke a bit.In the chapter on special effects, they are of pure craftsmanship, with computer, perhaps immense, but singing over not being able to work. It seems that there was not much budget for the filming of the movie and is quite noticeable when used more endearing slices and an artistic design that mixes good findings with authentic churros.As regards interpretations, are not notable, but yes we must make special mention of its protagonist, Edward Burns, making it frankly wrong. Well, it is wrong not to do, is it even acts. There are more dramatic feeling in the voice of his Spanish voice that in the face of the actor in question, which is always unimpressed. It gives the same that is talking to the girl about to be eaten by a dinosaur. In the end.And on the positive side, that there are "bugs" curious and enough situations to keep the viewer history with desire to see how this will all end. And not to be really interesting, because the truth is that something is done long, but because there is a well achieved minimum of tension and intrigue is sufficiently effective to not disengage. Thing that there are certain moments that seems to happen.In short, entertaining broadly, but very below what could have given them.</body>
</review>
