<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El buen pastor" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Portrait of the people in whose hands the fate of the world was but that could not govern himself.</summary>
	<body>Or God or the King, the case is that there is an army of anonymous servers faithful, priests or shoemakers, mercenaries who sacrifice the personal life, its intimate avatars, his honest desire to be happy in this world, to serve a necessarily high reality which, in the De Niro film is the homeland, the bars and stars, the cluster of ethical codes that make up the invisible frame on which underpins our society.What is the good Shepherd isn't the CIA and its origins, is not a prospecting on the roots of espionage in the United States or is at least not únicamento that: it is a long, failing, story about the gray and almost always little appreciated weight of the officer, who is, after all, is delivered in body and soul to the slow movementdesigned, meticulously designed pieces on the Board in the world. The character of Matt Damon, Edward Wilson, is the quintessence of the essential pawn, that soldier that meets not only the orders but that this obedience is a kind of intimate relevance that makes you, without hesitation, sacrificing marriage, children and life. There is no moral dilemmas in the evolution of the character: the Shoemaker of the King, as in a beautiful piece of the film are appointed spies, dehumanizing his soul, her clothes with the Vertigo of the work and the loyalty to a cause always necessarily more important than their small desires and their small domestic life. The CIA was formed originally by fundamentalists of good social class, white, not necessarily Catholics, but cultured, aristocratic and saved to safeguard a dark principle of homeland that les has been inculcated from childhood, when they already principian the values for which then they will be recruited and placed at the service of the cause. De Niro Gets the finger in the wound, but it does not hurt. It contains. Prefers reasoning nature of the Shepherd, his status as invisible guide a herd unprotected before the emotional shortcomings of its mission, its amoral acceptance of a destination and the abandonment of everything that goes beyond the broad lines of this company. All those sewers of the State, significantly the true good Shepherd, they must contain hundreds of stories that De Niro would have been able to use to offer a colorful spectacle of film of spies and we have no doubt that vividly, but he opts for the emotional plane, and without giving up certain moments of acute thriller, gives the viewer a powerful portrait of a country, yours, although there is a fascinating comment Wilson makes an Italian-American (played by a great, as always, Joe Pesci) who attacks him with the idea that all marginal groups have something in their hearts: the Jews have the tradition; Blacks, music; the Italians, family. But what have Americans? And have to America... and a vast expanse of world subjected to his ideological and commercial dictation. There is even one scene crucial that, for Christmas, all clustered around the tree and the consensual happiness, some sing "You've got the whole world in your hands / you have the whole world in your hands", the classic piece of the american songbook, while Wilson and a Colonel departen with damped whispers about the fate of the world and what part should be moved so that the game continues.Ambiguous, grey, bland, the character of Damon, their records on screen, are perfect. They embuten with mastery in the suit ironing of the official Wilson, ranging from a corridor to another, occupying offices, traveling the world to end only, fulfilled duty and the sense of the world, despite his effort, does not turn as you do for any of his efforts and their expertise. The terseness of his staging is important for history: their classic encuadros, its slow visual jewelry, its fabulous setting. What is no longer perhaps not so convenient is history itself - here De Niro has one lower fault - which weakens due to excessive footage (167 minutes) and the ambitious of a number of interesting stories construction but they end abruptly and they not coagulate in the plot the film unit. Perhaps because of this it is not a masterpiece but only a good or very good film.De Niro, in this second RAID behind the camera, has given us a very brave, honest, classic film by the way that I understand some film of the years 40 and 50 obviaban any commercial concession and only allowed licenses that reincidieran in the film itself. Isn't this film now is brewing thinking the Viewer, what you want and how to give it.</body>
</review>
