<review author="Pablo" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Frankly not felt me so horrific, the truth is that you could have done much better</summary>
	<body>These past few weeks I have read many reviews of this film negative. Her I went to see this weekend and frankly not felt me so horrific, the truth is that is could have done much better with both human and intellectual material that was available. But that matters little, the film will fulfil its objective outweigh.Today is already much the Duster to the American industry, there are just good stories but ultimately in the frontline film dominated the industry on the artist. And honestly it seems that producers have tattooed that saying of "more bad vale known good to know" killing in this way the risk and tension classical breathed once when descubrias for the first time films in which you were blind during the dialogues of the characters, excited and enfrentandote gladly to the unknown.Professor and famed simbologista Robert Langdon (Tom Hanks) is forced to attend a night the Louvre Museum, when the assassination of a conservative stops after about a mysterious trail of symbols and clues. With his own life at stake, Langdon, aided by cryptographer Sophie Neveu (Audrey Tautou) police, discovered a series of amazing hidden secrets in the works of Leonardo da Vinci, secrets that point everyone to a secret society responsible for guarding an ancient secret that has been hidden for two thousand years. Together they embark on a thrilling quest that takes them to Paris, London and Scotland, as they gather clues in a desperate attempt to decipher the code and reveal secrets that would shake the foundation of humanity.It is a classic adventure film, perhaps covered controversy, but in the end should not be forgotten that it is fiction. Special mention to the soundtrack that stands out significantly. It is the product that stands out above the lousy game.Perhaps the feeling that I've escaqueado a little comment on the film or to give depth to the analysis. It is true, I do not like to talk about films that I love. Even so I think this will be the last that you people cinefixia. By the way, have already bought the rights to Angels and demons...</body>
</review>
