<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Descubriendo a los Robinsons" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that will not go down in history except as a stepping stone in the recovery of the Disney label.</summary>
	<body>It is curious that the best commercial time of animated cinema has coincided with the decline of the Disney, to the extent that it has been abandoned, by now, 2D traditional animation to embark in the competitive world of 3D animation.His first attempt was the flojísima "Chicken Little" and now comes the second: "Discovering a los Robinsons" (Meet the Robinsons), directed by Stephen j. Anderson. "The improvement is obvious.""Discovering the Robinsons" it tells the story of Lewis, a smart inventor of twelve years whose last and most ambitious project is the memory scanner, a machine that will help you to find his biological mother and to have a family again. Unfortunately, the evil Bowler Hat Guy steals your invention. But Lewis does not lose hope and meets a mysterious boy named Wilbur Robinson, proposed to our bewildered hero a trip in time to spend a day with Wilbur's eccentric family?The biggest problem of the film is that it offers nothing new and even reminds, at times, "Jimmy Neutron". To say in its favour, in reality, it is not intended to offer anything new. Only its makers claim is the do have a fun time to the audience. And you could say they get, although without enthusiasm.And entertaining because the film has two good virtues. The first of them is the proper rhythm, the narrative fluidity, which leads adventure in adventure without that transitions or the moments of rest seem forced.The second virtue, which possibly will be most remembered by the public at the end of the projection, is its villain. The villain of the function is a character really well built and a beautiful tribute to the wonderful Jack Lemmon in "The race of the century" or Pierre Nodoyuna of "Wacky" (clearly inspired by him). A character that, bad and stupid, makes nice and even endearing.No much more to comment on the film. Entertainment and a good villain. I think two elements are more than enough to see a film that will not go down in history except as a stepping stone in recovery (that will come) the label Disney. final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 5.5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
