<review author="JLO" title="El diario de Ana Frank" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Claustrophobic, almost without foreign and using a couple of sets, despite the two hours and a half of duration the narrative is agile, using with intelligence and restraint the voiceover and avoiding at all times the melodrama.</summary>
	<body>The film is based on the famous diary written by Anne Frank during his stay in a room in Amsterdam, hidden with her family and other Jews escape the nazis during World War II. Living together for almost three years (12/6/42 to 4/8/44) of eight persons in equal conditions and in a very small space, they did that all kinds of situations, enriched by the pristine and lively look of the teenager emerge look Ana.Esa full of strength and passion that Ana had in his life and his art was very moved by director George Stevens (Shane)(, Giant), which allows the viewer empathy with all the characters by equal (done that it does not occur with the reading of the book), and a fidelity to the text which in this case is too positive.Claustrophobic, almost without foreign and using a couple of sets, despite the two hours and half narrative is agile, using with intelligence and restraint the voiceover and avoiding the melodrama at all times, as in the end where occurs the detention of persons, giving class of poetry and good taste. Despite being made almost fifteen years after the publication of the book, is less explicit than that concerning the sexuality of the protagonist, practically non-existent in the film beyond a hint or a kiss, although we agree that the book is not very bold to these times, worse much for the time.Other high points are firstly, the excellent photography of William C. Mellor, an intense black and white and beautiful game of contrasts, visible even in the photos that accompany the text. The music of Alfred Newman, overloaded, but used in small doses. The actions are also good and couples, highlighting Joseph Schildkraut as Anne's father, Anne's own (Millie Perkins) and the recognizable Shelley Winters as Mrs Van Daan, character which seems to lead, by his interpretation and characteristics, the mother of Stanley Kubrick's Lolita. The diary of Anne Frank produces the same feeling of rootlessness, resignation and tension than other films that deal with the same subject, showing the concentration camps, located without clash - perhaps less spectacular but no less felt - to the best contemporary exponents of the genre: Roman Polanski's the pianist and the list of Schindler of Steven Spielberg.</body>
</review>
