<review author="JLO" title="¡Al ataque!" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The tone of social commitment and including class struggle, with manners plot and a pace that reminds at times (and much) to Pedro Almodóvar comedies but with results perhaps something lower.</summary>
	<body>The marseillais director Robert Guédiguian we are accustomed to light comedies without an apparent social background - only apparent - as in previous films as Marius and Jeannette (1997) and la vie, à la mort! (1995). The attack! It continues along the same lines accentuating its political side. This time under the guise of showing the process of creating between Xavier and Yvan (screenwriter and director respectively), interacting among themselves to tell the plot of a political film in which a family and neighbors, try to save his mechanical workshop "Moliterno &amp; Cía." from the clutches of a multinational company that intends to expropriate for failing to comply with quotas for a credit.Agility is the mixture of the characters of one and another layer in parallel, with their various problems behind him, as well as also the problems of their own creators. The tone of social commitment and including class struggle, with manners plot and a pace that reminds at times (and much) to Pedro Almodóvar comedies but with results perhaps something lower. With doubts and differences between fictional filmmakers, with repetitions and turns back they get the more comical moments and also, her turn a little slow despite its standard length. Added to all this the hybrid gender - really a comedy-drama - ago Miss quite some depth and does not help in any of the two cases being halfway from both. Starring a convincing Ariane Ascaride in the role of Lola (Madam and fetish of the director himself) and a smooth deal with good performances both leading and secondary, highlighting Jacques Boudet as Pépé Moliterno, a beloved senile grandfather and likable. Released in Argentina in a difficult date and next to a tank as the Lord of the rings, it will go unnoticed in poster and rigour, nor is it too unfair. Anecdotally, Guédiguian used the same actors for the city is quiet (2000), filmed almost simultaneously with this and released with difference of months in France.</body>
</review>
