<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Spiderman 3" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Raimi gives us some of the most embarrassing scenes in the history of the blockbusters.</summary>
	<body>Of all the litany of sequels that this 2007 we have prepared, the first I've seen has been "Spider-Man 3.The film had encouraging background of "Spider-Man" and "Spider-Man 2", two good movies that, without reaching the excellence of "Batman Begins", fulfilled its task perfectly. It also had a so much fun as Sam Raimi director and the emergence of villains as emblematic as the man of sand, the Goblin or venom. Expected for this reason one of the shows of the year. Big mistake.Of course, anyone, to enjoy a feature film he comes with a display of special effects, it will be happy the film and will think that I am a pendante for not sharing your opinion. But if you are of those who ask more to one film. If ask you, for example, a script or a rate appropriate, prepare you for the disappointment.It is not that the film is totally boring, that it is at times, but what happens on screen is not the case with the naturalness and the fluidity of the previous films. Everything seems forced, the formula sounds repetitive, and although it is repeated, we should not notice it.It falls again and as seems usual in modern American cinema, in the dramatic action scenes, thus preventing the dramatic and emotional involvement of the audience in what happens. One can feel visual wonder at the special effects, but there is no room for emotion.It doesn't help that neither, the accumulation of characters that, in some cases, appears a mere excuse to satisfy fans of the comic, but that found them a suitable place in the script. So Gwen Stacy (Bryce Dallas Howard), a key character in the comic, is completely out of place and seems a simple introduction for a character that, leave the series Kirsten Dunst, could take role in following installments. J. j. Jameson or aunt May are also mere extras in scenes without sense.To say something positive, not everything is going to be bad, recognize that the man of sand (a successful Thomas Haden Church) and its history (in which appears a desaprovechada Theresa Russell), are the best of the script even though if they had only stayed with him as villain and had developed its story properly (asks it cries), would have fared better.But worst of all the film, are the moments in which Peter Parker (Tobey Maguire) is owned by venom and becomes a pimp. Just as it sounds. Raimi offers us here, some of the more embarrassing scenes in the history of the blockbusters. A difficult to understand horror and that becomes more unfortunately memorable of this painful and disappointing product entitled "Spider-Man 3 &#8243;."Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 2.5 out of 10</body>
</review>
