<review author="JLO" title="Desmontando a Harry" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>People loved Match Point, but we know that those people is that not like Allen. Woody is this film, by principles, by intelligence, cynicism, by nature and by quality also.</summary>
	<body>Woody Allen films could be divided into thousands of subgroups. The comic of its inception, the serious "to the Bergman", the safe, the great, the latest standard autopilot, etc. But let's talk about his best film of this last stage: Deconstructing Harry. Or rather, Deconstructing different Allen.Film and clearly exaggerated, a kind of Woody Allen reloaded. From its top, note the purpose of Allen by cause. A furious and choppy montage? used in throughout the film, unpublished in their cinema - makes the difference. And not to mention his politically incorrect humor. Very wrong.Despite being the protagonist?Harry Block - a monster without apparent virtues more than the literary becomes likable and irresistible. Could it be the own Allen? This character is a face more sarcastic himself?The biographical elements posts here are a mirror? its relationship with psychoanalysis, sex and religion – and so do appear. Although thinking a bit, its history with the coreanita, not desentonaría for nothing in this script.Unlike Allen's latest deliveries, it never loses its overwhelming rhythm. We said before a nervous and at the same time bright Assembly. A film is bad for women, all religion, so beloved psychoanalysis, the American middle class and even to himself. A rarity for its degree of acidity.The gags and the dialogues are unbeatable. Few in his film as imaginative as the actor that is out of focus (Robin Williams ja!). Or death touching the door. And we could say more.The jokes about Judaism are hilarious: "already be lost 6 million but records are to be overcome" "what's wrong with science?" "Between the air conditioner and the Pope, I prefer air conditioning". Or one of his former women reprochandole to teach his son in common phrases like "I shit on God".Level actors parade is endless, demonstrating once more the prestige and importance of the film of Allen. The amount of characters and endless stories of this film, show a prodigious management of timming, where never get to mingle or tired. And that shows people characters in the film more imaginaries more the characters in his book more. Uff. Genial.la people loved Match Point, but we know that those people is that not like Allen. Woody is this film, by principles, by intelligence, cynicism, by nature and by quality also.I I would encourage to say that you aside from his undisputed classics?Annie Hall, Manhattan, crimes and sins, this Deconstructing Harry is undoubtedly his best film. Or which best represents.</body>
</review>
