<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Zodiac" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Once again, Fincher has given another unexpected twist, has released us a new artistic bofeton to perform a true masterpiece and add to his amazing, harrowing and courageous filmography. Film on all four sides.</summary>
	<body>With Seven, Fincher regained renewed, influenced and pushed a fashion and a new genre of movies and television on serial killers. When already thought that after the unbearable "ceseies" saturation and imitations of that proposal for Fincher master, not needed any encouragement or creative space for anything else, Fincher returns with the surprising Zodiac, that also is based on real events, with what we know about starting the end of the film and the solution to the plot, champion again the most difficult yet.Fincher never loses sight his own style, his vision, or their intentions, the exact dose to take possession of the reason for the Viewer. With an overwhelming talent and amazing accuracy, get freeze us blood with the first appearances of the murderer or grab us to seat in the best style "Hitchcock". However, we soon discovered that the true protagonists are researchers, police and all those involved professionally and personally in a case police, desperate, dense and enigmatic that became hopelessly in a true media show.The story leaves behind and largely to victims or the colorful choreographies of their deaths and focuses on universal feelings like despair, hope, tenacity and obsession. Fincher resigns to seek answers, or motifs, because all of these are unknown. It does not provide absolute light, because the facts even today remain dark. Zodiac has extensive footage, and at the same time, with a mise en scene and a rigorous setting, a serious and appropriate distribution, contained and masterful realization and some isolated flashes will be, without any doubt, in the annals of the history of the cinema. Film on all four sides in almost three hours where we submerged himself in a dark plot, in an alley and hopeless, but that manages to remain in continuous dramatic tension. More it cannot be. Fincher, this time, expelled from class his usual Viewer, the generation of television, the frenzied advertising, video game consoles, the Blockbusters and video clips. That most accustomed to the waterfall of images, zapping, speed, gags, popcorn, mobile lit and the emule.Fincher has done here a meticulous, honest and accurate movie with existing material, as an exemplary film exercise, giving to it of most commercial and frivolous aspects. Once again, Fincher has given another unexpected twist, has released us a new artistic bofeton to perform a true masterpiece and add to his amazing, harrowing and courageous filmography.</body>
</review>
