<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Corazones solitarios (Lonely Hearts)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I like co-operation film noir that makes me hard to be gentle with these telefilms of commitment, not excited, much to regret, contain the pure classic cinema mimbres and be filmed with ex officio without anything chirríe.</summary>
	<body>It may not be possible to recover the black film, L.A. confidential apart. Todd Robinson does nothing which can regenerate the enthusiasm for a genus abandoned by multinationals, despite continue to enjoy the favor of the public. That that the customer is always right is a lie. The written history here is real and splashed American newspapers in the 1940s. A pair of assassins estafaban and then killed their victims, maids with possible solitary, desiring an adventure, ladies who saw a blade of risk and glamour in the midst of a life grey and confined to the tedium. Robinson does is put the weight of the fabric on the shoulders of the detective Elmer C. Robinson, curiously his grandfather in real life, which was who came up with the murderers and took them to the electric chair.Travolta is sobreactuado. Gandolfini is not credible after admire him as a mobster, rude, bocazas, and not in this simple piece of paper that does not have material to look as it should. I know this is a bias and admit that the Sopranos is lot number and James Gandolfini much actor as to not ask always a papelón, and not a few crumbs of talent in the middle of a film with bits of quality.Because lonely hearts is a vacuum device in the background. It was presented at Taiwan in October 2006. Then (here more than curious data) in the United States. Now, in Spain. It is as if the producers themselves were not entirely convinced of the pull of the film and escrutaran wide geography world to see what reaction would be in Beijing, put by case, rather than in San Sebastian, where he also was (without penalty and without any glory). Salma Hayek deserves separate chapter: have caught the wrong actress. It is not let me guided by what I've already read, that the woman who gives life, in reality, was horrifyingly fat and ugly shouting. Or perhaps. But the Hayek is, despite that effort by afear her, solid, how not, and already is in the poster of the film with what arguments they want to sell us the content. Worth plus two () that two carts. In the end. Jared Lato, the latin lover on engolosinar to the maids to then give passport to Pimlico, I say to the loving sky of pure souls, makes a role corrientita, pulling at bobo. And telling that the plot, well look, gave of themselves. So I put a regular, as says a friend my very aware that to see a movie then there is to put a note. In the school. Is this short, relatively good?</body>
</review>
