<review author="Bruji" title="Entre mujeres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Effective direction of actors, perfect frames, elegant use of the planos-contraplanos, a great scene in the rain. Rather what can be said in the current film, other many directors.</summary>
	<body>Film of good intentions and uncertain outcome, in the absence of a plausible script, seeking support in so stereotyped as predictable characters. A history lost between clumsy dialogues that, without effort, manages to cause the easy tear. Recommended for those who confuse the meaning of the word melancholy.To our dear Meg him begins to pass as well as the boys of the announcement of Coca-Cola. It has already convinced that it belongs to another generation. It's glorious past, who survived the French kisses, to the orgasms fingidos in a café, at the steamy conversations in meat Viva, tedious messages of Tom Hanks; becomes, in this Ribbon, MOM, for the purpose of seducing grandson all would like to have. in sixty years. More, as it was to be expected, you will find a fierce rival his own teenage daughter... or not. And it is that reveal the arguments, with all luxury of details, exclusive of a sector of the criticism that, in this way, manages to fill their articles. It gives the impression that he did not have anything more than. sometimes.To talk about this film, it is mandatory to mention, first of all, the successful work of casting; by precisely be the actors, the principal? if not the only - the first work of kasdan attractions. Even so, no escapes us in not a few moments, the interpretations of all of them are missed, in a story without consistency, supported by a few flat characters that corroborate each and every existing topics generational. In this regard, the screenwriter of the invention would have to reflect on upcoming projects, about the kind of genre you want to address, and not let this important aspect in the hands of Divine Providence, as? it seems - has made on the present occasion. If you ultimately decide by the romantic comedy (this film is not), you will find magnificent referents in the Filmography of his father. If attract you the stories of intimate Court, - those that are written by putting the heart by Inkwell - they should contact their gaze towards the slow, but sure, walking from Eastwood teacher; undisputed leader in the difficult task of transmitting the world of feelings. If you are interested in the female universe applied to the American comedy of manners, you will have to adopt the touch of irony, elegance, subtlety and delicacy which critics found in the work of Lubitsch. If you also intend to incorporate autobiographical, it is essential to learn a famous phrase by Joseph Mankiewicz, woman who said: "the difference between real life and the movies is that a script has to make sense." "Life, no". Attempting to carry out, in a first job, this mixture between drama, romance and comedy-tinged autobiographical, without reaching further none of them, to create an unnecessary amalgam; It's not pretentious, but extremely risky. A risk is not exceeded, does not convince the critics and ending pay at the box office. They say that with the talent, is born, and we do not doubt the rookie filmmaker's. His first film is a declaration of good intentions. But it is also true that any technique is learned, and the story of the film is filled with indispensable references to follow, that, in this case, it helps understand the mistakes of this opera prima. The most resounding comes the warning made John Huston, "There can be a good film if there is not a good script". In the absence of that good script, - of Kasdan condemns their characters to the reproduction of typical, topical and awkward dialogue, to consolidate a misleading story that even the kisses are predictable-, we are left with the effective direction of actors, the perfect frames, elegant use of the planos-contraplanos, a great scene in the rain, and that another in which grandson and grandmother remember the tender relationship between Ginger Rogers and his father, by San Judas Tadeo!. We are also left with the good work of Meg Ryan, who joined Olimpia Kukakis, Kristen Stewart and Adam Brody. We were, of course, the flawless performance of the Spanish Van Helsing vampire. And, why not?, we are left with the tricks of a filmmaker who, in a gruesome manner, manages to make us laugh and cry. Rather what can be said in the current film, other many directors.</body>
</review>
