<review author="Raccord" title="Xmen3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Superficial, okay, but very entertaining and sense of humor.</summary>
	<body>Multicine film in its purest form. It must be the brain of one of popcorn that swell to sell due to this film, to see something else, apart from the explosions and some very funny mutant. Surface; Okay, but very entertaining and sense of humor.The adaptation of a comic to the big screen that I liked most is probably the X-Men saga. Although it isn't saying much, seen the series of disasters that have filled our theaters lately. And probably the reason why these films of mutants, I love so much is that they not precisely intended to tracing the comic, such as "Sin City", but taking the original characters; create situations and new adventures. Which we are discussing, is of similar quality to the other two of the X-Men series. Here the story is a little more crude, and there is almost no new characters; but they supplement it with spectacular special effects (even for a "blockbuster" movie) and some quite achieved gags.Also want to speak too much of the plot, because I imagine that few the you have seen yet; and if I put to wander on the curiosity that give me the pout of similar (not out too in X Men III, by the way) because it would not be plan. So I will give the can on the villains in movies. In the 1980s and 1990s the bad Street par excellence were always heavy or punks "old school". Attend now astonished as Hollywood rather than overcome clichés transforms them: the mutants "bad", henchmen of Magneto, are the same young face of few friends of the ochenteras movies, but with a closer to Hardcore or the Gothic aesthetic. Hordes of young people with nails painted black and mittens fighting Wolverine and storm, as if they might come out super pissed a Marylin Manson concert. Is which the next urban by demonizing tribe? I already imagine the IV X-Men fighting against hundreds of Bakala.</body>
</review>
