<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Dreamgirls" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The tape provides enjoyment for who leaves to viewing it as a long video clip emerged by a minimum but not bland argument and much less boring.</summary>
	<body>We live in times of hatching of musicals for these payments, where previously just arrived the echoes of the taquillazos of Broadway and London. I do not know if recent film adaptations of popular this Dreamgirls or Chicago works have received the overwhelming kindness of the cyclic premieres of the Lope de Vega or the Apollo. And although it lacks accurate data, I very much doubt that both phenomena have reached gauging success. In my case, I've never declared an adept of the genre, both tapes seemed fascinating by its balanced commitment between a history of some interest and a brilliant audiovisual show. Topicazos outside, because the history of the rise and fall of the 'Dreamettes' abounds in the hackneyed structure of the so of fashion 'biopics' musicians (Ray, do tightrope?), tape offers enjoyment for who leaves to viewing it as a long video clip emerged by a minimum but not bland argument and much less boring. Contextualizada between the beginning of the 1960s and half of the 1970s, the film recreates how this trio of women first, resisted his predestined junior role as choristers and later, reached stardom in a country where it seemed still reserved to white artists. In this regard, the passage of the tape which shows how was common currency swiping successes to black groups distributed at the local level, cover them with a band of white and then get juicy revenues in national lists is very eloquent. Indeed, this issue, that of the hits and the struggle in the charts, is very present during all the footage from the tape. To the extent that many of the conflicts between the 'Dreamettes' come motivated by this issue, and the jealousy of some compared with other in the bid for higher levels of prominence. Moreover, some other good reasons to see this tape are attend the magnificent recital of that powerful whirlwind that goes by the name of Jennifer Hudson, discover a surprising double dramatico facet in Eddie Murphy and enjoy themed magnificent soul who squander rhythm pours more danceable versions and much feeling in his ballads.</body>
</review>
