<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Tideland" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With this movie you must relax, sit in front of the screen and let you carry. If you put any specific expectation on it, it is possible that you do not see accomplished.</summary>
	<body>Terry Gilliam said in the press conference that his wife had said a few words about Tideland which he had liked much: "with this film you must relax, sit in front of the screen and let you carry." "If you put any specific expectation on it, it is possible that you do not see accomplished." This kind of definition is perhaps ambiguous, but it is also the sense with that one can get out of the room. Personally, I I I debated between "just good" or "fucking good", but I understand that more than one would be between "just good" or "fucking shit". In fact, Terry already doing this game since always. One of its objectives is to provoke, do think. All his works he prints a very personal touch, a special magic that have few Directors today. And if ever it is flat, or excessively commercial, is because runout is taking to make the kind of films he likes. This is one of them. Like or not, will perform twisting of disgust or not, laugh or not, he will cry or not, but he has achieved what he wanted: that people react.Is it has described as a genre film, but I could not tell why. I guess it has an air of fantasy film, but it could well be a black comedy or a drama, adventure film, or a mixture of all. Tideland tells the story of Jeliza-Rose, a 9 year old girl who lives in a completely dysfunctional family. Accustomed to living in unfavourable conditions (his father has to prepare each night a shot of heroin, his mother can call you "slut" and "affection" in the same sentence, etc.), Jeliza-Rose has developed a great deal of imagination and easily evades the reality with the help of her four best friends (cutthroat dolls). The sudden death of his mother takes him to travel with his father to a lost House of Texas (grandmother's inheritance) and there begins a new phase of his life, where anything is possible (squirrels talking submarines in the middle of a meadow). Will hand in hand with its neighbours Dickens (a child with mental retardation) and his sister Dell (a spinster eccentric) find new possibilities for their incredible mundo.¿Y how is the world of Jeliza-Rose? It is hard to describe, but has something of Alicia in the country of the wonders and some fear and Loathing in Las Vegas. Never get to be a history intimate and full of adventures as the Alice, but not get to be as wacky as fear and Loathing in Las Vegas and scatological. Everything has a surreal air, but in the end nothing is as magical as it seems. If you press me also has an air to life is beautiful. The reality is that Jeliza-Rose lived the end of his family, the final decay, and that fate puts it in the hands of a family equal or worse. And, however, she finds adventure and new reasons for happiness where no adult could see them. Terry does is get in your skin. And the best thing is not to escape, not wanting to see it from outside. Then we consider if it was very hard, if it was fun or if it was empty.Aside from the story, deserve a special mention the excellent photography, aesthetics, completely adapted to the story, and the masterly interpretation of the girl child, Jodelle Ferland (also include Jeff Bridges in the role of father and Brendan Fletcher as Dickens).</body>
</review>
