<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Yo soy la juani" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Many relied not on his perverse and fornicadora mind was capable of representing the youth of the suburbs with such success that it could be entertaining and credible, but the truth is, as has done it.</summary>
	<body>When Bigas Luna submitted its draft "Yo soy la Juani" there was more than one to endure the laughter. But I knew that Bigas us would not leave indifferent and is we like it or not, is one of the greats. Many relied not on his perverse and fornicadora mind was capable of representing the youth of the suburbs with such success that it could be entertaining and credible, but the truth is, as has done it.This film you may like or not (there is a whiff to auteur, but of course if not was this would be a clear American taquillazo) but the truth is that the movie is unique, targeted and very very pampered.Best of all is logically Verónica Ehegui, discovery of the filmmaker whose fame discover new full of claw and talented actresses. Veronica will be if leave it, a great actress.Equally commendable is the interpretation of Dani Martín (the canto del Loco) and is this guy without being an actor, the truth is that it is better than many players in the same profile had been, congratulations Dani.A my is a movie that I liked, as it does not, meet many requirements to make it interesting. First bet for novice actors, more than 95% of the shit Spanish directors do not have the cojones to do second, is a topical issue (do though bland clear?) and third makes it adapting their art in the service of the script, which many do not respect, believing very great and then spoil the movie. Ay! I forget a fourth point, perfectly portrays the reality of many morons (including myself of course) marching to the capital to "artists", I thank God that fled the celebrity and I have not found in those cases in which found the Juani but the truth is that is how it isWhen you start?There to congratulate the "Yo Soy la Juani" creative because (as they say in my land "of the pelleja") he has gone out with all the Look &amp; Feel of the project. Sobresaliente.Lo I'm going to claim of this film is that the end is absolutely decadent, absurd, empty and stupid. Not liked at all and I think that he is loaded all the good things I mentioned earlier.I'm the Juani and it is on sale on DVD.Do to Bigas Luna, ask apologies for not accepting this role, but well I never liked for my? and on the other hand to encourage you to continue discovering people and giving them opportunities because if he does not he, Oh my God, Oh my God take us confesados.</body>
</review>
