<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Oceans 13" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do Ocean? s Thirteen is a film of entertainment, elegant, charming and fun as their characters.</summary>
	<body>To see George Clooney, Brad Pitt, Steven Soderbergh and company, one thinks if really what they do together in a movie can be called work or is simply a meeting of a band of buddies that are to have a fun time. In an industry in which multiply the disagreements between partners, it's nice to see a real group of friends enjoying their work.Do Ocean? s Thirteen recovers the best spirit of the original film of Danny Ocean, although it is a remake of La gang of eleven. On this occasion, Danny Ocean (George Clooney), Rusty Ryan (Brad Pitt), Lynus Caldwell (Matt Damon) and company trace a vendetta against Willie Bank (to Al Pacino), former partner of Reuben (Elliott Gould), to leaving tirado and on the verge of death. After the failed Italian experiment of the second film in the series Ocean, the action returns to develop in Las Vegas, with all the charm, mysticism and power struggles that surround the city of sin. In Ocean? s Thirteen leave aside the artificial history and eliminate secondary to focus on what really frames wants the Viewer: see the band doing burst the banks of a great Las Vegas casino. Steven Soderbergh repeats the keys to success, counting on a quick script, not too convoluted (many times the success is in the simplicity), and full of humor. One of the novelties is the removal of the female characters (except the of Ellen Barkin, the bad), which remaining intensity as a whole, and without them the history improvement, acquiring a greater packaging. And how, the main attraction of the tape are not actors, charming, attractive, fun, and scoundrels, rogues and thieves. From the ringleader, this master of deception called a Brad Pitt who laughs at himself, George Clooney, and ending in an Al Pacino which outboard the role of very bad. With similar mimbres, they are able to follow the saga almost to infinity.Do Ocean? s Thirteen is a film entertainment, elegant, charming and fun as their characters, and that neither misleading nor takes by fool the viewer at any time. And although it cost say that such elements are a great virtue, with the current film scene, we must surrender to the evidence.</body>
</review>
