<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Dame 10 razones" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Endearing, funny, original, fresh. This film can be defined with all these adjectives. I personally recommend, it is a simple structure and round movie.</summary>
	<body>Endearing, funny, original, fresh. This film can be defined with all these adjectives. I personally recommend, it is a simple structure and round movie, but so beautiful is what tells me that truth which has excited me and everything. We can always go further than what we thought, we only need the Jiminy cricket who plays Morgan. And always we Central America great things where least expected you and even find someone special as the character that plays Paz.Como production of Mr Freeman I have to say that it has been a success to make this movie, I like the line that leads to this film. As the great actor no more than the obvious to comment on, we turn to the despelleje that it is what mola os.Do paz Vega, sorry guys but I have to admit that this time not her I can criticize, is great, if it is, but? lol I can tell you "why". Interpret the character of peace required a diction that make credible his Latin status (by certain Morgan, the Spaniards are not Latino and Spain isn't in Mexico), so we need a great actress or therefore someone who speaks English horrifyingly, there you have it, peace is perfect, if you see the movie in original apreciaréis what I tell you. In addition the caching of peace is probably below the majority of actresses that Morgan liked and which would have accepted the role, which "save budget" and finally it must be acknowledged that the grace that has peace do not the American balurdas, she has grace d their land and it shows up in Hollywood. "It is very well directed," course is relaxed, focused and credible, not as in "does Teresa, the hodgepodge of? say the body of Christ".Do but I have to say my compatriot as follows: peace fields wheat, for the sake of Jesus Christ not accept USA more papers in Latin you're pigeonholing? and you not obsession with the body.And without further ADO, I'm going to give 10 reasons to see this movie: - Paz Vega (after Lucia and sex, his best interpretation).-. Morgan Freeman-it is fun-is fresh.-it is very pleasant-must support the actors emerging outside.-by the mane of peace-extra scenes of after the credits-by the BSO.-Ironcita recommended it.</body>
</review>
