<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Sed de mal (Touch of Evil)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Evil thirst is twisted, dark and tragic. One of those movies you must see before you die is and all that...</summary>
	<body>For many, even for many of those who have not seen, evil thirst is particularly famous to contain that, according to experts in technical watermarks of the cinema, is the best plano-secuencia ever. Camera, hung in an imposing crane descends sharply towards the couple formed by Charlton Heston and Janet Leigh (Vargas and Susan, his wife) to walk to the other side of the border to take an ice cream. At the time, someone puts a bomb in a car. What comes after is part of that story and should not be taken lightly.I remember I saw evil thirst for a long time and not filled me like now. I remember the sweat. The feeling of physical and mental strain: feeling that has not gone away, continues and, if possible, amplified. I think now more sordid than before: its obscenity is pampered to detail. Also it is sinister: his evil occupies the shadows characters are leaving in this border town between Mexico and the US (Los Robles). Orson Welles is Captain Quinlan, a FAT type to the cartoon, priming by the hatred of his paltry life in a disgusting corner of the world and eaten by a thirst for revenge not fulfilled (his wife was murdered and found the culprit.) Orson Welles reserves the juicy role. Perhaps Charles Laughton, which is one of my weaknesses cinematic, had played it with identical Office. Or Marlon Brando in his last days, before leaving at all. I can not imagine anyone more. Charlton Heston is the official Mexican narcotics you just put behind bars in the border mafia capo and just marry the sosa, inevitably sosa, Janet star. From here, Welles mounted a guignol on corruption and hatred empozoñado and leads the plot through the glassy eyes of the evil Captain Quinlan, which does not stop being a novelty.Evil thirst is twisted, dark (almost all the scenes happen at night) and tragic. Fascinated by the admirable picture of Russell Metty, by the inspiradísima and already immortal music of Henry Mancini (pure mixture of jazz, rock and roll and Latin music) and by the visual delight of his expressionism. Own character of Quinlan is already a fantastic discovery: a tormented man stopped himself, admired by their peers, but evil, in the background, aureolado of an evil rarely seen in the film. It is fundamental to the role of Marlene Dietricht, owner of a slum with piano in which a young Quinlan was "an exceptional man", but the violent death of his wife activates a mechanism of perfidy and impressive atrocity: Quinlan is ruthless, sullen, fierce in their laconic motion scenes.As impressive as the initial contrapicado is the scene in which Quinlan kills Uncle Grandi, another mafioso in poster, in front of a narcotizada Susan Vargas, thrown on a bed, farfullando, opening and closing the eyes shy, weakly: the way in which sausager gloves and place where Welles put the camera so we advise the cerniente tragedy, the fading light of the room, the agonizing death rattle of the victim. Everything contributes to the film teachers of Welles, his uncompromising talent to scrutinize the root of evil, his vast dominion over the human instincts. "Not in vain Orson Welles came to Shakespeare as soon as I could.""Cahiers du cinéma" defined it as "the best film of series B that has ever been made". Perhaps, despite excessive assertion, not missing the reason: the materials used by Welles are poor. The decorations are mínimso. Dialogs are not conspicuous by his genius. How from an irrelevant narrative or a very little props the genius of a director is capable of creating art. Art course, unhealthy, but one of those timeless cinematic experiences that one occasionally comes because you need an anti-wrinkle meeting of cinema in its purest form. Eschatological, in some cases. Symbolically, Quinlan died in a garbage dump.</body>
</review>
