<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El niño de barro" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A successful, interesting and humble proposal of good Spanish cinema.</summary>
	<body>"The tremendous kindness of the people of guess productions and the timely notice of muchocine.net not only allowed me the interview to Jorge Algora and Maribel Verdú but attend the premiere of"The child of clay"in A Coruña Filmax cinemas.""The child of clay" puts us in Buenos Aires, where some terrible crimes are taking place. Mateo (Juan Ciancio), a 10-year-old boy, hides a secret: sometimes your mind leads him to a dark place of the memory where is witness to the murders.To discover its secret many believe is the murderer. Estela, her mother (Maribel Verdú), with the support of the forensic police, Dr. Soria (KET Lera), try to find a rational explanation to the visions and thus undermine the skepticism of Commissioner Petrie (Daniel Freire).Although it is the first feature film released in theaters in Jorge Algora, it is not his first work after cameras as he has done before some documentaries and a TV movie. The same director told us that he had tried to prepare before his film coming-out. A humble attitude that honors him as a person but that, perhaps, prevented you more risk-taking in the Mise en scène.You choose a narrative style quite classic and well done, based on the solid script written by himself in collaboration with Christian Busquier and Héctor Carré, and delivered actors include Maribel Verdú and Juan Ciancio and Abel Ayala children that are frankly well Algora. In fact, the latter has a couple of really gruesome scenes, aided by the direction of Algora, who can leave the still camera so that what happens is shocking by itself.I can not fail to mention that to confirm his love for the classic film, the tape allows an intelligent and sutilísimo tribute to "M", one of the great jewels of Fritz Lang.Se supports the director, as I say, in a solid script (brave and little complacent with the Viewer) that sails with some ease between the thriller with fantastic touches and more stark drama, although unfinished fit perfectly both possibilities (something, of the other part, very difficult to make and that is achieved only very rarely).In short, an accurate, interesting and humble proposal of good cinema, things all of which we are not mates precisely, showing that we will have to follow very closely the career of its director.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 6.5 out of 10</body>
</review>
