<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Camino a Guant치namo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The road to Guant치namo is one of those movies that justify, beyond the mere and lawful entertainment, which the Lumiere brothers invented this film.</summary>
	<body>In the past Berlin Festival, its release caused a sensation that the directors of the film, Michael Winterbottom and Mat Whitecross, were accompanied by the real protagonists of the film: three British Asian origin, to be at the least opportune place and at least suitable time, were arrested as jihadists protalibanes in Afghanistan and transferred to this kind of place anywhere that is Guant치namoan of the legal and humanitarian aberrations by which the beginning of twenty-first century will be marked in the history of infamy and the ignominy.The film has been presented as a documentary, but it is not. Nor it is intended to be so. The faces and voices of the real protagonists overlap actors who represent them in a spectacular and precise recreation of his Odyssey: in 2001, invited to a wedding in Pakistan, young and unconscious three somethings, thinking that the threats of the United States.UU. attack Afghanistan they would not materialize, they decide to travel to that country to take a look. They are stuck on full invasion, detained in Taliban territory and taken by followers of Bin Laden.Alternando the testimonies in first person of the real protagonists of history with its reconstruction drama, filmed in Iran, the film is visually very powerful, with these images that resemble the amateur video of a tourist who travels by land exotic and fascinating, border and in permanent tension. Later, the recreation of the detention camps in Kandahar, torture, Guant치namo. This is creepy, without that managers use no sentimental tricks to win public sympathy.It is enough for the simple description of a few facts and deplorable acts by who are considered defenders of democracy and which are only getting that, the mere vision of the stars and bars flag causes disgust, fear and shame. Combative cinema, committed, essential.</body>
</review>
