<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Lost in La Mancha" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A documentary film interesting, heartbreaking, funny, sad, fundamental to really understand that the dreams of the filmmakers, are made and essential for anyone wishing to face the adventure of directing a film professionally.</summary>
	<body>Terry Gilliam is a film director peculiar, with a couple of great films and several anthological busts. Wonderful "Brazil", "12 monkeys", interesting "fear and Loathing in las Vegas" and "The Fisher King", but certainly his personal Titanic was accidentadísimo filming of "The adventures of Baron Münchausen", where the shooting of the film was on numerous occasions about to cancel, surpassing the budget estimated of unimaginable way and managed to kill harsh penalties. (As already happens earlier in Brazil ended up doubling the initial budget of $ 23 million).Audiences and critics, moreover, gave back, partly due to a regrettable promotion that made a $ 55 million production, to raise barely 4 million. From then on, Gilliam had chest fame director crazy, naive, irresponsible, and cursed. But if the great is hard to beat, as very bad is always surmountable and 12 years later, Gilliam would face one of the shootings calamitous and unfortunate history. Among many other reasons, because filming on Spanish soil which drew nearly 10 years of planning, several unsuccessful attempts of pre-production and search for funding worldwide, was inevitably suspended the sixth day, dragging with them a budget of more than 30 million dollars.This documentary, which only originally was intended as a usual off making, ended up being a single document on the unsuccessful filming of the project "The man who killed Don Quixote".Delay of the actors in the pre-production, failures of communication and organization, a volatile planning and something utopian, disasters and natural weather, aircraft that ruin the shots without remedy, an actor ailing protagonist who ends up leaving due to a double herniated disc Extras onstage without prior testing, pressure on the shoulder of investors and producers of the movie.A document shocking to understand what really hides behind the industry of cinema, the creative process and the real nature of artist faced of the success or failure of a cinematographic work that always depends on, inevitably, too many factors: the weather, the technical team, the artistic, luck, health, insurers, commitment, the divine will.Orson Welles suffered unspeakable in a similar crusade in the face of another version of "El Quijote de la Mancha". As if it were a strange curse, that filming was not completed. First died the main actor in the middle of this and a little later the same director leaving the work unfinished. A documentary film interesting, heartbreaking, funny, sad, fundamental to really understand that the dreams of the filmmakers, are made and essential for anyone wishing to face the adventure of directing a film professionally.</body>
</review>
