<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Oceans 13" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Thanks to the original implementation Sodebergh scene and a cast that happens it in big, Ocean? s Thirteen is a form of entertainment that can be seen.</summary>
	<body>Six years ago the irregular director Steven Sodebergh directed a film entitled Ocean? s Eleven, a magnificent top quality entertainment with a superb cast, led by the trio Pitt Clooney, Damon. Three years later, to see the hit which marked the first part, it was proposed to direct the sequel, that to me, I do not personally dislike, but not told me anything new. Do and indeed, following the second success, Sodebergh did not hesitate reunited again with the entire team, which seems that it becomes it Pearl, and carry out the third part: Ocean? s Thirteen may say that this film is totally unnecessary. What is more, I believe that with the first part of--for now - trilogy, already had enough. Already in Ocean? s Twelve the screenplay began to fall into the temptation of simplicity, but is that the plot is as simple as useless in the third installment. Do yet and so, thanks to the original commissioning Sodebergh scene and a cast that passes big, Ocean? s Thirteen can be seen, moreover, is a form of entertainment that is worth seeing, if only for the afternoon. The good thing about the movie is that you despite having an flojísimo argument with really stupid and incomprehensible actions, does not fall into the worst trap that a film like this can fall: boredom. Although Sodebergh would have achieved the high level of the first if it would have benefited from a solid base, and if he had quit so many useless and ido dialogues more grain. I must admit that, despite not being anything boring, the film comes to tire at some point for being so liosa and at the same time so simple. Let me explain: may seem, as exactly in the second part, which is very complicated to understand, because the smartass of Sodebergh skips many explanations (in some cases) and makes the viewer understand what is happening is extremely complex. But do not fool, this formula (with economic intentions, of course) that the director uses, is nothing more than a hoax. Yes, we can believe that all robatorios are amazing and very complicated, but in reality it isn't more than a simple and pure entertainment, and no searching, no way, logic, more than anything because in reality there. If you'll see Ocean? s Thirteen, not going to think, going to entertain you. And if you do not learn anything, because it is - a little - poorly explained, and not because you're stupid. I recognize that there are moments at which did not understand anything of what was happening, but I think this is what you want to Sodebergh.Como telling, sharing what has happened in large shooting this film. And it already shows! Almost all the scenes are of humor, and that is where it shows that inevitable spark have the actors and their absurd, but at the same time very effective dialogues. Get me the impression that this movie is a joke, but I don't know how, but has got me hooked. And just as the first part had a care script and some very nicely drawn characters, here these two aspects are lost altogether, and even so (I do not tire of saying it), it's incredibly enjoyable to see. There is chemistry between the actors, and there are several really funny sequences, and others, of course, pathetic (the change of the jewels and Vincent Cassell on the roof?) Who has seen already I mean). Do Yes, Ocean? s Thirteen is unnecessary, simple, less luxurious (by mcuho casinos that appear) than the second (do already do not say nothing in comparison with the first, because I could spend paragraphs comparing them and, indeed, Ocean? s Eleven won in all).And it is that along with your entertainment and the chemistry between the actors, there is another remarkable point and that it will fully part, and is the incorporation of two large and veteran actors Al Pacino and Ellen Barkin (who coincidentally worked together in interesting melody of seduction). They triumfan even more than Danny eco? sorry, George Clooney and his gang. They are the villains more fun and unique of the three films, even more than the funny and sometimes excellent actor Andy Garcia (careful to phrase that loose on the shadow that makes Pacino hotel to your pool). Between the latter and Barkin there chemistry, despite barely having the simple relationship of jefe-secretaria. But I think that she highlights more alone than together (great scene of her with Matt Damon). Although obviously not despreciaría the performance of the gang, to which they were joined by the always present there and already mentioned Garcia. Not to mention the entire team because they are many, but I am missing the presence of Julia Roberts (who appeared in the previous two) and Catherine Zeta Jones (that it only came out in the second and his role was very interesting, despite the fact that she is a bad actress), which provided that female air stood out above all the male gang. But it is also true that Barkin does equal or rather than the other two.In short, an entrenida film and nothing else, with a cast of luxury and, unfortunately, a style less care and simpler than the of two previous deliveries. Recommended for a Friday evening, in which you have no desire to think and Yes fun. That Yes, one-quarter would already be too. What's more: this third installment has already seemed completely unnecessary.</body>
</review>
