<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Enemigos Íntimos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Intimate enemies is a type of comedy that not abounds in the cinema today, fun, entertaining, and not offended or makes a mockery of the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>In almost all aspects of life, there are times of splendor and decadence, and the film was not going to be less. Years Golden in the decades of the 1950s, 1960s and 1970s, with some of the greatest filmmakers and actors of the history is lived in Italy, the seventh art. In this splendour, as well as the neorralismo they highlighted the subtility comedies starring magicians as Nino Manfredi, Alberto Sordi and Vittorio Gassman.Recientemente we can speak of a renaissance of Italian comedy, with new talents as Carlo Verdone, that not in vain the own Alberto Sordi appointed him as "heir". His latest film, which features the confrontation between Achilles (Carlo Verdone), a bourgeois married a wealthy heiress, and Orpheus (Silvio Muccino), a young man without ambition who intends to take revenge on Achilles for unfairly dismissing her mother reaches Spain. Thus begins a succession of esperpénticas situations and impossible to boot multiple laughter in the stalls. There are really hilarious scenes, such as the sequence of the voyeurs or visits to the hospital of both protagonists. It is also true that romantic tone of the story is slightly fade the intensity of the film, although it does not become a hindrance but a necessary accompaniment. Despite its long duration, slightly excessive for a comedy, the film is agile and pleasant, and the viewer never has the feeling of heaviness or the need to look at the clock. The best moments of the film are given from the confluence of a huge Carlo Verdone that pours the screen with each appearance and a no less brilliant Silvio Muccino, which gives an excellent replica.Intimate enemies is a type of comedy that not abounds in the cinema today, fun, entertaining, and not offended or makes a mockery of the Viewer. It neither falls into the uncouth, but it retrieves the style and those great Italian comedies of the 1960s elegancias. And confirms our best wishes: Carlo Verdone is the true heir of Alberto Sordi.</body>
</review>
