<review author="Bruji" title="El último show" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sensational staging in this tribute to the world of radio and a mythical program.</summary>
	<body>Sensational staging in this tribute to the world of radio and a mythical program. The always critical look and, in not few occasions, corrosive Robert Altman's falls on the last show of the Americas, the latest issue of the WLT. The last film of the last rebel. Farewell who knew that he could not convince death. "It was the last show." Everyone knew, but nobody said. People in the Midwest believes that if it ignores the bad news, they disappear. But I'm not from the Midwest. "."From somehow? possibly it - Robert Altman fired of lovers. He did work in the preproduction of a new project that would never be shooting lights. Also, as it could not be otherwise, with this phrase which is extracted from a context tilting frontally against the futile use and no sense of voice-overs. Impossible to resist the temptation to criticize a kind of cinema, of recent years, where any narrative technique, argument and even gender are valid to introduce the happy still small voice. Paradoxically, he employs with meticulous precision, in a timely manner, to put on the lips (in off) of the famous detective of the radio serial, absurd observations about the enigmatic femme fatale of your plot.In fact, a gesture that is not surprising in a nato provocateur. Remember that only he dared to trivialize on the war in Viet Nam when this issue still had not been in fashion; to question the American health system, health; to demystify the legendary Philip Marlowe in Raymond Chandler, in A long goodbye; slap the central axis of the film industry, in the game of Hollywood; break with the romantic aura surrounding players, in California Split; satirize the festivals of country music, in Nashvill; show the shallowness of the celebrations, in A day of wedding; destroy the impenetrablemente magical magnetism of the jazz in Kansas City; capture with cynical and accurate target the American way of life that so often caught his attention... beating pulse the adjective of rebel.Is possible that A Prairie Home Companion (real title of this film and name of a real program that airs from 1974) is the perfect excuse to meet on stage, for the last time, the passions that paid his filmography. The delicious country style songs. Crossed stories that feed its marked vocation towards the casts. Its excellent qualities in the direction of actors. The lengthy planos-secuencia the frenetic activity of the various characters, aiming to achieve them, sometimes, in impassable circuits. The recent dialogues, overlapping to create a false sense of improvised naturalness that has never existed in his film. And the continuous pictorial references, which recreated the scene of "The last supper" in MASH, or the portrait of Madeleine Stowe in lives crusades nude. A constant that, by way of painting Museum, the history of art lovers will find easily in the last Show. Precisely, the fascination and admiration that Altman felt for the painting, made that he decided to direct a biography of Van Gogh, Vincent and Theo, which is defined in the section on "stories rare and minority" in which there are others of his films, including three on a couch, with the collaboration of Glenda Jackson, or Quintetwhich intervened Fernando Rey. Those that only God and he understood. The essence of a manifest film irregularity which was chaired by his desire to monopolize many and varied fields, and his obsessive intention aimed at the destruction of preconceived ideals that emanate from the universe itself which weaves the celluloid.On this occasion, the exquisite musical numbers, offered live, alternate with crazy ads of Garrison Keillor, who advertised the multifunctionality of the duct tape, incredible pizzas Prince, in operatic tone properties, and praises the real sponsors: the powdered milk biscuits ranging in blue box. The truth is that any stupid sounds like glory, if it is sung in English. The culture of the show (only known by Americans) displays its charm. Behind the scenes, in a warm family atmosphere, began to worship the protagonists (all major) that only seem to serve the script dictated by his own thinking. Entrances and exits lawless. Hilarious moments. Mixed talks. Endless levels. This is Robert Altman. The filmmaker of situations, that rather than moralistic or deep, messages that offers his last function. The discoverer of actors such as Robin Williams (Popeye), and Clive Owen (Gosford Park), which returns to surround, as always did, from a cast of extraordinary quality. The possessor of a unique style in unsurpassed, unmistakable and unusual that it should only be admirar.¿Alan Rudolph? Paul Thomas Anderson? Do luis García Berlanga? not. I said: unique and unsurpassed.</body>
</review>
