<review author="Bruji" title="La cosecha" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The harvest complies with the overall goal of the seventh art, that is to entertain; and with the particular of the genus, which is none other that be scary. Very afraid.</summary>
	<body>Stephen Hopkins (strange crazy filmography director) is placed at the head of this story based on the old formula that exploits alleged ancient prophecies unleashed in our days. With clear allusions to the classics of horror, admirable photography and careful production, the harvest is, however, an irregular film, specially designed for the showcasing of a great actress and only recommended for fans of the genre. Sometimes, life gives a second chance that helps to understand the facts of the past, clarifies the own thoughts and obliges to believe again. With this approach, the producer of Alien Vs Predator (not kidding) discusses this terrifying project which is already among the curses of Hollywood, not by duty to its world premiere in Barcelona, but to be seen wrapped between hurricanes (Katrina and Rita) in Louisiana. Miraculously, the crew has even regrettable material losses, although the real miracle is that those responsible for a thing called lost in space have managed to get one film more than acceptable. In any case, the Joel Silver admiration for Gaudí's work, the Hilary Swank sympathy with the Spanish press and the threat of extinction of a genus which is reduced to the Eastern fantasmogénesis and sound effects to scare, draw us towards analytical benevolence.A priori, the harvest is not immune to the paranormal phenomenon of infestation, systematically, manipulates the film of recent years, and manifested in flashbacks "spectral" and "diabolic" voices in off. In this case, and fortunately, none of the constants are used as drivers from storytelling, being used only to demonstrate the cockiness of the screenwriter, to corroborate the various issues raised to reach a coherent explanation in the final resolution. Only that this self-contemplation, leads them to forget that the script has two major inconsistencies. The first, starring the fate of the priest, vilely mislead the Viewer, paving the way for a forced twist. The second, leaves open the possibility of a sequel, which could well owner "collection". Commonplace for a filmmaker accustomed to sign works such as predator 2 or nightmare on Elm Street week elsewhere, not can we talk about inadequate measurement of time, although Yes is true that rain's flashbacks, leading to a hasty end, it could have been avoided by adding fifteen minutes to the footage. We can appreciate the good intention that pays homage to the best mystery novels, in which the various secrets are revealed in the three last pages. Forgive the omission of, at least, two plagues that, surely, would have no relevance. The production of a 96-minute tape is appreciated. But not the horrible feeling of "bottleneck" that is patient when the lights are lit. Fortunately, that was not an argument of film noir.In the section of hits - out of the brilliant performance of the doubly born Hilary Swank and inherent to this type of movie special effects-, is necessary to highlight the amazing work of a camaleónica photograph that, at all times, follows guidelines dictated by the story. Blurry images that occur in the Chilean adventure, contrast with the sharpness of the panoramic views that show the blood swamps. The masterful lighting that triggers the last of the biblical plagues, alternates with the game of shadows that surrounds a memorable frame: the rise of the protagonist by the rungs of a ladder. Here is where the movie fan memory will make us rescue a mythical scene of the ladder of Caracol.De equal way, will be continuing the references made to other so many classics of the horror film. The "plague of pregnancies" will remind us to the village of the damned; the nightmare which culminates in feet stained clay, to the cemetery living; the figure of the priest, to the prophecy; the dream and the concentration of neighbours, two key moments of the seed of the Diablo.En paragraph of the blunders, we find the irregularity of Hopkins, capable of creating a certain atmosphere of tension, generate an interesting plot of intrigue, and shoot some shots with the clumsiness of the worst accused. It is then when assaulted another horrible feeling, which makes suppose that the entirety of the film has not been shot by the same director.Ultimately, the harvest complies with the overall goal of the seventh art, that is to entertain; and with the particular of the genus, which is none other that be scary. Very afraid.</body>
</review>
