<review author="Victor Omar" title="Saw 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is somewhat away from what we saw in the first</summary>
	<body>A year ago reached the screen a novel and original film of both physical and psychological terror. Criticism and the public welcomed her with open arms making it worthy of praise and well-deserved awards. "Saw" was those little tapes with the power to provoke the Viewer to be estremeciera in his armchair. The tension and anguish broad the audience during the hour and a half of footage. This sequel is trying to emulate his predecessor to stepping up the pace and the Machiavellian way to kill "Jigsaw".Jigsaw (Tobin Bell), psychopath dedicated to punish through horrendous testing to all those who need to learn any lesson from life by crook, now passes from darkness "Saw" to star in the film, in antagonism with the detective Eric Matthews (Donnie Whalberg), responsible for stopping him. Following one of their recent murders, Eric catches "puzzle", only to discover that it plans a new game, in which the son of Eric, Daniel (Erik Knudsen) is locked in a House with 8 victims more.Tenants should leave his prison before that a poisonous gas that thins the atmosphere ends with them. Obvious that not everything will be simple, because the House is littered with traps.Among the trapped is also Amanda (Shawnee Smith), survivor games in the prequel. The film then raises two main plots of Jigsaw/Matthews, in which the police must discover the whereabouts of his son to save him and the House, which is the combination of confinement and omnipresent gaze of "big brother" with the sadistic traps of "Cube".What can be reproached to the Director (Darren Lynn Bousman, in his directorial debut, then that James Wan, director and creator of the concept, decided to leave the sequel to concentrate on another tape), is the excessive use of editing tricks and I guess to some extent increase the intensity of the film, they end up like a desperate measure by adding weight to a plot that does not need.And this plot might not be brilliant, but it is certainly functional, fulfilling its mission of our expectations to be confused and surprised, albeit at the expense of the logic and credibility. It is a shame that the script has not affected a little more in the psychology of a few characters who never brings us to establish ties of empathy (just giving us like what happens them to members of the Group: we are just waiting for what will be the next to die).Even the figure of perverse serial killer is equipped with the capacity of characteristic of this type of characters fascination. With practically a trio of protagonists, the original tape allowed a deeper development of their personalities and dynamics.In the sequel we have half a dozen victims and the script should follow their progress into the trap while shows roughly their personalities. At the same time you have to do the same with the police and the killer. This fracture in the approach of the tape dissipated to some extent its impact, because it is obvious that the characters increase is due simply to the need for more almost anonymous victims and more scenes of bloody violence.Perhaps with a smaller cast had accentuated the importance of the characters, and it would have allowed us to empathize with greater vehemence in his plight. That does not mean that "Saw II" is soft or boring. Instead, their pace is frantic and cruelty that shows is equally disturbing (while sometimes feels a great effort to overcome its predecessor).There are enough scenes of blood and horror to satisfy fans of the "gore", and at the same time the story is interesting enough, both their ingenuity and their shameless manipulation of our perception.</body>
</review>
