<review author="Bruji" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do in this story, we find ourselves (not may be!) with a recurring voice in off and with the employment of? the no less socorridos - flashbacks, fashionable? and so bad used - in the film of recent years, especially in reference to tailored scripts.</summary>
	<body>Diary of a scandal? at least to the Spanish public - is not more than the Chronicle of a long-announced event and, with all luxury of details, destripado. A continuous process of advertising absurdities that lead us to a film that already nothing surprising, even the promotional poster of "woman against woman", usual stance of feminists of ABBA, a Barbra Streisand album cover, and why not say it? a clear plagiarism of the aesthetic Almodóvar. The precise adjective that is capable of expressing what trailers editors could do with some films has yet to be invented. They are supposed to be the first only the advance of the latter, never the abridged version of these. Ultimately, it is about selling an illusion without disclosing its contents.In the event that we discussed today, resorting to the term "barbarism" would be insufficient. This trailer is not limited to show some desubicadas images, highlight an effective phrase and conclude with a couple of associative indications. There is much more. Let's say that the whole of the argument is extensively detailed in a meticulous story, carried out in impeccable chronological order. The few álgidas scenes that does not emit (namely dos), would be known thanks to its four nominations to the Oscars, and the synopsis official (featuring thirteen lines) is responsible for clarifying the doubts of the confused. A nothing elegant way to banish the goddess surprise, that the lovers idolatramos.Do to get into this "tale of friendships and sexual poisoning" (as defined by its director), we are (not may be!) with a recurring voice in off and with the employment of? the no less socorridos - flashbacks, fashionable? and so bad used - in the film of recent years, especially in reference to tailored scripts. Without being Billy Wilder, Richard Eyre apply both techniques with extreme neatness, stood well above the contemporary filmmakers (we can think at Todd Field). A virtuosity that is appreciating in the direction of actors, in the resolution of dramatic scenes, excellent configuration of a perfect thriller and masterly treatment that tackles burning issues, such as the harshness of solitude, self-destructive life trajectories that derive from certain reprehensible behavior and irrationality that surrounds all kinds of falling in love.However, it is easy perceived the presence of a factor that clashes, which leads to the unreality of the events and reducing the credibility of the story. An aspect which comes from the adaptation of the novel. In Zoë Heller's book, the story is narrated in the first person, is a daily newspaper, which is why all the situations and characters are covered with absolute subjectivity, through the eyes of Barbara Covett. To transform the original text into screenplay by initiative of the own Patrick Marber, disappears the storyteller, creating a vacuum to try to rebuild the psychological characteristics of the rest of the characters. None of them looms with precision and the injured gran is Sheba Hart, the true protagonist, that looks blurred to collect life of its own outside the newspaper. His candor, the ingenuity with which faces adversity, the unit which contrasts with a Bohemian past invented by writer and, above all, the absence of a basic instinct of family protection is unlikely. Despite this, both female performances are unforgettable. It is possible that the great Dame Judi Dench, Lady of the British Empire, deservedly awarded in film, theatre and television, winning an Oscar for an appearance of just eight minutes in Shakespeare in Love (John Madden, 1,998), is always remembered for the role of Barbara, chilling Professor high school. Cate Blanchett, for its part, will be to give life to the unmatched Katherine Hepburn in the Aviator (Martin Scorsese, 2,004).In any case, their nominations were properly justified. Not so much the best adapted screenplay, or the soundtrack. The first, for the reasons discussed above, and the second to be impertinent in a harrowing story in itself.And, like all urban legend? so you can refer to this cluster of misfortunes, excess of coincidences, flurry of misfortunes coming together in a single person and at the same time-, the present will not be exempt from exemplary morals. Occur to me two. Who reveals a secret of disproportionate dimensions, becomes slave to his confidant, remained at the mercy of the good or bad will of his master. Before the juncture of pervert or be seduced by the glances, devoid of evil, in a tender bite, we will always choose take a withdrawal in time, which, according to popular wisdom, is the prelude to a victory.It would suffice with a "call me when you happy eighteen"... or thirty. Okay, they are still immature, you leave in forty and pico?.</body>
</review>
