<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Memorias de Queens" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great soundtrack, with beautiful and successful songs from the end of the eighty-one very well balanced interpretive cast, where everyone makes their work commendably.</summary>
	<body>"Dito Montiel is a writer of success that lives in California and has been very successful with his last novel"A guide to recognizing your saints,"semi-autobiographical." One day he receives the unexpected phone call from his mother, who lives in New York's Queens neighborhood, where Dito fled nineteen years ago. She tells him that her father is very ill and refuses to go to the hospital."Back to his old neighborhood, is recalling the events that made that very hastily leave from there".Very decent debut after the cameras of the writer Dito Montiel, who portrays semiauto-biographical form the last part of his youth in the neighborhood New York in Queens, specifically in the area mostly inhabited by Greek and Italian descendants.As mentioned the same credit, it isn't absolutely biographical, because some facts and figures are absolutely invented, as a very important character of his friend Mike, the Irish musical dreams. But merging this and that experience, that it lived in reality, constructs a mosaic of feelings and extremely interesting and painful realities.And does so in a way, I think, quite uneven. The form, the technique used, is not my complete taste, with a somewhat random montage and a formal compositions that denote some orginalidad, but that times distorts the narrative to make it somewhat difficult. And I think that it does so in a very personal way, Yes, but something free.However, importantly, this is what counts, is expressed with all harshness and sincerity, giving us know nothing complacent reality of some difficult years in a hostile environment, where will not stop to leave the protagonist suffered.Here, nor do I believe that I fully rolled the director, because some facts are not perfectly explained. For example, and this is fundamental for the understanding of the film, is not understood to one hundred percent the animosity of the protagonist towards his father, at least expressed as aggressively as he does. In its final part, alone in two master sequences between Dito and his father (magnificent Shia LaBoeuz and Chazz Palmintieri) is to live with intensity the misunderstanding and lack of communication between them. But before no, not expresses it clearly.Great soundtrack, with beautiful and successful songs from the end of the eighty-one very well balanced interpretive cast, where everyone makes their work commendably.Sometimes the young characters give the impression of being a little asshole, more than rebel or lacking in opportunities, but looking backwards in my own life, also lived in a working class district, although many miles of both physical and social distance of Queens, I recognize in some stupid behaviour. And if some not got them to perform I (on the route of the train) that I saw him do to any friend or acquaintance degenerate.In short, which is worth seeing, because although, I repeat, some facts are expressed somewhat arbitrarily, that at the end, in its last third arrives even thrill. Above all in the family scenes, in the confrontation between the protagonist and his father. Both want a lot but there is an insurmountable generational and cultural distance. This already I know him well I. So I have lived (although not in as dramatic form) and I've seen it on many occasions.</body>
</review>
