<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="La marca del lobo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Those to be expected werewolves film will do better staying at home that swallowing this sweetened love story interspecific.</summary>
	<body>Vivian lives in Bucharest, works at a chocolate shop and among her hobbies is occasionally practice "parkour". It also has a large extended family that likes to constantly tell you what to do and what not to do. A night after fighting with them for the umpteenth time, meets a young American cartoonist of comics (sorry, "graphic novel") and little it takes to fall in love with him. The problem is that the boy in question, Aiden, is human, and Vivian is a "Loup-Garou", a mujer-lobo in a race that has been around the world the past five thousand years. As it is expected, the thing brings problems when the congeners of Vivian decide to put an end to this romance as sui generis, because the girl does not seem to lay head (as if the fact of prendar of a cartoonist not ensure itself only a family conflict on a large scale).This, to large strokes, is the plot of Blood and Chocolate (2007), a film which has been titled in Spain with the dubious title of the mark of the Wolf, adding more confusion given gender, that we are not talking about really a film horror, as much that it appear werewolves eager to sink their teeth in human flesh. Like the novel on which it is based, we are faced here with a directed fantasy film explicitly female teenage sector and that it will tend to alienate any beholder. And if we add above that after this movie are the same producers responsible for Underworld (2003), is more than clear that no paints here nothing who does not belong to the EMO community. As for the similarities with the novel (have not read), these are apparently void, which is not the case at the moment.However, the mark of the Wolf is a film difficult to outline, it is completely dispensable. Everything it promises an endless series of clichés, from that picture of the most emblematic buildings of Bucharest (which could happen by a tourist brochure of the Romanian capital) until the amorous adventures of a Romeo and Juliet with Werewolves of medium. The Werewolves, incidentally, are not shown as bipedal monsters, but as human beings who are literally transformed into wolves in the middle of a Flash of mystical light. At first, the history not paints them not bad, even as beings that offer a true social justice in the underworld of the city, all ruled by their leader Gabriel (an Olivier Martinez putting more crappy accent it that far this year). The parejita protagonist does not stop ever, curdling while Agnes Bruckner comes here much more beautiful as the schoolgirl in the cursed forest (2006). Teammate cast, Hugh Dancy, on the other hand, is bland to the point that could be described as Orlando Bloom of the poor. The wolves never feel as threatening beings, and during the final stretch the male protagonist acquires an inexplicabes skills of action hero who certainly do not favor him.Among the few virtues we can find is that, all in all, the film becomes more bearable than be expected and passable. It will so far and never tries to pass through what is not (except, of course, advertising that it made the study). Those that go with low expectations might even enjoy it and let those shameful moments of video-clip in which history mounted us a musical transition for the sole purpose of advancing the plot. Everything about this film is so light and so forgettable that is difficult to Prime with her, and much less after returning from vacation. Those to be expected werewolves film will do better staying at home that swallowing this sweetened love story interspecific. As final note I can only add one thing: be a member of an ancient race of powerful creatures antropófagas and still receive a beating from a cartoonist metrosexual must be one of the saddest experiences in the life of any licántropo that should be respected.</body>
</review>
