<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Pasión de los fuertes" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is a perfect example to explain that does not know what is the western. One of the best western in the history of cinema.</summary>
	<body>The strong passion is anti-western: Ford dismisses set his talent in the pure action, although this comes at the time and set the epic and tragic tone of the genus. Nor is it a western Baroque: the economy of means and the absence of artifice gives an unusual poetic splendor, subordinate to the conquest of ideals and the romanticism of the birth of a nation. Because Ford has that: the founding of a country, the progressive laws seat that they will govern and living conditions for settlers believe a folklore, enabling the cult a religion and, above all, susbscriban the stereotype of a nation, because the United States of America are born with Wyatt Earp and these characters on the back of the fatalityherding animals by dusty landscapes and forging legends where the heroes obey strict codes of honor. The film is a perfect example to explain that it does not know what is the western: appearing in nothing and peoples who live around the tavern where the bar bars are endless and the whisky is the entertainment of the dispossessed and those who lampan for a better future; Sheriffs with a strict severe of duty and a well established moral integrity; pianists who come to be juke-box of the time. Passion of the strong (My darling Clementine) is, on the other hand, duel of the Titans, the time of handguns, Tombstone, duel at OK Corral or Wyatt Earp: are all the same movie. John Ford is the freest of the primordial argument version, which departs from the script and staged the socio-political vision of a man who invented, in their own way, a genre, the western. Tombstone, the anthological people, to whom Bob Dylan dedicated an accelerated immortal blues, is this Ford Tombstone. Henry Fonda is Wyatt Earp, the farmer that random and revenge become sheriff. Doc Holliday, the surgeon tormented, conflictive and continuous process of personal redemption is Victor Mature. And John Ford, of course, has the wit and sensitivity of violence become poetry, subvert an argument necessarily agile and prone to action in an intimate table of customs, in a beautiful portrait of a nascent society, where men killed and died by trivial matters and where the law was a conversation between Knights acodados in the bar of a bar.</body>
</review>
