<review author="Yul B." title="Oceans 13" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>?Do Ocean? s 13 (Thirteen)? It is for me a good movie because it has given me exactly what I wanted: fun. But if we compare, does not reach the master of?Do Ocean? s Eleven?</summary>
	<body>Do I figuratively bows before the fans of this franchise to recant part of my omens on?Do Ocean? s 13 (Thirteen)?.The superstitious who writes you underestimated advance this film to consider it as a stretched repetition of the formula, a tape dispensable and unnecessary, and a future sacacuartos.Today, view once, still think almost the same, but must admit that it has not hurt anything to pay for enjoy it. ?Do Ocean? s 13 (Thirteen)? It is for me a good movie because it has given me exactly what I wanted: fun. But if we compare? do does not reach the master of?Do Ocean? s Eleven? (from 2001).What is clear is that?Do Ocean? s Twelve? She sweeps it. They are night and day. It is the contrast between boredom and complexity, and the divertimento and the simplicity. It seems incredible that two sequels have been made by the same director and (almost) the same actors.In the second installment Soderbergh we riddled with long preambles, convoluted plans and sub-plots, and complex dialogs that looked like they were not wearing anywhere. This last? hit? It is completely the opposite. Now everything is infinitely easier: Ocean band performed again only and exclusively for revenge, nothing more. They will try to recover the honour of one of its members, Rebuen, scammed by Willie Bank, pretentious and greedy owner of a hotel-casino that is about to open in Las Vegas. The goal: quit bankrupt and throw the soil its prestige. The major obstacle: the supposedly impassable supercomputer called?Greco? supervises and controls everything that happens in the enclosure to the smallest detail.Under this approach the film unfolds with a highly ordered structure, fluid, agile and without strange twists of those that appeal to the director. Starting with the impatient preparations of the plan, through the entertaining implementation of such a plan, and ending with the surprising, that not unpredictable, the culmination of revenge, everything passes before us in an exquisite manner? but simple.This simplicity is that deprives this film to pass the test with note, being far from being excellent.On the one hand, the plot takes place smoothly. The band of Ocean comes almost everything right, and that did not fix instantly; and again, as expected, of which there is a minimum tension in scenes that you may have worried in the armchair. Only enjoy peacefulness and quietly watching how the guys, with apparent ease, go giving sticks everywhere to the despicable Bank.Aparte of this, there is no depth in characters. Each timely performance of each actor takes very few minutes, which speeds up the development of the film but left the public without taste of art who have guys like Don Cheadle, Bernie Mac, or Elliot Gould, to name three examples. Do but that is what has the? overbooking? Star. If you give footage one by one to show off the film wouldn't last two hours but six. Why Soderbergh has chosen this time, with success, the action rather than the mileage dialogue.It is palpable that those who leave the cod in this installment are secondary, which are the cornerstones to run well the plan. Oh, and Matt Damon he is at least more frequently.George Clooney and Brad Pitt, friends walk through the film as authentic vases, the low turnout which has the sweetheart of la Jolie in the plot of the sequel being blatant. At least Clooney is seen that it makes her role as supervisor with some interest, but Pitt has brought a good cut with this film because it has the bucket without barely disheveled.In addition, I have missed a most prominent female presence. I recognise that Ellen Barkin is a Cannonball physically; It is amazing how spectacular is this woman at his age of 53, and would like to see I to any girl encased tight dresses that brings me so well in the film. But you don't have the glamour and the prestancia of the rest of females involved in the saga, he said is Julia Roberts and Catherine Zeta-Jones.Para the end I left the master Al Pacino. I have already said that he would be one of the reasons why this tape would be. And I was not disappointed; What happens is that it has been eaten by the rapid Dynamics imposed by Soderbergh, and his performance has fallen short to make an apotheosis showcasing. However, I also said that this man filled the screen even silent and that I was not wrong.Andy Garcia is an anecdote.Anyway, while Soderbergh has dropped a rung on good do respect to her?Do do Ocean? s Eleven?, has been able to give this sequel a place recognized in the saga. For me the second best film of the franchise.If what you deprived the glamour, luxury, good music (amazing BSO) and spend a fun time without comeduras of pot, this is your film. Recommended 100%.</body>
</review>
