<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Tideland" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the more contentious and controversial of Terry Gilliam films. A title difficult but vision compulsory, even of those who remove the Undercity.</summary>
	<body>It seemed impossible to come brand new in Tideland Spain, one of the most contentious and controversial of Terry Gilliam films. But, luckily, comes already the product of monty American python from his pass for the Festival of San Sebastián, has created controversy over those places in which has been planned to our screens. And it is, as says its own director, before Tideland should take sides; or for or against him. There is no term means before so committed like this work. Due to its particular style and the harshness with which exposes certain topics, hardly his vision can leave anyone indifferent.The film, in a very specific sense, keeps a clear and large parallel with El Laberinto del Fauno that, like Guillermo del Toro, Gilliam has focused on the child world, translating into screen surreal fantasies that come to the mind of a 9 year-old girl when he is trying to escape from the daily horror that he lives.Jeliza-Rose is the name of the small cover of the Alice of Lewis Carroll, who stars in the film: a young girl who has grown up amid a hellish atmosphere and, raised by a couple of junkies, will depart in the company of his father, to distant lands, after the death of his mother from an overdose of methadone. Entering this deep arid America, father and daughter will be installed in the abandoned and lonely House property which had been her deceased grandmother. There, taking advantage of his father's endless holidays, Jeliza-Rose expanded his hermetic universe dolls decapitas and syringe, to establish contact with the peculiar inhabitants of a nearby mansion.Terry Gilliam, through this minimum argument, Orchestra a visual delusion in which witches, deformed beings, stuffed animals and hungry sharks will surround the macabre playground of Jeliza-Rose. A provocative touch of black humour and certain perverse aftertaste by eschatology, are the clear symbol of a filmmaker who likes to warp reality through large angular and twisted plans. And there, in the same epicenter of this show Dantesque and prohibited to minors, shines with their own light Jodelle Ferland, the girl who, through a tour de force outstanding, gives life to the dreamy girl who wielded his parents nurse for too many years: a brilliant interpretation that even makes less than a Jeff Bridges cloths immense (though near in the histrionics).Some catalogarán Tideland as one of these common (but magnificent) rants of its director. But, in my view, they fall into a profound mistake. It must be approaching Tideland gradually, cautiously, prepared to read honestly the proposal of Gilliam, behind these apparent hallucinogenic battering, is a huge and painful reality that many will refuse to recognize. A daily reality, unfortunately, very close to all; one of these realities that we want to eliminate the social map wielding the baton of false morality that both dresses today. And it is precisely those who practice this double (or false) morality, they will those who flee lament cinema to half an hour of starting the slide show.A wonder that arrives at our country with the misleading label of misunderstood. A tender praise to the mental strength of the smallest of the House. A unique and splendid film. A fierce and crude provocation ideal to awaken dormant consciences and eyes closed. A true work of art created by a kind brave and full of brilliant ideas. In short: a title difficult but vision compulsory, even of those who remove the Undercity.</body>
</review>
