<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Xmen3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Brett Ratner takes good pulse saga, although the script in some cases does not help it too</summary>
	<body>The new installment of the adventures of these mutants idolatry is captained by Brett Ratner (hour, Red Dragon) at the expense of Bryan Singer, director of the previous two films and has shifted from superhero to take care of Superman Returns. The result, in my view, is a film less than two previous deliveries, where Ratner has focused more to show than in delving deeper into the characters. Despite that X-Men: the final decision, has a very interesting social and political content, and which continues to be topical. The action is based on found the cure to the problem of the mutation, so anyone who has this anomaly can become "normal". Of course this discovery will leave supporters and detractors. Among these, they appear Magneto and his henchmen, which allege that there must not be cure, since there is no disease, and that in any case they are the cure.With this approach one can discern what is going to happen, but nevertheless does have some surprises and interesting parts, as see the aspect more humans Logan (Wolverine) that make for a return to lead to Jean Grey next to the good, because it is converted in Phoenix and is a danger for humanityincluding the mutants contrary to the cause of better Magneto.Lo of the film are his battles, something which many fans will appreciate, especially those who go in search of spectacle, by logic it is they are looking for the spectators who come to this kind of films. Within these battles stresses the new weapons that used the army to try to stop them.A point that has created some controversy are the new characters that appear, because they have changed enough to adapt the comic book and because some participations are ephemeral. Among those who have a prominent role is beast, played by Kelsey Grammer, (the fantasy Doctor Frasier and usual cheers) and is also the young protagonist of Hard Candy, Ellen Page, as well as the usual Famke Janssen, Hugh Jackman, Sir Ian Mckellen and Halle Berry, which have increased their participation due to their complaints.In final Brett Ratner taken with good pulse saga, although the script in some cases not helps too, and prepares us for a more than likely fourth delivery, while there in project movies as Wolverine, and some of its protagonists say that they do not believe that there will be a new adventure for the X patrol.</body>
</review>
