<review author="Antoni Messa" title="La ganadora" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A fairly compact portrait of what it means to live with the burden of a dozen of small and in a continuous state of poverty. Pity that in their last final minutes, decided by the usual aftertaste spielgberiano molasses.</summary>
	<body>Two years later it comes to Spanish screens The Prize Winner of Defiance, Ohio; IE, that here the translators have chosen to simplify the winner, a proper film that partly, and due to its aesthetic and the way to be described, refers directly to the style of Robert Zemeckies, his producer, who initially had in mind to carry out the realization. Several commitments and conflicts of agenda, made that it cede such liability to Jane Anderson, a writer with some previous experience as a Director in the television field.Based on a true story, it tells the vicissitudes that had to suffer the selfless Evelyn Ryan to take forward their ten children and deal, at the same time, with the outbursts of an alcoholic husband and serious psychiatric problems, which, every day, upon returning from his job as a mechanic in a factory, came home without a dollar in the pockets: the miserable pay received invested them in a nearby liquor store.The story begins at the end of the 1950s, an era that seems to motivate the best intentions of Zemeckis. An exquisite production design, the rapid beat of the swing as successful soundtrack, narrative and Visual experiments and a Julianne Moore in one of its best moments of interpretative, mark the fast pace of a melodrama full of humorous touches. The sides before the House of Evelyn Ryan, with the intention of telling the viewer how to remedy economic bumps that became his family, are more ingenious and original. Women, highly skilled for the rhyme, discovered a gold mine thanks to its multiple participations in radio and television advertising competitions. With the help of his mind, paper, pen, envelopes and stamps, he devised a long amount of slogans that, for many years, you were awarded, all kinds of gifts, by companies responsible for products to promote.The presence of Woody Harrelson is one of the determining factors for the success of the film. In it, through a too exaggerated physical characterization, it gives life to Kelly Ryan, the scattered and conflicting family guy. His bipolar temperament means work to the limit, always bordering with the histrionics, but without ever falling into it. Like his character, play with the ends until the last moment, being able to trace his interpretation towards more serene channels.The book The Prize Winner of Defiance, Ohio: How My Mother Raised 10 Kids on 25 Words or Less, written by the sixth sister of numerous offspring of the Ryan, inspired the screenplay of the own Jane Anderson; a script that stands out for alternate with the comedy drama wise way, way with the kitsch of the publicity of the years 50 and 60 and getting a fairly compact portrait of what it means to live with the burden of a dozen of small and in a continuous state of poverty at the same time. Pity that in their last final minutes, decided by the usual aftertaste spielgberiano molasses. But, despite this, it has the merit of not to fall into the easy tear.</body>
</review>
