<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Half Nelson" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There is nothing to say against this film, although it is not a masterpiece. Even a great movie, but is made with great sense of dignity, lovingly written and filmed without enfatismos. Its theme being so rugged, that - in these times of hyperrealism and dizziness film - is very, very welcome.</summary>
	<body>One learns to live with their sins and it is possible to achieve even lower of drama, forbidding them, consent that part are the life or that it is scarcely possible to repent of them, losing in the redemption or be sufficiently cynical to display them unprejudiced. There are lives escoradas to the tragedy, certain fatalism and others, frugal, that do not pass of the mediocrity of the grey and plumbous tedium. The life of the history teacher portrayed in this interesting Half Nelson is one of those which it coexists with their sins, save them in private corners and endures the days as good you can. Toxicómano, idealistic, sensitive and, above all, it is utopian. In fact the film does blood in drugs, although it could well do. In fact, there is no intolerable scenes. The drug world is drawn very tangentially: Dan Dunne (a sober and convincing Ryan Goslip) is not the addict sold by Hollywood to use productions. In fact, the film moves away with great discretion the gender and emphasizes more sociological or even political aspects than mere shots of crack or cocaine to show us how hung is the teacher, to which in two-faced Janus displays two sides of the same person: passionate teacher, aware of the absolute privilege of teaching and the fundamental value of the material at hand (human form)(, adolescents who see his pedagogy illusions to live better and habits of conduct regulated to live better in that society) and infamous human self-destructive, abandoned in a cubbyhole in which drug such as read a verse of Baudelaire (precisely Baudelaire) or listen a languid blues of Billie Holiday (precisely Billie Holiday). If something I liked the movie, even in its default, in his little attractive approach, is occasionally by his utter lack of ambitions. There is no gruesomeness. There are no surprises. Nor that pornography of needle and vein that, in other cases, color throughout the film and does not allow us to glimpse details. There are no superfluous chromatics: all agree to a grammar accurate, alien to any kind of subjectivity. The merit of the film by Ryan Fleck lies in acting sobriety of the 2 main characters: the painfully human master and pupil was devastated by a difficult world (brother in jail, money shortage crisis of personality) and suddenly finallly to him to help him lift the slump, whose wisdom and balance allows the rough teacher avizore a better future and recompose their vital State and their desire to be in this world. Ryan Goslip lost the Academy Award for best actor at the recent gala. It is not a role that like for a very narrow-minded Academy, but he deserved. Its says, is also easily arrumbable to the easy ground of fierce criticism, is that abuse of the camera in hand, that tired, really, but that maybe best for framing that world nervous, fragile, broken into a thousand pieces that condenses in the poisoned minds of the master. And tiredness, sometimes their images, not never override the viewer and leave him in a huge limbo of ideas, but sometimes little nuanced. It seems that it is a film that requires, as I wanted to Umberto Eco for its open work, an engaged reader, a spectator alert does not lose any message and can then find sense to all them and amalgamate them into a compact whole. If you get a peliculón. It can that Penza aren't neither prepared nor eager to dig so much that, on the surface, does not require so much dissection.</body>
</review>
