<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Oceans 13" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you feel something in the pit of the stomach so happy seeing all the friends of Soderberg you don't have to worry. Arcades is called. And it happens when just the film.</summary>
	<body>The actors in the series Ocean? s have a reputation for fun with the shooting and then promoting the movie. They spoke of it in Cannes with the same irony that if end of inventing, themselves, the irony. They resemble the characters from this book "FISH" which explains, inspirandose in the sublime example of a fishmonger, which are the rules to remember to make the work climate positive and not a dumping ground for energy. Fame is, at times, a perfidious damsel that gives her favors to whom deserves them less (the lamentation is true for both the book and the film).Danny Ocean trilogy consists of stories of fortunes that change of hand, millionaires and sympathetic men who deserve to be so. In the first 11, Clooney's character and Andy García competed in the field of the ingenuity of the money and, above all, in the heart of Julia Roberts. In the second they came to Europe to play with a European thief who all meaba further, the dollar or the euro? The third runs along the well-trodden path of revenge.Soderbergh transmits his camaraderie with the cast and also with the public. His style is to treat us as equals, why not wasted our time. Practice the ellipsis as an an accomplice who doesn't want to bother us. It is worth thank you, above all, if one owns the video-club that will be indispensable for all those who want to understand what has happened.Tunnelling machines, factories of dice, computer programs that read in the pupil if a winner has cheated. An irrepressible inclination there is in Soderberg to be epatados, with the magnificence of the casinos in Las vegas, either with the sophistication of the methods of the thieves of Las Vegas casinos. One of the parts needed for the coup, the factory of dice, suffers a strike of workers. For the protagonists the most unexpected surprise is discovering the ridiculousness of the amount of the sum of all labour claims by a picket. It is comforting to know as is the repampinfla all and lives the rest of mortals. It comes very close to how much we care about the rest of mortals as they live.If you feel something in the pit of the stomach so happy seeing all the friends of Soderberg you don't have to worry. Arcades is called. And it happens when just the film.</body>
</review>
