<review author="JLO" title="Shrek 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With the same resources from the first, it is a good film that would be best Court if it was not his own shadow.</summary>
	<body>It is difficult from the come on, bear the heavy backpack to be the sequel to one of the best animated films of the history. Yes, Shrek won that right for being a film almost flawlessly and enjoyable for adults and children from beginning to end. Endearing characters, a child film but without forgetting the many winks for adults, with in addition a script solid and very entertaining. To this day a true classic in its genre.That Yes, the writers now bemoan not having left more open between the characters to be able to exploit, surprised the enormous success of the original which was already confirmed, has assured until a 4th Shrek. And they have every reason for concern. It is not that wit or action lacking. The visit of the couple of ogres to the House of the parents of her, shoots a lot of helpful situations. The inclusion of the fairy godmother as new villain is both original and surprising, but does not make us forget the incredible Lord Farquaad, the dwarf Prince of the first part.The music returns to stand out with versions of Tom Waits, Nick Cave and David Bowie, as well as references to other films which are many-the Lord of the rings, Barbie, the Little Mermaid, mission impossible - and the guest appearances - and gags - Pinocchio. Everything enjoyable and spectacular. The inclusion of the new character of Puss in boots rather than add, subtract. It overlaps with the work of the donkey by dividing the comic parts. With the same resources from the first, it is a good film that would be best Court if it was not his own shadow. Even repeated in the message pointed out that we should not make any difference, and less on love issues.The truth is that Puss in boots, with the neutral voice of Antonio Banderas and singing the trilladísima Livin' la vida loca. It is too much. Let us hope that the imminent Shrek the third lift in something the aim.</body>
</review>
