<review author="Red Stovall" title="Tideland" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very bad, the worst of Gilliam, and that more time should be included in the batch of films coming to us with great delay (en 2005) and premiered in rare places. At this stage we are already used to, and in this case, better than best.</summary>
	<body>The former monthly Python Terry Gilliam has managed to create a career with some fame, along with John Cleese if this in the field of interpretation, which is such a fun group of comedians. Movies like?The heroes of the time? and?Do do Brazil?, and to a lesser extent? 12 Monkeys? and?The Fisher King?, are good sample of good make Gilliam, films of different thematic but very recognizable in the style of a director who almost always made what has given him pleases, though for this has had to deal with a good part of the critique, and also of the public. Something that has had its greatest exponent with?Do Tideland?, which is receiving some of the most ruthless criticism that recall, and the truth is that I'm not surprised at all.The amazing argument of?Tideland? It begins when the absolute protagonist of the story, a girl called Jeliza-Rose flees with his father, a finish and some rock singer, once his mother die victim of an overdose of methadone. They refugiarán in a lost House of the hand of God, in which the father will go on "vacation" due to the dose that so carefully prepares you his daughter, and this will create their own fantasy world, full of extravagant and rare characters.Does my companion Beatrice, in his review of the film, spoke of the evident similarity of this film with?The Laberinto del Fauno? Guillermo del Toro, who was also in the same directions. The truth is that one is a demonstration of how to do things right, and the other of how do them wrong. Do the curious thing is that in?Tideland? sees the hand of Gilliam 100%, its clear and recognizable style from beginning to end, but this time things have not the slightest sense, and Gilliam has made a film with the same intention, reputable and hated at the same time, other authors have from time to time: live from the tale. Almost dare to say that this is closer to the nonsense of David Lynch entitled?Does Inland Empire?, which laughed half the world and part of the other. Gilliam, like Lynch, has a name, and knows that arriving. But one thing is skating and offer a film well below the possibilities of its director, as it may be?Does the secret of the Brothers Grimm?, and quite another, do what come you in WINS, no feet or head and claim you uphold only because Yes.Do maybe clarify that during the filming of?The secret of the Brothers Grimm? He was there to do a break by the complicated shooting that had such film, and Gilliam or short nor lazy was rolling in record time?Do Tideland?, so if this film responds to a need to relax the Gilliam Lord by all the stress accumulated in the movie starring Matt Damon, then okay, can be understood. But, as public, we must decide what we think the film, and seeing it is very clear that Gilliam has given as the public passing by lining all the commandments, or rules, or as you want to call them.Things in?Tideland? they happen because Yes and without explanation. The dizziness that produces in the Viewer is not because Gilliam has demonstrated a confusing staging, no, there will not the topic, but thematically and arguably. For starters, the flight of the father with his daughter, after her mother dies, is totally incomprehensible and nothing credible. From there, everyone who believes in his head the breeding does not respond to any logic, which would have his grace if it were presented in attractive, but the lack of interest and boredom are the General tonic for the film. Gives us absolutely equal everything we see in the film. Gives us just why the girl is invented everything is invented, and does not seem to be because their parents are some drug addicts of noses, because she is very happy with them, not even because his mother will not let him take their chocolates, something really absurd. Then, in the imaginary world, call it so, disinterest is total, although in this case we have to endure to one or another character of most unbearable. And I am not going to talk about the foul allusions to pedophilia or necrophilia, to name only two examples soft. To film him fails to be absurd, bad and boring, it also has to be disgusting.Probably the only thing salvageable from this nonsense is its young protagonist, the girl child, Jodelle Ferland, who is delivered with passion to his character, and despite all their paranoia, manages to not be burdensome, even when he speaks with his unbearable head doll. All stakeholders appear to histriónicos clowns getting out of proportion to the Viewer, especially a desfasadísimo Jeff Bridges, with a poorly drawn character. It would also save the soundtrack, the work of the brothers Mychael and Jeff Danna.Por else a film very bad, the worst of Gilliam, and that more time should be included in the batch of films coming to us with great delay (en 2005) and it premiered in rare places. At this stage we are already used to, and in this case, better than best.</body>
</review>
