<review author="Bruji" title="Oceans 13" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Ocean? s saga, as the Danny? s band, reality and fiction, has a team of white glove that works.</summary>
	<body>The Ocean? s saga, as the Danny? s band, has the ability to know dock at box office, while no one will understand, with precision, the methods used. Either by the proven technical virtuosity that demonstrates Steven Soderbergh camera in hand, by their impossible planes, impeccable montage that characterizes their tapes, savoir être Clooney, or by the stunning physical attractiveness of Brad Pitt; the truth and truth is that, in both cases, reality and fiction, we have a team of white glove that works.Bad counselor is the glorious, although come disguised as enthusiasm and preceded by justified pride. Nor, apparently, was really the pretentious assertion that, back in the 2nd century a. c., formulate Archimedes of Syracuse: "Give me a place to stand and I will move the Earth"; nor, of course, is true of Warner's belief in the 21st century, according to which, "with big stars, are good movies". This technique, - mostly used by producers in the 1960s in full decline of the system of studies already became obsolete. More, as Mankiewicz in women in Venice said, "It is not so easy to do jump the Bank in Las Vegas as lead a fantasy to Hollywood", and Steven, the traitor of independent cinema, dares with both fronts for - and custom - sing an old issue of Mecano. One in which the eleven is one; the twelve, the two; and so, the thirteen three.If from a strictly cinematic point of view you may not catalog the thirteen of "good", it is undeniable that soon are significant, such as attractive and guarantee effective synonyms to define it.Effective is, without a doubt, its irregular, changing and misleading narrative structure, at all times, to the attention of the Viewer is not telecommunications engineer, experienced dealer or casino Manager. Brilliant in the first part of the footage, get enviable skillfully combine the continuous flashbacks and intermittent vocals in off in some interlocking dialogues that overlap to the central axis of the argument. Attractive is the prodigious direction of actors that performs an expert in choral tapes that, in addition, it develops complex sequences of perfect planning which, unfortunately, go unnoticed when trying to follow the plot between shared screens. Elite is the photography, special chromatic contrast, who, until recently, he signed as Peter Andrews.Y is that, despite him anyone else, the ocean? s saga knows the classics, to major productions of the best war genre, the allocations of first line which culminated in the cinema of catastrophes, the author of recognized prestige accepting commissioned work to continue with his own filmographythe obsession with the details in the perfect robbery of Kubrick, the asphalt jungle, Huston.En this last time, we came to the point in which la flor y nata of low-life is excited when participants of a television contest win a House, at the time that adjust you the accounts to an ACE (to Al Pacino) kept the writers in the manga. Gone are the adventures of the Rat Pack, stories of van and zapatazo, to make way for some criminals cults and "glamorous" style catches a Hitchcock thief. Are you miss, however, social criticism, and the character of acid of the dialogues of the gang of eleven, perhaps because in them, something or much had to see someone named Billy Wilder. The attempt of denunciation of the precarious economic conditions for Mexican workers, which contrasts with the cash rate of American actors, fails to taste because of the ridiculous jokes that are spent at the expense of noble people.And that is, we assume, the farewell of "a few players analog in a digital world", in which Valencia is California and the Greco makes mischief; just at the very moment in which those who shook the hand of Frank Sinatra (and which not) begin to tire of "props for pure props", the VIP and the NIP, the troubled face of Clooney, Pitt handsome pose and the slot machines. In any case, we should not forget that our strong point (the ego) is always our weak point, and that "when someone is ashamed of what always has been, it loses its essence". Wise advice, although coming from the underworld.</body>
</review>
