<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This feeling of audiovisual gazpacho has just a crematística and nothing artistic motivation. Verbinski, under the tutelage of business of a financier of the divertimento as Bruckheimer, has made the duties that have sent you.</summary>
	<body>When one is witness to the spectacle (no doubt) is the new release of the Walt Disney Studios Motion Picture Marketing and Distribution (most his partner, Jerry Bruckheimer Films), do not know very well if he has attended a film pirates (unorthodox, of course), a circus got ginkana, one of Laurel and Hardy, a surreal comedy to what how being John Malkovich, or even a naif love story. And it is that this incursion at the end of the world is also the step to the self-sufficiency of a producer who knows a priori winning. Why does the script come something secondary, which has just taken? from the hand of the tanned writers Ted Elliott and Terry Rossio (Godzilla, Shrek, the mask of zorro) - a wise choice of genres and disparate characters, extracted from the imaginary child to potential clients (children and not so children). This feeling of audiovisual gazpacho has just a crematística and nothing artistic motivation. Verbinski, under the tutelage of business of a financier of the divertimento as Bruckheimer, has made the duties that have sent you. And it has done well, and shamelessness. To Caribbean pirates 3 he notices too its Lair by the box office, and its security to sell a product that before leaving already exceeded expectations to rich to their producers.Why 3 Caribbean pirates it crimp its plot, allowing clonadoras licenses with schizophrenic speeches, or pirate rollingstonianos pirate code and the musical memory of parents who accompany their children to the rooms (or is the other way around?) And the conundrum of his script is supported because it comes sprinkled (as almost all the American cinema of rapid consumption) of an audiovisual earthquake that desencaja the eyes of the respectable and keeps quietly in the armchair, swallowing their popcorn and sipping the usual ration of syrup made in USA. Out of the room only it will be what we saw, i.e., mere smoke of sounds and colors and a few good euros less in their pockets. And to continue swallowing Fireworks artificial life are two days and finance and death do not forgive.With Pirates of the Caribbean 3, Spider-Man 3 and all its cousins is presented to us a little encouraging film our cinemas menu for who would have liked to see other titles equal or more juicy hanging in poster and more packaging (see Zodiac, among dozens more), and only finds prefabricated dishes that although they seduce at first glance, become later kitkats that kill the bug that one has good film (or if perhaps cinema) (to dry), and not digital sets retreaded by experts in marketing.Anyway, see you in the film (or the amusement park).</body>
</review>
