<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="La noche de los girasoles" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More than correct film. It entertains, worries, and almost unwittingly saddened, we plunge into the void where the characters are installed even after resolving the final drama.</summary>
	<body>On the contrary of what was happening in the recent forest of shadows, the night of the sunflowers is a drama resolved in an efficient and disturbing (despite its slow pace and little Hollywood) rural thriller where each and every one of the characters are immersed in a suffocating solitude which only the random event in an attempt to rape provided them excuses to release tension that threatens them. A couple stagnant in their relationship; a young man tied to an environment (the people) that he is Guy; a solo villager who refuses to leave his home after death his wife; a terrifying seller, embittered by the life he has had; a civil guard caradura, disgusted by his life of newly married? All are their misery through the tragedy that will be triggered.Without possessing the sense of staging or the expressive force of the landscape which does possess Fargo, the night of the sunflowers follows the path of this priceless portrait that draw the Coens deep America. Where Fargo is a police pregnant with sense of smell to the Sherlock Homes in this Spanish village appears a civil guard about to retire despite no less smell prefers to protect his daughter who enforce the law. And where in Fargo writes a classic script, without temporary fractures, in the film the rookie Sánchez-Cabezudo are a rashomónimo mounting without hurry (to the emotional rhythm of its protagonists) going drawing by subjective layers network events in which all the characters converge.The night of the sunflowers is one film more than correct. It entertains, worries, and almost unwittingly saddened, we plunge into the void where the characters are installed even after resolving the final drama. The scene in which the cavers return to the affected city and silent; This poor father presenting his resignation after silence (and pay) with the dark plan of his son-in-law named; This rapist returning to his home (as usual), delivered to the sisífica existence of sofa and TV. Or dramatic resignation of this son-in-law cloistered in his family prison. All of them make this film a thriller (one of the fear, that we say in Castilian) or police (civil guards in this case), almost desperate, sad drama about loneliness and its miseries.With the game on chance that vertebra the proposal for the Coens, never aimed to melancholy or existential drama, Sánchez-Cabezudo work does not play, and if we no or entertains. But it risks, coming out of the mere dialectical policía-asesino with a happy ending (so the Hollywood style) and opting for letting the Viewer without crutches that only interpret what is mere survival against loneliness.Still concerned see Manuel Morón (the father of the ball) of bad, very bad. Carmelo Gomez will of pearls that bland role as pusillanimous bursting of anger. The unknown Judith Diakhate is beautiful and accurate (in that order). Celso Bugallo keeps shrinking me with another natural but intense interpretation (as already did in Mar adentro). Also great Vicente Romero (recommended in the role of the Maquea in the TV movie father courage) and Walter Vidarte, a loco that the spectator soon consistent.</body>
</review>
