<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Volver" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Almodóvar has achieved a resounding and accurate full: the heat of criticism, the heat of the public, a taquillazo and a peliculón</summary>
	<body>"Back" returns us to an Almodóvar wrapped in the clothes of costumbrismo well understood and better digested, a tradition, rather than colliding with modernity, linking it to complement, join, and to multiply.For me, most detestable universe Almodóvar were those extreme characters that, frankly, seemed a real pain in the ass. I never could with both travelo-male locked in the body of a woman who, however, falls in love with a girl who had finally, implanted an artificial penis and silicone tits.Therefore when Almodóvar began filming more classic stories, talking about universal themes such as loneliness, the loss of the loved or love, his films won many integers. In this line were "All about my mother" and "Talk to her" and with "Volver", Pedro has borne him a masterpiece that you can not put a only but.Already in the boot, the credit titles, removed by the unforgiving wind of La Mancha, are a genuine Declaration of principles. And, from there, Almodovar is the presentation of the scenarios and characters, both major and minor, in fifteen minutes, with a concise, a neatness and a capacity of synthesis that will make the script of "Volver" in compulsory subject of study in any writing workshop film self-respecting.Then, of course, history. A story that intersects characters, legends, myths, superstitions and secrets of family, that mixes drama with comedy, the city with the people, the large family with the tiny apartment house, the gossip to the old-fashioned and which uses television as amplifier to reach all corners, etc.Because "Volver" is full of details, winks and gestures together and link the two Spains: rural Spain and urban, Spain half of 20th century and which wakes up with the Millennium, the Spain of traditional cuisine, anise and the point of a cross with the Spain of the catering, the mojitos and lycra. Two Spains in which, however, they are not so different things, then and now, as it handles well demonstrate an Almodóvar in State of grace.And it does so using a rich, dramatic and glorious ensemble cast monopolized by women. Barely leaving two men throughout the film and make it tangential and almost anecdotal way. The masculine gender, by Almodóvar become mere Mc Guffin narrative, which demonstrates that the parity by Decree, when there are genius and talent, does not lack.With "Volver", Almodóvar has managed a resounding and accurate full: the heat of criticism, the heat of the public, a taquillazo and a peliculón. Now only missing the awards. That it does not take to arrive.</body>
</review>
