<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sponsored by Fernando Trueba, the young director navarro has surprised everyone with a daring Ribbon. A notable film, pleasant, fresh, interesting.</summary>
	<body>Excellent debut of Félix Viscarret in feature film. Sponsored by Fernando Trueba, young director navarro has surprised everyone with a daring film, under the stars, based on the novel "The trumpeter of the Utopia" Fernando Aramburu. As said Trueba in the preview: best thing about Viscarret is that it has its own style, something that many fail to achieve never. I agree, and they must think alike in Malaga: best film, director, actor protagonist and novel writing.The story is relatively simple: Benito, a trumpeter second row, failed, borrachuzo and disoriented, returns to Estella, his hometown, to attend the funeral of his father. There to recover the time lost with his brother Lalo, good-natured and innocent, and decides that it is worthwhile to extend the visit to rid him of the woman that is going to marry: Nines (in another time binge and too early for everything). However, to know his daughter Ainara (rebellious and introverted) was born an unexpected friendship and open new paths.It is difficult to decide between drama with comedic overtones or comedy with dramatic overtones. In any case, laughter, even laughter, is guaranteed but it also has a very emotional point, a very human background, with characters lost, abused, unhappy, failed. Life no smiles them too and if ever they had dreams, they have forgotten. However, in others, you will find the sufficient motives to move forward. And one average film, can be concentrated, thinking in those things, cruel that life can sometimes be, injustices, etc. and to soon hear any bullshit at mouth of Benito (Alberto San Juan) and not be able to avoid doubled with laughter. No doubt the acidity of this character, calling her young friend puerca, and has no qualms about giving a little March to the burial of his father, is one of the strong points of the film. Are, in fact, all the characters, interpreted as well as excellently.Highlights also the photograph of Álvaro Gutiérrez and the music of Mikel rooms (both elements successful, care, always with the tone of the story but without taking the leading role). In short, a remarkable film, pleasant, fresh, interesting, to which, to put some sticks, perhaps left some footage.</body>
</review>
