<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Memorias de Queens" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Memories of Queens is a very real film but fails to address a story that really connect with the spectator.</summary>
	<body>Given the current film scene, wouldn't anything outlandish the creation of the figure of the Ombudsman of the Viewer. Someone who emule to Don Quixote and faced with giant windmills solo by safeguarding the honour and dignity of the public. At the same time, as show of support could be the film Indignados.Porque Association of consumers increasingly are more cases in which a movie deceive scam to the Viewer, or makes it a malicious campaign. I could say that memories of Queens enters the second field, that sell starring Robert Downey Jr., when it has few appearances on screen. The film is the debut as a filmmaker Dito Montiel, who adapted his novel Guide to recognizing your saints, inspired in turn by their own experiences of teenager. History is not a paragon of originality, is typical on young people in a slum in a big city that exposed people of various races and nationalities. The main virtue of the film is that it transmits the status of Queens in the Decade of the eighties with great wisdom and loyalty. But the feeling of verisimilitude and reality are not alone sufficient to justify tape whole, as to do so you need something more, a story that reaches the public, that catch, and that is well told. Queens memories does not have one or the other. His argument is simple and predictable, transmitting only the viewer boredom and tedium. Typical failures that could be expected given the inexperience of Montiel after the cameras must be added a fraying narrative, with a few temporary anything successful jumps. Interpretations, notably of Chazz Palminteri as well as sporadic appearances of Robert Downey Jr.Memorias of Queens is a very real film but fails to address a story that really connect with the spectator. On the contrary, it offers a plot without interest and that it will lead to many yawns in the stalls.</body>
</review>
