<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For me this is probably the best movie of the 3. The first found me appalling. The second I liked and that I loved.</summary>
	<body>For me this is probably the best movie of the 3. The first found me appalling. The second I liked and that I loved. What did Johnny Deep with Captain Jack seems impressive. The character that I am sure that the same producers expected has given a charisma. And it is terribly sexy a man so sexy that is not intended to be so. That's what we like about the Jack.Aun Captain recognizing that it is a product of mass I must admit the acumen of this 3rd part, although we intuíamos what was going to happen, when it happens we were equally excited (the magic of the film).Of course not all are joys to the pirates because I have several buts, that "it is too long," for my spare you 10 minutes of the match in the whirlpool and about 6 in the final battle. And namely what amounts the deleted scenes footage (as we will see when the DVD draw). Another but is that Keira has me tired with your pout, I mean let's see, okay get morros occasionally but it is that this girl is incapable of playing any role without taking morros, seems it not enough to miss the collagen that began to put before filming Pirates of the I Caribbean but must above us bore with an excess of labial meat which chorizo cantinpalo. There are also other stuff. Let's go shit director of clothing that allows the dancers that leads Keira are perfect throughout the film, doesn't matter if it gets wet or goes pro on top of the mud, are always good.We leave behind the minimaladas suppose that for any critical eye does not go unnoticed and let's really interesting. Orlando Bloom. I don't know if I like more pirate or Elf, as not I decide I thought could do a mix, Elf Monday, pirate Tuesday, Wednesday Elf, pirate Thursday, Friday. I know that he hates being a sexsymbol but it is. Well the artistic progression of Orly is clear to everyone that has memory and eyes on the face. Indeed his character in the saga suffers a progressive transformation that is really carried, to the point of finishing well being the absolute protagonist.</body>
</review>
