<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Himalaya" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pity is that Valli has no narrative pulse of Hawks and the caravan later both to boot because the movie is correct</summary>
	<body>"Himalayas" is not only a western in which doesn't stick nor an only shot but that, in addition, its action takes place about five or six thousand meters of altitude. Nothing less. Strange? Perhaps. But if Sam Peckimpah filmed his exemplary "duel in the High Sierra", to see by Eric Valli, despite its ironic name, would not be able to shoot this mountainous initiatory story, survival, overcoming and redemption.It goes without saying that the film was originally titled "The learning of a Chief" and that perhaps by the strong climbing Hispanic tradition, our distributor decided give it a name so generic as "Himalaya". We have a movie that, on the basis of an archetype as classic as the dead hero and the struggle for the leadership, shows us, with the precision and detail of a National Geographic documentary, the hard life of the inhabitants of a unknown town in the middle of the Karakorum.Se show us the funeral rites of the community, the puzzles and riddles used by priests to decide when is the auspicious day for the departure of a caravanpreparations, it teaches us the interior of the houses, clothing, gadgets of everyday use, etc.And then, the characters. Father afflicted by the death of the son, the new hero, the widow, the little orphan or the prodigal son star in a range of situations connected with the Greek classicism, medieval chivalry novel and, of course, with the western; not in vain, that "Himalayas" is driving a caravan through extreme situations, playing many of the experiences that Howard Hawks tell us in his "Red River".Pity is Valli have the narrative pulse of Hawks and the caravan later in both boot because the film is correct, the situations that pass the characters still predictable, they are very well resolved and, in general, "Himalayas" can be seen with pleasure.</body>
</review>
