<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Under the stars is a more than worthy first film, whose greatest exponent, apart from the prodigious work of Alberto San Juan, is its great realism.</summary>
	<body>A film generates high expectations before its release and is not a big Super production is good news for the set of the film. However, are not few occasions that these expectations may turn against, that it may not be equal to what the public (and the terrible and anti-social perfidious Albion so-called critical) had imagined. This may be the case under the stars, after sweeping to victory at the Malaga Film Festival has become one of the most anticipated titles of the Spanish film.Expectations created around under the stars are very large, both by his overwhelming I triumph in Malaga by the precedent set last year Daniel Sánchez-Arévalo. The film, which adapted the novel by Fernando Aramburu the trumpeter of the utopia, narrates the return home of a crápula, Benito Lacunza (Alberto San Juan), who on his return will find with many surprises, and not all pleasant. Sponsored by Fernando Trueba, Félix Viscarret performed an opera prima which deals with a complex, sensitive and thorny history. Shot as a comedy-drama, one of the greatest virtues of the tape is the strength of his script, which has a very well built and absolutely credible characters that anyone can identify. Since that starts the plot, the Viewer is immersed fully in it, experiencing the same experiences of the characters, laughing and suffer with them. In the movie there is a clear ambivalence between the drama and the comedy, battle the when no winner, which becomes a burden as they pass the minutes. There are some moments in the intensity of the history lapses, and in honor of the truth, the aesthetics of contemporary western that accompanies the first half of the film hurts more than it benefits; by this setting (music comes to become strident soon) there are levels reminiscent of the absurd and the pure surrealism. Apart from these details, the work of Viscarret is absolutely impeccable. The most remarkable low stars is the interpretation of Alberto San Juan, which endorses completely to this crápula tender and charming of Benito Lacunza.Bajo stars is a more than worthy first film, whose greatest exponent, apart from the prodigious work of Alberto San Juan, is its great realism.</body>
</review>
