<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very good movie, with well designed details, a right direction, a wonderfully elaborate script and above all, two amazing actresses that make the best performances of his career.</summary>
	<body>Helen Mirren was superb in the role of the Queen in The Queen and unfortunately I have not seen Dreamgirls to be able to assess the performance of Jennifer Hudson in his supporting role aclamadísima. Both actresses were the Oscar as best actress and best supporting actress respectively at the last Oscars ceremony, and I must admit that the first deserved it. Yet and so, if this award would have taken him Judi Dench for her role in diary of a scandal I would have pleased even more, because what you get with this performance is nothing more than achieve mastery. And the same applies to Cate Blanchett, in one of the most superb interpretations of this attractive and amazing actress.Patrick Marber is the writer of the film, which was also nominated for an Oscar for his more than correct work. As I say, the script from diary of a scandal is good, but what stands out here are interpretations of Dench and Blanchett, a few creations of magisterial stature with human sensibilities, and above all, a few personalities incredibly perverse and Bohemian, respectively. Their looks, their dialogues, its moementos peaks (especially of Dench, in a truly terrifying final performance). Not is that the role of Cate Blanchett is worse drawn or tried, but there is something in the Dench that attracts me much, and I do not know if it is that loneliness that is maintained and that perversity with which wants to catch things. The Australian is a more normal role, with its temptations and prohibited relations, and also, with their doubts and fears. Ultimately, perhaps the veteran winner of an Oscar for Shakespeare in love if you're here real Oscar, but Blanchett (who won for playing Hepburn in the Aviator) gets, practically to its height, with some extremely intense dramatic explorations (see the discussion in extremis with her husband, a phenomenal Bill Nighy). It makes me weird to speak at the beginning of a critique on the interpretations, but we should recognize that this film which truly highlights are two. Although obviously in a film not only can well be interpretations and else be bad. Here the address of Richard Eyre is more than correct, the screenplay of Marber is very well structured and the music of Philip Glass is simply moving. And not to forget the magnificent photography, carried out with elegance and colours very ochre and sometimes very gray tones. The truth is that everything in diary of a scandal works, not perfection, but yes in an appropriate manner, without exceeding at any time and always enjoyable proving, and, as in every movie of expendable, with superb moments and others not so much (the confrontation of Blanchett against journalists, somewhat forced).A very good film, with well designed details, a right direction, script, no Oscar, but itself superbly produced, a credible and oppressive atmosphere in several moments and above all, incredible two actresses that make the best performances of his career. Unforgettable in the interpretative sense.</body>
</review>
