<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Me siento rejuvenecer" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Masterpiece of comedy and inspection, a gem of a film. His extravagance, its absurd logic and its high sense of dialogs remain in the memory of the movie buff.</summary>
	<body>Howard Hawks said that the real drama is terribly near a comedy which has usually been one genre minor in the history of cinema and even literature. The payroll of filmmakers who have dedicated their talents to the "screwball comedy" going own hawks to Lubitsch, passing by Leo McCarey, Gregory LaCava, Billy Wilder, Frank Capra, George Cukor and Preston Sturges and actors that have immortalized this crazy film, powerful visual gags and dizzying parliaments were Jack Lemmon, Cary Grant, Katherine Hepburn, Walter Matthau, Charles CoburnMarilyn Monroe or Gary Cooper. I am rejuvenate is a masterpiece of comedy and inspection, a gem of a film. His extravagance, its absurd logic and its high sense of dialogs remain in the memory of the movie buff. This light operetta of monkeys running acetate half and alchemists of eternal youth is the quintessence of the genre along with the bringing up baby, also of Hawks and with similar cast. In a Cary Grant is an introverted University professor who lives to rebuild a dinosaur skeleton and raise money for the Museum which governs. In I feel rejuvenate, Grant is a removed and chief scientist who creates to have found the formula for eternal youth, although reality confesses that he has been Rodolfo, the monkey of the Indies, primate impersonator, to activity with test tubes and flasks, giving with the Holy Grail of eternal life. Hecht, Lederer and Diamond, which would then be narrative escort by Billy Wilder in his best works, produced a fabulous script that would have been delighted to Darwin and, under rope, showing with irony, the future of science and the inevitable interference in the business world to take advantage of their progress and make cash at their expense. The title in English (Monkey Business, business of monkeys) introduces openly the parade guignolesco, bufo and sexy of the plot. A prudish Marilyn Monroe, sandwiched in a narrow skirt until coronary stranglehold leaves that her tits, pointing to infinity with those times fasteners, so open and pujados, steal you (plane to plane) any interest in what he says. Then there is the scene in which plant his leg against the timorous Bernaby Fulton teacher that he appreciated the quality of the socks that he himself has invented. "Miss Laurel I was teaching their acetates", Lisp Grant before that the BREW manufactured by the chimpanzee makes rejuvenate, get to ride in a convertible Monroe or skate as a child. These age regressions lead to all actors displayed their most circus records. Up the own Charles Coburn, impeccable, always goose when Ginger Rogers, become girl - I add that never ceased to be it - gets a fish below the belt. Crazy Rhythm, the continuous zarandeo of implausible situations, but here logics become engine of fast-paced action, which does not let you breathe. In these times, in the film made now that it touched us to enjoy, there are some Hawks?</body>
</review>
