<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Black snake moan" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unaffordable tape blues and sweat, little teaching redencíones and topics of the deep Southern American, whereas pelmaza and unlikely since their first minutes.</summary>
	<body>Probably this tape to join without difficulty that famous adage of anonymous author who asked to make difficult virtue because Black snake Mena is a curious movie, at least, and is also different. Curiosity and the difference do not make good movies but are grateful when overwhelm us with taquillazos of foreseeable resolution and flat ingenuity. It is also a picture of customs, a picturesque portrait of the American South with coarse brushstrokes of primitive blues touched dry stick, born of the soul and sung with enough pain as to make it credible. There it is possible to be born all possible interest by Black snake Mena, although there will be who pay seat to see the obviously of Christina Ricci in a role of risk, but grateful and in which performs superbly: a fierce nymphomaniac has no meat that lend it and lampa by being crucified by any berraco bar bar to throw. Or to the Samuel l. Jackson boring until today - when was her last decent film? -that recreates a character depressed, closed, housed in the placid nebula of the blues and recalling the happy times when he played them on stage and was happily married. These two characters, marked by fate, movingly dragged by the miseries of life and almost no resources to overcome, are the only thing salvageable from the film, which is already fairly. To her around, a script embarrassing, impossible to believe, laboriously weary during a footage always too long, excessive.Let's bear in mind one thing: If a blues lasts three minutes, a film that recreates, in essence, a blues should be a short or a mini-corto or a clip of those files that occupy quasi-infinities of youtube. No, specifically, a movie, a feature film, as I said before. There is a moment in which we are saturated in history, soaked, tired of the girl with uterine fury is wallow with anyone because of his addiction to sex. The bluesman makes therapist, psychologist, father and guru to remove it from his slavery venerea and put again to pay to the society and be rewarded by this. Already. I would add - creates that damaged anything telling this small detail of props - as perpetrated by the old bluesman recovery methods is not tying the girl to a radiator and hoped that the "monkey" go and appeases the Vertigo of the meat. This absurd mix of guitar strummings and sweat will irritate more than one, I know. It's gonna bother who go to the cinema to watch movies. It is a mere display of brilliant performances, well mounted atmospheres and a great planning on mounting. Its says there is no script or which seems that it aspires to be it fails both lost in a shipwreck of great intentions, but vacant results. Conspirators in taking forward an irregular, strange, never credible company is, in any case, respect for a director, Craig Brewer, blues and formidable choice of actors in State of grace. They had done a music video for any new song of Robert Cray or my beloved B.B. King and this would have been the audiovisual coup of the year. At least on MTV. The music is the cure. The blues is the cure, who sang John Lee Hooker accompanied by Santana in a piece that I have started background to write this review with more motivation.</body>
</review>
