<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Cuando un extraño llama" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Being a trite story, with expressionless actors and poorly planned situations, the tape can be up entertaining</summary>
	<body>When you start the movie one has slight suspicion about where the shots can go. Through this introduction, banal by the insubstantial, is that if patent the tone of what is upon us, a new example of feature film helpings in the teen horror genre. Few dare to introduce changes where they perceive that a formula works: you change the scenario, you now to a character on the other, but you leave the disturbing atmosphere and scares, screams and races because of a psychopath with criminal instincts. Here there is a gas station in the middle of an inhospitable moorland or one College, but a luxurious mansion lost in the mountains; against the Group of young people with character type (snobs, stiffs, athletes, intellectuals) will impose a young woman with courage and determination? needed to sustain the film - that must save the lives of children who cares. In short, are the same patterns used nauseam but, as well as producers, then dan result at the box office. Everything has its explanation and which justifies the interest of Hollywood is in young people eager to suspense stories accompanied by a good Pack of popcorn and the groom or the bride well close.A Japanese horror title also was enough of the phone, in this case mobile, to announce the death of their protagonists. Missed call, which is the name the reference, plays with the same elements but reserved the letter of surprise, something that when you call a stranger is diluted as soon as the girl picks up the wireless two or three times. by the way, is mentioned already repetitive tone? On the other side of the line there is a serial killer who will be at the Gallery of murderers series because his modus operand is nothing special. And although they create just them gutting the film, not start cursing for free that they checked Simon West, its director-malabarista, makes it clear from the first sequence. Although us despite being a trite story, with expressionless actors and poorly planned situations, the tape may be up entertaining but only for those who enjoy the exponents of the B series and titles as Scream but warned: are not dealing with an incipient Wes Craven but talking about a title that offers more of the same and with more crime if it should be since it is based on the same premises recorded a tape of the 1970s. The producers of the current must be some of the few who saw it in his day. Taking advantage of forgetful which is our memory a script that, away from the blatant plagiarism, settlement otherwise worked.</body>
</review>
