<review author="Bruji" title="Carta a tres esposas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What is really surprising in the narration of the different stories, drawn perpendicular, is the vision which casts on the enigmatic central character and the refusal by Mankiewicz to explicitly deal with infidelity.</summary>
	<body>"Dear Debby, Lora Mae and Rita..."Following the advice of Louis Mayer, Joseph l. Mankiewicz "gateó much before starting to walk". Which means that, before heading, he did important work of production for the Metro, and became entrenched as one of the best writers of the 1930s, cultivating all genres and stressing as dialoguista. The prestigious "crawling" earned him the recognition of the Hollywood of the era, earning a nomination to the Oscar as a producer of George Cukor Philadelphia stories and another for the Skippy script in 1931. his first film after the cameras, the castle of Dragonwyck, arrives in 1.946 ill the ironic, delicate, elegant and subtle Erns Lubitsch; starting with her a meteoric and successful career which turns him into the essential filmmaker that never conceived a good movie without the livelihood of a solid story. Their own words: "the difference between real life and the movies is that a script has to make sense." "Life not".Sense, irony, sarcasm, humour and charm come together in this delicious comedy of 1949, which obtained its first two Oscars (screenplay and direction). Then come titles mythical in the history of cinema, as the nude Eve (won other two statuettes), the Countess barefoot or the footprint, its last footage.In a letter to three wives, adaptation of a short story by John Klempner, the authors contemporaries, - committed to incorporate voices in off in their films, find a masterful lesson on how to apply them. As it can be seen from this excellent reference, this, basically, is limited to the introduction of scenes, by channeling the argument and defining the backstory of the characters. At any time the omnipresent narration competes with images or subtract them protagonism. Know how to intervene and, above all, when not doing so. Its mission is complete, never interrupt or lead. Without a doubt, the balance did not reach the acclaimed Todd Field to spoil the games Secretos.Otro of the greatest attractions of this film adaptation lies in the successful use of the flashback, used by the demands emanating from the own script. According to the novel, Addie Rose do not attend the annual picnic of charity, failing her three best friends. Failing that, it makes them get a farewell letter, which, Furthermore, informs you that it has escaped with the husband of one of them!. The three protagonists recall their marital lives in order to find out the terrible truth: with what?. Another extraordinary film lesson that justifies the choice of a particular technique for needs resulting from the production, not by the mere whim to do so; attitude very taste of current Directors.On the other hand, the roster of actors than the most optimistic expectations. Linda Darnell expressions are memorable; the apparent frivolity of Jeanne Crain, plausible; and the interpretation of Ann Sothern, embodying the prototypical American worker at the end of the 1940s, unbeatable. Meanwhile, the male replica is not expected, being represented by the cautious and accurate work of Jeffrey Lynn, magnificent debut of Paul Douglas and the invaluable stage presence of the unspeakably good Kirk.El master touch is rounded up with some frames which oblige love cinema (the glances that direct the three wives to the phone booth as the ship moves away), with implausible situations designed to provoke laughter from the most demanding Viewer (starring the radio sponsors unusual dinner), scenes equipped with a touching dramatic load (the desperate monologue that shows the transformation of Debby), an impressive photography in black and white that diffuses smoke cigarettes, a retailer and mimosa art direction and the exquisite dialoguesimpossible and unthinkable in any recent film.But what really surprised in the narration of the different stories, drawn perpendicular, perhaps, is the vision which casts on the enigmatic central character and the refusal by Mankiewicz to explicitly deal with infidelity. About as significant as easy to explain aspects. We must only think that Addie is nothing more than the touch of care requiring the asleep loves the illusion that prevents the sentimental apathy. Something that, ignoring the warning will be heard at the beginning, which clearly has much to do with me... or with you.</body>
</review>
