<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Thumbsucker" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It allows you to leave the cinema with a smile, rather light by the drama that hides because, friends, grow and become adult is not an easy task</summary>
	<body>Between superheroes, serial killers and beings "romanticotes" who came across the Atlantic usually strain, very occasionally, a title branded "indie". This tends to be the most commonly used Word with a view to the promotion of Thumbsucker, as if this will be a sign of prestige. The use of the independent label sometimes gives result, otherwise coletillas as "the Sundance hit" or "the surprise of the Berlinale" are added. We must not be the things in their hands: the movie is not bad but not out of that select stronghold of titles that later we refer. It's a simple story about the very complex process of auto-búsqueda and reaffirmation in all stages of life, but with the addition of the batch of problems presented him a young man at the age of 17. A family environment that collapses and a child mania that will delight the psychologists, the sucking the finger, differ from the treatment of the history of similar titles in its conception and projection, as the recent e interesting something in common, with Natalie Portman, Peter Sarsgaard and Zach Braff, also in the direction and screenplay writing.Mike Mills also wrote the script from the novel by Walter Kim, but were not encouraged to star as did Braff. Focused on the more technical side although he did excitement in the realization, in all case ended contagious rhythm apprehended riding video-clips and commercials. Do the newcomer in the direction of long supported his low-budget film in very recognized names in the industry as Tilda Swinton (broken flowers, the Chronicles of Narnia), Vince Vaughn (wedding at wedding, Be cool), Benjamin Bratt (Traffic, the woodsman) and Vincent (d)?Onofrio (strange days, the fabulous life of the Altar Boys). We do not forget to Keanu Reaves, who has a brief intervention.As throughout history with alternative label, with careful soundtrack, actors and simple wrapper, Thumbsucker aims high, including the label of "did not expect such an impact". Remember a Beautiful girls although its characters are closest with everything for a dream, the roles of Matt Dillon, Nicole Kidman and Joaquin Phoenix, characters in their daily life are brought to the limit. Lou Taylor Pucci, silver bear for best actor in Berlin, has the gift of naturalness, with scary face and accepting the role of second which will soon give the surprise, a be poorly versed in the arts of communication that will change while approaching the end of this comedy different which allows you to leave the cinema with a smilerather light by the drama that hides because, friends, grow and become adult is not an easy task.</body>
</review>
