<review author="Luna" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story that could fall on the topic but that manages to rise to the height of an interesting proposal that will leave a good taste to all those who dare to see it.</summary>
	<body>For a few years, numerous directors novar them are getting projecting his materials operas on the large screens with uneven qualities. It is not the case of this film, that despite being the first feature film of this director shows great maturity with its mise en scène and makes a solid and interesting approach in relation to script and Assembly.Preceded by the obtained awards in Malaga Festival in 2007 (best film, best director, best actor and best screenplay novel) I'm sure that is going to have a long distance both in commercial theaters Awards (remember the similar case with Azuloscurocasinegro that so many satisfactions has given to its director Daniel Sánchez Arévalo).Viscarret has adapted the work of Fernando Aramburu "The trumpeter of the Utopia" to tell, without falling into sentimentality cheap, the story of a musician who returns to his hometown to bury his father. The reunion with his brother, the girlfriend and the daughter of his girlfriend will completely change you life, and it is that as its slogan reads, "all deserve a second chance".Especially memorable is the relationship that Viscarret gets translated into 24 frames per second between the trumpeter (Alberto San Juan) and girls (Violeta Rodriguez), a relationship film and real as life itself.Indeed we must highlight the work of Alberto San Juan, as one of the best of his career, and the election of Violeta Rodríguez has also been very successful. Perhaps the work of Julián Villagrán less prominence by being a character more taken to the extreme, even occasionally, as a caricature of the different and eccentric artist. Alvaro Gutierrez, director of photography, get a magnificent lighting, sometimes almost magic, and aftertaste to the 1970s. The use of a few great backlights superbly supports the narrative thread and the tone of the film.Mikel rooms music, sometimes reminiscent of Western films, offers the perfect counterpoint and musical underscore for a story that could fall on the topic but manages to rise to the height of an interesting proposal that will leave a good taste to all those who dare to see it.</body>
</review>
