<review author="José A. Peig" title="El cazador" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is one of the best portraits of which the war of Viet Nam meant for class American media. A look intimate and tragic at the same time.</summary>
	<body>Exhibition and conceptual simplicity couples attend a husking speech, with its rhythmic narrative, as regards one of the most tragic paradoxes of human existence: the need for harmony and balance, friendship and love, faced with the reality of war and violence. Somehow, there is also a need for violence, and the most unique of the movie he directed Michael Cimino, is to synthesize the paradox in a single character, "The Hunter" interpreted by the perennial Robert De Niro, who already in their garbeos mountain, in the first third of the film, shows such a search in their hunting of fawns: the shot and the agonising death of the animal, and suffering reflected in the eyes, they seem to reproach the free violation of life, beating both the consciousness of the Viewer as to the of the own De Niro, who on a second occasion misses the shot and let escape her prey in accordance with a new scheme of values emerged from the experience in Viet Nam ("deacuerdoooooo").Solo but friend and companion of his friends, the main character is located on the central axis of the drama be strong in courage and determination, will save his friends in the most fierce trances and comfort women of the lost. "The Hunter" may have two readings that complement each other: on the one hand, is the story of a man who reaffirms his personality through the experience of war. On the other hand, is the story of a group of men and women whose lives degenerate from the stability of proletarian and puritanical American society based on patriotic traditions: families, work, alcohol and casinos. The aggressive industrial terrain of the city - in their first sequences, a noisy truck enters the people throwing smoke and loitering by the factories, the landscape shows rough that opens the film - serves as the ideal context for a superb display of human relations that are broken after the "crusade" in Vietnam.La illusion and represented in the first stretch Festival contrasts with the subsequent abatementdeception and disappointment. And thus it can be said that the contrast is one of its main features, even by the abrupt way of shifting the Viewer from a docile universe and costumbrist (a group of friends in the casino, listening to the music of a piano, with a gesture of deep melancholy) to the hell of war (corpses and the screams of a Vietnamese burning alive is what we see in the next scene)mounting is configured so that the history is better than ever when it is referred from the whole, not so much by the development of its parts and moments, some of them hurt by unnecessary use of the slow pace, with which the narrative falls, often in purely descriptive. Said might add that this film would have been much more round with a cut in the footage.The final scene is really illustrative of the essential intention encourages the film: a patriotic song in memory of the lost friend, the only consolation that remains. This is one of the best portraits of which the war of Viet Nam meant for class American media. A look intimate and tragic at the same time.</body>
</review>
