<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Hostel 2" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not only satisfies the expectations of all those who we enjoy with the first part, but it meets merits to please even those who crucified.</summary>
	<body>Few films of recent years have been so beloved and defenestradas as a Hostel (2006), the second tape of the protégé of Tarantino, Eli Roth. The more benevolent her described as grossly exploitative, misogynist and xenophobic, which surprisingly much in these times in which so easily entroniza dandruff of the 1970s (perhaps is that we only want this type of tapes as something already last but not we have the courage to accept its existence today). However, were not few those who think that Hostel was one of the best bets of horror of the past year, one in which Essentials was not the amount of guts and hemoglobin released on screen, but what he meant with that particular violence, exposure of a sub-mundo of neglect and depredations was hiding behind the appearance of refined most of Western "civilization"as well as a black man I descojono made with very bad grapes. This Slovak hostel where the rich paid to torture young boys kidnapped at least thematically, is the equivalent of our time to what was then the rural 70s slasher, puteado today until the tired.But even many of them love the film were in agreement that if something is not needed was a second part. Given the particular conditions of the history, it seemed impossible that Eli Roth could draw the manga a worthy sequel. With this in mind I entered the theater, and frankly I could not be more wrong. Hostel 2 (2007) not only satisfies the expectations of all those who we enjoy with the first part, but it meets merits to please even those who crucified.No surprises as to the argument, because the scheme is largely repeated: rather than a trio of boys, this time the victims of the Slovak hostel are three American girls art students who are drawn to a supposed Spa will be where the pieces of fun for a group of millionaires eager to torture. The difference is that, on this occasion, history will be also shown us from the point of watched sadistic participants of the "Elite Hunting", especially two American millionaires who travel to Europe from the East willing to move to the "next level". It is this plot twist that gives the film a look that its predecessor lacked, and that apart from hondar in this decadent world of sadism of wardrobe, leads to the tape to completely new land. The homage to the European horror film could not be clearer, not only as regards certain sequences that replicate the work of the genus explotativo from the old world, but by the presence of former stars of the caspoteca European as Luc Merenda and Edwige Fenech diva, as well as the surprise appearance and nothing concealed by Ruggero Deodato (director of Holocaust Canibal (1980))(, another of those movies beloved/hated) in which is probably the best cameo in this year.All the other elements of the first part are there, from the increasingly bizarre methods of torture (attention to the tribute to the Countess Elizabeth Bathory) until this gang of crappy kids that you wouldn't want to be found. But what remains is that desparpajo before violence had been shown to Eli Roth in his previous films. In contrast to what we are accustomed to seeing, charcuterie in this story is beloved by the constant game that makes it. Also (and this is definitely something not so common) is good to see that the violence in a movie is not an ornament gotten shoehorn and intended for the enjoyment of the less privileged sector (intellectually at least) of the room but is an integral part of the history and the style of what you want to tell. Perhaps that is what differentiates Hostel and its sequel of hundreds of tapes of torture psychopaths who have endured in recent years. My only conclusion is that those who have enjoyed the first part have a thousand reasons to not miss this tape, but on the other hand, those who have hated should also hold and check with Roth we have a guy that you know what you do and that, sooner than you think, it might surprise us with a masterpiece.</body>
</review>
