<review author="JLO" title="Segunda piel" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Small story told with all possible nuances, with a solid acting task and direction.</summary>
	<body>Small story told with all possible nuances, with a solid acting task and direction. Elena (the always excellent Ariadna Gil) is happily married to Alfredo (Jordi Mollá) a prestigious aeronautical engineer. Now realize that things are changing to meet the account of a hotel in the pocket of his pants. She can never imagine that the fight should be with Diego (Javier Bardem), which completes this love triangle. A triangle of several falsehoods and lies.Director Gerardo Vera (A woman in the rain, La Celestina) never issued judgement on them, leaves flow characters through dialogues and leads with simplicity and good taste, to reveal the feelings of each of them. Already in the first scene, we anticipated a well determined bed between the two men, as it is the story and its treatment. Everything starts to complicate the undefined and disorientation of Alberto, beginning a series of deceptions that inspire distrust and pain in their two couples. Great performances of the three, considered almost the best exponents of his generation in Spain. Punto y aparte for Bardem: depressive and crippled in meat Trémula. Gay poet in prior to that dark. Dirty hyper violent in Perdita Durango. Here, traumatologist homosexual and repressed. All papers treated with the same intensity and credibility, making solid characters and sometimes being stereotyped too much. I am not mistaken in saying that we we have one of the best players in the world at the time.Cecilia Roth doing wildcard of the Spanish films oscarizables, without weight in the story or the film, almost like a simple cameo. The soundtrack is too melodramatic and repetitive, reloading and stressing that show the (good) scenes. The end if you like is somewhat predictable, moralizing and concesivo, closing that if a film without low blows and ruin a good achievement.</body>
</review>
