<review author="JLO" title="El imperio del fuego" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Movie failed on several points: it is not entertaining despite being the genre of action, without any political message and not despair never transmits no dramatic tension necessary.</summary>
	<body>To see the poster of the film with the Dragon advance flying over and threatening an entire city in flames, I entusiasmé and I said: at least guaranteed fun! But I failed by far the palpitation. Movie failed on several points: is not entertaining despite being the genre of action, without any political or perhaps no message - an Anglo-American Alliance is nothing new in these moments - and despite being set in a medieval apocalyptic future, not transmitted never despair nor necessary dramatic tension.Yes the battles between humans and dragons are achieved but they are too limited to support the film (and noblesse oblige, the animal model is the same Dragon heart but without the voice of Connery).Filmed entirely in Ireland (special country to search for locations of castles), tells the almost disappearance of the human race at the hands of these gigantic and fearsome bugs mythological being the only hope a handful of men without armament weight and the fight against hunger and the elapsed time. Chata, with stereotypical characters (the good is sooo good and the bad in the end becomes), without humor except a nice theatrical parody of Star Wars, with correct performances especially in the harmless Matthew Mc Conaughey (unrecognizable with its new look like Conan) and the secondary Christian Bale (American Psycho, Batman Begins). The film starts promising in its initial half-hour and then begins to fade, reaching his absence at the bottom and becoming a hybrid between adventure and suspense coming to yawning. The main fault which can be reproached to a director and his work, is the not to translate in short nothing of what was proposed, seen the poor results.</body>
</review>
