<review author="JLO" title="Maybe Baby" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A script simple and seamless for the unknown Ben Elton also surprising in the direction of his directorial debut.</summary>
	<body>The romantic comedy belonged since the beginning to the Yankee film. By both their own right and perform them very well, as if they had precise timming and the formula. When those comes to imitate are achieved mamotretos without life or identity. This is not the case.You know that in an English comedy you will find beforehand a personal style: good performances, leisurely pace and up some stiffness saved only at few times in recent years - four weddings and a funeral, Full monthly - to mention only two successful.But if as stated add you a couple acting with weight, efficient, more comical situations without using the coup low by the topic - infertility-, the use of gags "to the American" but without abusing's tenderloin with dramatic situations to the tone, we are faced with a successful film that without being any wonder, leaving the famous contemporary my great Greek wedding as child's play.A successful couple has everything but that most craves: a son. From there start a thousand attempts to solve the problem adding a sudden lock creative in Sam (Hugh Laurie of Stuart Little) a writer of television screenplays of little success and his girlfriend Platonic Love Lucy (the dreamer Joely Richardson of the Patriot, 101 Dalmatians) of a new coworker, the handsome Carl (James Purefoy of infidelity)all further complicating the original problem.Surround them side achieved as Tom Hollander as Ewan, a filmmaker released (almost a clone of Ben Stiller) and Roman Atkinson (Mr. Bean) as a hilarious gynecologist and freak. Also is Emma Thompson as a friend mystique of the couple'd in a character without grace and insubstantial.A script simple and seamless for the unknown Ben Elton also surprising in the direction of his directorial debut. In the must, some loose gag that adds nothing like the scene of dandruff of the protagonist, and the English and pedantic idea to put prepo and recited Shakespeare on either side. A collage of romance, melancholy, comedy and drama. So much or so little. To finish the review, detail of a horrible subject of Paul McCartney in the initial titles. Re-read Lennon, you forgive.</body>
</review>
