<review author="JLO" title="El hundimiento" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Manipulative, didactics, a solemn moments and clearly necessary. Oppressive in many moments, with steady pace and excellent performances led by Bruno Ganz.</summary>
	<body>Oliver Hirschbiegel (the experiment), finally was responsible for one of the toughest, most realistic works made in the World War II film, mention of a mea culpa German which comes with many years of backwardness. Light years from the the list of Schindler and the better the pianist victories, although aunque ambas both they pecarían of lightness in comparison. This does not mean that the sinking meets all expectations - and less policy - but the world and the rules of the film. The last days of the great dictator are addressed with harshness and didacticism - is not a theme or an easy to make film - based on the book by historian Joachim Fest (Der Untergang) and mainly in the memoirs of Hitler's Secretary, Traudl Junge.Comencemos leaving clear some of the criticisms that were made to the film, one of the most criticized and bless that year. This film never gets to be condescending or mitificadora of the figure of the Fuehrer. It is true that it is affectionate with his Secretary or to the kisses with his dog, but does not focus at all in this. Moreover, ten minutes one already hates. His paranoia, his lack of tact, his delusions of grandeur and a murderous conduct prevail. It is not claustrophobic while everything takes place in the underground bunker in Berlin, where Hitler spent his last days but only apparently. They are displayed the city streets and the vicissitudes of the people with a child and a medical German soldier - Professor Schenck - examples of civility, and also to achieve some empathy with the Viewer.It is true that nothing is shown of the concentration camps, but is another story that there is here. Germans themselves are who are exterminated by the Red Army, while being the "bad" of history. The collapse also is manipulative, didactic, solemn moments and clearly necessary. Oppressive in many moments, with steady pace and excellent performances led by Bruno Ganz, a realist and therefore delusional Hitler.Su stooped back, his advanced Parkinson, his look lost part of a whole which astonishes. "Naked us (without overacting) the decline of the largest global nightmare at the point just cruelty, that even expired, you want to drag as many people as possible with him."Not I have pity. We do not force them. We voted and gave us a mandate. "And are now paying" said in a moment of anger. Without words. The error of the director is gloat with some performances with strong images - like the children of Goebbels - and not show of himself with his wife, with a saving ellipsis. Mistake made to lose part of the ability to question its own black history but not tarnishes the outcome of the film.</body>
</review>
