<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A Council: when someone say that a film is "fresh, unpretentious," to hang out and relax run as soul that leads the devil</summary>
	<body>For reasons of travel and move I have come late to the discussion, but I cannot make a brief comment addressed to all those who, in one way or another, have met their children good work doing its small contribution to the immense fortune of Dan Brown. These lines, as you will have guessed, are dedicated to all those who, like me, have the particular experience of watching the Da Vinci Code (2006). Some have not only suffered firsthand this event, but they have been seduced by the temptation to write a few lines and even more (as Gandica, which to date has gone a whopping three consecutive innings).And I will just forgive Mr Gandica, but on this occasion I will have to disagree with the statement made by him in his article widely. Assess a work (called cinema, literature, painting or whatever) only by its controversial factor is, in my view, a critical defect inexcusable. That the book of Brown or Ron Howard movie have put the willies to the Catholic Church or the members of Opus Dei undoubtedly has its anecdotal value, but not enough to save this unclassifiable disaster that have tried us to sneak as a summer blockbuster from the bonfire (certainly the most publicized since the beginning of the year)(, because looks that we have been up to their noses with this code). I have no idea where to start to disassemble this film made nonsense, but as well to flight bird occurs to me launch deserved stones against a boring Tom Hanks (whose hair cutting is without doubt the most controversial point of the tape), a dreadful script work of not less deplorable Akiva Goldsman (who has A brilliant mind)(, but let us also Batman &amp; Robin, not forget) and an unbearably sosa Audrey Tautou (I will say it without fear: Amelie, a film so cloying that I would leave stiff a diabetic can not stand) whose role is reduced to put face of astonishment every ten minutes. Not to mention the laughable Paul Bettany as the monje-psicópata or the misguided Jean Renó in her role as police of the Opus. The solitary soul makes more or less something to save the day is Ian McKellen, who is apparently the only one that is not this pantomime psuedo-conspiracy as if out Shakespeare.Pero go back to the starting point: what is the merit of this film? The answer is simple and painful: none. The less timid have attempted to defend it (as advocated in his day the book) arguing that you it's a work of fiction, a superficial divertimento which should not be taken in serious (**). Those who say this fall in a double mistake: firstly because your comment is redundant to be precisely the seriousness with which many take everything this story the main reason of dismay from those who rant against the book by Dan Brown, and secondly because Dan Brown himself noted on the first page that what he is writing is based on real documents and factsso that from the beginning the work aspires to more than mere entertainment. Any person with a minimum of general culture and four fingers in front (which also serve to make a quick Google search) will know that the arguments about whether Jesucristo had children to Mary Magdalene are based on a conspiracy theory that is recognized as humbug up by themselves agnostics, i.e. the people whom you most suda cock (never better said) if Chuíto left or not offshoots worldwide. Not to mention the numerous descriptions throwing both book and film of works of art, historical and other facts, deliberate falsehoods (or at least Frank ignorance) that could deny to a high school student. I do not speak of this because it was already in charge of Rodrigo Fresán item, and if looking for sure they are au article out there. And anyway, I don't think that the mere fact of opposing something, create controversy and cause is in itself and by itself a good thing (and you that lee should not believe it, because that when much is outdated rhetoric of the French may).But all this would certainly be forgivable (generous I am today, almost nor I admit) if not were to a sleeping, pretentious, boring movie, without the more minimum sense of rhythm or character, a disaster continued arriving to balance up three different endings and whose greatest detallazo has been awakening the wrath not only of the Church (which proves once more be the best history advertising agency)(, because you have to see the tantrum of a spoiled child that has been mounted, of course causing more people to go see the movie) but also a happy national organization of albinos (where but in United States?) who are tired of the "non-pigmented" always appear as the bad guys in movies.And certainly more fool of all am I, that I have fallen into the trap even after having read the book two years ago and know in advance that this smelled of catastrophe. One scene in particular made me shudder of horror: the moment when a priest (very bad bad very bad) says "the blood is being dumped" and to highlight his brilliant phrase, spilled wine on the table. From there the tears began to fall. What I was coming over was luxury.I will give you advice: when someone say that a film is "fresh, unpretentious," to hang out and relax run as soul that leads the devil, because it will probably be the worst crappy have seen in his life.</body>
</review>
