<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Best thing is its first third, something more, where we can attend a fun and perfect psychological study of the various characters. Estimable first job in the film of Felix Viscarret.</summary>
	<body>Good first job in film directed by Felix Viscarret, who had already given samples of his talent in some short-covering letter, Fernando Trueba gave him his first opportunity as a director in a long.Here adaptable bastente Fernando Aramburu's novel, "The trumpeter of the Utopia", mixing comedy and drama harder in a attractive and emotional way although, in my opinion, not entirely convincing.It has many positive elements that makes this film a very estimable work more taking into account that it is the first work of its young director. But it must be said that the irregularity in its rhythm and situations are that it is unbalanced.The best thing is its first third, something more, where we can attend a fun and perfect psychological study of the various characters, especially of its displaced protagonist, a highly imperfect man but with a nose and joy of life undisturbed.Viscarret manages to show the weaknesses and strengths of a number of people, who try to be happy, although life imposed on them over and over again even insurmountable and challenging tests. During its first third comedy takes over history, which may not be tougher, but to be filled with funny dialogues and jocular manners situations, arouse the sympathy of the spectator, that enough laughs and smiles at all times.However, its final third is a dramón with fear, well narrated cinematically, but makes it descompense a bit the final result, that it remains good, but, at least to me, left me a small sediment of dissatisfaction, apparently I that rhythm and narrative intensity decaría somewhat.This is not obstacle to appreciate this movie, which I consider to be, in time, the best Spanish to date, inter alia by heartfelt interpretations, especially of Alberto San Juan, which is immeasurable, and the music, very appropriate.</body>
</review>
