<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Comandante" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are who criticised the documentary as "a love letter to Castro" and I find no passion in the lines of Stone. The dinosaur has soul and here even tenderness, repentances, vices and sins.</summary>
	<body>dictator, ra. (From the lat. dictatōre [m]). m. and f. In modern times, person he arrogates or receives all the extraordinary political powers and exercises them without limitation legal. m. and (f). person who abuses his authority or is harshly to others.Away from the reflection more banked to the hagiography of the character and historical, Oliver Stone left fiction and undertake the enterprise document life and thinking of the old Cuban leader. This ideological Cookbook not ignores the controversy: like in her role as pamphlet not to the taste of all sides and not even siquier to taste from the biografiado camp which is, at times, under siege, become a star of the celluloid to suddenly, shares with a courageous and complete questionnaire that not censorship Bay of pigs, torture on the islanddissent in Miami, censorship, the new world order, the murder of the validity of Communism or even the cinephiles of the dictator, which seems very interested in classic American movies. There are who criticised the documentary as "a love letter to Castro" and I find no passion in the lines of Stone. In any case, there is an admiration, a sense of the relevance of the work that is being done. Fight the verbal incontinenca of Castro is already an achievement. Domestic intimacy that exudes the film allows the Commander to relax, feel comfortable in the role of absolute character of the tape. All dictators have exacerbated love for his person. Castro is no exception: it is not a megalomania Saddam Hussein-style, but the whole island breathes Castroism and dragged and sweet voice seems that it vagara, as phonetic, piers and squares spectrum so that the people don't forget who reached the revolution and all that here, in Europe the welfare and democracy, we think an old tale told to those who still do not have matured enough to warn the miseries of that culture. Stone is an American seriously ashamed of his homeland: he does not hide, but qualifies that his anti-Americanism is not abstract and freezes the image of Bush sending troops to Iraq, subject Stone criminalizes openly. Full Spanish production, Commander part of thirty hours of tape reduced to 100 minutes of film. There are times that Stone seems intimidated by the academic rigor and the Baroque oratory of the Commander. Others that takes the helm of the words and seems that it knocked out the opponent, but it is false: there is no any round. The boxers, closed Chamber, take ron and smoke cigars, I imagine, cheerful limited partnership. Historical flashes are by far the best of the tape: the arsenal of documentation that has accessed the director shows the history of Cuba and also the history of the world in the 20th century. The revolution is already almost 50 years of success in the island. Castro seems immortal sausage in his red Sweatshirt or its Chief of the militias casaca. The village lives anesthetized by the ideological intoxication of a líder-padre who has literate a people and has put in the path of pure socialism and continuous improvement. Concerned about the destruction of identities and the "monoculture" prefers to have a McDonalds in Havana rather than in New Delhi or, at least, not being too complicit in his word, we understand that there should be none outside the US, that is where there is truly a culture that guardianship and protects those excesses of capitalism. Castro also comes to tell us that the precise revolution of all time worldwide and thus on this premise, he not invests any fraction from time to shave. Those "fifteen minutes a day" are used in tackle solutions to the problems of the people. Case that the dictator had spent those minutes shave equal today Cuba was a member of any democratic organization and its citizenship battle the usual battles of all free States. That is, unemployment, violence, terrorism, housing and education. Populated Beard has been well seen. We see the Commander in love with a big screen where watch movies as La revolution Manda or Rita Hayworth or that Italian, Sofia, said that it was crazy. In the chapter of actors stays with Chaplin and Cantinflas, whose films would be able to see them all again. "The history of first ladies" is ridiculous because politics should not mix with the family. "That life is good with you" said to be Stone and Castro at the end fades into an emotional embrace while Cuba continues its Vertigo of prisons without trial, their elimination of dissidents and that its custom of not hold democratic elections to listen to the voice of the people.</body>
</review>
