<review author="Raccord" title="Misión imposible 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Offers only action of the good (which is not little): the plot is too credible nor the villain is the height of Ethan</summary>
	<body>Tom Cruise returns to interpret the hero Ethan Hunt in the grossing series "Mission impossible" to continue giving us adrenaline and explosions. This time also, as producer of the film. Between that and the ego must have the dining room friend of placentas, it was logical that as a result there was a film by and for himself and his showcasing. Innovations very little walks, but who wants to?. They found the formula and her exploit: countless gadgets of latest technology, luxury cars, and a team of elite to help the héore. Of course, the bad guys are very bad (although never know why) and good, with a honesty without fissure, less any secundarillo, which inevitably in these films, just passing the enemy.Perhaps less flip to the previous film in the series, in "Mission impossible III" we try to show that Ethan Hunt in addition to distribute tow, is a human being sensitive and affectionate with his wife. This subplot is completely stuck with shoehorn and has some truly joke moments. In my humble opinion, if they wanted to give greater psychological depth to the character, it would have been much better that they raise the friendly relationship between Ethan and his team, with his young woman, with flashbacks of the wedding and the moments which spent together confectioners. (That by what you've written seems that not liked) is otherwise a very good action film, with moments of tachycardia, and others in which we only babear before the sobrado hero and millimetric plans to attack the bad units. By the way, assail the Vatican! Do they will be giving to understand in a veiled way that the Catholic Church is a mafia or some sort of criminal organization? If I can confirm that it is the case, I promise to edit criticism and put a 10. offers only action of the good (which is not little): the plot is too credible nor the villain is the height of Ethan. You should something more grateful sense of humor, and that pseudo history of love to give depth to the character, it was a little more convincing. It is worth seeing her.</body>
</review>
