<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="300" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The sequences epicismo and heroism, nor entertaining battles (in slow motion?) has the film, sweet and the sour sensation of having witnessed an absolute smallness, compared to what could have been really have been able to remedy.</summary>
	<body>First of all, I would like to say that I am of those they loved Sin City (although her I have not seen since its release in theaters, waiting to come out an Edition on DVD at the height of the circumstances), but not of those who have read the graphic novels by Frank Miller in which the aforementioned are based, and the film before this text: 300, directed by Zack Snyder (director of the very enjoyable dawn of the dead), so do not know if it is a faithful and adaptation to the height of the work of the Lord.I wanted to see this film, thanks to the magnificent trailers and clips from the movie Warner us has been offering as bait for which more expected to see her, all the time we have been waiting for this release. But the fact is that created high expectations for a film of considerable relevance artistic and economically speaking, such as 300, might be a blunder. And is that I could not help me feel a tad disappointed by the end of the projection. 300 is an audiovisual show unique and true to the style of Frank Miller, as already occurred in Sin City. A delight to the eye (there are levels that are true works of art, and does not detract any merit which are a copy of the drawings of Miller) and ear (the soundtrack is fantastic, an explosive mixture of genres without precedent in the peplum). There are battles of spear and sword to give and take: A real feast violently explicit and entertaining, which seems to be no place for historical accuracy. In addition, the cast is one hundred percent (Gerald Butler, King Leonidas, huge for my taste).But unfortunately in this case is not gold that glitters (although it might have been perfectly).From my point of view, the best way to define 300 is compared to a "gift-matriuska": make you delivery of a huge box with very colorful wrap, touching the exquisiteness. You open as if wishing you was life in this, to see what is inside, but you're with another smaller box. So once, and another, and another, until you find a small box which is inside the gift, that to see it, you like, but what you also think nothing out of this world for both envoltorio.300 so. It is technically perfect, but something goes wrong. History not found me nothing of another Thursday. At first it interest, but that interest will deflate as it is spending time. In my opinion part of blame for this is her argument, which does not give almost two horazas duration (there are several "scenes of stretching" quite boring for the crux of the film.), and the complaint and absolutely excessive use of slow motion, which just overloading, and gets only loathe and put more sticks to the wheel of the already irregular rhythm of the film.But in what may be, her I enjoyed, but sequences of epicismo and heroism, nor the battles (in camera slow.) which owns the film, have been able to remedy a bittersweet feeling of having witnessed an absolute smallness compared to what could have been really.</body>
</review>
