<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="V de Vendetta" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I will always remember on November 5.</summary>
	<body>Finally, after so much time looking forward to seeing it (thanks to a few rave reviews and a very promising trailer), just got back from the second session of V for Vendetta, film adaptation of the graphic novel created by Alan Moore (screenplay) and David Lloyd (drawings), back in the 1980s.My expectations were sky-high, but always accompanied by a hint of bad vibes, as the script for the movie is borne by the Wachowski brothers, creators of the Matrix. and its ineffable sequels. and with that I believe that I have already said everything. But, oh! Surprises gives life; each and every one of expectations in this film have been fulfilled without doubt, all unlike the bad vibes that gave me the word Wachowski before 19: 00 hours on the day of today, and will not underestimate.Vibrant and stunning, would describe V for Vendetta as the sensation of embobez you have to watch an exhibition of dominoes forming drawings, shapes and dimensions thanks to its peculiar effect, which has some role in an excellent sequence of the final act of the film. You know keep pace with minute to minute without getting bored at all, despite the fact that has three scenes of action be counted on the fingers of the hand in the one hundred and thirty-six minutes that comprises the footage, thanks to a direction and screenplay impeccable and elegant in identical parts. Like some interpretations you sublime part of the cast, but especially by a Natalie Portman in State of grace. A brilliant interpretation yours, that I am not surprised nothing that carry several nominations at various film festivals. And Hugo Weaving, the star of the role and who plays v, uncertain character hidden behind a mask of Guy Fawkes, to which you do not see the face in the film, but that he wasted some sympathy and overwhelming charisma.I do not know if the V for Vendetta film (and James McTeigue-do led?) is a good adaptation of the graphic novel. But one thing that I have left very clear: is a fucking great movie. For all these reasons I have mentioned, and as much more, deserve plenty of the first 10 of the year. I will always remember on November 5.</body>
</review>
