<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Portrait of an obsession. Zodiac escapes from the genre of assassins and policemen, decanting without objections by offering an almost documentary film cold although of disturbing plot.</summary>
	<body>When one sees this film suspicion that one of the possible reasons that could have led to our exhibitors to delay its release in many theaters in Spain is that - despite the expected by a spectator bit informed, or simply confident in the effective but crematística motivation of those who carried out the promotional trailers - are not dealing with one of those products with intelligent murderer to the Lecter and even more clever police on his hunt. Nothing further of what gives us Zodiac, whose long but superbly mounted footage is engaged only in thirty or forty minutes initial describe? without sanguinolencia or sadismos Visual, and Yes with a leisurely serenity that worries and even puts the willies (that's premeditated sadism!)-the murders of the Zodiac, based on real events that took place in California in the late 1960s.Five victims, four Cryptograms, letters to the press, live revelations to television, more than thirty years of research, some suspect but no detainee. A cocktail which had been to juicy scripts in the face of the box office if they had focused on the point of view of the murderer, or the dialectic of the police after the track of a clever criminal. But no, Fincher decides to bet - as did, but in a darker tone, Seven - by a dash more serene, classical if possible, which is weaving unhurried (as own research describes) a plot dyed false leads and hopeful signs we soon returning to move from a truth never fully clarified, and that only believed to arrive who perseveres, but leave in the way their private lives and their health.Zodiac escapes from the genus of murderers and police, decanting without objections by offering an almost documentary film cold although disturbing plot (centered on the obsession with Graysmith and Toschi, and cirrótico Avery), which analyzes the puzzle that those few rare men (i.e. risky for what his contemporaries concerned) seek to desmadejar, despite its difficulty, to name an elusive assassin with pretensions of showman of terror or Einstein of the puzzles. This option of Fincher bored fans of the police more and less bizarre (Lt. Callahan included), but will delight anyone (including who writes) expected a cinema research Pakula or Frankenheimer-70s style. Incidentally, the very discreet and always correct David Shire signed the soundtrack for Zodiac (so far Fincher is trust of Shore), as as it did with all the President's men, or the conversation (Coppola, 1974).This narrative discretion and that emotional estrangement not removed the creator of Seven us again to shrink the stomach in these excellent scenes of the murders, extraordinarily planned in order to leave us without breath waiting for the (fatal) outcome. Despite the coldness of the research process posed by the film, the pace is maintained and compels us to seek with their characters if it really is or not who believe the Zodiac killer. Now we do not know who is brutal in their crimes (that already almost forget the hour and a half of footage), but by the pure obsession to close the film in a certainty that we consuele. As it is to be expected, both the reality and the fiction are in this case dark and more disappointing than it expected.On the other hand, note the exciting cinematic references that paid Zodiac. In fact, the same movie revolves around fiction (the wishes, to be precise) as a trigger for human actions. Fincher's recreates the noveladas research on the book of the insightful cartoonist (and boy scout) Robert Graysmith (Jake Gyllenhaal again embroidering the role of Platypus, after that gem called Donnie Darko). The Zodiac killer works of projectionist in a cinema and was impressed by the movie the evil Zaroff (Pichel and Schoedsack, 1932), looking for more late recognition media through the press and television. Toschi (content and credible Mark Ruffalo) police just serving as a Muse of the dirty Eastwood Callahan or Bullit McQueen (could be the pistolón?).Fincher is pessimistic. Humans seek ghosts that may not exist, and at the end we are victims of our own passions, as the Zodiac killer, as three detectives, as the irascible character of Brad Pitt in Seven, like me, like you.The best: ** how to shoot the murders. ** levels air ciudad.* the scene of the encounter with the (alleged) proyeccionista.* the scene of the murder frustrated of the mother and her baby with this terrifying elipsis.* that start with item Easy To Be Hard, Three Dog Night, and a city lights, almost optimistic, single-family and teenagers that listen to Donovan or roses Lynn Anderson ballads and his Rose Garden.* caricature of the naked Yoko Ono and Lennon in the drafting.</body>
</review>
