<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Tideland" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You don't ask is the time because it is boring, that it is not. If not because it is unbearable to see both sufimiento and a situation so miserable.</summary>
	<body>Terry Gilliam seems a genius but his genius in this case bordering on madness. Tideland would inaugurate a new genre, the film of bad feeling. A film that you can not believe what you are seeing and you left between the naúsea and the irremontable downturn.This peculiar "Alice in worseland" is perverse, dirty, ugly and Gilliam serves cold and very little done, almost raw. The protagonist is a girl that coexists with two drug addicts. Upon the death of his stepmother, she travels with her father on a flatulent journey to nowhere, to a home in the countryside. The small wild……, fantasizes and borders on Schizophrenia while preparing him PAPI his injection of vitamins in what are some scenes that herirían the sensitivity of Charles Mason-but are not the only ones.With this panorama, the girl becomes an emotional girl and engaged relationship with its neighbours: a woman who lives terrorised by the wasps and his son, a mental retarded adolescent. But sometimes it is better to be alone than badly accompanied and his psychotic DELIRIUM is increasing while becomes child forced Norman Bates.Do do do and with these ingredients it is evident that the film, which delights to show small possessed by his avoidance of reality, makes that you will pass the footage thinking about three things:? that someone call social services?,?Do if I had a daughter non had I left him star in this film? and? when hit this??But it is not that be requested time because it is boring, that it is not. If not because it is unbearable to see both sufimiento and a situation so miserable. As well as in the laberinto del fauno, the protagonist locked in his fairies and their bugs to survive and the imagined story was more attractive, in Tideland happens otherwise. It is so insane the environment, the fantasy, the scenarios and characters that do not know what is worse and shrinks the stomach, the soul and the heart.Sorry but I not noticed if he had good photography, soundtrack and art direction, result that just looked.</body>
</review>
