<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>While under the stars is a remarkable debut, the expectations created in its path by Malaga and the salivamiento of the critique that has put it in the clouds, make that it happens typically when create you many hopes: you are disappointed.</summary>
	<body>Sound the trumpets but not rockets. While under the stars is a remarkable debut, the expectations created in its path by Malaga and the salivamiento of the critique that has put it in the clouds, make that it happens typically when create you many hopes: you are disappointed.The film of Viscarret outlines a history of sympathetic losers - not reaching fall friendly - adapting the novel the trumpeter of the utopia of Aramburu. An Alberto San Juan that makes you want to give a sponge and ten euros gets into the skin of a musician cantama침anas returns to his village, namely Estella.A grudgingly come to see his dying father and scrounge up that gets shot, primarily to his brother, an Ibarrola of the metal that makes impossible sculptures and has few lights although enormous heart. San Juan between patxar치n and patxar치n is dedicated to establish friendship with the daughter of the girlfriend of his brother - a cuellicorta feral-, which despite the little respect that trafficking, is thrilled to life with his new uncle, who also gives him tobacco.The story takes place between these relationships and a drama that is sensed from the two frame. Although the movie - seen so - isn't it isn't so bad, suffers from a script that outlines but not specific and an excess of lyricism that while it is aesthetically appreciated, contributes little to the storyline and slows her down. In short: I bored and did not excite me despite the good intentions of the debutante. That Yes, the realization is impeccable and navarro landscape and the landscape are very well portrayed - although not all are so garrulos-. Merit also of Viscarret is having succeeded in a dusty atmosphere, very close to the western. The soundtrack is very good starting with the central theme. Enrique Morente sang Stella by starlight with a tear that neither Tom Waits. And mention the expected resurrection of Emma Su치rez, a great actress who works a little lately.And please someone I can reply to this? Why the Spanish films - in which more - are as given to show the actors miccionando?PS: As I know that when do waves to a home movie you falls from God is Christ ready I am. That Yes, I've been benevolent because my two companions demanded me as the six euros and I will no longer let choose film anymore. Although now that I remember with one of them I saw Bienvenido home and inexplicably we remain friends.</body>
</review>
