<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="Hostel 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Full of inconsistencies and absurd elements in his ridiculous script. The film too takes to boot, and everything that shows has not the slightest interest.</summary>
	<body>Eli Roth is poised to become one of the worst directors of all time, and soon his name will occupy a place of honor next to others such as Ed Wood or Uwe Boll. ?Cabin Fever? do had neither feet nor head, and?Do Hostel?, despite some point of black humor and true pace, did not stop being a joke a bit, focusing on sadism of characters without ton or they are, pure and cheap offal only because Yes. ?Hostel 2? It is even worse, and the truth is that it is a totally useless sequel, because it adds absolutely nothing to already seen, and it shows that it has been quickly and only running to generate easy money. And although his results are far below other blockbusters, the truth is that he will recover more than its ridiculous budget and amasará a good figure on the international market. In addition, Roth has managed that Mr. Tarantino House it within it and now identify you with him, as if that siriviera something to justify the zero quality of their tapes.The argument of?Hostel 2? It is virtually identical to its predecessor, simply change to guys for girls (not I who complains), is otherwise almost modeled to the previous. A group of three friends who are in Italy, end up in Slovakia, passing is of fear (never better said), and will go to a site that will be used to meet the hidden desires of a lot of depraved that pay for killing someone torturing him.But the only torture that exists here is the movie itself, full of inconsistencies and absurd elements in his ridiculous script. The film too takes to boot, all shows not has the slightest interest, the presentation of characters is long and boring, and when what happens already sabmos in advance that is going to happen, the film ends, no more. All lovers of gore and strong images, will come out greatly disappointed the film, which only contains three scenes of foul calls, that, that Yes, Roth cutting an iota to show all kinds of atrocities, to each which more beast. In fact, the film it based everything on that, which does not last or ten muntos on screen, so the joke is brutal.The characters are all absolutely stupid, and you want up to they load quickly to any of them. Then, the film has the habit of wanting to give back to emergencies, exchanging the roles of some characters, but everything is as little credible and too forced. In this respect I refer to its final part, in which one of the protagonists takes the reins of the matter, resulting everything absolutely implausible. And not to mention the dialogues, where there is not a single intelligent sentence. It is better for a film of this style will have dialogues to the Shakespeare, but one thing is that and well another vulgarity which here looks.A crappy monumental, completely lacking sense of humor, and which allow a nod to the godfather of the event, in a scene in which two characters are watching TV?Do Pulp Ficiton?, and which you don't pay too much attention, though it may seem otherwise. On the other hand, and much to our regret, despite the hardness of the images from the movie, this not dares with some possible lesbian relationship that had added you some curiosity to the subject, but nothing at all. On the one hand, the film is passed, and on the other hand, does not dare. Roth now prepares the adaptation of a Stephen King novel?Do Cell?, and says it will take a long time making it. That don't worry, some not demandaremos it apure.</body>
</review>
