<review author="Caruco" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The work of Viscarret WINS thanks to the interpretations of its actors. Especially to an Alberto San Juan, that achieves a scoundrel of his ilk get to play the chord.</summary>
	<body>"Under the stars". Homeless and wandering without fixed abode, or protecting with a blue mantle broken dreams or unfulfilled. Suggestive title of the directorial debut of promising, or so hope, Félix Viscarret, a pamplonica, under the auspices of Fernando Trueba in production, leads from Madrid to the lost village navarrés of explodes, to assist the process of maturity, and reunion with himself, of Benito Lancuza (Alberto San Juan).A trumpeter who, in that search for your destination, escaped from those valleys and people in an attempt to succeed in the metropolis. And there was it renamed, artistic and symbolically, as Benny Lacun.Pero talent or luck, were not allies of this "great" Benny Lacun, actually a gift no one, a loser, a cafre and a drunk. Unable to shed a tear, or by his dying father on the deathbed. Question of selfishness, or trauma that go back to childhood. And Benito, big kid, ready to find their way.Human tapestry has been enriched with a good-natured brother until the pathological, nicknamed "tuboloco" or "Iron" for his unusual gift for making sculptures with simple scrap (excellent Julián Villagrán); a girl, now women punished for his past, trying to overcome the future (Emma Suárez); and a girl, silent, enigmatic and rebel (Violeta Rodriguez) capable of stealing the heart this man who could not mourn.Do do not lacks poetry and sensitivity to the proposal, nor a touch of alleged boorishness mountain mixed with urban nihilism, in this work of rookie Felix Viscarret that seasoned their images of naturalness? amateur? and careful carelessness in the framing and mounting. But especially, not scarce the more dramatic elements, always under the varnish, over that of the stars in the comedy that both helps us to move away from the rigidity of the tragic. Still, more conventional and, at times, lead, than is desirable, the work of Viscarret WINS thanks to the interpretations of its actors. Especially to an Alberto San Juan, that achieves a scoundrel of his ilk get to play the chord. Divertídisima, for example, the sequence in the phone booth with benito talking with her lover of Madrid, Pauli (Luz Valdenebro).Do special mention deserves also the music of Mikel room ("Romasanta", "Baghdad Rap"), and good eye, it is assumed that Fernando Trueba for choosing composers, with a splendid theme? country? do do that links with that tone of? western? to the navarresa has sought its director.And although the argument, adapting the novel "The trumpeter of the Utopia", Fernando Aramburu, does not offer more, but not less, get attest that, in this earthly world our, "under the stars", in the same way that the scrap can reach to sculpt art, also between the lives covered in dirt and debris can have hope.</body>
</review>
