<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Historia de un crimen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>?History of a crime? revisit the same place, the same episode, if it is true that the tone gives the director Douglas McGrath, is subtly different from that conferred Bennett Miller to?Truman Capote?.</summary>
	<body>Does not stop being curious the simultaneity of some projects reaching the film at the same time: remember cases high-profile, such as "Les Liaisons dangereuses" and "Valmont", that fantasy to the big screen the drama of Choderlos Laclos, or "1492." "Conquest of paradise" and "Christopher Columbus." "The discovery", who put on images at the same time the Columbian adventure. "Now returns to happen: little more than one year ago was released in Spain"Truman Capote"(see criticism in Criticalia), excellent approach to the life stage of the exquisite writer in which a quadruple murder in Kansas he subjugated to such an extent that, written his masterpiece"A blood cold", on the immortal story, never again he returned to writing anything new.""Historia de un crimen" revisit the same place, the same episode, while it is true that the tone gives the director Douglas McGrath, is subtly different from that conferred Bennett Miller to "Truman Capote": here the relationship between the writer and the murderer Perry reaches levels of physical intimacy that other film hardly aimedproving to be more evident the link previously suggested than anything else. Greater emphasis on the relationship of friendship, is also at times almost of hatred between Capote and writer Harper Lee, author of "To kill a Mockingbird", and the melifluo approach that forced Truman to reach the head of police in charge of the case and the village society of Kansas. It would be unfair to compare both versions, because the two are valuable and provide stimulating insights into the life and work of Capote, especially on that period of its existence, which literally changed life. In this case the director chooses to include fragments of alleged interviews with those people (performed by the corresponding actors) who knew him well, with which adheres to the concept of mixture of fiction and non-fiction which was the germ of the novel "in cold blood". It is true that Toby Jones, the actor who incarnates to Capote, opts for an interpretation of the writer less affected that which masterfully conducted Philip Seymour Hoffman in the other film, but both performances are excellent, without that it fit to censor his compositions. Yes it is true that, in this case, the distribution is extraordinary: appears as notable people such as Sigourney Weaver, Isabella Rossellini, Gwyneth Paltrow (this one in a slashing the cameo role), director Peter Bogdanovich (which recently makes more movies as an actor than as a filmmaker) and Sandra Bullock (which seems to have wisely reconducido his career since its inception ñoños more substantial characters)Jeff Daniels and Daniel Craig (so far from his character James Bond in "007 Casino Royale").</body>
</review>
