<review author="Berto" title="Habitación sin salida" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It serves to hang out if you are able to accept the countless holes in the script, but it does not stand a minimally serious analysis. Norman Bates would be the hands to the head.</summary>
	<body>This seems to the ugly truth is putting out House in USAmérica. You trying to get you by those of eight-lane highways, or the first diversion you take you are part of the menu of Caradecuero. And this is to say nothing of the motels road, shelter (and often grave) of unwary travelers. Then the couple in divorce proceedings formed by David Fox (Luke Wilson) and Amy (Kate Beckinsale), does not seem to take into account the wisdom that is reflected in the film, because they not only get a strange desert road, and let a stranger makes them a few odd in the engine, but they end up spending the night in a seedy Highway motel run by Mason (Frank Whaley) in which are the only guestswhich they discover when they see a few tapes in his room where there are recorded torture and murders committed in that room. What follows varies a bit between the "run, run, that you get", and "now you see me, now I don't, and you will see the leap that you paste when it appears". Curious thing about this case is that the players are not completely stupid (well, she did until near the end), although the real merit is the erratic behavior of the bad turn, that suggests if the Marx Brothers are not hide under the mask. The best of the movie the claustrophobic atmosphere of the room is enhanced thanks to the fixed cameras installed in it, although as too much imagination would require to develop an hour and a half movie in a closed room, soon the thing becomes a slasher of the corrientitos. Actors chillan and bleed as it is assumed that they should do so, and Luke Wilson, also has the advantage of not being his brother Owen, what makes it infinitely more bearable than the colleague from raids of Ben Stiller. Is Beckinsale doubt whether is a great actress, or is that she has a face of disgust of itself, but I tend towards the latter. It serves to hang out if you are able to accept the countless holes in the script, but it does not stand a minimally serious analysis. Norman Bates would be the hands to the head.</body>
</review>
