<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Corazones solitarios (Lonely Hearts)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A recommended title to extend a little more, the mythical existing on the macabre couple immortalized in the film Leonard Castle.</summary>
	<body>Lonely hearts is based on a real case happened between late 1940s and early 1950s, in the County of Nassau (EE.)(UU.). The story of a couple of crooks and murderers, Ray Fernandez and Martha Beck, who joined their forces in the art of deception to approach single women announced the search for a partner through magazines of contacts. A story which previously already had been taken to the cinema several times since, the first of them, the assassins of the honeymoon, a film considered cult which was directed in 1970 by Leonard Castle and in which the dates of the events were upgraded to carry the action at the same time in which it was filmed. The visual harshness and cold treatment that gave the couple of criminals were also the same constants of (for me) the best approach to the subject: he did Arturo Ripstein in deep crimson. In the title of the Mexican, opted to move the facts to his home country and for giving him an outstanding (though bitter and brutal) touch of black humour.The tape just released, directed by Todd Robinson, advocates focus on the police investigation before that in the thorough description of bloody acts of the criminal couple of lovers. Or, at least, in the section that shows the relationship between two police officers leading the case, where works best film. On the basis of the theoretical suicide of a lonely woman, Robinson pays a special attention to the obsessive behavior of the character played by a bright John Travolta, the agent Elmer C. Robinson, a man who, traumatized by the violent and unexpected death of his wife, will not cease in its efforts to sickly by demonstrate that, after the apparent suicide, are killer hands. A type this to not believe neither superiors nor his own partner of fatigue, James Gandolfini so great (in all aspects) as always.An attractive Salma Hayek and Jared Leto give life to the two lovers who ended up receiving the long nickname of the assassins of the lone hearts, the already mentioned Ray and Martha. And, precisely, in the choice of Salma Hayek to play the virulent Martha Beck, lies the great mistake of the tape since, as they demonstrated other past products, was a homely woman marked by an extreme obesity, exactly the opposite of what happens with the actress born in Veracruz. Outbursts of jealousy and the unit facing Ray Martinez, a woman so beautiful and sensual as the Hayek, difficult to believe, thus, some situations of high tension created between them and their victims, is I seem too forced to be credible. Yet and so, its director, with an elegant and unsuspected dryness resolves those murders which displayed on the screen.The courage to use one little girl as another of scapegoats bait of the criminal duo, is an unequivocal sign that such Todd Robinson has happened (luckily) of political correctness and the false moral Hollywood that, in recent years, attempts to keep children away from the actual extent of criminals mercilessly. A, almost strict rule, which had only have jumped to the Bullfighter people like Cronenberg, A history of violence, and Florent Emilio Siri in the magnificent prologue by Hostage. A way that compensate for the failed election of the protagonist of Frida who, incidentally, is not not bad in its correct working. To give more the pego, here should have placed that mustache looked under the nose of the Mexican writer again.Its setting in the North America of the 1940s and 1950s, the voice of the character of Gandolfini, his (almost close to the documentary) narrative sobriety and mental decay and morale of the detective Elmer C. Robinson, (although keeping distances) close to some of the titles born under the protection of film noir. His lack of pretensions, the serenity of a concise script and anything bizarre (written by the filmmaker himself and also real grandson of agent Robinson) and the simplicity of an actual production make this (and despite their mistakes), a recommended title to extend a little more, the mythical existing on the macabre couple immortalized in the film Leonard Castle.</body>
</review>
