<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El Motorista Fantasma (Ghost Rider)" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mediocre gimmick of series B or C that aims only to sell an image and open, if possible, a franchisee...</summary>
	<body>Spoil the Ghost Rider with this prank with budget has no forgiveness. Da like Nicolas Cage is placed the chupa of leather, boot the fardona bike and arda as a yankee mascletà. Da same as bunglers responsible for selling us this crappy have sworn by Mefistófeles who love the Marvel Comics Group. What they have done is enfangar her, spoil a good opportunity - which was given to Spider-man or the X patrol - to ensure that the myth of the comic reaches a new audience, though I imagine the barque of adolescents wagered on queues won't demand too much and their faces leaving will be glittering and bpublish. The mine, which is far from having acne, already a few decades ago has not gone of the spasms. Or perhaps disappointed because I like Cage, I am devotee of the Marvel fan and always have the noble desire that does not spoil these material noble that led my childhood into my teenage years and now, in different formats, guardianship children of my son towards his. In any case, the perpetrator of this flamboyant infamy (Mark Steven Johnson) already warned of his mediocrity when I put in the still less worthy Elektra or Daredevil Billboard. Now confined itself to write (multifaceted boy) a modeled script of the comic that has contributed nothing personal. Away from these creative levels fantastic the unforgettable Simon Birch, but inspiration eloped as had, apparently, reflexes, or desire for a prosecution in rule. This Ghostrider has, however, a notable technical level, what less. The rider Burns credibly, go sentence. The trouble is when there is no combustion: there everything is languid, dull, poorly led and worse presented. Pseudo-religiosas comics activate mechanisms mystical that already I do not share, but not slow to understand that there are public avid for these apocalyptic brass bands between the day of judgment day and the arrival of the Antichrist: echoes of Dan Brown for modern minds. Anyway the original story of Acrobat Johnny Blaze sold his soul to the devil is most and is not just burdening it with these religious speculation again minted. To make higher the pira expiatory add dialogs are ridiculous, although one has confidence that this trash of parliaments was written wrong to post to give a touch can spoof? to the farce. Peter Fonda near a motorcycle seems Easy rider, but here are painfully drag and not at any time gives the impression of acojonar staff in his role as the devil mismísmo. Eva Mendes her dress up as if to burst the shirts by his breast audacity and Nicolas Cage, note that I've left the friend to the end, does not put any efforts to be an actor and confined to exercise some horrific grimaces that do not give the tormented Blaze traces facial of truly being under the chains of torment. A long time ago that master Coppola's nephew does not give the size in a big screen Adaptation (the man of the time) because Wicker Man and World Trade Center are harsh evidence of the dramatic pasotismo. Not the lack of ambition of the film should be overlooked in very specific areas: poor little wealth. The rider those snack in a blink of tap. Or that ride in the desert (ay that air comic) into the dusty and spectral village with two riders in flames on the back of their respective groups. Up the Terrible villain is laughable: what lack of courage, what little enthusiasm. And finances are not argument: are loose when handling digital truquitos and other tricks of face to the gallery and the wonderful trailers. Here he had enough, have known, see which advertised. We had spared us both.Better times will come and will bring us other heroes and other villains. Meanwhile I'm going to the shelf and I wear for this night predator. John McTiernan in its best times. The only salvageable Schwarzie movie. The apotheosis of action cinema. A caste, racial hero, brave and ready: no mystical or lost love. A villain bastard and perfect: not reflexes hablaba.0 all reflexes.</body>
</review>
