<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A superb film that manages to transport the Viewer to the decadent but haunting late 19th London.</summary>
	<body>In general, and although it is not very Orthodox, usually considered the presence of Michael Caine enough incentive to watch a movie, and to presuppose the film concerned a minimum in terms of script and interpretation. If to this we add that the rest of the cast members among is an increasingly more tanning Hugh Jackman, my interest increases even more.The final trick is one of those movies that one likes to see with time, relaxed, and taking a gin-tonic, enjoying every scene, every dialogue, each gesture, and above all, of a logradísima setting that transports you (in transport also helps the DRAM), old London of late 19th, decadent and spellbinding, while capable of embelesar.To the already highlighted grandeur of its interpreters (not to be forgotten, although brief and secondary, the emergence of Scarlett Johansson), and their scenarios, must add the absorption capacity of a script prepared lovingly in the details.But as nothing and nobody is perfect, The Prestige also suffers from defects. Starting with difficulties to clearly decide what to call it is The Prestige?, the prestige?, the final trick?, do the final trick, the prestige?. This indecision and complexity in the name, will cause that in the end, most end up referring to her as that film of magicians of Michael Caine, in which also left David Bowie (I forgot comment before the curious even little appearance of Bowie playing the mysterious Tesla).I would also say that it is not uniform in its pace, causing at times is a little lost interest and cost work maintaining attention. The truth is that these details, especially its Cadence, make this a film magnificent, but not exceptional. In any case, one of those movies that nobody should miss. Although for tastes the colors.</body>
</review>
