<review author="Hartigan" title="Historia de un crimen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>History of a crime is a round and well looked after film that it makes to enjoy from the first moment, doing as well as the mild it rubbing the intention a source of satisfaction for the respectable.</summary>
	<body>Beyond what certain visual resources can be achieved in a production involving copyright, how to narrate a history approaching the slightest what could be a book is, if you say so, the dream of many filmmakers. The nuances of a story, the parallel realities and other literary retainers never are hole in the celluloid except in rare and experimental times. And behold, history of a crime, if possible, does resemble the novel that never was. Very pompous around, as you can see. As it was Capote more buffoonish version, something that the unknown Toby Jones has been able to capture as if it were a Siamese brother. Because he is the absolute and well-deserved protagonist of a film that has twisted crime of the Clutter, in Holcomb, earthly research after the assassination and the strenuous efforts of writer New Orleans to create a new genre which earned him applause from the profession and who baptized and blood cold.It is essential to reach a conclusion - that occurs just at the end, as it should be – meet the hero of superficiality that Capote was to understand as well how, in spite of itself, its existence was a heavy cross on his shoulders. And the number of records that the actor in question is able to offer to the House leads to an unusual range of sensations. Pity that last year a great Philip Seymour Hoffman already acaparara holders by this same. But let us not compare.The skeleton of a crime story comes wrapped with the Lasso of the thoroughness. A presentation of characters longer than normal helps to form an idea of why Act so all of them and what is the reason for their misfortune - a folio in white, a suicide, an incomprehensible punishment, etc.. No sentimental ornaments or purported justifications. Snapshots that placed in row comprise a temporary x-ray that starts with an ending and ends with an approach. When one realizes, however, that everything that has seen so far is a lie, the director has been a good time talking about non-evil humans. And all based on perspective jumps, soften not yet received the case. Let us not forget that we are talking about an appalling event. The gossip in town, with forgiveness, led until the last consequences of a jet set eager to adventure is more than we could want an chronicler. Why Capote was well with them.A broad and too-familiar cast could have come to be a handicap for the script, but this is not the case. From Sigourney Weaver up Sandra Bullock - and it will several good performances of the Queen of Hollywood - are wonderful companions of Jones. Only the it thumping, as always, perhaps, is the hard uncle of Daniel Craig. The postmodern executor of the inexpressiveness may this time has been made slightly more credible, but you still have something prevents him to grow. Finally, the introduction of the resource of the interview in the film gives one even larger fiction margin, oddly enough. History of a crime is a round and well looked after film that it makes to enjoy from the first moment, doing as well as the mild it rubbing the intention a source of satisfaction for the respectable. It is a job that will certainly deserve one? rereading? occasional. And you already understand me. (M.M.L.)</body>
</review>
