<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Un engaño de lujo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The first minutes of A deception of luxury do not predict the worst disaster, but halfway the film turns and back into an acceptable product of entertainment.</summary>
	<body>There are few film genres as old as the romantic comedy, which theoretically simple to produce, films are cheap, and they generally work well at the box office. Another thing is that the writers repeated the same pattern until the satiety and do not offer a small novelty. The blame is not yours, who by the less some try, but in the romantic comedy is all done.Jean (Gad Elmaleh) works as a waiter in a large hotel in the French Riviera. One night he meets Irène (Audrey Tautou), a beautiful fortune seekers fell in love with. Get to conquer her to pretend to be a rich heir, but when Irène discovers his true identity he rejects. Jean does not give up, and to regain her decides to invest all his savings to try to keep it. The first minutes of A deception of luxury do not predict the worst disaster, but halfway the film turns and back into an acceptable product of entertainment. The script is not the height of the originality, although if he had started from the premise of the two caza-fortunas, the tape would have earned significantly. The comic moments we must seek them with magnifying glass, although there are a couple of really funny scenes that are the exception that proves the rule. The film shows a blatant lack of pace, essential in any comedy, although fortunately Pierre Salvadori not shows signs of sadism to the not recreate the romantic moments. As for the actors, Gad Elmaleh completely overshadows an Audrey Tautou who performs a bland, bland, unconvincing performance. In fact, it is easier to imagine to Joan Laporta uploaded in the Cibeles celebrating the title of League for Real Madrid than to Audrey Tautou as a sly and seductive fortune seekers.A luxury deception fortunately isn't the typical romantic comedy, although it has most of the shortcomings inherent in the genre, which could however have been a fun and enjoyable film.</body>
</review>
