<review author="Bruji" title="La reina de Nueva York" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do a film that, despite carrying to extremes the appellant? battle of sexes? and contain the most memorable discussion of the history of the cinema, never have the consideration of other comedies of the era.</summary>
	<body>"New York, the city in which up to the truth, to the contact with the ground, becomes more false than a glass eye".Some critics of the 1930s popularized the belief that Hollywood had become a vulgar brunette the most sophisticated blonde. Referred to Carole Lombard, whose elegance was obvious, and which the fame of "vulgar" came you, logically, not by the color of their hair, and yes the language used to joke with his co-stars.The undisputed Queen of comedy, protagonist of mythical titles as being or not being, or the service of ladies, (to be nominated), made this great sense of humor that characterized it for screen sharing with an actor who despised, Fredric March, in Nothing Sacred.El script for this movie, - based on a play that had been published in an important journal of the time-It was written entirely in a train and was intended, precisely, to be interpreted by the actress. The plot, full of social satire, already in 1937 spoke of characters who sell stories invented to the press to be famous, media not contrasting the information received because their only concern is the print headlines strange vibration morbid this kind of gossip and tabloid, cause in the population.With this basic component, the Wild Bill (William Wellman), designed a product in line with known comedies "screwballs", in which not missed a sour criticism of Vermont residents or insinuating sensual undertones. A film which, despite carrying to extremes the recurring "battle of sexes" and contain the most memorable discussion of the history of the cinema, never reached the consideration of other comedies of the Decade as A great news story or the Fiera of my girl the distribution – which contained one of the best performances of the spectacular blondewhich managed to Eclipse, even a star called March, inside and outside the screen-featured attractive appearances, as in the German comedian Sig Rumann (for whom David o. Selznick felt weakness), the wizard of Oz wicked witch and the "Mommy" of what the wind is brought; work that both would come them two years later.At a technical level, their main strengths reside in the use of innovative photography in color in the original music of Oscar Levant that emulated the great Broadway musical, in outlandish costumes designed by Walter Plunkett for their heroines, and the personal touch that brought the tape Cameron Manzies as second unit director.History failed in 1953 in theatre, and was brought back to cinema in 1954 in a curious version, under the title of living his life, starred by Jerry Lewis.La Queen of New York, Carole Lombard, lost his life in a terrible plane crash at 1.942. He was only 33 years old. Left a famous widower, Clark Gable, a total of 75 films was (unable to attend the premiere of the latter), and one of the greatest talents the seventh art has ever known.</body>
</review>
