<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Corazones solitarios (Lonely Hearts)" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lonely hearts is a film that soundly fails in its attempt to emulate the classics of film noir, offering a history that despite being based on real facts nobody is able to believe.</summary>
	<body>If there is a genus that is could qualify as symbol, as the epitome of the classic Hollywood, would certainly be film noir. Some of the greatest films ever made belong to this genre, such as Casablanca, doom, the Maltese Falcon, Cayo Largo or evil thirst. Not to mention the filmmakers who directed such productions (do Welles, Huston, Wilder, Hawks, Preminger?) and great actors who worked in them. It is difficult to find a great Star of the classic Hollywood to not make at least one of these movies.Go these lines as sincere and heartfelt tribute to an era of cinema to a genus in particular, today already practically defenestraded. Not only because just return to him, but because many of the recent examples are abochornantes, as that nefarious the Black Dahlia. But let us focus on what we are discussing, it's lone hearts by Todd Robinson. The tape is based on real crimes committed by Ray Fernandez (Jared Leto) and Martha Beck (Salma Hayek) at the end of the 1940s, and in the capture of the latter, in which Elmer Robinson (John Travolta) played a crucial role. Coincidences that has life, it was the grandfather of the director. The film drags a serious mistake since its inception, and is the approach which has in the form of flashback, showing before the final that the outcome. If this lastrara not enough history, Robinson tells very poorly, no sense of rhythm, slow times and atropellade in others. Admittedly, the script not missing anything to be full of clichés and own mediocre samples of film noir topicazos. The characters are merely empty shells, and as it could not be otherwise, both the protagonist and villain live tormented, suffering each his own cross. Lousy interpretive work, better let alone.Lonely hearts is a film that soundly fails in its attempt to emulate the classics of film noir, offering a history that despite being based on real facts nobody is able to believe.</body>
</review>
