<review author="Bruji" title="Lo que no se ve" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The producers of "The sixth sense" are responsible for demonstrating the irreversible coma of the screenplays, the death of the originality and the resurrection of plagiarism.</summary>
	<body>The producers of "The sixth sense" and director of "Blade Trinity" (dangerous collaboration) carried out this thriller, remake of a Swedish film. An irregular and, at times, entertaining history student with far-reaching claims that, in their multiple twists, is responsible for demonstrating the irreversible coma of the screenplays, the death of the originality and the resurrection of plagiarism.As "the essential remains invisible to the human eye", has to admit the possibility of finding before a cult film, one of those movies that will serve as a reference in the future. But for now, everything points toward another "what television as one starring Harrison Ford, that only left us a memorable and recurring scare in the bathtub in what the truth hidden in the year 2000". from the stories to not sleep of fourth Millenium (this great program), the writers have made multitude of incursions in different genres, the horror drama comedy, through to reach this "supernatural thriller that gradually becomes a romantic story of redemption", in the words of the director. Too much flourish to define a fantasmada, in the best sense of the word, according to the mine.History rocks between the teen horror of fear blue (1985) and the theatrical Ghost (1990) for lead in an unexpected twist, original surprise, finding atractivo.si would have not known it in a romantic comedy, Ojalá Fuera Cierto, 2005. The steps you follow to both, we discovered that this, The Invisible, is the remake of a Swedish film Den Osynlige, year 2002, based on a novel by the author Mats Wahl, also Swedish. Do for its part, the excellent comedy by Mark Waters, that had in its cast Mark Ruffalo and adorable Reese Witherspoon, comes from the literary adaptation Et if c? était vrai. the French writer Marc Levy. Strange coincidence!. Only here not ending the match. One of the directors of Den Osynlige, Joel Bergvall, prepares his Hollywood debut with Addicted, remake of a Korean film. of identical theme!.At this point, the viewer begins to marvel of originality that governs the world, there must be another collateral damage of the effect of globalization, and "that" is written in Singapore already thought in burrows, but is he published in Philadelphia. It would not be strange to the 2,060 year someone comment a film premiere alluding to "what is not, as that classic of the year 2007". Another of these curiosities that govern the history of cinema.For the moment, only perceives a plagiarized story with a narrative structure of infuriating linearity with the ups and downs of the worst TV movies, with redundant phrases which derived into sub-plots that remain in the air, and with a modern soundtrack, which would be only missing a seductive voice that reminded some "Things to do in Denver when you're dead" to become the pilot of one of those new breed TV series episode. A film which based its main attraction on the supernatural phenomena that run without resorting to special effects (Ojalá Fuera Cierto again), with some far-reaching claims that other many directors, writers and producers reflected with greater intensity and lower camelo. To sounds them what that "Only shows the life when you experience the absence"?, perhaps to what beautiful is live Frank Capra?. Ultimately, all are surprisingly different and terribly similar, only you have to break the facade that makes the image of others comes to us distorted, because, almost always, beauty is in the heart. Not remember them this beauty and the beast of Jean Cocteau?. Once again, nothing new under the Sun. Just a regrettable screenplay of Davis, entertaining in their development when obviate their ridiculous frequent failures. However, we remained with the great work of the later Marcia Gay Harden, with the deadpan boy in the war of the worlds (that kind of actor who, inexplicably, kink producers) and, above all, with a draft of Angelina Jolie, with less lips and more talent. Attention to the gymnast Margarita Levieva, if it is not it eventually for dramas, may always be used in the third installment of Lara Croft.</body>
</review>
