<review author="Albert Puyuelo" title="Takehis" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Takeshis is a surrender to the easy art, or is the confirmation that Kitano has just set some principles for anyone go back?</summary>
	<body>Takeshi Kitano autoreivindica. But it does so with a spoof record really strange and very far from the sobriety that used to present his works (except Getting Any?). Takeshis? It is designed to be hated or praised, according to the public that cross. Takeshi-san wanted to summarize what has been said so far with their previous you films, but adding some necessary proposals for any film buff. The plot of the story, as often happens in most of his films, can be summarized very briefly. A supermarket manager is physically just as a celebrity in the world of the show, and their lives will begin to cross in real spaces and fantasy. Both characters are played by Kitano, a fact which emphasizes even more all auto-paródico content of the tape.Levels and games contraplanos that Kitano us has delighted always, still have their presence in Takeshis?, but in smaller amounts. The film focuses much more on wanting to repeat action scenes over and over again. Think the genre of action, for its part, the final abandonment as get with the reiteration that the viewer reaches the desired distaste. The film is, in itself, a declared immolation. Those looks lost in the horizon are interrupted here by characters who appear from nowhere, nor only gives us time to think what will be in the off field. Behind the camera is the film itself, to put it in some way.It is not advisable to find an exact to every sequence sense, it is easier that it not be tied anywhere. The flashbacks return to deceive in Hana-Bi, the dreamy scenes come and go when want them to? but without falling into the nonsensu nonsense. The pace is hypnotic enough as to be carried away through a delusion something felliniano, and conclusions that draw a whole they vary according to the eyes to look at. There is no specific explanation in the film, but a game of mirrors in a great film montage. The axis is called Takeshi Kitano and more is known to this author, most can scratching of the film to get information. But surely, this is not the real intent of the film. It is advisable to look same autoparódicos eyes with which one of the best directors in the world wanted to sign his work more "rare".Do you know a little wrong discover Takeshis? that is the very same Kitano who wants to bury the yakuza-eiga, fashionable today. Their shots become constellations known worldwide, and his work of extortion are more auditions and fantasies, than not at the Centre of a sane argument. The hilarious joke of the grasshopper appears to synthesize the idea of ending an archetype in particular. But there is another significant change. We are no longer a film before it might seem a set of static images shot with a fixed camera. This time, there is only a character that acts autistamente, the rest move with an unnerving binge. Far are the protagonists of Boiling Point, A scene at the sea or the couple in love of Dolls. And the character that used to interpret Beat Takeshi (name of Kitano when it is credited as an actor), who was the police face-of-stick with outbreaks of violence, becomes a simple oldy clown. With his latest film, he wanted leave patent his facet of iconoclast, perhaps to Japan, once and for all, don't see you as comedian which was yesteryear. Is Takeshis? a surrender to the easy art, or is the confirmation that Kitano has just set some principles for anyone go back?</body>
</review>
