<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If I had to compare to Shrek the third with some stories, this would be no doubt the tale of the dairy, because both the pitcher goes to the source which in the end is broken</summary>
	<body>If there is a place on the face of the Earth that all stories are known to imply, undoubtedly it is Hollywood. The Mecca of cinema is a large factory that spread the message confectioner's "and they lived happily and ate partridges". Not to mention another of their specialties, the Chinese tales, which sold to the world with no less enthusiasm. But if the stories have taught something to Hollywood, it is the philosophy of the goose that lays the golden eggs, and we should exploit the successes to its logical conclusion.All this has a good reason, and is that the OGRE more sympathetic, transgressive, green and performed by computer has given the entertainment industry returns to the screens. On this occasion, before the death of King Harold, Shrek will depart in search of Arthur, only legitimate heir to the throne of very very far. However, Prince charming has their own plans and try to gain the throne, recruiting all the villains of fairy tales. Shrek the third is a new and unnecessary return of nut to the world of tales, which tries to repeat without success the keys to the success of the films that preceded. The ingenuity of the previous scripts has disappeared entirely, and is replaced by a series of jokes and easy jokes, besides not having grace, crossing the line between irreverence and apricot and vulgar. The characters have worn out over time, and in this third part we find acartonados, without the spark that characterized them. Only the inclusion of the posh princesses group and some sequences in the Institute show signs of freshness and originality. This Shrek the third becomes an indigesta tape while sucking the staff in a deep slumber, bored children and elderly, whose end is not grasping reach. But not all bad news, at a technical level it is a feat of digital animation, who not consoles is because you don't want to.Shrek was a real revolution in the animated film, as was his acid sense of humor looking more at adult audiences that to the child. Shrek 2 was shown as a worthy sequel, but this third installment is manifested as a new attempt of Hollywood by extending a history already didn't over themselves just to get good dividends. If I had to compare to Shrek the third with some stories, this would be no doubt the tale of the dairy, because both the pitcher goes to the source which in the end is broken.</body>
</review>
