<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Crónicas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Chronicles is a film that shows the darker side of the human soul in all its aspects at the same time posed hard topics in a stark manner, and that certainly will reflect anyone you see.</summary>
	<body>There are movies that it seems that they premiere at the most opportune moment possible by the political or social situation affecting a country. In the majority of cases, it's pure coincidence, and in others, it is tape that soon no one had paid attention and timely reach the screens at the ideal time. Chronicles is one of those films that encompass the second group, when it comes to Spanish screens with more than three years late.Denying that the current society lives mediated and that it depends in good part of the influences of television would be crazy. It would also deny the sordid and morbid sells, ethics gone part of the journalistic profession, and if he is not enough to turn on the idiot box at any time. Chronicles deals with very complex and sensitive, issues mostly related to the world of celebrity and entertainment. On the one hand, the film depicts the horrors being committed in countries of Latin America, impotence and police passivity before such cruelty, and the null (not sensationalist) newsworthy that cause these facts in the first world. On the other hand, chronicles denounced the attitude of the media, and raises the viewer questions where there to mark the boundary between the necessary informative rigour and morbid sensationalism and personal ambition. To achieve a greater impact on the Viewer, Sebastián Cordero offers a hard belt, sometimes excessively uneasy, that does not give or a second of respite. There are really stark scenes, such as the lynching initial, capable of putting the hair tip anyone. The work of actors is good as a whole, although it highlights an ambiguous and disturbing Damián Alcázar. Chronicles is a film that shows the darker side of the human soul in all its aspects at the same time posed hard topics in a stark manner, and that certainly will reflect anyone you see.</body>
</review>
