<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Ladrones" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Thieves hook thanks to the extraordinary chemistry between Juan Jose Ballesta and Maria Valverde, which embroider their respective roles of tormented but charming pickpocket and cock capricious and unsatisfied.</summary>
	<body>Spanish film takes several years to enjoy very good health, not to say excellent. At least in what refers to the artistic and creative, ground where the amount of materials more than interesting operas that are especially noted. The bet made by the producers for the new Directors is really commendable, although perhaps from their perspective it is not therefore matter of budgets.Jaime Marquis Olarreaga made his debut in the direction of feature films with thieves, one of the films that gave more to talk about in the past Festival de Málaga, where he took the special jury prize. Although his title may evoke a large number of possible arguments from a sour comedy about the ins and outs of Telefónica to the experiences of a bank branch, thieves has another kind of history. Alex (Juan José Ballesta) is a young vocational pickpocket who has mistreated life and who is unable to manage by other means. One day meets Sara (Maria Valverde), a girl from a neighborhood well, enjoy that commit small robberies to feel something that does not feel in his tasteless and comfortable routine: emotion and excitement. Both begin a peculiar relationship, in which mixed equal parts love, desire and theft. Jaime Marquis offers to the public a film that moves away completely from the image of el ladrón de guante blanco, and shows a portrait black has nothing to do with the glamour and luxury. With a sunset scene minimalist and sober, but for full effects, tape immerses the viewer in full in history, making him of the joys and miseries of perfectly built characters. Highlights the good Ivan Aledo mounting and excellent photography of David Azcano. The film hooked from the beginning (even the opening sequence something strident), thanks largely to the extraordinary chemistry that develops between Juan Jose Ballesta and Maria Valverde, which embroider their respective roles of tormented but charming pickpocket and capricious and unmet cock. As you would say that, it may be the beginning of a beautiful artistic collaboration. However, halfway through the plot knot, the film is falling until entering a dynamics of free fall little by little. In addition, the end is come easily, perhaps telegrafiado in excess. However, despite its faults, Jaime Marques performs almost impeccable work for a novel, although at times filmmaker peca a somewhat weary and monotonous rhythm.Thieves is a good movie that demonstrates the high level of the Spanish film, and that this kind of stories of pickpockets and scammers of little rides not only dominates them Hollywood. And above all, it consolidates the two best young interpreters of the Spanish film scene.</body>
</review>
