<review author="Dragon negro" title="Transformers" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Transformers is, despite their defectillos, a great movie of action and effects, fun and entertaining and above all that can be seen and you can enjoy cinema of evasion in its purest form but that it holds under its own weight.</summary>
	<body>Yesterday I had the opportunity of attending the European premiere of the latest film from Michael Bay, Transformers, in the Auditori of Sitges. First of all there is to say that Transformers faced, personally, the challenge to be above other major blockbuster productions that have been presented this year as Spider-man 3 and Pirates of the Caribbean 3 which have been two disappointments, it is very difficult not what I had, but apart from that I had to convince and view once, I can only say that Transformers Yes convinces and is that palomitera film of great special effects and action were expected to view.The film focuses on the character of Shia LaBeouf, apart from carrying other parallel stories, but who carry the weight of history will be its character, whose tatatarabuelo was discovered in the Arctic a great giant robot, a secret that will make you suffer the consequences in the present. His character is the typical flacucho Institute in love with the popular girl, but far from being the standard Peter Parker, here we see as no doubt stand up to the players on the team and espabilar for your account when necessary. Little takes to appear the first Transformer at a military base in the desert and sown chaos in a spectacular scene of destruction, the first of a few to the length of the film. The fight will focus on finding the cube of the spark of life and see who can do with it.Combines large doses of action and spectacular effects, best seen in what we have year and I doubt very much that are overcome, with large doses of humor that really make you drop more than one laugh. The plot unfolds in parallel in three or four lines argue them that they combine perfectly without being over any of them. LaBeouf carries the weight of the film with some dignity and has left me pleasantly surprised and eager to see their role in Indiana Jones 4 where already I have no doubt that it will do really well. Just manages to be eclipsed by John Turturro in the role of an agent of the Government most chulito and past very insane thread. The girl, Megan Fox isn't bad and his character moves away slightly from the typical girl placed vase to make nice, which is to be welcomed.All this is fine, but is not at all a round film, and is that we must not forget where we are and that this is a family film and for a mainstream, and that is noted in the, at times, excessive jokes and ridiculous situations carried the limit to win the favor of the smallest. A humor that has times is excessive and that at times he can talk the talk of the rest of the film, but all in all is forgiven. The other weak point from my point of view is the design of the robots, which have never been to my liking and always have preferred classical designs. Transformations are fast and quite chaotic with much movement on all sides that does not let you see where everything goes, robots are too nimble and fast for the size they have, and resemble too much between them, to such an extent that it sometimes costs to recognize which is even a Decepticon and what an Autobot. But just assumed this point remains enjoy fights and action, successful and improsionante, and with some scene in slow motion that leaves the mouth open.The music accompanies the film very well and we have since epic melodies, the arrival of the Autobots is superb, with music writing when it comes to the turn of the battles.Transformers is a great movie of action and effects, fun and entertaining despite its defectillos, and above all that can be seen and you can enjoy, not intended to be an americanada as often happens in these productions and has a fast-paced rhythm that barely lapses during his two hours and peak duration, cinema of evasion in its purest form, but that it holds under its own weight.</body>
</review>
