<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="La profecía" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An entertaining film that will delight all those fans to the genre who have not seen the original</summary>
	<body>The hour of the remakes long has begun, and which Apocalypse signals indicate that creativity has been terminated and that it is preferable to pulling titles yesteryear successful to try to stick something and repeat formula now. The "best" of this is that increasingly more remakes of films that do not have or twenty years old. On this occasion, with such significant date 6 of 6 2006, us it comes to screens "Prophecy" with the added title of ubiquitous evil number (666).First this new revision part with disadvantage, that the extraordinary 1976 film directed by Richard Donner, has become an icon and one of the best movies of fear in the history of the cinema. To this must be added the special cast which took the original, captained by Gregory Peck and Lee Remick and featuring Harvey Stephens as Damien. There was never a better chosen child, as anyone who has seen this film will recall the face of bastard who had the "sweet" creature.Another fundamental aspect of this classic is the score composed Jerry Goldsmith, with which he manages to get the willies. So John Moore is placed the habit and try this new version does not fall into hell. The truth is that comparisons are odious and in this case there would be no rival, but to all those viewers who have not seen the first and take "The omen 666" as a new and original film, you will find a worthy product and hook them in his armchair, due to history and some scares that introduces at certain times in history. Liev Schreiber and Julia Stiles are the marriage has to take care of the small Demian, portrayed by Seamus Davey-Fitzpatrick. This trio it must be added to Pete Postlethwaite (in the name of the father) and Mia Farrow as the nanny. The direction of actors is correct to achieving the main goal which is to us what we believe, although the child there are sometimes that just not convincing at all. Since I have spoken of Goldsmith, his "replacement" is Marco Beltrami, composer who became known for the Scream saga, and also meets creating interesting atmosphere, although he occasionally employs the shock, elevating music and giving a blow.I have to say that one aspect that stands out is the artistic direction, continuously emphasizing the colors red, both with insignificant elements and other more explicit as the wine (pours at the scene of the suicide), strawberries come Damien and that leave remains in the mouth before committing an act that we all know, is also used in the nightmares faced by the tormented parents, especially the mother. And finally a detail which although it passes unnoticed seems to me that it is too explicit are forms that have been used to wallpaper a room with Damien, leaving clearly see the silhouettes the sixes by way of ears of wheat.To sum up "The 666 prophecy" is an entertaining film that will delight all those fans to the genre who have not seen the original, (although really lovers of terror will be already viewing the masterpiece of Richard Donner), and for those who did: because one film more, with some interesting moments.</body>
</review>
