<review author="Red Stovall" title="Historia de un crimen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very good movie that does not deserve the little dissemination that is taking. Plugin if you want to see it, because I don't think it lasts in billboard long, especially now that approaching more summer blockbusters.</summary>
	<body>Compare?History of a crime? with?Truman Capote? It is something totally inevitable, as are two projects that were on par, and the two are about the same: the facts that led to Capote to write?-In cold blood?. Even so, why one of these films garnered critical success more important nominations to the Oscars with a well-deserved award for Philip Seymour Hoffman and the other delayed its release, occur almost of surreptitiously, is something which is beyond my understanding. Because?History of a crime? (do ridiculous translation/dubbing of the original:?)(Infamous?) It is superior in many respects to the film by Bennett Miller, that being good, it was a little cold.The argument leads us to see how Truman Capote in full swing of his career, decides to investigate a murder in a small American people, focusing on the consequences that the horrific crime took to the small community, and write everything in a newspaper article. The capture of the assassins, and the possibility that Capote can interview them, led him to decide that he should write a book. Does this book became one of the novels most important and influential of the 20th century, making immortal Capote.?History of a crime? much warmer is that?Truman Capote?, making the central character much closer to the Viewer, to the extent that this greatly sympathizes with him. In this regard, it is cited two elements really prodigious. One is the excellent interpretation of Toby Jones, who it was easier than Hoffman, physically looks more, but just as one is superb, and although it may seem otherwise, it never falls in excess or the histrionics, composing a character full of nuances, and which easily goes from funny thing to moving with astonishing ease. The second element is the humour that pervades throughout the film, in which reference is made to the sexuality of Capote. A humor cleverly inserted into the plot, which never falls in the helpings and it is made with utmost respect, it helps integrate further into history, which quickly become hard to difficult to endure limits in addition to the Viewer. And anyone who has seen the impressive Richard Brooks film?-In cold blood?, know what I mean. Indeed, the comparison with the legendary Brooks film is also inevitable.The film boasts an art direction really exemplary, and a totally accurate vision of American life in the 1950s, with all these parties that were in the houses, in which someone used to be the center of attention. Sensational sequence in which Capote wins the confidence of the people in these parties telling their stories in the world of the celluloid with people like Bogart, Sinatra, Jones or Huston. Detail this is not placed in the story only because Yes, but it is very correctly used to explain other things very well, for example the beginning of Capote relationship with one of the murderers, Perry Smith.A despite the film focuses on the years that capote led him to write?-In cold blood?, we can say that it covers more aspects of his personality, thanks to the shown moments as if it were a documentary about his life, in which several of his friends speak of him, scenes these that could be considered a stumbling block in the narrative, but I personally see very successful that help to understand the character. The same could be said of the relationship established between Capote and Harper Lee (does the writer of?)(Do kill a Mockingbird?), and Capote with Perry Smith. Both are very well displayed and described. The first surprises an extraordinary Sandra Bullock, Yes, Yes, I said extraordinary, highlighting especially in those scenes in the key of documentary. And in the second, which is probably the best of the film: an impressive Daniel Craig coming out here a little makeup. Incredible instant in which interprets a song while he plays the guitar.The rest of important players is totally anecdotal, except Jeff Daniels that plays the policeman who took the case, and also forged a curious friendship with the writer. But both Sigourney Weaver and Isabella Rossellini as Peter Bogdanovich have short interventions. Even the case of Gwyneth Paltrow is still more curious, that only comes out in the credit titles initial, performing a song, time it in which case something unpredictable, unexpected, sensational and unique. A small magical moment that manages to excite as few and that for a server is already one of their favorite moments of the past few years, and which is also cleverly used to learn a little bit more to Capote, while captures the attention of the viewer hooked him until the end.A very good movie that does not deserve the little dissemination that is taking. Plugin if you want to see it, because I don't think it lasts in billboard long, especially now that approaching more summer blockbusters.</body>
</review>
