<review author="Florinda Chic" title="Last Days" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This feeling of a movie I like a posteriori know it is strange, but I do that recommend it. Although patience, armed with eight hours of sleep of rigor and the lemon between teeth mentioned.</summary>
	<body>Candy and Tideland, films on Billboard with drug addicts from through, joins from Friday Last Days. Gus Van Sant makes a film in which a depressed rock singer wanders its unwillingness to live and his distaste a rickety House. An effort for the viewer that should purchased with the entry a lemon to suck during viewing and avoid the cabezada their images and zero action produce.Really when I came out to see Michael Pitt as Kurt Cobain in the days leading up to his death I wanted to recreate Elephant with the filmmaker and his team. However, rested the film because I now like, seems to me that as I've seen a few times in the film it portrays what is vital passivity of an addict and its surroundings.The character of Pitt - that at no time the tape you referred as the singer of Nirvana - a huge pity and it is easy to empathize with him in spite of the obvious distance between him and the rest of mortals. Do wanders, wild…… barely pronounced Word and her? friends? less that they take advantage of him and him depart from a kick when they see him on the floor.This feeling of a movie I like a posteriori know it is strange, but I do that recommend it. Although patience, armed with eight hours of sleep of rigor and the lemon between teeth mentioned. Gus has taken it to be calmly and scripts run with the same Cadence than if the whole team would become tranquimazin.Mr Van Sant has put part of his experience when he became a celebrity among his friends, following the success of Drugstore Cowboy and My own private Idaho - two peliculones. As Cobain bought a house in which is acoplaban all. Jope and this has happened to me and I'm not a star, so in the next, nothing of sofa bed.Special attention to the soundtrack with a song written for the occasion by the blond ephebe protagonist: Death to birth. Also features the track Venus in furs of The Velvet Underground.</body>
</review>
