<review author="JohnTrent" title="Takehis" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A disconcerting film difficult to qualify, but at times very interesting to see and to try to understand. Takeshis is not far, a round film, but may be the last thing that search.</summary>
	<body>It is very difficult to do a review on a movie like this. More difficult is to position in favour or against, although I suppose, within its viewers, you have both thrilled and disappointed or angry. I also have to say, before moving on to give more details about the movie, that that this writes, is not too familiar with Mr Kitano film. Of his facet as director only have seen the right Brother, the very disappointing and boring Zatoichi (Yes, already is that some think that I've become crazy) and now this Takeshis, which seems to be the best option for someone little given to the cinema of this man, precisely because it is a very personal and risky proposal. Even so, despite having several defects in lines general it can be said that he has convinced me, although without excesses. His main mistake, from my point of view, is one in the usually fall films copyright Oriental: the tedium. And it's lack of pace, and the tendency to extend more than enough certain frames, makes that films which could have been much better, staying just within the correct or even sometimes not even that. Takeshis is saved because of their hypnotic in much of the oneiric journey stranger by which the same Kitano, divided in two, makes us go different sensations. Without a genre defined, except the own work of author of a disputed genius of celluloid as well entrenched in the Festival industry, Takeshis is the palpable sign of how film is often the instrument uses its creator to tell us their ideas, joys and frustrations. And that is what is actually about the film before us: altered head of the triumphant Kitano, star of film and enshrined author makes what gives him the win, and the sunken Kitano, emptied, restless by create and be recognized where no is possible, though his character ends up being destructive, because his film for manyIt is impossible. A disconcerting film difficult to qualify, but at times very interesting to see and to try to understand. Takeshis is not far, a round film, but may be the last thing that search.</body>
</review>
