<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Entre mujeres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The staging and narration, although they do not end up being too personal, reach a level that surpasses the telefilm.</summary>
	<body>I do not think that anyone in his life has not seen a telefilm of Antena 3 in the afternoon. I confess that I've done more once, and two. We could say that they are divided into family and "psychological" thrillers or romantic dramas. Among women, I believe that it would have been better still a telefilm than a film to theaters. And why? Well simply because it has all the features of one of these clunkers, but yes, with successful points and convincing performances. If these two aspects was them, include at least I, to the film by newcomer Jon Kasdan list of these telefilms.Already in the beginning, I could distinguish this difference, with that scene of "break-up" with a beautiful Elena Anaya (only intervenes in this short sequence and a few flash-backs where just that kissing). This scene is well shot and the dialogue is minimally well. But is from there when things begin to roll. The chicho becomes the absolute protagonist and travels to his grandmother's House to change of scenery. There he meets two women: a mother and daughter (two charming Meg Ryan and Kirsten Stewart). And I guess the writer also falls into the temptation of knowing other techniques and leave that you balance the script. Here is where it shows that inseguirdad in set containing the film and this lack of narrative force. Also note that sometimes you don't know if you're watching a drama, a comedy or a romantic movie. I think that one of its most serious failures is not finding what genre belongs. Between women can qualify for irregular, insecure and lack of personality, but we can also say that it is a film, at times, quite well narrated and some interpretations, not excellent, but notable. So I will go to the grain and you comment on what seemed to me better.As I say, the staging and storytelling, although they do not end up being, in some moments, too personal, reach a level that surpasses the telefilm. Examples of good planning would be the two scenes of kisses (the rain with Ryan and the night with Stewart). Both get a convincing emotion and that the truth is it is appreciated, because many other films do not succeed. And finally, speaking of the actors. Adam Brody, the protagonist (many I have seen in the O.C. series), plays its role properly, without more. It offers what we want, a performance nothing surreal nor pedantic. But what stands out, at least for me, is the appearance of the already not so young Kirsten Stewart, in a role that you take affection thanks to a really successful interpretation. Meg Ryan, I guess it passed through there, is the "key" role of the love story, though he is only appreciated his appearance by having not seen for years, because its interpretation is nothing out of this world. And it is rare that in a type of film and actions come to be the best of all.In short, we have a film failed, generally speaking, albeit with a few correct interpretations that make us look a bit in memory (for the next two hours out of the film, obviously). Still, it is too irregular and on almost every occasion lacks personality. If you have not seen, do not need that you lose time. Not disappoint you, but it will not like you. It is, simply, sosa.</body>
</review>
