<review author="Albert Puyuelo" title="Last Days" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Last Days is nothing to explain something that would have been able to say in a short film. And would have been very nice, but an hour and a half watching Michael Pitt strolling is far too long to not ask yourself if you are kidding.</summary>
	<body>True fans of Nirvana may be happy with this movie, but it won't be the same with the young poperos who have only purchased merchandising on Kurt Cobain. In one of his songs, the artist read as follows: "I am so happy." I found my friends. "They are in my head?" and then continued "do and I'm not afraid, I turn on my candles, stunned, because I have found God?". There has been much of the new film by Gus Van Sant saying that it was not a biopic to use. And it is true, gender, but Last Days adapts perfectly the spirit of his famous protagonist. We have before us a small biography of the last days of a myth of the music. Even so, do not expect to find Nirvana songs or a review of its glorious moments.Last Days is the interpretation that Van Sant has made which led to the singer-songwriter to commit suicide. Following the narrative structure used in Elephant, history suggests the viewer looking at her in different ways. They are explained over and over again the same facts that change depending on how you look. The center of the story is a young boy named Blake, that emulates a Kurt Cobain that goes throughout the film spinning through gardens and forests, or sleeping in the first place that while Mumbles some unintelligible words. His solitude and his inner pain not understood from what Blake we can explain or teach, that is not much, if not through the secondary characters and their interrelation with the singer. The overall pace of the film is fairly constant, and too slow. The amount of information that gives us each sequence is minimal, and becomes a little difficult to follow the proposal. It is impossible to sympathize or hate a series of characters that do nothing. Gus Van Sant has innovated not formally respect to Elephant, and in Last Days is nothing to explain something that would have been able to say in a short film. And would have been very nice, but an hour and a half watching Michael Pitt strolling is far too long to not ask yourself if you are kidding.</body>
</review>
