<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Historia de un crimen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If they already saw in his day Truman Capote, not give them laziness facing this new vision. A parallel vision but with very different elements. Do not miss. Neither better nor worse than its predecessor: simply a brilliant film.</summary>
	<body>The film world is sometimes funny, not to say absurd. Years and years without approaching ever a bizarre figure of the defunct Truman Capote for which, with one blow and with little more than one year apart, have released a couple of titles that, apart from having the writer as a character, discusses the process of construction of A blood cold, one of the best regarded as works of contemporary literature and was taken to the big screen, by Richard Brooks.A in the late 1960s and masterfully, regret that the production of the two films was almost parallel, the first to arrive was Truman Capote, an excellent recreation of that phase of the writer why, Philip Seymour Hoffman, would get the Oscar for best actor because of his unforgettable creation. Just last Friday premiered history of a crime, the pathetic Spanish translation of Infamous, a much more subtle title and that, moreover, in its attractive opening credits, allows its director Douglas McGrath, a curious chanza with the aforementioned word that by removing one of its consonants, manages a witty portrait on the bipolarity of the character of Truman Capote. So, I Famous (famous Yo), with the emergence of the "n", then becomes InFamous (infamous).The comparison between the two films is inevitable since both indisputable way, looking for the same, although the treatment and final intentions are quite different. The two depart from the same fact: the discovery by Capote, a story in the New York Times, which reported the brutal murder of a family of farmers, and the fascination it awoke in the writer. While Truman Capote was quite cold and distant with his characters, a crime story seems to clothe them much more, at the time its Director wields his courage courage to draw the writer as a being somewhat Manichaean, individualistic and ill with arrogance. His relationship with one of the two accused to the crime - who was interrogated to obtain personal data for its novel, clearly demonstrates such a description, since it scales between attraction and falsehood.But where the film better moves in two very specific aspects and which, in general, dominates a tone of comedy may remember, on many occasions, in the style of humor used by Woody Allen in similar situations. First is the satirical way of presenting to the snobbish intelligentsia of New York in the 1960s, a group of elitist pedants quibble, in their own way and in his universe, were not more than a circle of porteras chafardeando in a hairdressing salon. And, secondly, in the humorous game perpetrated by Douglas McGrath with the presence of a type as unique as Truman Capote in the middle of the small enclave of this America deep in which occurred the bloody crime; an America not just understand the mode and the gestures of the writer and who, in his eyes, turns into a kind of Martian just arrived from another planet.History of a crime is an elegant, witty, funny and crude; very crude. A perfectly orchestrated product that, by its treatment becomes a wonderful complement of Truman Capote, its predecessor title, and in which English Toby Jones, giving life to the renowned American novelist, has nothing to envy to the November Seymour Hoffman. Personally, I would say that Jones emphasizes less exaggerated gestures of the character and is physically, even rather similar to the real. And there, next to this man often and, at times, both infamous, is she: a Sandra Bullock able to accept new challenges in your career and bring them forward with high note. Giving life to Nelle Harper Lee, author of to kill a Mockingbird and intimate friend of Capote, the Bullock is surprising and overwhelming, and atypical work, just giving an intimate dimension to a woman that, ultimately, was the only person able to understand the ambitions of the writer and the obsession of this by creating a new type of journalism.If they already saw in his day Truman Capote, not give them laziness facing this new vision. A view parallel but with very different elements and that, above all, escarba in the creative and psychological difficulty of an author for wanting to always overcome his earlier work. A perfect congregation between comedy and melodrama in which, at the same time, it can recover the presence, among others, actors of the stature of Sigourney Weaver, Isabella Rosellini, Jeff Daniels or the very James Bond (Daniel Craig), here converted into Perry Smith, one of the two criminals who were sentenced to the death penalty.Do not miss. Neither better nor worse than its predecessor: simply a brilliant film.</body>
</review>
