<review author="Hartigan" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nevertheless, the product is. Classic gags are still his grace and there are some that another worth to be repeated.</summary>
	<body>The responsibilities of married life have come to the quiet world of Shrek, for whom his only concern was to have something tasty to put in the mouth and a good pond of mud where take a bath. The sapo-suegro of the most famous ogre of the Kingdom it has died and to Shrek is not forced to find an heir to the throne if you don't want to deal with sceptre and Crown game. Adventure that arises is not so simple, as the said heir is a pardillo teenager who can that you of more headaches that rule the Kingdom of very, very far, so similar to Sunset Bulevard. On the road he will face to charming, determined to occupy a throne that does not correspond, and all his offspring renegade story. But pardillo cousin and the image of a shampoo advertisement will not be the main concern of the ogre, who magically (others call it natural law) is going to be dad. Something that is mournful. Luckily, that can always count on the invaluable help of his two favorite minions, Puss in boots and donkey. And Fiona? Because pregnant women of Shrek, far from staying in Palace making sock while waiting to her amantísimo husband return with the heir gets to guardian of the Kingdom in his absence. That Yes, account with the well-intentioned collaboration of other fairy tale princesses. Read more Rapunzel, Cinderella, sleeping beauty?Under the title of Shrek the third comes the third (forgive the redundancy) adventure of the Green ogre, whom the marriage not has sat as well as expected. And it is that our OGRE has lost part of his spark to make way for a kind of sentimentality that clashes with his appearance. This new chapter in your life is too ñoño to maintain tone thug from its predecessors, although it still has his grace. So much headache if will be a good father to their shoots or sweet eyes that look at Fiona a little break the magic of the anti-tradicional tale that we always wanted to sell. Nevertheless, the product is. Classic gags are still his grace ("better was that inside" is already part of our vocabulary) and there are some that another worth to be repeated. As for the characters, they are the same with some that another incorporation as the princesses of fairy tale or the bad (do Captain Hook, the stepmother?). In conclusion, only make them a recommendation: see the dubbed version. The dubbing of ass by the moreno of Cruz y Raya, far exceeds, Eddie Murphy. No point of comparison. (M. J. TO.)</body>
</review>
