<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Shrek the third is, perhaps, the film most intelligent of the three, because life is not complicated and intended to be what it is: an animated film for the family so that is what happens in large during one hour and a half.</summary>
	<body>We are in summer and reach us all palomiteras blockbusters of the year. The people have no desire to see Russian documentaries nor Polish dramas. People have wanted to have fun, and in a way, I understand. But what happens is that this desire to have fun the producers of such surpluses used to get slice. Examples of this would be year Transformers, Harry Potter 5, Caribbean pirates 3 or Shrek the third. However, I must admit that I crave some of them see them, more than anything because they are very entertaining and very well done. That does not mean that you go to see wonders how history of a crime of which you speak very soon. The case is that the last of these palomiteras movies is a real delight, because it follows the fantastic line of their previous two deliveries.In Shrek the third, so called and not Shrek 3, her could be called as the jewel in the entertainment and fun. And it is that I was not going with the intention of finding me a complicated plot very well thought out, but with very good and hilarious, although not exactly original gags. And that I found. This is a fresh, entertaining and hilarious movie. I, at least, am not asking more. Luckily I found not a boring, pedantic and far-fetched film. Moreover, he preferred to see one thing nothing complicated, but it is very entretnida, which make me think every joke released. Here the jokes may not be more original and strange, but I came to tears of laughter (especially with Merlin, who ate organic things!). In Shrek and Shrek 2 the laughs were more contained, although, of course, movies, not only fun, but also very good. This third perhaps don't have as good script, but I assure you that if you want to pass you big, go to see her, you did not disappoint. Special mention, not only to Merlín, but also to el Gato con botas, which here makes a really fun role and not as tired in the second part.In this third adventure, there are three parallel stories: that of Shrek in search of Arthur with his two colleagues (donkey and the cat); waiting for the return of the OGRE Fiona and the Princesses (Disney?) and then, interrupted by the third story, Prince charming and his evil friends who want to seize of very, very distant. Not expect more complicity which there is. However, these stories are perfectly compinchadas and once they collide, the chaos and the entertainment cause the viewer a feeling of incredible satisfaction. Here the problems are well resolved, with a series of endless and hilarious gags by in the Middle, and once comes the end you're too satisfied of the show that has been to see this marvel of the entertainment and fun.New and hilarious characters appear in Shrek the third: the first to mention (for the second time already) is Merlin, who helps Shrek and his friends to solve a small problem that makes them arriving late to save Fiona. It is curious that I has laughed so much with this character, because he had never done both from the Dori in finding Nemo. I beg that you fijéis in blood teeth of Merlin, due to eating stones, or the sequence in which puts a half romantic half dramatic melody to help Shrek to Arturo console. The problem is that the absent-minded Wizard puts at full speed, which is why not let the OGRE talk with each other it. It's great! Another excellent incorporation is the princesses friendly Fiona, all them a few believed and posh Gothic. With them I had big, seeing as they prepare to fight the Prince charming or when they give Fiona the gifts by her pregnancy, where snow white looks with a phrase (a gift!) really delicious. Personally, the character of Arthur (the core of the journey of Shrek and company) I had not fallen as well as others, but I recognize that it is well done and there, at any time, any kind of creeps nor is pedantic in any of her scenes (do well, perhaps in the Crown a little?). As it is expected, the other characters remain in its most comical line, or are even more fun and not so heavy, as it is the case of the donkey and puss in boots.Another of the strong points are the incredible graphics presents. As well as the first two, the image quality was very good, here is still more, much more. Only start already you're speechless with magnificent resolution images and excellent expressions showing. The staging is also great, but this feature could already see in the other installments. Music, of course, could not be bad, so they have followed on the same line, the introduce songs from artists several and also a soundtrack performed by the always correct Harry Gregson-Williams.No know as the majority of people this film they found, or extremely tired either unnecessary, but I find that, in what could beIt is an entretenidísimo, fun film and nothing pretentious. It is perhaps not so good film quality as the two previous installments, but Shrek is and will remain a myth in the animated film. It has the appropriate duration and gags are introduced in an intelligent manner. Is Shrek the third, perhaps, the film most intelligent of the three, because life is not complicated and intended to be what it is: an animated film for the family so that is what happens in large during one hour and a half. No more. He has energy, it has rhythm, has fun and charming characters. And that is precisely what I wanted to see.</body>
</review>
