<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Días de cine" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A powerful argument for those who criticize the subsidized, subsidized and decadent contemporary Spanish cinema.</summary>
	<body>To many times I do with little faith, I am still of those who try to defend Spanish Cinema of reproof criticisms that normally receives by people that do not even bother to see films before flaying them. Say with little faith, or none, because there are cases in which the task of finding the positive side becomes quite uphill. And believe me when I say that before us today is a clear example of this.Days of the cinema is an aberration that aims to parody the Spanish uncover-era film, and you do through a miscellany of characters which are a copy of brazen, disrespectful and zafia in some of the actual past artistic icons, to which little or nothing have tried to modify in order to avoid a mockery at the end is not offensive because precisely this film isn't more than that which is determined in criticize. A script without wit, blunt dialogues, characters defined with bad taste and little imagination are the dominant notes in this crappy lighting in the light of some of these magnificent grants that the filmmakers in this country charge again of the State, and that it makes them unique workers need not do its work well to collect in a magnificent way. In an era in which the market sends, in which writers, singers, restaurateurs and vendors are subject to the acceptance of the public, these artists do not need the approval of the respectable, because even the private broadcasters are obliged to subsidize them and pay them huge amounts, but not worthy them of his work, which is in many occasions, like this one, shameful.This is noted in the little care has been taken in this production with the details, and that on one occasion even sees the reflection of a microphone in a bar. Although undoubtedly the most flagrant negligence occurs when in one of the scenes the protagonists will walking down a hallway and spend a few posters that advertise a bullfight of José Tomás, El Spain and Finito de Córdoba, who in 1977 (time in which the movie is set), they were children of chest or they were not even born.I don't want to lose or lose more time talking about this garbage, which should have felt embarrassed at having participated Fernando Tejero, Alberto San Juan and Miguel Rellán, actors with a name and a path to their backs.Maybe if buying more to develop quality scripts and less to be in the door of the Congress, in demonstrations, by signing manifest anti PP and appearing in political rallies, Spanish film wouldn't, according to the CIS itself, one of the least appreciated by the citizens of this country.</body>
</review>
