<review author="Monich" title="La profecía" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I left the cinema with the conviction that for a long time did not see a movie as bad as this</summary>
	<body>Just they are 11 and 20 at night and although still missing 40 minutes to the start of the film, Leuzor and I must be in the positions 61 and 62 of the anxious waiting the Avant Premiere of the prophecy, the remake of the classic 1976 blockbuster. But then the only possession demon that seems obvious in the narrow corridor of Cineplanet Alcazar is the novelero spirit with their dose of nostalgia ochentera - as in my case--that encourages eating popcorn waiting for the beginning of the peliculeta of yore more than one, or most.Following the game to the urban legends of 666, journalists are on the hunt for those who want to talk about the end of the world. Several photographers ignite the lights of their cameras and blind to average concurrency. It was the only thing that dazzled me that night, because after almost two hours I left the cinema with the conviction that for a long time did not see a movie as bad as this.To the point: the only thing salvageable: gestito of damn nanny Baylock, coach incanzable of the adorable Damien Thorne in their first wickedness, for the sake of modernity no longer made, for example, with tricycle but with Scooter. With their respectable wrinkles, Mia Farrow has built the face of the "apostate of Satan" nadita resembles the Rosemary from the end of the 60´s that one day bore innocent and victim the son of the devil. It dishonored the poor Roman Polansky to putting it in the roll of film B. The thing is that the former blonde of Woody Allen has the unique performance, say, salvageable.Because the others. Ay, others. Lev Schereiber is miles to match the performance of Gregory Peck in the role of Robert Thorn, the alleged father of Damien. New and sustained earthly stepfather demonstrates his lack of resources at the time of the dramatic progression. There are no shades, everything is flat in the face and the body language and is also unable to convince us in its disjunctive final remove or not the son of the beast.Although a little more successful in the moments of tension, Julia Stiles, who plays Kate Thorn does not arrive or ten per cent of the interpretation of Lee Reemick in the original version.It is assumed that with all the technology available, this could be a Ribbon ready to bristle us hair every second. However the theatrical thrashed too the only thing he did was to make it more predictable than it already was to have better addressed earlier. However, the Artistic Director and photography had their successes to show us scenes and atmospheres cold and surreal moments, as the psychiatric clinic where the Thorn went in search of answers to the incomprehensible conduct of the adorable creature.It was not that expected more than this product, the original becomes, in my opinion a great movie, or a cult movie, but I think that some respect should be to try a new version of those works that somehow stayed in memory of the spectators of the world and are part of the history of the cinema.</body>
</review>
