<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Historia de un crimen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fails to masterpiece, but I assure you that with a couple of well polished details it could be perfectly. Magnificent.</summary>
	<body>Unfortunately I did not see Truman Capote, this acclaimed film directed by Bennett Miller and performed by a November Philip Seymour Hoffman. And, honestly, having now released history of a crime (crime is the translation into the Spanish, because the original title is Infamous - infamous-!) do not think that it would have made me too lack. It is inevitable to compare both films, as they became almost in parallel, although the first premiered before, but like me that have not seen, can not do it, so I shall confine myself to describe you the sensation that has caused me to see the film now, with delay, we can see that the film of Douglas McGrath.Como all know, both films recount the process of creation of the novel in cold blood from the point of view of the controversial Truman Capote. To do this, the writer, upon learning of a terrible news about the murder of a family in a farm, turned to the scene to write it more closely. Although the relationship with one of the murderers lifted a huge controversy in the life of Capote. From what I have seen, in history of a crime not only explores this process of creation, but also the human personality both the writer and the murderer. It is a shocking and very emotional film without being sentimental or tear. It is not cold, and I believe that this is a plus, it appears that Miller Yes it was, but not bad. This is not the typical biópic on a famous writer. Come on, anyone who thinks that better that her not going to see. This is a pure and simple drama about the human race, which explores incredible way, not only the crime that happened, but religions that both Capote and the killer carried out after their very intimate relationship throughout the days. Perhaps this the best part of the film, the dialogues both remain in prison and the last look mutual keep, incredibly accomplished. However, this film, without being choral, presents a wide variety of characters that look especially in the scenes where they explain their relationship with Truman and peculiarities.Say that one of the strengths of this film is its staging and Assembly. Both are harmonized to perfection, acting intelligent and disorderly manner during all the work (many scenes begin to be explained and then abnormally within this type of films are concluídas with another scene without phrases just). It is charming to see history of a crime, not only because it is well narrated and performed, but because it has a taste of extreme delicacy. All, absolutely all the scenes are shot with calculated levels and to not talk about the setting, that would not surprise me that you take an Oscar next year.Secondly, highlight its stellar cast. There is no actor in this film that to realize an even simple interpretation. All are splendid, although, of course, not all appear in equal parts. Special mention to the large Toby Jones as Capote in a perfect, realistic and superb; Daniel Craig, who gives life to the murderer with whom the protagonist has relationships with a brilliance already not so inexplicable; and this time Yes, Sandra Bullock, who makes the best role of her career (not, in Crash not so embroidering, here yes), thing that seemed so impossible. These three actors look incredibly, but as I said, the amount of side appearing not fall short, but they come in their own way, to the expected interpretive level. Sigourney Weaver, Jeff Daniels (all appearances are formidable), Isabella Rossellini, Hope Davis, Juliet Stevenson (pay attention to the phrases which maintains with the Chamber explaining the anecdotes of Capote) and Gwyneth Paltrow in a role that could be considered cameo, but nevertheless makes it awesome (look at the time that cries while singing).Talk about his superb screenplay. There is no time in history of a crime that lack, or not to miss. Everything is in your site, well placed, although sometimes a bit messy, and therefore more elegant. It is a classic air film, because it has many qualities similar to the old films of wealthy people, but it is the structure of the script which MASCAGNI the rest. Thus, due to the excellent work of Douglas McGrath (both of the script as the address) gives this film a different air, a more independent air and nothing commercial, that Yes. There is a huge dramatic capacity and has a narrative strength uncommon, because the scenes not used to be Grand, so the emotion that produces (more contained) has more merit. Attentive, above all, to the dialogues that keep Jones and Craig in the cell. They are really amazing.It is no doubt that the technical section of the film is of first quality. The photography is great, with a few really prodigious close-up and also amazing movements of camera in the tiny cell of Craig. As I said earlier, everything related to the Assembly and the Mise en scène is enviable, to say nothing of music, classic air with songs like the introduction, very touching.A sensational movie in every way capable of thrill at all times and expose the evil and human personalities. Everything in history of a crime has a why, and everything, absolutely everything, is conducted with great skill. I hope that this is one of the candidates for the next Oscars, thing that would not surprise me the least. Fails to masterpiece, but I assure you that with a couple of well polished details it could be perfectly. As I say, great.</body>
</review>
