<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Todo lo demás" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Woody Allen is the master of ephemeral lovers on screen. About love and sex, about the intimate drama of these two drives, it raises one acid and only farcical function. Here stays in half-measures, but above the usual average in many other directors like comedies.</summary>
	<body>Woody Allen is an author of easily exhaustible narrative. Anyone lampamos by celebrate the liturgy of their releases know their material shines rare novelties and the charm lies in the variations on this seemingly narrow inventory exercises the dazzling talent of his genius. Everything else is a new necklace for the same dog, but ladra with new ringers: the couple in crisis, sex as any epic tap, the paranoia of the Jewish conspiracy, humor as livelihood or the psychoanalyst laconic and soon resolved. Tireless, Allen is not moved from his favorite props, Manhattan, and nor relinquish filter his socarronería, his skepticism, his increasingly evident love for the difficult emotional balance that we have humans to go us living in this world rogue. His puzzle of characters is always beautiful, heroic, amplified or minimized according to the tragic or comedic records of his scripts, gadgets of a verbal incontinence test of bored spectators, a huge puzzle of interchangeable parts, tensile and destensadas, amplified or minimized to desirability of the oral epic of his characters.Here an aspiring writer, neurotic, tormented by a poor sex life, meets a girl from proven, dysfunctional promiscuity, nymphomaniac at times, very innocent in the background. Jason Biggs and Christina Ricci embroider his excessive roles while Allen reserves the candy of a formidable character: the sentimental guru traumatized by the fragility of his placid life and fascinated by weapons, likely a post 11-s stress echo, a species of domestic, intimate, immediate emotional adhesions, reasonably hysterical Hero (is Allen) and benefactor of impossible causesand the improbable loves suburban philanthropy. Everything else continues to be a revamped version of Annie Hall that drama-free.It also husbands and women or Manhattan. For the viewer who knows from hearsay of Woody Allen filmography, there is here a natural, affordable, baptism makes no fanfare of the usual neuro of genius, but that drops them, soft, constructing a recitative of memorable phrases, an academic compendium of their topics and, above all, an exercise in moderation waiting to deal with projects of over rising bad milk.</body>
</review>
