<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Memorias de Queens" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hello, my name is credit and I will leave everyone</summary>
	<body>He says an adage that the artist always fable about what lives, or that other whereby if you want to be universal begins speaking in your neighborhood. Rookie Dito Montiel has been the story and in this his first work (runs and signature script), simple and honest, tells us that, himself, him and of his friends, his father, and neighborhood of Queens (named in honour to Queen Catherine of Braganza, wife of Charles II of England), the neighborhood where he grew upwhere he taking with his colleagues, where stealing kisses his girl, where measured his teenage arrogance with Puerto Ricans, but also where he saw die little by little the last lifeboat to leave this neighborhood that began you to stay small, and in which sensed would end or dead or selling drugs. At this his last and stifling summer of 1986 know that part of what that linked you to its roots, it should betray to grow and that sooner or later these roots would remind you who was, who did never be despite living five thousand miles from his family.But memories of Queens, despite its title, is not a story told from the nostalgia (as it is once upon a time in América de Leone) nor is a costumbrist painting in farcical key describing us the ups and downs of its protagonists (so have the family life of the Italian-American of Rockaway Beach? in the neighborhood of Brooklyn - described by Allen in radio days). No, memories of Queens is is the writer who speaks, who reads his story to the Viewer - from the memory of the child returns, after fifteen years of absence, in the skin of a perplexed man narrated? as every modern man, desmemoriado by the sirens of the road, in constant search of his Ithaca - by the news of the serious illness of his father, one who renegara his son after seeing how fleeing to California, the other end of their roots, the other end of everything. Because Queens is the Rodeo, and racial America of maternal plate on the table and street life, raised by immigration. "Why go to China?" There are Chinese in Queens. Why go to Puerto Rico or Italy? "All are in Queens." However, fresh California Sun was by then a symbol of the promised land of opportunities, where America picked up to his caínes wounded by poverty or dreams.Dito tells us, rather, account to itself at the time which passes through the current Queens, shy desmejorado reflection of the proletarian spontaneity of then, and prey to real estate speculation, the large shops in leisure and culture, and the idealized advertising memory of a time that is no longer. London Soho came likewise, going from working class district of pubs, prostitutes and poets without a penny, posh neighborhood where the great art galleries of the capital are located. Credit returns, Yes, and does it so by the chance of a heart attack which was not so unexpected, the heart of the old Monty Patriarch whose heart no longer resists, and whose pride nor refuses to leave the neighborhood even to go to the hospital. There, he must die with their boots on, perpetuate the inheritance, say himself that not nothing happens, there is no nothing that could not stand, despite disastrous in a neighborhood poisoned by apathy, violence and lack of future. "It's hot?." But of course that it is hot, it is summer. "Do tell you, Antonio?" But do not hold a credit, the heat is unbearable in Queens, and dreams of clean beaches, cool breeze and the television dream of a California prosperous, away from provincialism and misery?Memories of Queens reminds a bit of A history of the Bronx, not only by having the nearby Palminteri cast (even was the screenwriter), not only by placing the story in a New York of Italian immigrant neighborhood. No, its ratings are often in the parenting relationship, although if in the De Niro film the father serves as protection against the dangers of the neighborhood, and the seductive gangster Sonny (Palminteri) doubled in second father who discovers the boy what is made the world more sheltered from MOM and dad (as the median Lewis girl is seduced by a tattooed De Niro in Cape fear of Scorsese)do, in memories of Queens father becomes tragic metaphor of a neighbourhood that refuses to lose their identity? as Dito members, who know that they will be betrayed by friends that or die will go from there. And to it, the young credit must grow, widen his eyes beyond Queens. Why usa ticket of return to his Irish friend, filling the brain of musical dreams, that will take you to the beaches of Connie Island first as who travels to a distant country, to a small branch of the California to come?The best: the ellipses in which a teenager Laurie (Melonie Diaz) becomes a beautiful Rosario Dawson left already expected the return of who was his first love after the window of his house.The scene in which returns to the neighborhood and notes amazed how where there was a store of buns now stands an elegant business of go you know what and run by people who are not in the neighborhood.The images of the train, the train that takes us beyond the neighborhood, to other worlds are not this.Agile, everyday, sliding, dialogues like that camera constantly moving after a few characters that roam the streets aimlessly, without future.The character of Antonio, antagonist of Dito, alter ego of Monty, living memory of a neighborhood that spits miseries and resists on foot.The final scene, that silence.</body>
</review>
