<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The talent has given way to the monetary gluttony; appears at times, but does not produce the joy that we had with the other memorable 2 deliveries.</summary>
	<body>The miracle, is not did although neither was foreseeable that an epiphany of butterflies at the mouth of the stomach produce astonishment, which is the first command in the line of text of good cinema. Good film there was the first delivery: irreverence for adult smell, tenderness and good feelings for child membership and an excellent script which intended to snatch the throne of animation for Disney. Box office and critical confirmed the audacity. The Visual findings of yesteryear, the high level of the dialogues and nasty that deconstruction of traditional tales - who to Propp him had seemed a great audacity - does not appear in this third delivery almost anywhere. The "almost" allow Shrek the third's not horrific and leave some welcome: simply does not require much. The inventory of characters has grown, but all are predictable. The first two stories was subversion and irreverence, here is an outrage of burned gags that never bother (is true), but they produce the strange feeling that we are witnessing a blatant mental flatulence whose most manifest purpose is to gouge us Pocket without that, in return, provide us what nostalgia promised, i.e., intelligent eschatology, humorada critique, the happy encounter between adult - in this case, animated - film and the film child, so reviled, so become a commodity, and expendable and insignificant material for so long. It has struck me this wasted time, but I am not disappointed to not recommend. They centred two or three unforgettable scenes to justify the journey. I remember now a simply brilliant: ñoña melody to the Disney who soon is encabrita and hence, without appreciable fracture to the demonic screams of Robert Plant in one of their wild vocal epifanías. Perhaps it is there, in the formidable musical selection - Damian Rice to the Paul McCartney Wings - lies the still hectic charm of this prodigious period of summer sales.</body>
</review>
