<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Entre mujeres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is clear that the intentions are very good, although Daddy Lawrence should give some lessons to his son before embarking on a second title. Surely, everyone would come out winning.</summary>
	<body>Among women is the Opera prima Jon Kasdan, son of the renowned director and screenwriter Lawrence Kasdan; an inconsistent work containing very little of the film his father's wisdom that, in his debut, apart from a topic too trite in other similar titles, shows have very little narrative nerve and certain inability to baste a minimally attractive argument with hook.Under the false guise of cinema, among women is a species of bland movie desktop which tells the awakening to the life of a young writer of 27 years who, abandoned by his girlfriend and tired of working for television by-products of three to the fourth, decides to move away from its usual scope to take refuge, over a long seasonin his grandmother's House, which begins to detonate many memory problems. There, while he devotes part of his time to take care of it, it will start writing the book always ansió and will begin an unequal relationship with the females of the family of the House front: a woman mature, unhappy in his marriage, and his two daughters: a beautiful teenager and a small early.The screenplay, written by the filmmaker himself, opting for a realistic tone, but precipitation and predictability as exhibits, the little entity of its male protagonist (a decaffeinated Adam Brody) and that feeling of empty end that leaves the Viewer, make forget even the perfect performances of an atypical Meg Ryan and an excellent and fun Olympia Dukakis who, giving life to a senile old woman, stands as the best of the stereotyped product.Ultimately, this is a new and failed approach to that air of family and collective disappointment that Sam Mendes reflected a charm, in his magisterial American Beauty. It is clear that the intentions are very good, although Daddy Lawrence should give some lessons to his son before embarking on a second title. Surely, everyone would come out winning.</body>
</review>
