<review author="El mágico" title="Hostel 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hostel 2 part of a terrifying premise and is only dedicated to enhance most frames that do not contribute much either in originality or create the necessary climate for a film of this kind.</summary>
	<body>Eli Roth I tell them, I do not think a great director, many critics believe that if didn't by friend Quentin Tarantino, not would be filming movies so often giving his fìlmico background is quite poor in terms of resources. "Hostel" in its first version had a good idea but was badly carried into practice. The idea of thinking in small European hostels where gangs of kidnappers capture people to serve on a platter to cynics and assassins with high purchasing power was chilling and very original. Who was not passed by the head that this could be true? That is the only point in favour of the two productions of Roth: depart from a brutally possible concept. From then on, as the director the weapon, is something else. In principle, this "Hostel 2", three American students in Rome choose a weekend where with one of his bandmates art trip. They are young, adventurous, uninhibited and wanting to try new experiences. The young woman (not named the actors because they are more than illustrious unknown and none has a future in the industry) is also conducting a "exotic getaway" and invites them to accompany her to a place where you can relax and forget the stress of the city. But there you will discover that there is an organization in the shadows is responsible for pricing their lives and provide the physical space for millionaires to navigate to massacre. Film values? Few, blood, a lot! Very, very strong scenes, viewers of weak stomachs, abstain! And a dull, listless, pace that barely reaches logic adrenaline levels when the deaths begin to occur. There are many unnecessary scene (the end, with the theme of football, for example ball) and little capacity to be original in the treatment of resources that the general idea of the story suggests. As I have already said, "Hostel 2" part of a terrifying premise and is only dedicated to enhance most frames that do not contribute much either in originality or create the necessary climate for a film of this kind (the black humor of Roth is weak and poor). To be honest, as an old friend of mine said, is only a film more "to soak the sandwich".I mean I? Loose part and we will wait to improve in the third, they say that the third is the expired not?the seasoned Viewer.</body>
</review>
