<review author="El mágico" title="28 semanas después" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not stop falling into the clichés of the genre, that Yes, but takes its time to go armando a line of narration that reaches the climax at the time just and showing at all times as attractive in its conception.</summary>
	<body>The continuation of "28 days later", which became known in Argentina as extermination, was really expected within the horror genre fans. Here already does not direct Danny Boyle but produces and has invited Juan Carlos Fresnadillo to put hand to its original creation. This director is known for an excellent movie I do not remember that it has premiered here, "Unbroken", and the truth is that it was a good choice to lead behind the camera. "28 weeks later" starts then six months after the virus has ravaged Britain. The United States Army declares that the war against infection has been won, and that the reconstruction of the country can begin. The script follows a parallel route between the images that describe as it was resolving the issue of the virus on British soil and the return of a first wave of refugees to the philosophic London post-epidemia. There is a subject, Don, Robert Carlyle in a solid work, who in a confusing situation to open the movie abandons his wife at the mercy of zombies during the first outbreak that we already know. After his escape, Don will receive their children, who are abroad and returning to District One, which is the security zone free from infection in London in which he is a character with almost unlimited freedom of access. Well, there is the meeting of a family which was separated by the terrible events that took place then, but one of its members carries, without being conscious, a terrible secret, we can anticipate little but you will know before you enter the room that the virus had not yet disappeared completely and this time, it is even more dangerous. The screenplay written by the same Fresnadillo with Rowan Joffe (who comes from American TV and is relatively newbie on this) is very well structured. Not stop falling into the clichés of the genre, that Yes, but takes its time to go armando a line of narration that reaches the climax at the time just and showing at all times as attractive in its conception. There are zombies, marines, deaths, mutilations, sangre.todo you expect a fan of the genre. In addition, there is some correct performance of Amanda Walker and Rose Byrne, between side intense, good photography and a care tempo that makes the film just sits in the body. "28 weeks later" is fast, exciting and how much you want to look at the clock already will be the lights and people coming out of the room.Perhaps I expected a more complete job with regard to the displacement of the Group of survivors in London, but I hope the version of the DVD which, like the previous one, will probably have more extras to enjoy. It is a right product, but only for lovers of the genre.</body>
</review>
