<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="La vida de los otros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I wish all films intended to explore human sensitivity were like this. And he explores not only her, but also her it conveys us. A masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>Within my ideals, I achieve perfection is impossible. Florian Henckel von Donnersmark fails with the lives of others, but yes reaches a level of absolute pulidez of contents feelings and of exceptional beauty that, no doubt, deserves a well deserved Oscar. Germany has always been a country where cinema that takes place is rather controversial. There are small wonders of blockbusters, more or less, such as Good bye Lenin!, but I think that if we had noted a European country with the highest level, cinematically speaking, end up opting for France or England. But with this powerful and sensational movie, I don't to think that the film of this country begins to like me more. It is true, too, that many of the most famous German films have tended to opt for political issues (not saying the lives of others to do so, because the espionage here is a pure and simple backdrop), most of them located in the fall of the Berlin wall or the time of Nazism (behold the)(, considerably recent sinking). Yet and so, I acknowledge that I have not seen enough movies belonging to Germany as to compare or judge if they are better than those of other countries.I do not think, or rather, do not agree with those who call cinema in its purest form, for example, the Lord of the rings. It will be visually speaking, but I believe that to reach the Summit of the best film you have to explore many more aspects. Donnersmark film, by ponero another example, yes would reach this totalism. And it is that it is really difficult to talk about the life of others focusing on a single point. The good thing about this film is that everything is perfectly done, everything is absolutely dazzling. And this is what they have the masterpieces. I, unlike some, who think that this is an overrated film (very few, that is also true), believe that this powerful mental exercise, this metaphor on human decisions and the distinction between good and bad, is honestly, masterful. In addition, not only it is directed by this, so far unknown, Florian Henckel von Donnersmark, but also written. Perhaps not coincidiis with me, but is that the cinema is always deeper, more creative and, above all, more staff. Yes, there will be directors who do not write their scripts and are authentic teachers, but I at least see Unlike them those who are authors. Author cinema is more risky, perhaps simpler and less spectacular and, finally, I've noticed that many times is the best thing that previously did not so clear. But I am not going to be child. I recognize that there are infindad of filmmakers who directed and not write his films that are, without doubt, overflowing creativity (I am not going to give examples, there are too many). What is clear, and let shift me, is that the lives of others belongs to this type of cinema, risky, difficult, concise, graph, apparent simplicity and very, very deep. And is that you one of these strong points (which are all, rather) of those who spoke about the film is Florian Henckel von Donnersmark, creator of a disturbing, atrapadora, realistic and together formidable atmosphere.The lives of others is a necessary film, a kind of the secret life of words without hope as the main theme, a relationship between two people, albeit here without touching, between two worlds, though here, one of them empty and another not so much. It is this envy, that fear of loneliness and that fear of losing more dear, rather than you hope. And not only necessary, it is also very intelligent. A film like this has to be addressed with awareness and knowledge, not only with regard to policy, also about the human feelings of deeper. Here presence that feeling be living what happens on the screen, are these two terrible and atrapadoras stories which keep you in tension during these 135 minutes, and not political frames (which are well easy to understand). The connection between parallel lives, behind that, already old, backdrop which are, in this case, these political intrigues, yes it is difficult to understand at all, and is not that the film presents a structure to the Arriaga, but maintains strong classical approach, knot and outcome composition, but this complexity of the personalities of each and their intentions that make the lives of others is a film so extremely deep. As I mentioned before, what predominates here are contendias emotions. You sometimes do not know if what is happening is as desired by the / actors. It is this containment, to no less pride, which makes you delve that perverse inner world of the protagonist and the private lives of the pair of artists, spied on at the same time for the professional spy and by us.It could be the end of this movie as a teacher. Belongs to that kind of late that are absolutely round, without being grandiose, above all. Those in which you have to stand to think in an instant, not because of the speed with which advances the matter, but with extreme difficulty to which the characters are subjected. I desvelaré any detail about what happens, but I assure you that you quedaréis people, especially that no physical contact with these emotions so contained and expressive at the same time, this discovery of the terrible facts occurred. And attentive, especially to the situation and final phrase, a little gem that rounds out this masterpiece.Also be considered brutal entregadísimas interpretations of the cast. It would be unfair to not start by Ulrich Mühe, the protagonist and spy for the work. His performance is indescribable, or rather, so superb that it seems to be real. It is certainly a terrifying character, without a penalty own life that manages to arouse their feelings watching the lives of others. And not only exemplified us with the aesthetics of your floor, also with the most chilling expressions shows to hear the couple's intimate scenes or the aforementioned end. It is not only the central character of the film, that referred to the goodness and the apparent naivety, but it also puts more difficult entregación, because with a few words penalties conveys what is transmitted, and, that certainly deserves a long applause. Although I will not mention also wonderful interpretations of Sebastian Koch and Martina Gedeck, two completely different characters, however, joined by the complexity of the feelings and pain. They simulate that apparent perfect, Bohemian couple where everything goes well and that in fact, both need outside help. He who really needs is support and does not wish to, in any way the solitude. She, on the other hand, wants to ending his terrifying (at least for her) life, wants to, once and for all, stop feeling that pressure inside (also present, in some way, therein) and you don't want more lies, but not lying. Without doubt, this trio of characters, to which more complex, is perfectly which develops the story, because without them it would not be anything. It is as I said, this is a movie where everything stands out and every aspect needs the support of others, since all of them which are brighter.A unforgettable movie in all its senses, exciting and at the same time contained. Sensitive and atrapadora, terrifying and human, contained and no grandstanding. Her final, absolutely masterful and emotional (not corny), reminds us that this is an absolute masterpiece of modern cinema. I wish all films intended to explore human sensitivity were like this. And he explores not only her, but also her it conveys us. A masterpiece.</body>
</review>
