<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Taxidermia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It blasfema puerca, vulgar, indecent, pornographic, taxidermy is agency this string sound epithets and even lampa by any noisy yet. Under the offal there is no bad film, there are no evils Arts: what sinks, and how, the props, the lewd showcase of animaladas of majaderías of tronado.</summary>
	<body>If just write that taxidermy is one of the strangest films who has borne him this 2007 you would be doing a great favor because the fact of the strangeness is not always in the Viewer, sometimes rendered adhesions and conceived the film authentic as a tour de force of news that finger you of lethargy that you have led hundreds of normal films (say) exempt from anything truly amazing and designed with own asepsis of a Pulcher surgeon using the scalpel with majestic choreography without specifying any improvised movement I uneasiness to the hypothetical public attending your function.Taxidermy is strange because exhibits ways of strange, i.e. of different, from avenible to escoradas circumstances of the norm, but in addition taxidermy is grotesque and also unpleasant. I do not know if the script hidden in the mind of the pertrechador of this monstrosity (György Pálfi) was impossible to translate to images without the integrity of our stomach was called into question. Bad taste, the crass eschatology, the painful feeling that the human being, basically, is a viscerally primitive animal van gripping the patience of the viewer until the vomiting, in anticipation of mental anguish, principia arcades in the vocal cords. The Hungary portrayed through the vital adventures of three family member (grandfather, father and son) is the decadent story of a miserable country, slowly phagocytosed by the charms of capitalism that demonstrates the rigors of a grey communism not giving to the people any incentive to cope with a postwar dignified, noble and well fed. All this comes to talk about this work awarded in various festivals (this was one of the causes that it moved my interest, cursed is the hour) that, taken together, could be saved by the risky visual concept that handled its pyrotechnic architects, by its deliberate aberration, which is resolved without shame and oscillates between pornographic (penises in ardent delivery) and unequivocally gore (the final part of the tape is not recommended for sensitive souls).Go to the Dantesque for staging the deflagration moral and social devastation of a country eaten by Communist paranoia can be a point of view among many, but not the only one. Taxidermy spends all his heavy narrative machinery in the strength of a disarmingly complex images because there are moments in which one is raised (with seriousness, without prejudice) leave the room or consider the show as an exercise in masochism goer whereas equal to forge the spirit and Taming all the taboos that we have been keeping well inside since thewell little ones dad Disney inoculated his terrible poison in our natural way of seeing the world.This summer, ambitious as few, shameless and stacked their excrementicias prowess, will have her addicted audience, his barque of amply plentiful souls of value and meaning of the art. I lack that sense: left it in some chapters of Salò and the 120 days of Sodom by the poet Passolini or some titles of pure and simple gore I've had luck or misfortune of getting into vein (la mentirosa Holocaust canibal or calving gamberras of the toxic factory of Herz and Kaufman in his delusional Troma).Nothing remains to the beautiful adventure of imagine, everything is violently thrown into our pupils awarded, because finally, the certainty that over time (or as already we do him) taxidermy will become one of those tapes of worship that they promote lit moviegoers speeches and give rise to regular outbursts of fascination and of collective hypnosis which many movies "cult" inevitably seek to their faithful membership. More freakie Jack Fisk of head borradora cast in a film by Jose Luis Garci, taxidermy, their troubled way, no longer a scathing criticism to the conventions of a strangulated country's close Communist policy and which is the removed uprooted all capacity of Jubilee. That, I think, is the most cultured substrate of this indecent whirlwind of characters open channel for artistic reasons or to kill straws, not exaggerating, or to vomit a galore at the time that between push and push reason the deeper nature of love and its Candida Symphony of colors. It blasfema puerca, vulgar, indecent, pornographic, taxidermy is agency this string sound epithets and even lampa by any noisy yet. Under the offal there is no bad film, there are no evils Arts: what sinks, and how, the props, the lewd showcase of animaladas of majaderías of tronado.Very delicately sustained by its unique charm (exacerbated tremendismo, scatological passion, recidivism irreverence) taxidermy it is a rare bird in our bulletin board and will be a rare bird greater, more sad and harsh in his silence, on the shelves of the patriotic videoclubs. Oh, I forgot: your pass even on tiptoe by Cannes awakens my astonishment.The curious fact is that the production company which finances this tragicomedy of sputum, semen and pseudointelectuales farts is called. Fortissimo. Do not, please, faint-hearted and sensitive.</body>
</review>
