<review author="Bloody Will" title="28 semanas después" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do this film contains all the elements to become a classic, and no doubt enter the annals of? sequels very at the height of his original?.</summary>
	<body>What careful we already in the aftermath. It seems as if this year were cursed and every second or third installment which premiered in theaters is a direct kick to the stomach and a clear turning point to avoid future sequels. What illusion, how much time has passed to say:? is 28 weeks later?!!! It is the cane!Juan Carlos Fresnadillo disembarks in the USA after a single film?Intact?, he left a very good taste and a very peculiar form of roll film. Do do these ways, hobbies and customs are reflected in full in? 28 weeks later?, which together with a well done script, an unbearable tension and many, many media, make the very best I've seen in recent months, let alone the best zombies movie for years.The question always: better or worse than? 28 days later?. Man, Danny Boyle, who started this deadly virus, has a very characteristic style and the previous delivery was very British. Fresnadillo has eliminated that as slow pace and that environment so a the Mad Max to turn London into a land ravaged, apocalyptic and now, razed to the ground, all this in more rhythmic form and course, racing and a spectacular soundtrack. It is entertaining and all enjoyment that passes as a sigh, two characteristics that antojaban impossible in this summer.Six months after the events recounted in the first, the American army has taken London and narrows areas where going to be repopulated the city. The city reach Andy and Scarlet (Rose Byrne), the sons of Don (Robert Carlyle), which have lived the tragedy of the appearance of the virus. Not to say that everything will start, but you will have to find out how.Do this film contains all the elements to become a classic, and no doubt enter the annals of? sequels very at the height of his original?. The initial 15 minutes are impressive tension and already it lays groundwork for what you see throughout the remaining minutes, it is action to not stop. A series of fireworks that has nothing to envy to the catastrophic blockbusters put the icing on the cake. Hair-raising me were when Don starts the race chased by a few undead. Is the scene of?Intact? through the trees, improved 100%.Terror puts it the darkness, the hopelessness of the inhabitants of London, the unexpected leader of the zombies, and the anguish that anytime someone will bite and voila!, are lost. Without having a minimum current gore fan, the few viscera and mutilation that appear in the film fit perfectly with what is counting at that time. This means that it is not used the blood for free, something that is simple but little respected in the current movies.A second flawless Act and a final of those that you are engraved in the memory put Fresnadillo in the crosshairs of terror of quality and I am secure that he will not go unnoticed in the USA. Carlyle is perfect. Rose Byrne is incredible and the kid, an irresponsible of volume and pork loin with Madrid shirt, has one more than successful debut.But everything has a fault, and here is very clear: the camera. Do do I remember that a few months ago we hang a preview of the film saying something like that? the action scenes were shot with a camera on top of a dog?. True at all. Sometimes much movement is sickening, and in key scenes would be welcome if the director put on a tripod, or a crane, or something other than the steady-cam to taste better what happens? but more gives me, I repeat? do 28 weeks later?!!! It is the cane!"Come, fill the cinemas for so mustios with so much tedious trilogy, to enjoy with the zombies made in Fresnadillo and patiently wait for the DVD edition of the Assembly of the director, this has to be born!"$·&/***.</body>
</review>
