<review author="Bruji" title="La vida de los otros" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We we have a practically perfect development, that part of one of the last decades more intelligent approach to lead in an impeccable direction of actors.</summary>
	<body>Fifteen minute. Scarcity of production, poor art direction, photography of dubious quality, excessive recuperated planes, absence in the synchronization of the Assembly, predictable initial dialogues. With these components, eighty percent of American films are sentenced. German films still has not spoken his last word."Clumsy devise" leads us to a conclusion so shocking as desperate, a friend who lacks answers and a situation that begins to be nearby. In the end, "what does an author if it cannot write?." Same as a projectionist without film, that a Miller without wheat. "There's nothing". In how many times is formularían this question many Spanish writers in 1936?. On the other hand, is how he felt Luis Rosales?.A point of inflection, and the work, according to the compositional procedure of the piece of music that praises, accentuating the existing contrast between exposure of technical factors and the development of the script, faces a trajectory of ascending evolution culminating in the film jewel as we know it.It is likely that Lenin had to leave to hear the Apasionata, number 23 of Beethoven to be able to complete the revolution. It is certain that the sonata Gabriel Yared engaged in a good man manages to tear down the walls of incomprehension, the stronger we are able to build human beings of thought.From this moment, the directorial debut of Florian Henckel Von Donnersmarck radiates a supernatural magnetism that envelops the Viewer, supersedes the prejudices that could survive against European cinema, the less commercial, and satisfies the critical sense. The shortage of production is justified. Do the pale picture in which the sky is never blue and the painful art direction? often chaotic - which comes from the wing this history are not offset by an excellent script, they are relegated to a background of intentionally, deprived of any attractive element that seeks to undermine the role to the account, which can distract from the plot. It is then when the Assembly demonstrates its consistency and can be seen clearly notable printed narrative rhythm based plot, in which the most accurate predictions is diluted.We are, therefore, to a practically perfect development, that part of one of the last decades more intelligent approach to lead in an impeccable direction of actors.The impressive bet casting is based on a curious and cash triangle. The insecure and easily impressionable character of the Martha delicious, Martina Gedeck. The almost British phlegm of the impassive German conformist, so well portrays Sebastian Koch on the character that both recalls which interpreted Ralph Fiennes in the faithful gardener. The penetrating and indecipherable gaze of the captain of the Stasi to the life-giving Ulrich Mühe, actor fetish of Michael Haneke, worthy successor of the best dramatic records of Anthony Hopkins.Esta film is positioned within the emerging German film of recent years, placing his debutant film director in that quarry of Directors than with exquisite precision has managed to confront its history. We should not forget the audacity of the sinking of Oliver Hirschbiegel, who, in the year 2004, dared to treat the figure of the Führer from a human perspective. Not the look nostalgic that throws Wolfgang Becker in Good Bye Lenin!. Now the news reaching US from the "democratic" Germany, dated just twenty years ago, and that they seem science fiction, so far away from the adventures filled with Western supporters that we met in 1966 due to the Rasgada curtain of Hitchcock.Tres essential titles that obey a common denominator, the ability of their filmmakers to incorporate the public sharingmaking us participants, direct witnesses of the facts which are narrated. An important lesson about how has to tell a story.Obviously, Hollywood rewards it. Its peculiar and always tendentious approach not repaired in the impressive work of the main actor in the majestic direction, nor on the quality of his original screenplay, but recognizes it as a whole, perhaps due to not only film. Is possible that also by the longing for the old days, those that still had a tangible enemy of easy location. In any case, black lists, the search of delatores confidants, espionage and the marginalization of the possible subversive foci, not them are unknown.</body>
</review>
