<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="28 semanas después" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>28 Weeks after is nothing more than another failed and unnecessary sequel, whose argument seems sometimes joke, and has no feet or head.</summary>
	<body>There are some films which by themselves can revitalize all a genre film, or at least a whole subgenre. This is what did Danny Boyle with the movies from zombies, or undead, with its 28 days later. Not only provoked a flurry of new works which remained in his line, but that it reached the Acme, to give rise to the hilarious parody of Zombies Party.Y with these ingredients, which had to add a great success of critics and the public, is mascaba in the environment the appearance of a sequel. 28 Weeks after is an atypical part, because not to repeat neither the director nor the survivors of the original cast. Six months after the rage virus has destroyed the United Kingdom, NATO begins its reconstruction, and laying down the first refugees in Central London. Among them is a family which was separate from the crisis, and one of its members in hiding a dangerous secret. To bring to fruition the company chose the Canary filmmaker Juan Carlos Fresnadillo, winning a Goya Award for intact, and nominated for the Academy Award for best short film. From the first scene jumps to the eye, never better said, that this sequel is not recommended for sensitive stomachs, that it is even more gruesome, violent and bloody than its predecessor. The script it has more lakes than the region of Ruidera, and as shown here is the sequence in which Robert Carlyle seeks to Mary McCormack in a facility of maximum security military. Not to mention some elements, giving more than fear real attacks of laughter. In fact, the plot can be summarized in the following sentence, which must be interpreted with the maximum, sarcasm and recochineo: "do come children, Dad loves you give a hug?". Fresnadillo you will notice the almost six years of inactivity, it has lost the domain of film language that characterized him in his earlier work, and offers a monotonous direction, with a listless and weary rhythm. Of the actors, they are only saved from burning Robert Carlyle and Rose Byrne, but that takes the cake is the repellent child, Mackintosh Muggleton; undoubtedly, a large majority of viewers will want his character a fateful and tragic final.28 weeks after is just another failed and unnecessary sequel, whose argument seems sometimes joke, and has no feet or head. Worst of all is that now we can start preparing, if the box office does not prevent, for a third installment, in a display of originality will be called probably 28 months after.</body>
</review>
