<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Café solo... o con ellas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Only coffee? or with them is simple and simply pathetic crappy filling by the nephew of Agustín Díaz Yanes. If this is the type of films like viewers, it is completely normal that that same audience not likes the Spanish cinema in general.</summary>
	<body>Still suffering the effects of the already famous survey which said that more than half of Spaniards do not like Spanish cinema. Something so has a myriad of interpretations, analysis and opinion, but does no more than say a great truth, whether we like it or, disagree or not. There are people who think that Spanish Cinema just the same kind of movies over and over again, crazy comedies and dramas intimist and boring. Coffee Solo Debuts to corroborate the theory of these people? or with them, who coincidentally won the audience award in the Festival de Málaga Cine Spanish past. An award which last year obtained the remarkable Un Franco, 14 Pesetas, Carlos Iglesias. Given that thinking, eh?.This raises interesting reflections, because if don't like most of the Spanish film, and it is believed that always do the same, why are they always the same type of movies that more box office collect? Perhaps the problem is more basic, and is that in general the vast majority of spectators attending the rooms go for quick consumption and palomiteros consumer products that for the rest of proposals, be they Spanish, European, American or Asian. Always there are Honorable exceptions, some proposals interesting, fresh or original thanks to the word of mouth out well left of the struggle at the box office. Having said all this, those who are reading these lines must think who subscribes to them has become crazy or something of the sort. No, what happens is that it is much more interesting to write about these philosophical digressions that about the coffee Solo film? or with them. There is nothing good that can be said about such crappy, unless they hopefully will become a taquillazo, which will encourage their investors to repeat in other productions. It is not even honest with the public to whom it is directed, that does not end if the typical juvenile comedy descerebrada, but it has an important romantic background which will cause numerous desertions. It goes without saying that the script, absolutely infamous, it is full of jokes profanity and bad taste are not above the slightest grace. At any time of the tape is reached even to outline a glimmer of a smile, but is to laugh at the absurdity that vomit projectors on the screen.Only coffee? or with them is simple and simply pathetic crappy filling by the nephew of Agustín Díaz Yanes. If this is the type of films like viewers, it is completely normal that that same audience not likes the Spanish cinema in general.</body>
</review>
