<review author="Noa" title="Los amantes del círculo polar" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A love story to slow fire, a tale of coincidences of circles, eyes.</summary>
	<body>Back in the year 1998, Julio Medem premiered his fourth film as director, the lovers of the Arctic circle. He confessed to have included many autobiographical references in the story, and also confessed the depression suffered at the end of filming, after their total involvement in the project. I think that he corrected it with happy end of "Sex and Lucia". Symbols, colors and music by Alberto Iglesias are the main signs of identity of the personal universe of Medem.Cuando film a movie radiates charm and I love deeply, do not leave me the written words. Something that describes this melancholy film is difficult to explain. I shall start with Gonzalo f. Berridi, responsible for the photography. It hard to think how managed so the coldness of the images fit like a puzzle in the love story of Anne and Otto. It certainly worked, as a deep sleep where there is nothing warmer than love, the rest is cold, fragile and intangible. Here we also see as Medem rescues the mother of Otto of the icy weather. The story is sublime. A life full of coincidences or perhaps a default destination. The protagonists are responsible for telling the same story according to their points of view, making the script in an almost poetic delight, and at times shocking. Some will see it too corny, maybe, for tastes nothing is written.There are so many things that they fascinate me the film I can not stay with one. Isn't wonderful that phrase of love writes Otto in the paper airplanes? The director did not want her to discover that each envisaged the perfect love phrase. Najwa Nimri is splendid, evocative and mysterious, Fele Martínez may be underneath it but complies to the young actors like (including the son of Julio Médem) which interpret different stages of the couple, Nancho Novo and the rest of the cast. A love story to slow fire, a tale of coincidences of circles, eyes. The destination, Finland, Alberto Iglesias, Najwa Nimri. A history of brave jump out the window, waiting for the chance of his life. Lovers of the Arctic circle or a hypnotic wonder.</body>
</review>
