<review author="Bruji" title="El ilusionista" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without a solid plot, nor even with a brilliant script, manages to baste a narrative structure of flawless consistency, to confer master's degree to the result.</summary>
	<body>Everytime I see Casablanca, I hope peregrina that Ilsa does not rise to that plane. When I recall the tragedy of the lovers of Verona, I imagine a parallel story in which the messages arrive on time and without distortion.Without wishing to alter or mythical scripts question literary classics, it is possible that, at some point, Neil Burger think like me. Like most of the romantics of the world.The illusionist is a romantic thriller that manages to grab the viewer's attention from the first frame for a single reason: it's an excellent production, or what is the same, a film that is well done.On the one hand, we have a footage that, without a solid plot, nor even with a brilliant script, it achieves spinning a narrative structure of flawless consistency, to confer master's degree to the result. The atypical case where, on the basis of a subject premium bland (the original text), gets a product, at least attractive. An important, - attributable to the address - achievement that will not go unnoticed.The secret of this narrative success lies in the use of elements of worship, all of them recurring in film, but always effective when they are used correctly.The story begins with a close-up of the protagonist, which lies in the middle of a show in which the audience participates. And it is here where the lovers of the classic film could get "hooked", because the situation shown, the excitement in the stalls, the ambiance and up the architectural elements of the theatre, recreate the stagings of Alfred Hitchcock's the 39 steps. After the starting point, and within a dysfunctional script that begins with almost the end of the story, it back in time for the details of the life of the great Eisenheim through an attractive flashback with narrative voice-over. About journeys that start with the opening of an objective, which closes when they conclude; forming part of an elegant style we already know by tapes of other genres, to the have been used by François Truffaut and Martin Scorsese.Entre the efforts of the young Wizard, we find the existence of a love forbidden, away from their expectations. And, again, lovers will recall to another virtuoso in the world of show business that reaches an extreme case because, to cause or as a result of a female presence, the great Flamarion, 1945, Anthony Mann.Por elsewhere, there are outstanding technical resources, which include abuse of planes recuperated, in accordance with the plot of mystery; successful Visual effects; surround photography of dark tones, and the sumptuous and cleanliness of its artistic direction. But perhaps the most striking aspect focuses on dream-like environment that manages to create, own tales, present in Tim Burton's Sleepy Hollow and Coppola.No Dracula in vain, this production is based on a story by Steven Millhauser. In fact, a simplistic Chronicle that, at times, recalls the tragic fate of the son of the Empress Elisabeth of Austria-Hungary and, at the last moment, leaves transcend a moral recoils. Namely: when the desire to impart justice in a world lacking it loses the meaning, is room for revenge, an attitude ignoble and disproportionate in the case that it concerns us, it leads to the conclusion that the postman always calls twice, and the second, does so with more originality. Finally, to narrate the outcome, is uses the best adaptations of the novels of the Queen of crime, Sydney Lumet, John Guillermin, with a profusion, confusion and diffusion of explanations? under my point of view - absolutely unnecessary.Within the distribution, it is necessary to underline the excellent interpretation of Paul Giamatti (the new Richard Dreyfuss), who jumps from story tale (comes from the water boy), to Excel among their peers; Rufus Sewell acceptable; a Jessica Biel and room for improvement.Regardless of the arguments, which are intended to convince the reader that this is a good film-(realmente,_lo_es), I look at the possibility of that not missing those who fall into a deep hypnotic trance, which you not wake up until the lights of the room being lit. If this were to happen, it would be a proof that Edward Norton is not only a great actor?(is it really?), but also the real Ilusionista.En any case, well is enthusiasm, disappointment or indifference what this story provoked, do not forget to follow the advice that gave his witness of position at 1,957 Billy Wilder: "Please strongly not having the end".</body>
</review>
