<review author="Bruji" title="La dalia negra" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite being a blockbuster in 2006, the Black Dahlia is an impressive sample of the black film of the 1940s.</summary>
	<body>Despite being a blockbuster in 2006, the Black Dahlia is an imposing example of the black film of the 1940s; a film genre par excellence, which owes its name to an invention of the critics of Cahiers du Cinema. In this film, meet some of the best elements of the Brian De Palma film, although the worst mistake of the filmmaker is also incurred: starting from a bright idea to achieve outstanding development, and top it off with an ending that doesn't convince, far removed from the mastery of English genius of suspense, often chased by who signs this tape.All those people who, after the first viewing, get set an exact mental outline of the full plot of this movie, enjoy, from this moment and forever, my admiration. I it would be reassured to know that James Ellroy wrote some chapters in a State of drunkenness, as he confessed to having made Raymond Chandler in the sleep eternal, but I'm content to think that there is dirty in the approach, impossible to tie cabos, deception, or simply a basic component inherent in film noir: the complexity of their arguments.Do effectively, we are faced with a stream of ambiguous auxiliary frames, without prior notice, converge in an infinite number of first and last names, into a single plot base, the murder of the Short Dalia.Betty? character real would be the reference classic "Holly is it mounted in Hollywood"? fictional - body double in 1984, by the same director. The repeated story of an aspiring actress who is wrong door and enters a world of seedy and not recommended. The life of this character? and all - are described through the dialogues. Essential and impressive conversations that are never uttered at random, and Yes as an essential part of a whole developer.His career shows in white and black, with the projection of its tests of casting, in which the researcher takes the role of "intruder", in the purest style of the window Indiscreta.Su death, the spectator becomes indirect witness, thanks to a stunning flat impossible: no one would have liked being in that his blood-soaked mattress.As the crime fits within the film, are continuous references made to the world of the celluloid. Mentioned on numerous occasions to producer David o. Selznick to Mack Sennett, or resorts to La Dalia blue, starring Veronica Lake, which the novelist feels genuine weakness in history that Curtis Hanson to adapt for the screen: L.A. Confidential. Although perhaps more existing parallels between both arguments, be referred to the traumas that drag their characters. Remember (for example) the role of Russell Crowe, who lost the nerves to the cases of ill treatment delivered to women, and relate it to the role of Aaron Eckhart, who leaves an important case to focus on capturing the murderer of the young actress.The discovery of the corpse, is on display at a spectacular level synthesis, which links the main plot with another important adjacent narration. Both scenes appear in crows as annoying and unwelcome animals in an illustrious nod to the birds. Finally, not to conclude this section dedicated to Betty, without explicit reference to the good work of Mia Kirschner in their interpretation of a bad actress. A curious paradox.Gender experts, say every good film noir movie requires the presence of a woman, without being the protagonist, always marking patterns of action; and here is where comes in the meter-sixty blonde... and how do it!. A camera movement without hover on his back, discusses her from the left side and focuses on the wing of a hat, which rises to pronounce an indifferent hello! with a hoarse voice. Et voilà miss Johansson. More than a great actress, she is a great product that is forged in the moment in which his mother her baptizes with the name of the protagonist of what the wind. A myth that is kept by demonstrations implausible, but effective, as the funeral who said having organized for his annoying of colors. Without any doubt, an indisputable diva, inside and outside the screen, protagonist of "inventions" that already derided master Lubistch be or not Ser.Sin however, the real star (the femmes fatales are always moray eels) is Hilary Swank. Poor rich girl!. Sometimes fragile and unprotected; at times, ruthless and lethal, with a characterization and an acting suspiciously reminiscent of the Italian Alida Valli, to star in the process Paradine 1.947, of how not? Alfred Hitchcock.Dentro of this footage of important technical values, is necessary to draw attention to its installation, key to the best films of De Palma. Nor has lacked an exceptional photography, faithful to the classic chiaroscuro of the genre, constantly oscillating between the shadows lamps and vague. A photograph in which have managed to sneak, very rightly, images captured through blinds or between the handrails of the stairs of the strange family, which looks through a foreboding subjective level...And here I write about the history of a homage to the classic films made in the 21st century. A movie that will enjoy the lovers of this genre, the complexity and the loose. For my taste, too.</body>
</review>
