<review author="Txapulin" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie can be seen quite well and is entertaining, and although it is very difficult to reach the quality of the first film, at least this maintains the level of the second.</summary>
	<body>I criticized the second OGRE anti-establishment became something so in line with the system as a Prince Consort. In it, these things happen in life, such as the death of the King, you have to be the new King. But this time the writers wanted to be consistent with the character and send it us with his friends the donkey and puss in boots to find a new King beyond the seas in order to be happy in his pigsty. Meanwhile, in the absence of King in very very far, Prince charming organizes a revolution with the bad guys of all stories to win power.Well, no one expected that the argument was very very Original, therefore this movie looking for laughter, narrative pace and many references. On the laughs, there are some that are good and others that do not stand out, but it entertains. On the pace, there are a few ups and downs, some scenes where supposedly you have to be descojonando and they do nothing of grace, as fifteen deaths of the King, the encounter with Merlín or the exchange of bodies between the animals. The good thing about this release is still in references to the children's stories of life and its parodic distortion. It's great that convert Camelot into a posh secondary school, or create a kind of A team with the Disney Princesses including transsexual stepsister of Cinderella, sleeping beauty, Rapunzell and a snow white really surprising (his scene in Lady of the Beasts plan is acojonante). The Group of villains of story also has its charms; It's great that hood is part of the villains and the Wolf is good, for example, or that some of the snow white dwarfs are also among the bad guys. There is no loose characters that stand out, instead, as it highlighted the cat with boots in the second, here the characters individually are neglected, perhaps because we tried to do too much.The movie can be seen quite well and is entertaining, and although it is very difficult to reach the quality of the first film, at least this maintains the level of the second. By the way, here, as he had in the previous two, we did we expect final surprise after the opening credits and was a disappointment. Concluding, fairly predictable scenes would certainly make that function.PS: For my generation, the film deals with one of the hot topics of the 30: paternity (or better: the lack of paternal feeling), so that some us can feel quite identified: P.</body>
</review>
