<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Mediterráneo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Highly recommended comedy. Playful tale about a group of forgotten Italian soldiers on a small island in the Aegean that took on their own merits the Oscar for best film from non-English speaking in 1991.</summary>
	<body>First months of World War II. A small group of Italian soldiers landed on a small island in the Aegean Sea. Strategic importance: zero, enemies in sight: zero, population: a few children, women and old. This approach was presented in 1991 "Mediterranean", film of Gabriele Salvatores which took the Oscar for best film of non-English speaking.Unknown to the general public, this Italian comedy has its strength in simplicity. The argument is simple: forgotten by his own army, held incommunicado and without a goal clear, several soldiers with very different personalities must adapt to the quiet life of the island to find a way to return to Italy. So they spend three years, during which adapt to the quiet of the villagers beat and customs until that are finally presented with the opportunity to return. However, for some of them the life in the middle of the Aegean has marked a before and after.With this simple story Salvatores entertains us for an hour and a half recreating in the pequñeces of every day in the desvariaciones of soldiers somewhat bizarre, something crazy, with strengths and weaknesses very marked. Highlights the character of Sergeant, played masterfully by Diego Abatantuono, as soon as summarizing everything on "is a bitch", as shown understanding and peacemaker to the everyday dilemmas. Perhaps what unites us to the Italians have more likely to feel identified with this squad, so to see them satisfied with your four covered needs (sex, football, food and alcohol) one thinks that we would not really acted very different. But I wonder what thought the Anglo-Saxons, so disciplined and responsible, to see the picturesque panorama showing Salvatores. Laughter, is certainly assured but never find the easy joke. they are their characters, with their actions and reactions, who end up forcing you to have you.It has been said that this film was overrated at the time. It may be. Perhaps its potential is untapped and indeed, despite that I liked, I recognize that it leaves something hanging stories and never just delve into anything in a particular way. Anyway I think is a highly recommended film that also leaves an interesting reflection on the loneliness of the human being, love, and the nonsense about the war in the last minutes. And, of course, leaves us also beautiful images of landscapes to remember. who could miss some time on an island as well!</body>
</review>
