<review author="Silvia Giner" title="28 semanas después" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film does not give Truce to the Viewer, keeps you on guard absolutely all the footage and also causing a sense of prolonged anxiety. If you've seen the first and you liked, this new installment is going to freak out and if not her dresses, go to see this worthwhile.</summary>
	<body>Juan Carlos Fresnadillo was out of his own skin directing this film to the surprise of those who think that second parts "were never good" and to the delight of those they already vibrated once visionando Intacto.Para those who have no knowledge of who is Fresnadillo, recall: screenwriter and film director Spanish born December 5, 1967 in Santa Cruz de Tenerife. Among his major works are the short film Esposados 1996, candidate for the Academy of Hollywood, and unbroken 2001, film that gets the Goya Award for best novel director. In 2002 he made, together with Alejandro Jodorowsky short Psicotaxi.Hay to say, unbroken is undoubtedly one of films intended to become a cult object, it is a film of few resources technical and low budget yet absolutely round and great. The same applies to "28 weeks after", it is an absolutely round movie and there is certainly a difference "28 days after" (the first installment of what appears to be a saga) tremendous.I went to see the film animated by the fact that Juan Carlos headed, but I found more than I expected. The film does not give Truce to the Viewer, keeps you on guard absolutely all the footage and also causing a sense of prolonged anxiety. If you've seen the first and you liked, this new installment is going to freak out and if not her dresses, go to see this worthwhile.Banda Sonora of Linkin Park, fabulous and as usual in my reviews, I will talk about the physical details of the actors. At last! I find a good detail in a movie, finally something realistic and it is the following detail: Las eyebrows without wax Rose Byrne (Scarlett) and is that this girl who plays a doctor of the army, takes a completely neglected eyebrows, full of "Puyones" and hairs to grow. And why?, because because a doctor under such circumstances, would never be concerned about its appearance, i.e. wax eyebrows, them would be totally neglected, with which great detail. (By the way Rose, stop saying that you have 27 years because you have 34 daughter and you note in the face, the age). Mention that the makeup of the movie is great also.To give some defectillos, I would say that there is excessive use of the vibration of the image and some scenes are too obscured (am assuming that is has osucrecido digitally, at least has all the earmarks). The images of the ravaged City are impressive.Finish my criticism, mentioning that you I platónicamente in love with Fresnadillo, that face pachón dog, these green ojillos, lost, saying "Protect me", in the end this guy is a talent, a shoo-in for the infumable cinema Spanish, who should invest in diamonds in the rough as this guy, rather than go happily dividing the impoverished budget allocated to the cinema, to the buddy and sucking outside years we directors.Lords of the Government, want more Fresnadillo, more Sánchez Arévalo, more Amenabar, the church more and less "since the sun rises like". damn.Fresniiiii, Fresniiii I Love You! (You will already see as this guy is going to give that talk, let me fall the breva to work with the one day).</body>
</review>
