<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="El juicio de Nuremberg" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A palpable demonstration that any item, rugged as it is, can be treated with elegance and serenity., and in which Stanley Kramer directed a cast imprensionante and certainly unique.</summary>
	<body>There are films that are unable to make any impression; others, who impressed when they see; and there is a third small group of films that impact since that reads the cast. And precisely to him belongs the judgement of Nuremberg (winners or losers?). This claim, which might seem exaggerated in principle if not referred to the cast, transforms into logic when names appear as Spencer Tracy, Burt Lancaster, Richard Widmark, Maximilian Schell, Marlene Dietrich, Montgomery Clift and Judy Garland (there is that).The film, which as one can assume tells processes judged the scarce Nazi heads who survived or were arrested after the war, was made in 1961, 16 years after the end of the war, and therefore with a sediment of calm that the pain and anger had not allowed to have before.With some characterizations and some magnificent performances, the film goes beyond the easy criticism to the losers of the war and its atrocities, and delves into the personality and feelings of an ancient German judge who is being judged for his performance during the regime and the war. Interactions with the judge (the unforgettable Spencer Tracy), and this with the character played by Marlene Dietrich, make up a huge quality product and whose extensive footage, arriving in three hours, is passed in a sigh.The delicacy in the account of the facts, treating them firmly but without ruggedness, is no doubt merit Stanley Kramer and Abby Mann, director and screenwriter, respectively.Winners or losers is a film without fanfare technical, not needed by another party, in which the weight of the argument rests on the dialogues, and where once more, have great weight body language and the use of the close-ups and silences.All these virtues made her worthy of several nominations for the Academy, of which two of them fructicaron; one in the person of Maximilian Schell, as best actor for a performance full of force and intensive, and another for best adapted screenplay.A wonder that no one should not see; either for purely cinematic reasons, or by the simple fact of knowing a story that isn't so far away or is as unique as it might seem to the recent generations.</body>
</review>
