<review author="Yul B." title="Transformers" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The amount of CGI effects and history of?Transformers? stirred in me the feeling of seeing a movie without a soul. The art takes it into the visual, but does not transmit anything authentic in its plot. All about topics and clichés that seek the answer always the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>What meaning you dais you the word? entertainment?. Think for a moment.Do if we get us a dictionary of the Royal Academy of the Spanish language, and look for this term, find the following definition:? action and effect of amuse or entertain?. Not to get anything clear, is not it?. Okay, we are still trying.Do do do if you locate the word? entertain?, said the following:? fun, recreate the mood of someone?. This is going to be long, so I abrevio; If we are pulling linguistic meanings we finally reach the concept clear that entertainment is a feeling of pleasure produced by a cause external or internal, perceived through the senses. Come on, that let you with your guy or your girl is entertainment.Thus entering a spiral of never-ending, because moving that definition to the world of the film could be argued emphatically that the same film can clearly produce a distinct sense of fun in one or another Viewer, i.e. may or not to entertain them, according to their personal circumstances, including the age, and their ways of being and thinking.Come on, with this stuff that I'm releasing you mean that my concept of applied entertainment to?Transformers? iba by the following sensitive paths: special effects to cut off breathing + history without topical and moderately intelligent. Which would have made him enter the section of film? good? (excellence is not readily available).And sure that many of you will be agree with me with this requirement, many others will give more importance to the CGI effects that history, and others more to history rather than fireworks.The fact is that, in my opinion, this binomial is has failed. And I start to dissect the filet here.I begin by what everyone called more attention and that most us has sold. I can say with absolute confidence and conviction that this film is the best that has been done to date in CGI effects.The accuracy in the details of the Transformers is impressive. I had never seen as much mastery at recreate a mass of iron with a flexibility without limits and at the same time genuine 100%. Best of all is the presentation of the Autobots, a puntazo the scene of the Hideout in the garden, and an explosion of hallucinates the battle end, which is a visual and sound of mastodónticas proportions orgy.What I would have liked is to delight me pleasantly with those details, not only during the process of transformation, but also in his robotic State, because the gigs that have stuck in ILM has been milk (18 hours to make each frame), and deserved a greater pause in its contemplation. But I understand that if everything had been slower had slowed down the film's gruesome way and would not be a film brand Bay. The scenes to slow and the close-ups of the Transformers at rest are almost all that let us see the Majesty of a job? multimedia? that verges on excellence. Another but is the Bay to move the camera. In other films, you can give the feeling of greater reality but in this case it does lose the approach to both Autobots and Decepticons clash, and the clash of their structures. Sometimes not sure who is on the side of one or the other (except Optimus Prime and Bumbleee whose colors are very characteristic).By the way, according to the press kit they gave us, was consulted over the Internet the Transformers fans on his new design of production for this film, and apparently gave the go-ahead. So that now not be may complain if his metamorphosis is not the original, i.e. If they are transformed into different objects to those who originally were. Except that has consulted 30 creatures forofas nothing else, which would be almost a crime after a hoax.Do and the last but very important: the ability to surprise at these so amazing advances in CGI is lost completely with both promotional trailer? Ripper?.Because I have clear that this is the adjective? Ripper?. The policy? hype? It continues today with the blockbusters has the huge disadvantage that destroys and kills any sense hiperorgásmica that you can feel in front of this show. If not it managed a cinema blog, next thing that would see these films before its release are few trailers that trumped on TV a week before appearing on our billboards because I go? Virgin? to this preview in images of?Transformers? and me meo taste. A pity.And now to the tricky history.I know that I have asked much to Michael Bay; knowing his film would that you have thought beforehand that this filmmaker cares argument which I am fishing. Nothing only just you a fairly sustainable plot for adornala with cliperas, strenuous images to the limit. That style so shabby, but effective at the box office, he has been so far. And sure that with?Transformers? encumbrará you as the master of the acción-ciencia - fiction. With a godfather as Spielberg did not surprise me, they are already doing.The bug that I made is believe me those views that I read somewhere that they claimed emphatically that this film is the best Bay has done in his career. You can do so it, but his style. Do I believe 100% that the history of?Transformers? Yes could have been much more than, it could have been moderately intelligent without being complex. Simplicity does not mean the imbecility.In this film has fallen into the trap of sustaining in a script that has been written seeking the appearance of complexity, with the interlaced bird of frames, but that finally turns to how easy, without risking: the topicazo of the boy half graceful graciosete with scarce economic resources that makes everything possible to get a perrillas to buy a car and have possibility of approaching the chicha unattainable dreams buenorrato which she loves expensive cars and the guys with money that are guaperas but no brains. And in the end her get, after forced clashes with its natural charms (and a bit of action of course).Or to the topicazo of the battalion of marines formed literally by 4 soldiers which seem to 300 when they fight, and with a vomitous American pride (missed the detail of the USA flag). I like the Hollywood cinema but not patriotic.Or also the topicazo of the Cabinet crisis that turns to superespecialistas analysts that leave slips another buenorra egghead and a callus of hacker programs unimaginable to the decipher them themselves signals that any Government specialist has managed to reveal.Is the touch of humor prints Shia LaBeouf to the Ribbon, which is the only one that is worth something in the cast that conforms liberating?Transformers?. I could see it in V.O. and I can confirm that this kid is the perfect successor to friend Harrison Ford in the Jones franchise. Save the movie in the most critical plot moments. Anthony Anderson also left their label.Jon Voight is not credible as Minister of defense in the United States.UU. Rachael Taylor and Megan Fox are two chocolates which lack liquor. Josh Duhamel looked like he was on vacation in the Montesito and was engaged from the face with quick-change robots to relax. And John Tunturro best not say anything, to see if I offended the clowns; one thing is that this film is a humorous touch and another thing is that desmadre with the performance of some.I am sure that the Spanish dub will save from burning more than one of these actors.And after all this tell me what you expect if Bay?. Because a Yes?Transformers? It had been regarded as one of the cinematographic events of this year would be because it is a round film. And, I am sorry to say that it is not.?The wars? or the Indiana Jones saga are round films as for entertainment because they combine to perfection special effects (for its time) with attractive stories, ably developed despite their topics, that keep you with our eyes open each and every one of the minutes that last. That is what I was looking for, taking into account that he spent there the hand of final Spielberg.En, and resuming the binomial that I talked about at the beginning of the criticism, the amount of CGI effects and history of?Do Transformers?, as I have told you, resulting in me feeling to see a film without soul. The art takes it into the visual, but does not transmit anything authentic in its plot. All about topics and clichés that seek the answer always the Viewer. Me not me has entertained enough.Sorry, so can not say that the film is good. Or tell me, when give it something, you look more in the packaging or gift?. What matters in the end is the gift, the other is only dazzling role.Does 90% of viewers in the age between 7 and 17 years old, and some talluditos Strip, fliparán in colors with?Transformers?. It is an exemplary product of the current film in which live: business and more business. Make money with palomiteras films to continue making more palomiteras films, and thus continue to live in this industry. The hopeful in finding something else in?Transformers? knowing that there was enough material to give a distinctive touch, we will stay to tables. We will be enchanted fireworks but always consider that grace lacked to launch them.</body>
</review>
