<review author="Alex Largo" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am among those who praise and those who say that it is nothing out of this world. And it is that, as a film, I expect more. I don't know, I imagined it different. But this has nothing to do with the film to be a product of high quality.</summary>
	<body>When premiered during the month of October "Infiltrators", followed very closely the views of the people on it. Some praised, others said that there was nothing out of this world and others said that it was badly bad. So I decided to wait for to come out on DVD to view it quietly. Everything changed when took 4 Oscars. Best film editing, best adapted screenplay, Best Director and best film. then my curiosity for it grew and grew. Until I saw (ago, already more than one month), and now I speak of it.Cover me in one of the three groups I would say that I am among those who praise and those who say that it is nothing out of this world. And it is that, as a film, I expect more. I don't know, I imagined it different. But this has nothing to do with the film to be a product of high quality.Speaking of his Oscars Best Director is more than deserved. The adapted screenplay, so little can speak, that I have not seen the original film. In Assembly. Yes, it has a good montage, but. I've seen better.And speaking of the Oscar for best film. Since then, no one in their right mind could give it to "The Queen" (7/10). "Babel" (9/10) was not a great bet at the Oscars (look at what happened to "BrokeBack Mountain"). "Little Miss Sunshine" (9/10) was too "ñoña" for some. "Letters from Iwo Jima" (that Parallels have not seen, it was my favorite) did not win by causes unknown (that everyone said she wonders). E "Infiltrators". I do not know. It was a remake, it was highly unlikely that win in this category. But there he was, with 4 of the top Oscars under his arm including the of best film. Although there are some who say that it should not have won why be a remake, to my seems a good choice (but not the best).Let's talk about the film, so, in general. In addition to being full of swearing (feel being so repipi), has some (again, some) actors that make an enviable job.Which looks worse is Matt Damon, and I say that not to say that it would have been better a puppet without joints. The most. "weird" is DiCaprio (which was nominated for the Golden Globe for this role). It is a strange mix between hard, whiner, clown and llorica. The result? A character that there is anything wrong in the movie, but does with the public.Another matter is Mark Wahlberg (nominated for an Oscar), Martin Sheen and Jack Nicholson yVera Farmiga.El first, just nominated. Although the truth, would have nominated (and winning) to Jack Nicholson for his PAPELÓN (Yes, with capital letters), unjustly forgotten role in nominations to the Oscars. Martin Sheen makes a very decent and charismatic role. But that most surprised me to been Vera Farmiga, who composed a very difficult character who eats the screen when it shared with the dull Damon or the "stranger" DiCaprio.Otro noteworthy aspect is the soundtrack work of Howard Shore. But, unfortunately, for the painful montage of sound is drowned at all times.With regard to the work of Scorsese. I would say that. own a genius.</body>
</review>
