<review author="Alex Largo" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>As I said, "The source of life" has a very good script, tells us an idea, with three stories. But the most important of these 3 stories is what you tell us, and tell them us how.</summary>
	<body>Almost that, by chance, I learned that one such film called "The Fountain", of a such Darro Aruofski (that is how he called I before it), was a subject that always caught the attention. Eternal life.This was the case, and, searching, I found the soundtrack (a genuine wonder) and the date of the premiere in Spain: 27/4/07. Sincerely saw the film the day of the premiere, then, you girls wonder: why has taken both to publish criticism?The truth is that for reasons beyond me not I have done until now, a real shame.But that does not matter we now (or never), so. Let's talk about the film.To begin with I would like to express my displeasure at the fact that in a room for 400 people, at a meeting at 6: 30 pm, we were only 10 people. There is who might think that the film is bad (as the criticism says), but I tell you is not, for nothing, bad.You can call it rare, strange, paranoid. but no one in their right mind can say that the film is bad. Even so, critics of Venice were the boots with the film.Nothing further from the truth. "The source of life" can boast of a spotless script, a few actors to carry out their duties more than and with apotheosis special effects and of biblical proportions that have been made with a derisory budget for a film of this kind.It is true that this film is for a select audience, to an audience willing to think, to compare, and to enjoy a film that requires the viewer gets into it to be a film capitalized. And, unfortunately, this is something that the people are not willing to do, the engage that way in a film. Phew. and think at the same time. It is a pity that we have used to sit in the armchair and see.As I said, "The source of life" has a very good script, tells us an idea, with three stories (which although are performed by the same actors), have almost no connection among themselves (except the visions of Tommy by the road to Xibalba tree). But the most important of these 3 stories is what you tell us, and tell them us how. I won't say anything more than the script for not disclosing important data.One of the strengths of the film assets, is the work of its director, Darren Aronofsky. "Inspired" is the word that defines the work of Darren after cameras. Man seen desire and enthusiasm making a film that has sunk into the more honda miseries on box office refers.As I said the actors are great. Now that the distribution top it a fantastic Hugh Jackman and an immeasurable Rachel Weisz, magnificent after winning that well-deserved Oscar for "The faithful gardener".As for the soundtrack. as I said at the time. That's great. And most brilliant even in the film, where it acts as a thread and merged with the images of an enviable way Aronofsky. It is also an essential for special effects accompanying. And both elements give the film a Bíblico-Paranoico air that makes you stay in the armchair of foolishly cinema.To give you an idea, since the first sentence appears on screen (a quote from Genesis), the film served on my what I call "the effect Palau".I am going to explain what this "Bucket effect": imagine someone going, grab a shovel and you loose a host in the face that leaves you lost fools. So that, that you stay as a fool.As I said, the movie leaves you as a fool, is something very curious. It is as if you could not clear the eyes of the screen, as if telling you the movie (a journey to a dying star, death bereavement, the search for the Temple of the tree of life.) you would be turning to you. As if all of this had a sense (the funny thing is that you have, but you have to stop you to think).</body>
</review>
