<review author="Alex Largo" title="Banderas de nuestros padres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although Eastwood made a magnificent job which makes the tape drive is the script, rather than the script, the story. A story that has no claw and becomes something sosa for the Viewer, a story with the same emotion that Eurovision Song Contest.</summary>
	<body>Clint Eastwood is one of the great personalities of the contemporary cinema is more than obvious. By it when it was announced that Eastwood would be the history of the two sides which fought on the island of Iwo - Jima in two films followed the project with great interest.At first, "letters from Iwo-Jima", sister of "Flags of our fathers", was to be released after the Oscars. But someone had the happy (and a priori the most correct) idea of advance premiere of "letters from Iwo-Jima" so that he could compete in this edition of the Oscars.Y apparently seen and read read, "letters from Iwo-Jima" (which I have not seen), exceeds "Flags of our fathers". And the truth is that I think so, that exceed the level of this cannot be anything complicated to Eastwood.Ojo, this does not mean that "Flags of our fathers" is bad, because it isn't.It is true that it is not no masterpiece, but it is not bad. And that I never I have excited too war films (in the strictest sense of the word) dealing with the war of Viet Nam or any war of the Yankees. Why it was not surprising that I was not going to excite this film.Although Eastwood made a magnificent job which makes the tape drive is the script, rather than the script, the story.A story that has no claw and becomes something sosa for the Viewer, a story with the same emotion that Eurovision Song Contest. Although you may have some guilt the Assembly, which, although very correct, does not have the spark needed to produce any feeling in the Viewer.The Mise en scene isn't spectacular (history not asked for more) and the actors do not make any teacher work (something pretty obvious watching the actors template).The only remarkable thing of the film is the direction of Eastwood. And in addition to being the only thing that stands out is that most stands out. Since Eastwood makes what does neither the history nor the actors, gives "grace" to the issue and makes the somewhat enjoyable movie.</body>
</review>
