<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="28 semanas después" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The first ten minutes of tape, when the infected take stormed a hut where a group of survivors takes refuge, are masterful, intense, asphyxiating. Unfortunately, any time the movie is at the height of this first scene.</summary>
	<body>How good (or bad, who knows) zombie film is that it is a very popular genre that entry has more or less guaranteed success. It is ironic, however, that recent tapes of undead fever has its origin in a movie that came out not even mobile corpses. And it is that while 28 days later (2003) exploited all the codes the film popularized the master George Romero, his creatures were not reanimated bodies hungry for human flesh, but humans infected with a rare virus that made them killers irrational, mortíferamente fast and without any notion of piety or intelligence. Its director, Danny Boyle, managed to create a small but effective Legion of fans about his horror indie tape, so a sequel was expected. Well, four years has been slow in coming, and this time 28 weeks later (2007) came wrapped in great expectations. They are justified? Yes and no.In recent months there has been much of this sequel (directed by Juan Carlos Fresnadillo Spanish this time), and even before opening already were many who claimed that it would be superior to the irregular part. Some even have seen him as well. Unfortunately I must associate myself with the opposite view. While it is far from being a bad film, the truth is 28 weeks later is not a tape too remarkable. It is not only better than the first, but even made me wonder if I was not too hard to judge its predecessor, at least without being a great movie, had a unique style, and despite falling in repeated plot references to the then trilogy romeriana, knew offset with a truly original aesthetic (although for the most part was product of its technical limitations). On the other hand, the amateur look of the first part has disappeared in the film Fresnadillo, pointing more towards action and the sample of those details that worked before. but now in big.First the good news: the first ten minutes of tape, when infected take stormed a hut where a group of survivors takes refuge, are masterful, intense, asphyxiating. Unfortunately, any time the movie is at the height of this first scene. On the contrary, once it comes in the fabric of American soldiers taking control of a solo London, tape suffers a considerable downturn. Once the virus springs back between the population and the chaos it seizes the American control zone, we are seeing a repeat of the first part, only to desganados and cansones schemes. Unlike what happened in 28 days later, this time the characters are much less interesting (which makes it more difficult worry about their survival), especially that interprets Robert Carlyle (actor who, ironically, refused to participate in the first part), whose development over the plot is implausible and inexplicable to say enough is enough.What we have between hands is a banalized exploitation of the first film, and while it is true that contains some good time, also shows points too many deaths, too many plot holes, too many turns without explore and, above all, very little interest in "taking the pulse" of their characters. There has been some critics who wanted to see some parallel with the situation of the American soldiers at Iraq in the history, but I frankly do not see this relationship by any side. The presence of the army of the United States see more as a move by the producers of that country to seek the attention of the public house, because the truth is that the nationality of the occupying force is absolutely irrelevant. And is that in the background that is the problem of the entire film: everything is so inconsequential, so irrelevant, so "of manual of style", really, there is nothing to do highlight tape, as it's not its action scenes are actually a calque of its predecessor, as well as other movies like The Crazies (1973), to which reference is made of little disguised form. To make matters worse, the end has little claw, although for very different reasons for the Danny Boyle.Es film a well-made tape, undoubtedly, and worth a viewing, provided it is accepted in advance that we have one of the under the year releases, and not the film (with capital letters) zombies of the 2007.</body>
</review>
