<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Lo que no se ve" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Predictable telefilm dead half die and filmmakers to the Middle form that seeks to empalmados yawns and the feeling that we are taking very seriously the hair. There are monsters of worst artistic brewing, but - I don't know why - the argument might have worked...</summary>
	<body>The supernatural, on film, in literature, has always been easily marketable material. The ghosts of yesteryear, those who were born aureolados from romantic and distressed tirelessly towers, battlements and biting basements, mystery and prophecies, are now vague pop stars, snowmen got by the roller coaster of the box office, that is, to the Cape, the heavenly gate, the eldorado businessmen and productive. The chieftains of the cinem치togr치fica industry are old dogs and know making clunkers with decent wrapper as the case outlined here because what is not seen is an ectopl치smica boring, expensive telefilm with pretensions of tape of cult is seen the g칩tico-menstrual concoction in a thriller Film Institute, a youth Operetta and dead are not bad with little heart girls. The protagonist occupies a very wide spectrum of emotions that never, under any circumstances required by the capricious script, we know what is do what does or does not do, which is to be identical thing. So we could say of the tormented poet of the yuppie Seer who finds a passageway between life and death and runs between the sorna, the stupor and a vague whiff to Sherlock Holmes 5th class.I, I saw Ghost with age you have to see Ghost, understand that this unbearable hodgepodge of impossible love and astral travel comfort the teenage soul, requiring simple metaphysical ardours of modern melodrama not too laden with meaning. However, the film - which seems to be a remake of a Swedish film not distributed around here - is not among the bad ones of the year, but has lacked really little. The perpetrator of this almost-infamy (David S. Goyer) has in its showcase of achievements have written the great script for Batman begins. In his cajoncito of sins is directing Blade Trinity: that rare combination of hits and fatalities could not guarantee that here we were frank luck and we staged a good movie. It is one already very of return of boys tormented, touched by the numen of the beauty and very sophisticated destined to redeem the pecados ajenos with your generosity and wide philanthropy and what is not (The invisible in English) there is one particularly pelmazo, irritating, pain in the ass to a very great extent.</body>
</review>
