<review author="Josini" title="En la cuerda floja (Tightrope)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Through a detective and auto-revelador itinerary, Clint will heal this wound of abandonment and loneliness have produced, and that makes it approximates to the brothels across the line which should not pass a police officer that only looks for answers.</summary>
	<body>Tightrope is the story of a policeman who has discover and arrest a violator and murderous psychopath, however, has the same taste and seems to know him thoroughly. Through a detective and auto-revelador itinerary, Clint will heal this wound of abandonment and loneliness have produced, and that makes it approximates to the brothels across the line which should not pass a police officer that only looks for answers.Clint Eastwood plays a policeman in New Orleans as contradictory as good, gentle and tender with her daughters, a character far from police archetypes that made him famous, very suitable for its qualities interpretative, given to radiating subtle gestures, thoughts and experiences not communicable with words, own of the finest actors.His screenplay is exquisite. It's a script prepared and pampered to the point of contain tracks, symbols and repetitive elements or items that give the movie buff the possibility of intellectual desfrute, which is almost the same of a police thriller.I like because it is one of those movies of the paradigm of genera that perhaps I like most, is that of the police thriller of the eighties, that where the streets of the big city are and will feel as they are hard and coming, where violence restalla and is not hiding, and where sexuality lives contorted. In the paradigm of life without sense of the great American city, the characters of Clint Eastwood, Al Pacino or Charles Bronson have overcome the wounds of their pasts - already too reused in the film Hollywood – which they paralyze them or prevent them from enjoying life and lock them in the sordid world of crime and murder.These classic stories contain women, could not be otherwise, make revitalization archetype of the soul to these tormented characters, the female symbol of women who, for the depressed man, returns to reality, giving resources to deal with it. Because here Genevieve Bujold in the main plot does not help anything, it only hampers, however it is in the relationship you have with Clint where his advice help you not to find the murderer, but to find himself.</body>
</review>
