<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="La noche del cazador" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The only film that led Charles Laughton, and a product in which the nuances and the specific scenes are more important than the whole.</summary>
	<body>Robert Mitchum was without doubt one of the great screen, but perhaps never him has positioned at the height of other peers with similar talent have reached higher levels of popularity and recognition.In the night of the Hunter, she plays an assassin who meets a thief sentenced to death by hanging for murdering two people during the Commission of a theft of $10,000 of the era, who were never found in prison. In its belief that the children of the deceased know the location of the booty, he married the widow to try to get it.Equipped with hard characteristics and optimal characterisation, Mithcum plays the role of a man hypocritical and misleading, while preaching the word of Christ, kills and steals with extreme cruelty, managing director and own actor provide a great credibility to the character, which conveys perfectly the feeling of being a person without any scruples or feelingswith a look empty. The interaction of this evil being with the children of the deceased, generates an intense concern in the spectator, which envisages a confrontation between two forces disproportionate among themselves, which on the other hand could be the incarnation of good and evil, words that incidentally has tattooed on his fists the preacher.The ease with which deceives the world, contrasts with the speed with which the child discovers his true evil intentions. A conception extremely macho life, typical of rural America from the 1950s, is observed throughout the entire film and most of the dialogues.In any case, must not fall into the temptation to take it better than it is by the mere fact of belonging to the classic film, nor because it is performed by one of the greats. It is an entertaining movie, but without more, with several gaps and excessive use of fades and forced scene changes. In addition, nor is, nor by far, the best interpretation of Mitchum, which by necessity to the script should produce with excessive hieratismo, in a role that did not favor his qualities. Laughton was best actor to director, although nobody can deny what the originality in the approach to this film, which while it is being improved, is an undeniable quality.</body>
</review>
