<review author="José A. Peig" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The main flaw of the film lies in its scheme, too discursive and repetitive, raised as a brilliant representation of Japan on the beaches of Iwo Jima, but superfluous drama to the end and all, always comes back on them? tics? without developing a story that can be deployed its complexities.</summary>
	<body>"The need to identify with a flag, with an army representative and defender of the ideals system of life, to reaffirm with a uniform and democracy acts by a group of boys who, much to his regret, makes them prisoners of this network of myths and symbols." "Victims, nothing less, the screeching, despair, manipulation and the hypocrisy of society which lost to his friends on the battlefield, what really cared."These words define part of the spirit of "Flags of our fathers" - and that already published in his day - first installment of the diptych on the war and their meanings, and it complemented with letters from Iwo Jima, a free and personal project of this prodigious called filmmaker Clint Eastwood, could say overly ambitious by claim to be something like this as the final "testament" on the second world war, and on the tragedy of the war itself, by deploying two positions and perspectives: American culture as opposed to the Japanese culture. We talk about two military cultures, with peculiar characteristics each of them patriotic values and the duty of the soldier.The contrast between the two cultures finds its best expression in different attitudes and values: for Americans - go the text to opens the comment-, still being victims of the myths of the war premium first and foremost individualism, friendship and family. The country is the monster that are revered. A tribute of bitter taste, seen through the eyes of Eastwood. Instead, for the Japanese soldiers, the collectivity and the motherland are above any other consideration. My personal beliefs are the beliefs of my country, said at one point the character more representative of the film, in a scene which the Japanese military facing the American aristocracy. We come to mean by this that the diptych of the battle on Iwo Jima contains - among other things of equal or greater calibre - a speech about two cultures, two communities that are organized and face the war holding values and divergent reasons.However, the common factor is predominant ultimately: others suffer the same fear to not return to meet with loved ones, death, loneliness, the raw violence. Eastwood dissects and "naked" to the military of both factions to leave the common to all humanity to become authentic protagonist of the war story. Beyond of divergent cultures, humanity converges in a same pain and same expectations. Thus we believe that they will be valued in the future these two films that have so little enthusiasm aroused to day, without ceasing to be a valuable document on various topics of enormous significance for our time.Little more needs to be said: Eastwood is limited to exhibit - without further or develop with too much, it must be said - the values of the hierarchy in the Japanese military code, the sacrifice and the cold discipline of the kamikazes. The approach to the main characters this free all Manichaeism, and although one can speak of absence of topics - because any, and in addition we seem quite inevitable-, is an intimate approach without sensibleros excesses. Everything is stark reality and strong sample of unavoidable psychological and physical tension inherent in war, supported by superb performances, actually the actors are splendid in their respective roles.Apart from the possible topics, the main flaw of the film lies in its scheme, too discursive and repetitive, raised as a brilliant representation of the drama ran up on the beaches of Iwo Jima, but superfluous to the end and all, always comes back on the same "tics" without developing a story that can be deployed its complexities. That is, it is a narrative too schematic, a mere exhibition without any dynamism, and this is what makes slightly less than "Flags of our fathers", as it introduces the analysis towards a revelation of bitter self-criticism in a circular progression that leads to the reason that justifies all the footage.Here we have a product more "stretched", to lead the buried cards to hide the feelings, the vulnerability incompatible with iron discipline that only pursues a collective goal, to the detriment of the love to the friend, the family, the beloved wife. That underground in the form of hidden letters beneath the Earth, humanity contrasts - but converges - with military uniforms lying on the sand, as we see in the recent levels of "Flags of our fathers". In one case and in the other, what emerges and reveals is the vulnerability and feeling human in the midst of the battle.</body>
</review>
