<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Worse, perhaps, that whole story revolves around characters who do not want to accept a gift that makes them life.</summary>
	<body>There is a scene in which Shrek has give a talk to the young Arthur, so sweet music goes up very high, Shrek goes around angry and discovers that it is a montage of Merlin who is trying to create sound environment. But it is not Merlin, is the director which indicates its own narrative traps because he knows that he goes to a public that is back everything. The public speaks of film with the same terms as a critic, known film resources and complains about the details of the interpretations of the pace. This type of audience are directed films as Shrek with his metalingüistico message. There are fierce wolves, pigs, ginger cookies, dormilonas princesses who only know how to use the trick of sleep to solve their problems, a Congress of bad fairy tales giving vent to his resentment for the role that touches them to do in life. They are not the characters in a story, they are the characters of the famous stories. Shrek collects topics to play with them. Others given back to leave them in evidence, for example, of the OGRE bad and dirty which is ogritos bad and dirty, or Arthur not turns out to be a brave man, but a young loser of the Institute. Puss in boots is a mockery of the sentimentality of the tales, when placed plaintive eyes of minino; the ass is the character that laughs at himself.The three deliveries consist of put us on our guard against the tricks of fairy tales. The end serve to tell a fairy tale now that we have low defenses. "Once it has become clear that viewers are not idiots, and we are tired of the stories always (if possible of what makes competitors of Disney), the good and the bad are faced in a final as in any other story battle.""Shrek the third" adds an interesting element to that battle. And it is that Prince Charming, that we should have translated by Principe Azul and not charming, does not conform to defeat his enemy Shrek. You want to do so in a theatre, in front of an audience, just like Nero needed a fire real for his poem, just as Hamlet which needed to represent the murder of Claudius before Claudius. The theatre within theatre frightened Borges who saw a hole to the infinite. The case of this film seems so elemental as the puppet who ask children where is gone bad, or the canned laughter of the sitcoms. The final battle occurs in a theater to involve the viewer of the film in history following the example of the viewer of the play.It is not the worst that can be said of Shrek. Worse, perhaps, that whole story revolves around characters who do not want to accept a gift that makes them life. Arthur does not want to accept a wreath and Shrek does not want to accept his role as father. I do not know which of the two grieveth me more.</body>
</review>
