<review author="Jose Contreras" title="28 semanas después" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If the public has not applauded it is not the fault of the director, is that he was not advised that in addition to see zombies carníboros was going to need a tissue.</summary>
	<body>"28 days later" Danny Boyle was confesa or not, a film of zombies. The terror consisted of the same characters, which both ansíabamos they escape turned into zombies and suddenly wanted to be destroyed; It was that human feelings, compassion was a weakness, and the army, who had to save the healthy, was a danger.The zombies of Boyle put to test our Christian sensitivity. In his world, only survived the insensitive. Fresnadillo did not want to go further, as, indeed, we were waiting for. He wanted to humanize their monsters, and it has taken a step backwards. The protagonist falls prey to rabies and start hitting the walls. He is no longer with us, it is one of them, but Interestingly, the camera follows him. It is a subjective camera. Do you want Fresnadillo we identify with the patient? Not you quit? Boyle had not made that mistake.The innocents of this version are so afraid of zombies of the army. When the time comes, the soldiers receive the order to kill the human. Fresnadillo points to the objectification of a part of society, of the army, which is so easy to make guilty of anything. But the message of Boyle was much deeper because it pointed to the very essence of the human being. The family of the protagonist carries a genetic variant that is completely consistent surprises at the end, both the humanitarian as the tragedy. Fresnadillo has wanted to put into question the bleak message of survival over the love of neighbor and has wanted to sneak a positive message, as a choir of angels in the middle of the Texas Chainsaw Massacre. If the public has not applauded it is not the fault of the director, is that he was not advised that in addition to see zombies carníboros was going to need a tissue.</body>
</review>
