<review author="Alex Largo" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In general a film of high quality with a good story with a mise en scène that removes the hiccups and excellent work by Zhang after the cameras.</summary>
	<body>When I saw "The curse of the Golden Flower" did not know nor in passing its Director. All knew the film was that it had the participation of Gong Li, Chow Yun Fat, who had held a nomination for the Oscars for best costume and the criticism were divided into two groups: very good and which branded it of desilusionante.For this reason, when I started to see it, my expectations were very few.And precisely for this reason, as the film unfolded, my expectations were crushed by a monster with a speed that left me nailed on the site.And it is that the film has a solid script (which not outstanding), a remarkable work by the director, a few actors who eat the screen with a staging more spectacular (and without digital effects).Let's go by parts.As I said, the work of Yimou Zhang (director) is magnificent and full of enthusiasm (the scene of the guard of the emperor with the strings in the cliff is spectacular), something that is appreciated, that Zhang demonstrates very good taste when it comes to shooting the action scenes. Action scenes than ever are treacly or exaggerated, simply. fine. And it seems rather than fight the characters dance. With highly dangerous sharp objects, but it seems that they dance, that is such harmony of movements that you can not more than stay enthralled watching as they make those impossible stunts with amazing style and grace.The script is good, but not outstanding. The film is based more in the implementation stage and in history to note that in the script. The cast looks extremely good, although they are not her best roles show that they are a few immense players. Especially the two who head the cast, Gong Li (to which we saw not from "Corruption in Miami" and made a magnificent "Memoirs of a Geisha" role) and Chow Yun-Fat (which saw recently with teeth very dirty on a ship in the seas of the Caribbean). Both are very credible and correct action and are perhaps the two actors and two characters who Excel more in history.In the technical field stands out in two areas: in the locker room (amazing) and the (immense) sets. Both shows the hand of the director, which demonstrates a great MIME as regards the Mise en scène, as evidenced in "The House of the Flying Daggers".The soundtrack, although elite and correct, clashes occasionally and can be somewhat pompous.In general a film of high quality with a good story with a mise en scène that removes the hiccups and excellent work by Zhang after the cameras.</body>
</review>
