<review author="Alex Largo" title="Déjà Vu" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Broadly speaking, we can only say that we we have a film with the seal of Bruckheimer, with all the good and bad that entails.</summary>
	<body>Jerry Bruckheimer has always opted for the entertainment, already know, Pirates (the Caribbean), Kings English (King Arthur), terrorists Patriots (the rock). And precisely terrorist Patriots is "Déjà Vu", although here the terrorist doesn't have even half of protagonism that Ed Harris in "the rock".The film begins in an interesting way, with an attack. Although the scene is good, I think they could have done a top job, although, truth, have never had in great esteem to Tony Scott, although that does not mean that the man deserves the wage.Then, all what comes later, almost exclusive subject of Denzel Washington, the eternal police. In fact, the first part of the film, before "Snow white", relies on Denzel so the Viewer does not lose interest in the film and Denzel us once again shows why always police. Because it does superbly.The second part of the movie, everything that comes after that Doug choose to avoid the attack and all deaths, makes the tape off interest. But that for the work of Washington and his co-stars, the tape more earn interest than correct direction of Scott and the script.The end, although it could have given more than itself (the character of the terrorist could have been used better) is good.One of the best things of the tape are the action scenes, which although not brilliant are really entertaining and never become heavy.Perhaps what most plays against the tape is, precisely, Déjà Vu. All this (frankly idiot) explanation of the space time is already taken with Tongs and does not convince anyone. Necessary to make the story fairly credible, although the writers could have been currado something better explanation, but as mine is not physics.Broadly speaking, we can only say that we we have a film with the seal of Bruckheimer, with all the good and bad that entails. Entertainment, nothing more. With the addition of a good cast (with the exception of Adam Goldberg) and an interesting story.</body>
</review>
