<review author="Alex Largo" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although the animation is superior in everything else, Shrek the third stays behind, but very, very back.</summary>
	<body>Shrek. Who does not know this Green ogre who, with the help of his "noble steed" swept the box office around the world in 2001 with a fresh, original and fun Ribbon.As it was expected, came the second part. That, although it was not the first, was a very good sequel which consisted of 2 extremely charismatic characters that hechizaron to the public, with his wand (the great fairy godmother) and the other with their eyes (Puss in boots). And who does not want the thing, became the animated film highest grossing of history.And now, and as you would expect, comes the third part. Third party that should never see the light.Since it was announced that Andrew Adamson left the work of director and that the original writers were leaving, many feared the worst. "And with good reason.""Shrek the third" starts well differently from their predecessors, and only the prologue predicted us changes. changes for the worse.Although the film remains, slightly, the personality of the previous installments, it fails. Where the others were surprised, this is sinking. Why? Because it never ceases to be a rehash of the other two, with a plot worthy of an episode of the Lunnies.Aunque animation is superior in everything else, "Shrek the third stays behind, but very, very back."And perhaps, the major culprit is none other than Arthur, Arti. If "Shrek" (9/10) surprised by its freshness and "Shrek 2" (8/10) is arropaba of good characters to maintain a good argument and a minimum of quality, "Shrek the third" only counts as only new character to Arti. A flat character, without grace, no spark, and primarily responsible for that the film lacks interest.As for the gags. Pretty poor considering worked were in the other two and quite simplistic (attention to the pathetic final play of the Prince), not to say terrible.Not reel me too I can only say that, this year, it is a very bad year for the third parties, I repeat, a very bad year for third parties.</body>
</review>
