<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film animation very entertaining on a green bug fat and rude, but big heart. For all ages, although safe more Sin her they measured better than elders. Recommended.</summary>
	<body>Shrek was a blow of fresh air in the panorama of animation, as a counterpoint to certain lifestyle to create films. A Disney idea of showing drawings animated, focused towards children and the elderly, with jokes for everyone. It was a great hit, of course. This third installment follows as the rest of the series, with the same sense of humor, but with the handicap of the loss of freshness.The film is about a fat and green ogre who has to make himself King of very, very far, given that his father-in-law (a frog) dies. As it does, decides to go looking for Arthur, the next in the line of succession. To all this, Fiona, his wife, is pregnant, causing her a great anxiety. To finish messing, the previous suitor, returns with an army of waste to reconquer the Kingdom.Well, let's see. The movie is funny and entertaining. We can compare it with the previous, but does not seem quite fair. What fault does this good was the first delivery? I personally you made less more tidbits from the previous ones, as the OGRE burping (I'm fan), but certainly not worthy. It is very nice, with great moments and a script without many pretensions, but well spun. There are hilarious moments, some demented, and one incomprehensible of songs that made me clench the teeth of horror. Well, say that it was a critique of the animated musicals so it can fit in my young mind.In short, film animation very entertaining on a green bug fat and rude, but big heart. For all ages, although safe more Sin her they measured better than elders. Recomendable.Besitos.P.D: The dwarf that give you to Fiona is nailed to Rajoy.P.D.2: that you have safe children that you can enjoy all the secretillos that hides the movie (which you will see hundreds of times, obviously).P.D.3: Merlin has a very good point.</body>
</review>
