<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Hostel 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Part II was never good, and this is certainly not an exception. Stolen the surprise of the first, it is something very insubstantial, slow and heavy, that us is out of the boredom with a little of offal. See and that you delete the brain before reaching the parking.</summary>
	<body>After see the first and leave quite disgusted with the poor Eastern to which had sopleteado the face, I said not to see the second part neither of coña. But as you know I have less Word to those who leave in the discussions of the TV, so that I have seen. That Yes, knowing of the three scenes of disgust that I I have wisely covered the face. A guy with the hairs of the eggs canos, being silly in that way. In the end.The film is about a boy who has escaped from a species of field of horrors, where the people are dedicated to pay money for killing people. Well, the two scenes begins to discuss three American kids who are in Rome and want to go to Prague to visit her. In these intersects them in the way a woman with everything very well because it suggests a spa in Slovakia, where they were in a Hostel. Uhhhh, that am.Well, let's see. Fear, what is said fear does not give. It gives much more sopor and boredom, given that the little action that runs very lentita and sparingly. Except approaching the end, the rest is a pestiño. Then there are those who say that this shows us the power of money and not be more. I that I learned. I went in the first, that the idea could be good, but the development is mediocre. And scenes of disgust, there are, but as I was prevented, because I can not say if they did or not. Ah, the end is cut the box to laugh, to tontez.In short, part II was never good, and this is certainly not an exception. Stolen the surprise of the first, it is something very insubstantial, slow and heavy, that us is out of the boredom with a little of offal. See and that you delete the brain before reaching the parking.</body>
</review>
