<review author="Caty" title="Ultravioleta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not only bad of solemnity in its approach, but that, for the first time in my film buff journey I meet a film that, could not tell exactly his synopsis.</summary>
	<body>I thought that I had seen everything. He believed that any film, bad that it were, could make me bring Manus again to the cabeza.pero you see, Madam!, I was wrong from part to part. Ultraviolet is not only bad of solemnity in its approach, but that, for the first time in my film buff journey I am with a film that, dear readers, not could tell exactly his synopsis.They say that it is more easy to talk about a bad film of a buena.pero definitely in my case is not so. I must admit that when I left the cinema he was eager to be able to complain about all of it, but as it has happened other times (by jemplo, when I saw "Timeline"), difficult to talk about something that you have not enjoyed in good absoluto.pero, hairs to the sea and here we go.Ultraviolet, in principle and without having seen anything of her, as a brief trailer is another film of these bleak future due to illness, of wars, of pollution. and I am not going to deny that as a general rule they fascinate me, mostly because they know join social critique of why humanity reaches the moment that comes with a quite interesting action point (we have most excellent examples as Matrix)(, Blade Runner, Equilibrium, the Terminator Saga.) but Ultraviolet has overcome all fear when using these elements in an inappropriate way. Normally, when these two elements not marry perfectly (as in the above examples), always we can stay either with the apocalyptic and moralistic argument or with the well posed action entretenida.en film, the argument simply does not exist, and the action is extremely absurd. In teoría(y_digo_en_teoría_porque_en_la_práxis_difiero_totalmente), the story that exposes us to the Distributor is as follows: at the end of the 21st century comes a group of human beings with a genetic mutation created by a virus. As there are more infected people fear of the Government increases and those infected are treated as to marginalized, they were being subjected to gruesome evidence and put in quarantine. The Government has taken the determination to put an end to them, but a woman with a terrible past is determined to prevent it: beautiful and lethal Violet...And now comes the sound JA! that this servant them delivering in the face to those who have drafted this paragraph. Here comes mine. (Attention: contains details reveladores-si is there something to reveal - the "argument") At the end of the 21st century and without apparent reason there is a new disease in the world who does not know or where has left or what. and people will and spreads. Physicians stand with the power to better control the population. Ultraviolet in theory is one of the "infected", a lady that changes color of hair as Jorge Vestrynge of political party, and that seizes the weapon that can kill humans? You'll end up with the hemófagos?(to know), she leaves a child. Children don't know why awakens in her a maternal feeling and aunt insists, against his companions and his enemies on save him?.The child dies. Appears in the middle of all this a few guys who call themselves "Chinois de Sangre" or quienes(para_qué_explicar_lo,_¿verdad,_señores_guionistas?) we know a bad very bad in the end is that it is also hemófago and the typical hero marginalized semi in love with the character of the Jovovich. The child, in the end, is that he is alive. Do not ask me how. Point and ball.I must admit that when I saw that the director was Kurt Wimmer, the same of the unfairly defenestrada by publishers "Equilibrium" and appearing therein currant William Fitchner as actor secundario(uno_de_mis_favoritos), I thought that maybe I would find something like the famous cult film before named and not distributed in Spain for mysterious reasons. But it is the day Kurt Wimmer accepted roll "it" wasn't very Catholic, of course.Dialogues: topical, empty, devoid of any reasoning or linguistically correct approach. Not even the presence of William Fitchner(actor_fetiche_de_Wimmer) manages to save the muebles.y the truth, with similar script, little can do the actors.Action: as said earlier, grossly absurd. He tired at times due to excess. Is at odds with the argument, it is unpleasant and nothing is beautiful ver(que_ael_menos,_ese_consuelo_nos_quedaría), but that above, computer effects are evil deeds. Badly made. I've seen B-movies with best digital work that Ultraviolet.La music: Repetitiva, tiresome, and a bad shadowing of "Equilibrium". With the difference that here, no sense none or accompanied. At the best of times, it passes unnoticed, in the worst, you overwhelmed. In short, a totally forgettable film in its many facets, a blur in the career of the Jovovich and Wimmer, and a waste of time if you thought have see it.</body>
</review>
