<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Transmorphers" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tremendous Truñaco of a director need of resources and ingenuity, has decided to pull the pull of the original to sneak us this. Only recommend seeing "made" special effects, which are to die of laughter.</summary>
	<body>It was so quiet at home when my friend Benito Trujillo tells me that he has of the Transformers on DVD, that Yes, with subtitles. Very soon seemed to me, still not been released worldwide, but my friend Beni almost never lies. So I I quickly started to see her. Bad begins when I see that they destroy the Earth's atmosphere, and worse when I get the first shot of beam laser, painted with tempera on frame. Bad, bad.The film is an apocalyptic future, where after having contacted the aliens, they annihilated us (like hariamos us, nothing new). After 300 years hidden in the bowels of the Earth, humanity is ready to retake the planet, which is why out of the freezer to a type (round and round microwave). And that will, as you not have the end, just over me has been recorded.This film reminded me a friend who said "I sack me and if suck me it, because what I have won". Time ago I see no peculiar character. These smart people have brought to the shadow of Transformers, this truño of colossal dimensions. If some unsuspecting pica and she swallows it folded as a server. The argument no feet or head, special effects for die and the protagonists lironda monda. As a point, two curious things. On the one hand, that the protagonists are lesbians (nothing of lesbian sex, my readers pajilleros). And the other that when they shoot the shots with a Bic pen are painted (this had already said, but it is deadly and truthful).To sum up, tremendous truñaco of a director lacking resources and ingenuity, has decided to pull the pull of the original to sneak us this. Only recommend seeing "made" special effects, which are to die of laughter.What I could laugh with the worldly effects.Besitos.P.D: The final should be a tribute to Blade Runner, but as if I say that my balls are a homage to the monster of cookies (by the hairy, that everything must explain it).</body>
</review>
