<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Tu la letra, yo la música" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Put the language in a jar of jam and polite viciously glass.</summary>
	<body>Viva harmless film, Strawberry mermalada and Wham melodies: you the lyrics, I music is harmless, off film of all claim to survive or remove any social, political or even aesthetic awareness in the public. It is not that speech in his foundational libretto; It sobreabunda the tedium, one viscous and jingle Christmas machine-gunned a Superficie.Como great invisible speakers all romantic comedy, lacks philosophical pretensions (up Matrix had halo of mystical sandwiched in a tatami infógrafico kung-fu) and does not break any of the many conventions of the genre: triumphs of love while the couple flirts with uncertainty andfor the greater glory of the sweet ferment of all romance, they bypass difficulties that are compensated by a glamorous and apparently ending a long dozen of times and although we have many WINS lend fuel and turn her, the film touches our sensitive heart.Who felt a tremor effervescent in the heart to hearing a pop melody, who has heard in his memory the notes of his song choice at the head in a bus queue at the very moment that you are going to meet in the Delicatessen, this is your film. There will be no disappointment. Hugh Grant is a correct - not the Cary Grant who tried to sell - comedian, an actor cómodoamente installed in a series of dramatic patterns that has internalized with appalling trade. Drew Barrymore is giving away the inconveniences of this melifluo film to then put the hand and his name not to be missed in the tangible warp of the divas that are on track to be. In any case, nothing remarkable in this graciosillo toy, nothing relevant: not intended. The tape passes its legitimate Olympus of frivolity paid to a sentimental Cookbook as predictable as inane and inconsequential. It is not possible to be too rogue to write a few lines which, although they will never/never be laudatory, nor enter fiercely in the flesh, digging in the pure viscus</body>
</review>
