<review author="Bruji" title="Flyboys: héroes del aire" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Technology can never compensate for the failure occurring in a screenplay adaptation</summary>
	<body>While is correct that the great films of dogfights were always filmed by real pilots? and the November Bill Tony is-, nor it is a lie that its stereotyped and bland script, lacking in verisimilitude, to Flyboys becomes an amorphous hybrid between the Pearl Harbor of Michael Bay and the legends of passion of Edward Zwick. An irreparable nonsense, that the away from mythical titles to which could overcome.Do do scary everytime people like Michael Bay or Dean Devlin (producer of Godzilla) determine that? long ago is not a war film?. Do the first, already played to the? chicken? in his particular Pearl Harbor; While in this case, the intention of Devlin was non other than the pay homage to the legendary Lafayette Squadron, one that, with more courage than media, fought the Germans in the first world war. Of course, the result leads to the belief that it is fortunate that no member of the glorious squad can see the film. Let's say that the tribute is lost in the production notes, without reaching transcend to the screen, because of an ill-fated script. What, no doubt?Do c? est an dommage!, I'd say the beautiful Luciana.Con ambitious pretensions, not exempt of goodwill, Flyboys is dedicated to search for references in the classics. Is a significant and worthy fact to deal with the management of the project to a professional driver, as they were the mythical William Wellman, Howard Hawks and Howard Hughes, who left us titles like wings (first film winning an Oscar in the history of the cinema in 1929), the dawn and Los Angeles the hell Squad (widely recreated by Martin Scorsese in the Aviator)respectively. Years later, Welman shot another film with the title of La squad Lafayette. Having Tony Bill after cameras guarantees a technical virtuosity in the airspace that isn't continuity on the Mainland. It is precise to emphasize subjective levels which gives this tape, the choreography that draw the little planes in the air, the close-up of the pilots, both reminiscent of silent film scenes, and the obsession for showing the precariousness of those flying kites that must have been the first aircraft of war, as always did Howard Hawks. The truth is that they yearn more minutes of flight in the footage.On the other hand, it would not be fair to mention important historical advice, apparently, also the work of Bill. ?Knights of the air?, as agreed in calling these bunnies of Indian historians, were the last to show a code of Honor in the heights, in these last medieval tournaments, which are so well reflected in the film. If both aspects, add them the spectacular soundtrack of Trevor Rabin, the perfect photography Henry Braham (only have to remember the reflection of the squadron in the transparent waters of the river), its excellent sound effects, the good work in the interpretation of Martin Henderson, the acceptable art direction; and, in addition, we consider that the air and the aircraft of the first world war never managed to great works of art in film, we realize that this could really be the great tribute that he deserved the squad noble. However, it is not. Technology can never compensate for the bug that occurs in the adaptation of a screenplay, and Flyboys violates the great message which derived of the best war productions, which already enacted Wellman in 1929, which ratified master Kubrick in paths of glory, which issued Lewis Milestone in without quiet on the Western front. ?Nothing does the heroism that involves losing everything by the way?. Instead, we have a modern version light of the facts, to justify participation in any war when you're winning. Thanks to it, are achievable goals that always dreamed. Neither more nor less than what usually happens when a story set in the France of 1917 is transformed into an americanada. Independence Day type.</body>
</review>
