<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Café solo... o con ellas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Malilla, torpona, GLib, simple, empty and another series of adjectives that are never compliment, but that might be more corrosive.</summary>
	<body>Upon entering the film can only be a question: is it as bad as it seems? And to leave only a response: could be worse. Eye! This does not mean, nor much less, be good. It is not even mediocre. But stays in quadrille, torpona, GLib, simple, empty and another series of adjectives that are never compliment, but that might be more corrosive.Of the argument do not need nor speak. Four thirtysomethings looking for its place in the world, and everything naturally revolves around the women. That if I want to marry me, if I have left me, that if I do not like me a rosco, that if I am a flirt but I can't find love. Finally, four situations more views than the comic book, which mingle without grace or art and only from time to time are able to offer some comic situation worthy of a smile.Coffee alone, or with them will be another one of those movies that in two days pass into oblivion. Taking advantage of the fame of a pair of actors in television and the pull of the format "romantic comedy ñoña, but funny, but not so funny or so ñoña" they rush to cinema with the hope that the four bored teenagers and four despistadas couples that teem by the Multiplex is swallowing this monstrosity. It is bad without objections, but not kill boredom. If you have nothing better to do and someone pays you the entry, maybe even you agradezcas any of the four crap that make laugh throughout the film. In fact, if not seek shamelessly easy situations, supposedly emotional or sweet, it would up had some interest. And also would have to change most of the actors, of which only unless the Dumpy. And also the soundtrack, with the stuck to fill 40 hits or so get oldy without coming to story. Well, thinking well, to spare so many things that we should make another movie to give it interest.</body>
</review>
