<review author="José A. Peig" title="Transformers" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Transformers? It is only a circus of special effects and does not comply with some minimum attributes so that it can be a clever commercial product.</summary>
	<body>Often the debate always arises: the problem of putting special effects and noise to the story and characters in a suitable climate dramatic settings. And yet when it's designed films, exclusively, to entertain in the summer months, it is not so important that the narrative is well-structured as the story itself is interesting, innovative, intelligent. Do you realize the reader of how complicated it is to make a good movie?. When no fault structure, fault history, when the story is good, it fails the estructura.¿Transformers? It is only a circus of special effects and does not comply with some minimum attributes so that it can be a clever commercial product.The story: nothing at all. Bad robots, good robots. In the end good ganan.los (ja-ja-ja). But they are also good because Yes, because neither the design nor the characterization of the aliens on sides indicate any antithesis. See what reduces the character of Optimus: do Hello, I am a good robot and I am here to help you if you help me, because humanity deserves to be saved?. And megatrón, yuck, is the reostia: do I am megatrón and I am malisimo, human beings are a few worms.?. It is disgrace.So the story has a soul, or we can also define as can dramatic force?, the characters must occupy a space, this dramatic weight to exijimos in a plot deployment. But happy robots are history, neither story nor argument: are a spectacular and noisy gossip, do many stunts, they metamorphosed with an overwhelming visual display, stick jumps, they shoot, they organize camorras between them how nice.Speaking in silver, do Transformers? This is the version for the summer of 2007 of similar products as do Independence Day?, do Godzilla? or the day of morning?. Or is what is colloquially called a do americanada? without substance, bland, designed according to the popcorn and propaganda: the army always plays a crucial role in the struggle between the human and the external forces that invade us. It is a blatant transposition of the same story, changing the external appearance of the main elements, the writers copied the scheme according to a commercial formula already exploited until the nausea.And a story this, Shia Labeouf, undoubtedly the best of the function (its hysterical humor is priceless), diluted - and with it, the little interest offered by the plot - before the progressive involvement of the military. And I hope to not be expressing me wrong, I'm not saying that the film is bad because the military are not to our liking (we know, here tastes or one) but because the character of Labeouf was who could lead the soul to history, the helpless citizen who suddenly is involved in a transcendent mission. In other words, the uniqueness of the work. Do all this becomes Borage water when, above all in the last third, the film becomes a plagiarism and remake of bad movies as?Independence day? and similar. When is cinema not cinema, but a showcase prefabricated for the less demanding young public.The movie is not boring, record. Do you have good moments of humour, even it would seem that motivates a healthy parody of usages and customs in the current? american way of life?. The pitorreo, in that sense, is constant, and covers even the end credits. Eye patch: is not that the film be taken seriously itself. First and foremost, the film is pitorrea and mocks the Viewer, and especially of lovers of good cinema of adventures, good designed cinema for teenagers, that there have been and, hopefully, it will occur.</body>
</review>
