<review author="Raccord" title="Marnie la ladrona" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After this film he entered a creative slump that already not recovered</summary>
	<body>There seems to be a general rule in the movies, which ensures that with a bad script as a starting point, it is impossible to shoot something good. I agree with the sentence, but it would be "Marnie, the thief" as an exception: a dash of suspense from the lot to the good of Hitchcock behind the camera, turns into something quite interesting. The story is predictable, at times flat, but instead has one (or more) great sexual perversion sub-tramas.The first and most obvious is that the character are Connery, most Pigmalion (or Pretty Woman, which is to be the same), the role of protective galán style really is a child rather than get aroused by someone so far from his world as a ladronzuela. The girl also has a point of sophistication and inaccessibility that probably only do take firewood to the fire of his passion. This explains his behavior throughout the film much better than if there had been a kind of father to her, only willing to put him in life. The second and more hedging is that Marnie does not support men (for reasons that are revealed in the film) and diverts their sexual attentions towards horses. I do not speak of bestiality, but simply that your subconscious is the substitute for sex in horseback riding. And it does not seem to be what Hitchcock intended to hide; do we see it riding horse several times, petting horses, betting at the racetrack? She is obsessed. We then have two protagonists much more interesting by the semi-pervertidos, that even if the plot is a little glib, the subtext gives much of itself.The work of the director is admirable as it could not be otherwise in the case of Hitchcock. It makes a good direction of actors, supported by their sequences planned millimeter giving much quality to the product. A detail that caught me my attention are the brazen double funds, in other films in English are conspicuous by his absence. They should not walk very well of money at that time in the producer. But less good (repeat) is the script. Minor characters from cardboard, very little brilliant dialogues, a couple of deadlocks? They say that after this movie came in a creative slump that already could not recover, but it wasn't bad. It is clear that fails in many things, but it is not much less a bad film, although the shadow of chained or death in the heels is elongated.</body>
</review>
