<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Transformers" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bearable metallurgical Vertigo that will delight many and will be the infernal tostón of others.</summary>
	<body>The mastery of Michael Bay action film can not be taken a joke: has raised an empire in the segment of the entertainment film mode that did Steven Spielberg (who incidentally co-produce the film) based on very precise and unabashedly profitable elements. All are past by the alembic of patriotism (point of American taste) and none lacks a generous helping of impressive, sweeping, syncopated and exultant visual spectacle. There will be no one go to see Transformers and not leave literally noqueado. The overwhelming display of special effects Tomb to the stricter Viewer: one already previously conjurado to boycott any pleasurable sensation received his academic brain, instructed in more depth film, alien to these blockbusters of summer that they dazzle the teenage rock and generate outrageous dividends in box office and a circus of figurines of an apotheosis Burger. If someone wants to sit in a comfortable armchair in a cinema and be contaminated by a spasmodic barque of shocking images, please join the film on the agenda and will not be, in any way, disappointed. Line followed by this fanfare of effects, the thing has its miga of humor, its point of comedy and even a small love story with acne that works with astonishing naturalness. And there are hilarious scenes that persuaded or at least not disgustarán too much (I insist) to the critical acid that already comes with written lines and only hoped that gilipollesco of this type of film discourse confirm that its very agile and trained professional vision had already planned: a desparrame bloating of wonders of computer ahombradas a bland scriptmagro in talent and always too long. I'm in the scene in which the robots of yore come home of the main character in search of an absolutely necessary object for the correct development of the plot. Or some surreal dialogues sidewalk of the goodness of democracy and as a zen method of decontamination intellectual masturbation. The rest: Transformers is an overwhelming film. It must be by the metals. It stretches without and abused what one good accept it like: the choreography of firing savagery, the mass destruction of everything what comes to pass. If we avoid the luxurious pyrotechnic device, we found only faults in the ground, obvious fractures, limitations to prosecute this warehouse of electronic stunts with meridiana objectivity. Very different case would be if the excited Viewer is already properly heated to the event by having been a fan of the series or fine taster of yore in his early years toys. Then Transformers is not only his film: will be your Bible in pasta, its digital catechism, his love of infinite summer. Or all together and greased with oil sidereal that does not lose composure Mystic Assembly of the pieces. It is not that, no, my case.The americanista stench of director undermines the universal interest of history, but golosamente apoltronados in his armchair, adolescents eating popcorn and sorbiedo with DIN soda do not require semiotics or committed the quality of your entertainment with no Professor of history of cinema that seeks to (any) crush action cinema just as action (genre usually ignored in the historiography and sparsely glorified in the usual lists of best films). These kids will spend an unforgettable time. The film should entertain and this makes it in major mode. Is that a roll of film? Roll fat last summer and this summer and another, but some time ago that one film not looks sweep at the box office as you are going to do this. And that is, and that is where Bay and Spielberg (Dreamworks, please) put all its efforts.</body>
</review>
