<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Transformers" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film is undoubtedly one of the musts of 2007. A compulsory step for the film. the pace in Crescendo, paste a small prick 40 minutes before that end up worst then back, notaréis it by miraréis the watch at the time.</summary>
	<body>Michael Bay directed the first sequel of what we plan to be a memorable and historical saga, the sengunda part entitled "Tranformers 2" is scheduled for 2009. And that first delivery gentlemen, absolutely stunning, and it was really difficult do something tufara to movie East of Z series, but good when you have a producer that chracter Spielberg, the thing is not provided. Michael, who has been responsible for the photography of Coyote Ugly and the direction of Armageddon, applied their noble strategies to this spectacular film, but has his stuff. Thus it is that you are obviously going to notice parallels with the films mentioned above, and is that at the end and the safe place that spiritually speaking, shrewd Mr Bay, it was preparing for what will be a seal of quality in his filmography.Transformers boasts the latest in imaging technology and FX with digital processing, so is that you are going to freak out. The storyline is very faithful to what we have seen of children in the famous children's animated series that bears the same name. It is clear that we are following the general tone of Hollywood to film old glories of the comic and TV but as long as the world is full of useless paid a paste for touch 3 times, the thing continue. Anyway I think that this stage we live in cinema was necessary, because the mass public would never know or known the existence of stories as wonderful as Sim City or 300, were it not for this new trend we are going through.This film is undoubtedly one of the musts of 2007. A compulsory step for the film. the pace in Crescendo, paste a small prick 40 minutes before that end up worst then back, notaréis it by miraréis the watch at the time.It has been incredible to see with so much realism to Optimus Prima and his soldiers, the same megratrón &amp; company, brilliant absolutely and dramatic transformations.And now go with the incongruencia:1 - if a casualty has no pulse how can be screaming? or perhaps screams and then it is without pulse? 2 - if all communication systems fail, as balls suddenly work randomly when it suits the storyline? And why the Defense Minister must give 2 times the same absurd order of the shortwave, by God to malo.3 - How can put a head of section 7 as clown like that? the interpretation is dire and the character does not paste anything, seems that it is in another movie, I am sure that is a jewel of Spielberg, is him but gets infantilism by somewhere not far tranquilo.4 - as a guy that is dragged by a 350 m bike to all ostia on the tarmac, when it rises only has a small rupture of the clothes in the fatal codo.puff that detailIt has worn the art and costume.And now, the despelleje: well the despelleje of this criticism is going to carry the plugged Miss, toady, buenaparanada Megan Fox who plays Mikaela Banes. That all the actresses are removed years is already a general tone, removing 3 or 4 years, it's worth. But fuck, remove 7 years. This lerda intended us to believe we have 21 years old just turned, to see Megan daughter, who see you legs of rooster, I do not cheat me, you have a foquito by down all your flat primerprimerísimos to illuminate your face and or so the you hit me with age. In addition to more horrifying skin full of pimples that then you have digitally retouched with a great veil that you have and the indirect lights, but we are back to the same thing, not her das me. You just have to look at the time sunset at the beginning of the movie when you climb into the car with Sam, hence perfectly see you the skin of horror that you have, you had the rule that day? and I'm going to tí pq going great. Collagen of your upper lip focused in 3 rooms front of the lip line "sucks", only thing decent you have is laser whitening. The Loofah hair, not everything is be thin daughter. the forzadísimas faces of situation, you strive to portray the beauty all the time neglecting the naturalness that should have a character with so much action. Anyway, it assumes your 27 years and takes some classes of improvisation. Finally tell you daughter, that you'll be happy pq are going even if your makeup is pathetic (Orange key) you have favored the most in your plans.On the other hand comment when he left the film, had a few young extrahormonados, happily commenting, dialogue was shit. Well well, these guys, I must say, that one must obviously know what kind of movie is going to see when you enter in a film. Obviously in a film like this are not going to find great dialogues that already of itself the comic does not fuck, if you wanted to see deep dialogues are why not you going to see independent film buds? your dialogues that are shit "iyo iyo botellón".in finEn super general terms, I recommend it absolutely.</body>
</review>
