<review author="Taliesin" title="28 semanas después" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you expect Fresnadillo would give a personal touch to the recipe that masterfully prepared five years Danny Boyle, you can already become to the idea that the only thing new you will see is a Real Madrid shirt.</summary>
	<body>You can not go to the cinema with expectations. At times the film is what you expect from it, one in every hundred exceeds those expectations and the vast majority of the times salts of the room with some disappointment. What has happened to me with 28 weeks after, although I admit that it is that is blame mine, because expected me one little more than finally stayed in an outline of something else. I alegaré in my favor that 28 days after already offered a novel approach in a genre that did not have much to contribute, except a bit of bloody entertainment. This, added to the director and screenwriter was Juan Carlos Fresnadillo, responsible for the interesting and at times surreal intact, was predisposed to see something entirely new from the magnificent first delivery.Finally, what we have is more of the same with a twist that would say the English, but more of the same to the end and Cape. Not even appreciate differences in point of view and I almost dare to ensure that appropriations could appear as director Danny Boyle without that nobody suspected otherwise. If anything are some novelties in terms of decoration and abound the close-ups that Fresnadillo seems to feel comfortable. On the other hand, the idea is the same: the man is worse than the own infrectados of anger that, at the end and out, can not resist the disease. And that is not bad, but if at the end the film falls on the topic of the Group of strangers who join forces to flee from a disaster, the main idea is diluted and lost all power. After a very promising start, and half an hour of preparation of a frightening scenario occurs a climax that threatens to make you have a bad time if it stays. Unfortunately, the fall is almost chopped and the second half of the film is a package of clichés with some touches of author, to make it clear that they didn't want to do the same as always. Towards the end, everything is quite predictable and at times excessive.The characters are too blurred (especially the aggregates at the end) and this does not will affect the least both if it eats a sick with anger as if they are with a bullet. In addition, suppose that Robert Carlyle cache should be so high that they have been forced to include it in some scenes in which simply does not look anything. On the other hand, there are characters untapped, as the wife of the protagonist and the American military command, which could have lengthened the first part of the film and delayed the explosion which breaks the delicate balance.Ultimately, expected that Fresnadillo given him a touch of personality to this film and it seems that the only thing that has brought is the shirt of Real Madrid of the child protagonist. I see too much ISM and have the impression that good ideas are accumulated in the boot and are exhausted to middle road to the end, leaving a film without soul. It is true that 28 days after (that I think better than this) desbarra at the end, when they arrive at the military camp, but at least it was a more risky than the of 28 weeks later proposal. At the end I was the sour taste of what could have been and was not, although always can fix it in 28 months after, clear.</body>
</review>
