<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Transformers" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Transformers is an acceptable action film, which despite their flaws will delight lovers of this genre</summary>
	<body>There are some people that are synonymous with success, and in Hollywood nobody discusses the ability to attract the public with both Michael Bay and Steven Spielberg. Both have made some of the greatest campanazos in recent years, and their first collaboration promises to burst the ticket offices of half the world. So confident are the success of Transformers, that even before opening, its sequel is already announced.The Autobots and the Decepticons fought a civil war for millennia, and both groups sought cube, an artifact of unimaginable power. Thousands of years ago, the cube crashed on Earth, and now the only hope for mankind lies in Sam Witwicky (Shia LaBeouf), who holds the key to find the artifact. The oddest thing transformers is that being a film just on the transformers, you forgive the repetition, they have so little prominence therein. The characters of American soldiers, have much more importance and minutes on screen for example. And it is not to create any diplomatic conflict with United States, but film exhales a jingoistic whiff cheap Strip on his back. And we do not want to delve even deeper into the wound, but what a coincidence occurring coincidentally these coincidences, in the majority of countries premiered on July 4, that if someone does not know, is a national holiday in United States. Let's be honest, the script is not exactly a marvel of cinematic prose; It is full of the typical clichés, inconsistencies and crude jokes, typically in an action film, we will. The film takes enough to boot, the first forty minutes aren't but a tedious introduction to some charitable soul had sever in the editing room. It seems as if that first part of the tape outside a mere excuse that Michael Bay recreate in the figure and curves of infarction of Megan Fox. It may be that the type of audience who directed the film was not clear enough. Once they enter in scene the transformers, the panorama changes radically. And it is that Michael Bay you can be criticized for many things, but we must recognize that it is a great director of action stories. While it is true that there are some sequences in which seems to be more aware look flat impossible to carry out a coherent narrative and show to the public in an appropriate way the action that takes place. The transformers are very well made, thanks to an excellent work of the Visual effects team.Transformers is an acceptable action film, which despite their flaws will delight lovers of this genre. The best advice that can be given when watching the new work from Michael Bay is that it should not take very seriously. If not, infuriating startup and continuing failures and inconsistencies of the script traumatize anyone.</body>
</review>
