<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Yo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I is a film that will lift passions among the spectators who see, and offers a good range of questions, reflections and readings that will vary depending on the eye that judges.</summary>
	<body>For several years is fashion the term independent film, which includes all those movies theoretically carried out without the support of the big studios. A so vague but at the same time as inclusive definition which is quite snobbish. And if still entails certain logical talk about United States independent film, talk about Spain independent film is absurd. For there is independence of industry, first there must be the industry as tal. when a film crossing the threshold between originality and innovation and delves into strange and incomprehensible? Perhaps the difference is only situated in a film can win in various film festivals in which to compete. For example, when David Lynch at the Cannes Festival presented his then-latest work, Mulholland Drive, the first question asked in the press conference was but what is Mulholland Drive? The directorial debut of Rafa Cortés, I, has got something similar. It's a really strange story that has no feet or head. But you have been chosen as the Fipresci revelation of the year and be presented at the Cannes Festival, automatically has become a cult film, when previously it did not nor distribution. I will not leave indifferent anybody, there will be spectators to connect immediately with the proposal that raises the film, and them will have that soon they will be asking for the time. Rafa Cortés you cannot be denied their good do as director, and to deal with her debut in the film. Still lacks Polish many aspects, but it creates an atmosphere that surrounds altogether, conveying that feeling of strain and restlessness lives Hans. Nor can say nothing to the impeccable interpretation of Álex Brendemühl, screenwriter as well as protagonist.I is a film that will lift passions among the spectators who see, and offers a good range of questions, reflections and readings that will vary depending on the eye that judges. For some, cult film, for others a real waste of time.</body>
</review>
