<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Suspiros del Corazón" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sighs of the heart part of a good premise that unfortunately not been known shape or develop properly in the film, making it predictable and slightly boring.</summary>
	<body>Currently, a large number of comedies from the Hollywood of the 1940s and 1950s us are really endearing naivety that characterized. Yes, agree, in the majority of cases this ingenuity was part of a major advertising campaign: had to show the American dream without a hint of sordidness, corruption or vice. A clear example is the great sighs Capra.Con heart Frank, Enrique Gabriel intentionally takes the path that marked those classics through a modern utopian fable. Fernando Valbuena Montijos (Roger Coma) is a young and promising businessman who is about to close the best deal of your life, but this disrupts completely when he sees all his horoscope forecasts are met, and goes to his neighbor (Alejandro Awada) in search of Council. Finally, Fernando desperately seek the Publisher of the magazine to get his next horoscope before closing the contract. Enrique Gabriel raises the film as an homage to a photoromance (Idyll publication) magazine that actually existed in the Buenos Aires of the 1950s, as well as some of the people who made it possible. Sighs of the heart has a promising start, but gradually the story loses bellows. It's another example of something very abundant in the film, a good initial idea which has not been able develop or translate into a good film. Enrique Gabriel also you has gone hand in hand with ingenuity, and it has finally become a sticky cake not suitable for diabetics to the tape. It has ups and downs in the pace, and there are some scene than other which can cause embarrassment, as the confrontation between the two old exiled fighters, one Italian and another Spanish. The interpretations are generally correct, but two stand out, unfortunately for different reasons: while Roger Coma is seen forced at all times, to the newcomer Maria Dupláa is seen with ease, making a very natural and fresh interpretation.Sighs of the heart part of a good premise that unfortunately not been known shape or develop properly in the film, making it predictable and slightly boring.</body>
</review>
