<review author="JLO" title="El crimen del padre Amaro" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A small disappointment. By both rejuvenated and now strong new Mexican cinema, and the topic of this film gave for some more.</summary>
	<body>A small disappointment. By both rejuvenated and now strong new Mexican cinema, and the topic of this film gave for some more. Light years from the surprising at the time Amores Perros (Pulp Fiction to the Mexican) with the point of a Gael Garcia Bernal this time too loose or unconvincing in the role of father Amaro, a naive and malleable priest.Corruption within the bosom of the Church and its power (too similar already within the scope of a political party) is known to all (even by the own faithful) here reduced to a simple problem of skirts. Nothing new under the Sun with memories in mind more strong as Camila or El bird sings to death.The problem here is not the script (which in truth not spare you nothing) but the cinematic look, almost without view of depth, as a fact to the light and more like a soap opera that evening at a movie with glimpses of complaint. It tells father Amaro within the church growth and the discovery of things not so sanctas and its subsequent decline, renouncing the celibacy in the hands of a beautiful parishioner. Unrealistic characters in unreal situations, with side barely or poorly outlined. A guerrilla priest, an inept Mayor to say enough is enough, the same Amaro passing of naive to amoral in five minutes. Another example of how free is the character of a humble old man that occurs in the first few minutes, and that briefly reappears towards the end without any apparent justification. Its director, Carlos Carrera seems to take the text of Portuguese Queiroz (1896) too faithfully in its tone, flat and without explosion unless by some isolated scenes (returning to the meaningless) as those of a sick child or a hospital bleeding.Well managed that Yes, the grim aspect of a chapel of the town with its overabundance of images and whiff to business and a pronounced nihilism from beginning to end. Only its non-conformist meaning is the apparent reason for existence of this film. Amen.</body>
</review>
