<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Scary movie 4" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>How can pull themselves together in a single film the arguments of the war of the worlds, Million dollar baby and Saw without that Miss the thread?</summary>
	<body>How can pull themselves together in a single film the arguments of the war of the worlds, Million dollar baby and Saw without that Miss the thread? It is unimportant, because the viewer sees Scary movie does not seek a coherent argument, but a flurry of allusions. Other films include: the curse, the forest, Brokeback mountain. And two moments of television: the interview of Tom Cruise, and the scene of Bush reading a story in a nursery while attacking the twin towers. And, by the way, there is an allusion to the blogs.David Zucker is a veteran of film parody. He made his debut with his brother Jerry Zucker (Ghost) and Jim Abrahams in "Lands as you can" and repeated the success with "Top Secret". Took over in the third installment of Scary Movie and it is already preparing the fifth. The first two films Scary movie, by the way, I've not seen, are of Keenen Ivory Wayans. The fourth installment is the first I see because my prejudices. And that reminds me that I have to rent the above, because it is not negligible.Many jokes of Scary movie are of coarse salt, or "caca-teta - ass-fart-pis" as calls Javier Ocaña. But they do fulfill their function, separate us from the emotional strain that the movie itself could create. It is not going to see movies, but of making fun of the film. And in the parodic vocation, there is plenty of deconstruction. Those same elements that made us suffer, or engage in the original dismounted before our eyes so we can laugh, just like an actor that will remove the bloody mask so we were there trick.Says Noel Carroll in his book "Philosophy of terror" or paradoxes of the heart that we see movies of fear to immunize us against what we are scared. More reason to watch films ridiculing the fear. It is also dismantle other typical effects of the film, as the mythologization. During a movie actors reach seem Ethereal, why Zucker makes that Carmen Electra in the role of the blind of the forest within the Assembly that confuses a bathroom and do your needs in front of everyone, or that the father scared of the war of the worlds take advantage of one of the thunderous lightning to throw a fart. It's dismantling our sympathies towards these vulnerable beings, such as the Dakota Fanning of the war of the worlds which here takes all the hits. We like that they mistreat her because we have spent two hours suffering with Spielberg that will not happen anything.</body>
</review>
