<review author="JLO" title="Saw" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Low cost, with a rookie director - film James Wan, fresh out of an Australian film school which also collaborated on the story - that gives us hope for a genre, that increasingly makes a best effort to be what it was.</summary>
	<body>This original thriller, mix in equal parts of terror with the now more famous psychological thriller, is a pleasant surprise in the genre.Not by its idea, which refers immediately in its first minutes to Seven but to its construction, full of all the known clichés but this time used in a very beneficial dose.	 Unlike the aforementioned film, does so with unknown or eternal actors side: only the face of Cary Elwes is barely recognized (slips in Twister, Robin Hood, the shadow of the Vampire, liar, liar, etc.) being the best actor by far film. Danny Glover appears as the only exception - and unnecessary - the Gallery of celebrities.		 With almost a single scenario, an underground bathroom where the two protagonists are prisoners and who are victims of a macabre game and difficult resolution. These first moments, oppressive and loaded with flashbacks gores, are defined the dark film with a pace that not decays almost miraculously.The use of a nervous camera in some passages seems to undermine the narrative, but then it is used as a resource to make more fluid passages and not as a vacuous modernity, winning also in agility.The successes of the script - for the also co-star star Whannell - make it solid, no potholes or loose, nothing obvious and that with the arrival of the famous "turns of the screw" don't you lose the line and coherence obtained in the footage.The game of fear - the original English is Saw: "sierra" (original are here in Argentina in names!)-It is a low-cost film and with a rookie director - James Wan, fresh out of an Australian film school which also collaborated on the story - that gives us hope for a genre, increasingly makes a best effort to be what it was.</body>
</review>
