<review author="JLO" title="El señor de los anillos: Las dos torres" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A show that points and gives blank, which is unusual in the current Billboard. In short, if you want to know what is an epic adventure, here it is for you:</summary>
	<body>The Tolkien universe seems at first glance a unfathomable challenge both for its size and by their infinite sub-tramas and its many and varied characters. After seeing this film and direction performed therein Peter Jackson, it seems fairly easy to do or at least, the best way to achieve this. More incredible seems to be the same Jackson who began his career with Bad Taste (bad taste, 1988) a film gore-trash with the easy label of bizarre, but of sympathy and an improvisation at exaggerated doses now demonstrating a growth and maturity (with films of transition as heavenly creatures) little seen in Directors of her litter.So enjoyable returns to be the route for over three hours and peak action and adventures that will be briefly and further, improving the pace of the first. Jackson is faithful to the book again, taking the essence and discard (as in the first part) scenes that perhaps we would have liked to see but that would have made it even more Marathon than it was. The two towers starts to any action with one of the best (maybe the best) film beginning of the year. Welcome also the fact to have been filmed all three parties in continued owing to this his fluid narration, agile and effective, with excellent photography and other technical aspects.This time is more important with the passage of the footage guerrero-héroe Aragorn (Viggo Mortensen, measured and innocuous) and his many battles with his companions Legolas (Orlando Bloom) and the dwarf Gimli (John Davies) to the detriment of the long continuous journey of Frodo (Elijah Wood) and even the resurrected Gandalf (an as always excellent Ian Mc Kellen). Another advantage is having made the virtual Gollum (a being likable and obnoxious at the same time), a character functional in history and not a mere entertainment or escapism and for example of this, just one example: Jar Jar Binks.En only must include a tedious incidental music that emphasizes some dialogues already on their solemn and have wished a greater dose of humor, but really not necessary in this type of story.		 Surely will be compared until the tired with their contemporary Harry Potter and Star Wars taking them a body by the time both in implementation, effects and at maturity, but it will have to wait to give the final verdict to conclude all the sagas but saying is, already leads them a significant advantage. Interestingly in all these series the second parts are better than the first, as if needed Yes or Yes an introduction to then be able to evolve and delving into the history more clearly.A final battle without respite (and a real challenge to overcome in the third and final part) crowned a brilliant film in every sense, a spectacle that points and gives blank, which is unusual in the current Billboard. In short, if you want to know what is an epic adventure, here's to you: the Lord of the Rings: the two towers. Enjoy it.</body>
</review>
