<review author="Alex Largo" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To me, the truth, has caused me a pleasant surprise to know that this saga still has something to offer us.</summary>
	<body>Little is expected of this franchise whose unique (and blatant) objective was to squeeze the maximum fever by the teenage Wizard. Very little gave us the first part, child like few and, in my opinion, quite sosa. The second, although more dark not gave us a great movie. And the third. Let's say that the third was a "turning point" for the series. Suddenly a man appeared (the by all known Alfonso Cuarón) took many liberties with the plot and got a few scenes which, although good, a little desentonaban (occasionally with shoehorn). All films of the young Wizard has good and bad things, but the third had very good things (Alfonso Cuarón showed us (and we again demonstrate with the magnificent "sons of the men") was a director as the top of a pine and we offer a magnificent scene, the trip to the past) and things tremendously bad (the design of production left a lot to be desired)(, as well as the script). The fourth, although took liberties with the original plot of the book, was a pleasant and entertaining, movie only, exclusively that. Entertaining. Why is he could expect little of this fifth installment of Harry Potter. Imagine my surprise when today, in a Madrid press pass, the film offered me over (done muchísmo) than expected. Only the appearance of the logo of the Warner already makes it clear that the film is going to be much darker than the others. The logo, as the title appears in a whitish haze, and basically, what appears to be the prophecy. The film starts with Harry in the Park and discussion with Dudley. This scene serves more to remind us of the end of the fourth that for anything else. And then begins the movie. The movie takes a frenetic pace without pause from the Dementors attack. Although omitted large amount of details (and some really important, such as the fact that Petunia remembered the Dementors) the film offers the best scenes of the book with total consistency (something that was missing in an alarming way in the third and fourth). Arrival at Grimauld Place is curious, and in just 6 minutes condenses us everything that happens before the arrival at Hogwarts without let's lack great thing. Once arrived at Hogwarts we occurs quickly and in a very concise way to Dolores Umbridge, with a personality a tad exaggerated with respect to the book. The Dumbledore army gains importance with respect to the book and is very faithful to the idea of the book, even the change of "traitor" with respect to the book is completely consistent with a couple of new small details. Everything follows its normal course until we reach the end. The battle of the Ministry. Since the arrival to the Hall of prophecies until the end David Yates tells us, although with little experience, he knows much about this. Indeed, the entire scene that takes place in the Ministry is frankly superior to any scene in the series. Spectacular, dark and emotional. Since the attack of the death eaters in the Hall of prophecies, the battle in the Hall of the veil and the battle of Dumbledore and Voldemort. Frankly a few minutes that make that entry already worthwhile. The final scene of Dumbledore and Harry is very small and explanations are conspicuous by their absence, although, probably, those who have not read the novels not cast them in lack. No doubt the "culprit" that this delivers whatever is David Yates. Man faces the challenge of adapting the book longer and with more details with enthusiasm and desire (something that was missing in my view to Mike Newell), but above all with talent. I do not even come to think of the mess that could have been conducted if another director would have been at the forefront of this film. Yachts gives us a very good work after the cameras doing some moments resulting from the most emotive while the film has a devilish pace (too much for some). Highlight the amazing work being done at the end of the tape, especially with the battle of Voldemort and Dumbledore. A scene which, although in the book works very well, was very difficult to that function in the same way in the film. Picking up some elements of the book (the snake, the bubble of water.), David, gives us a scene entertaining and personality a palpable throughout the footage. The script on this occasion was carried out by Michael Goldenberg, who had just written 3 scripts before this, although it is not magnificent, is correct. Goldenberg, unlike Steve Kloves, synthesizes the dialogues, not the plot. What I mean, is that Kloves was more given to delete scenes. Goldenberg, almost all scenes of the book are in the movie, but, in return, has eaten large amount of details, for example, and perhaps the most unforgivable failure is that at no time was reveals the name of the person who pronounced the prophecy nor of which heard (Yes, is may sound strange but it is). Another totally different world are the actors. As a general rule, say that with respect to the book, the characters have very few changes and are very well reflected on screen. Daniel Radcliffe, Harry Potter: although it improves their performance with respect to the "Goblet of fire" (although there directly not acted) is not to throw rockets, but perhaps more surprising is that, in the final leg, his performance in no time strident, although during the footage "enjoying" a couple of moments that pulls any theory to keep serving in a position to land. As I said, his role in the last section, is more than passable (and there may be who say you do well). Although there is a moment during the possession of Voldemort, that. well, the truth, no one could have dropped this speech with little grace. Emma Watson, Hermione Granger: although to be unfairly branded bad actress, anyone who understand a little of the matter may not deny that his character in a brilliant way embodies. Watson makes us give a tremendously charismatic character with the new nuances that Hermione presented in the fifth book. Rupert Grint, Ron Weasley: although with slightly less prominence than usual, the case of Rupert is exactly the same than Watson, in fact, Trio protagonist, Emma and him are acquiescing with more note that Radcliffe, although improved, did not reach the level of these two. Michael Gambon, Albus Percial Wulfric Brian Dumbledore: as always, Gambon is superb. But rather than talk about the work of Gambon I like to talk about his character, a character who suffered a terrible change of personality and was turned into a clown in "The prisoner of Azkaban" and "The Goblet of fire" was somewhat dazed. Here, Dumbledore, returns to resemble the Dumbledore of Richard Harris, although with small amendments to not be too strident with respect to the previous. Ralph Fiennes, Lord Voldemort: without any doubt the best of the tape. Those who disliked the teatricalidad of Fiennes in "The Goblet of fire", they will have to swallow the words this time. The appearance of Voldemort in the movie is really wonderful. These effects of smoke in the face of Voldemort give necessary force the character to star in the best scene of the series. A scene (I mean the fight) where Fiennes does so many fuss as it did in the fourth. Although not thought that Yates was going to surprise it has done, and one of the causes is Lord Voldemort, which, as you can already see is better than ever. Imelda Staunton, Dolores Jane Umbridge: bad, twisted, sadistic. This is the character that gives us Staunton. Although, as I have said, something more exaggerated (mainly because it was more than necessary in this installment soon outline the characters), but at the end and after Umbridge. And that I was one of those not wanted in the role. Gary Olman, Sirius Black: though does not appear too, Black appears necessary so the end makes sense. Oldman offers us his talent in an outstanding manner as the godfather of Harry Potter and looking better than in "the prisoner of Azkaban", where, in a couple of moments sobreactuaba a little. Evanna Lynch, Luna Lovegood: without a doubt, not could have elected someone better, and it is that Evanna is Moon, at first can seem more crazy than normal (or at least in Original version seems it), but as the film progresses we find a very faithful portrait of moon. Also highlight the role of Luna in the film, as were many who feared that it ended being a flat character, but no, dedicate you their time and ends up being a character taken directly from the book. Now let's the characters with less footage and minor in General. Alan Rickman (Severus Snape) great, as it was in the first, the second, the third and the fourth. In this installment, Rickman shows us a facet more serious and "violent" Snape, especially in the scenes of Oclumancia. The character Filch stays along the same lines as in "Goblet of fire", that is used as a buffoon, but not in a way so sad and so degrading to character as happened with the fourth film, where the character Filch was mistreated. Here Filch is taken directly from the pages of the book and starred in some of the best gags. Neville has less prominence than expected, and although it tells us the misfortune of his parents and the motivations of Neville to improve does not have as many minutes on screen as for example moon. Tonks, somewhat bland, although the viewer congenia quickly with the character of Natalia Tena, appears very little and his name appears only named in passing on a couple of occasions. Bellatrix, although not enjoying great prominence, remains well profiled enough and so you hate, and Helena does a great job (and passes it on pipe) playing this woman who is truly crazy. Trelawney is something more round than usual, and quite more disadvantaged as it was in the third film, although, as I have said, the character is faithful to the book. And now, ending with others who are "behind the scenes": Nicholas Hooper, a great unknown in the world of the scoring to break into the scene with a great soundtrack that will delight in the film, providing great force to some moments. Special effects are really impressive, and the scene of the Ministry is what it is, in part, thanks to the superb special effects. Highlight to Grawp (who by the way is very but very well) and the effects of smoke (attention to the battle of the veil) in the order of the Phoenix, the death eaters and Voldemort. Another noteworthy aspect is the brilliant work of the production design team. That they do an incredible job, from new and fascinating creatures of the world of the boy wizard until the decorations of the Ministry, frankly stunning. To me, the truth, has caused me a pleasant surprise to know that this saga still has something to offer us. </body>
</review>
