<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="El señor de la guerra" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Risky, thoughtful, virtuous, necessary and really fabulous work</summary>
	<body>With brand new press pass, I went to see, during morning hours, this film without knowing too much about it. The films, they reach the viewer or definitely are on the way. "Lord of war", in my case, has managed to dent. I has overwhelmed, entertaining and I enjoyed generously from the outset.Begins with an absolutely brilliant sequence, summarizing, during the opening credits, the overall intention of his footage. One amazing subjective from a bullet, since its manufacture until to get to snatch the life to a human being. Its director, Andrew Niccol is responsible for the "Gattaca" inspiradísima, who wrote also "El Show de Truman" and "The terminal". In this case it faces here a script very complicated for his risky and controversial subject. Few were not American producers that ran before such a project, and much of the funding has come from foreign producers.There are several points that made the purported success of this project, a mission almost impossible: A plot that he flirts with the documentary, despite being mere fiction and that, at the same time get apabullar in the visual section. The mixture of both formats is never an easy task and the result, when it works, is something that, to me, personally, I wonder. Similar theme, but as a mere documentary, we got more than one year ago the shocking and essential "Darwin's nightmare".Another difficult point is to get away with a plot-driven by a voice. I guess that negative criticism may arrive precisely at this point. I think in this case it works, at least it not at odds and it not thumping, which is already fairly. Another section is the of trying to achieve the necessary empathy with a protagonist who is a real son despicable bastards and unscrupulous does not hesitate a second trample, buy and sell up to his own family to get lionize in a trade as morally respectable, as it is that of illegal arms trafficking and the financing of wars and massacres in half the world. This character is Yuri Orlov (Nicolas Cage), a character inspired by five characters supposedly real that here one only. A Ukrainian victim of the American dream, which already once in New York in the eighties, get transformed into a powerful and respected billionaire thanks to his talents on the international black market weapons. An atrocious and destructive character able to move mountains with only blinking and which recognize right away, because it represents these white men that already warned us before Michael Moore in his books and in his documentaries. And precisely what terrifies us is really feeling this strange empathy with the character, and get to understand their motivations and their arguments: "tobacco companies also mercadean with death and are not persecuted" "And if my business is not currently illegal enough to stop me, because who make the laws in the world are my best customers or my bosses" "what more does?"", if I desaparezco, come immediately another at my place" and thus, Yuri, where terrified, his wife, an international model which it worried buy as if only a luxury Jewelry Diamond was, asked please abandon once and for all the business, this responds: "Can not, because this really I feel very well".And also we recognize immediately in the wife of Yuri, (Bridget Mohynahan) prostituida by the luxuries, for the money, for the material, but at the same time, single and bereaved personally, as any real character on our consumerist society, materialistic and capitalist. And then this brother of Yuri, (Jared Leto) embodying the role on the other side of the coin of this modern society, of the "American Dream", as a victim more as doll broken and addicted to drugs, witness and participant in the Yuri bloody business, as millionaire, so corrupted like him and so empty inside. And this elitist world power and exacerbated luxury comes in contrast with the portrait of a third world helpless, rotten and hungry, victim of wars, disease and misery. Victims of their own dictators, customers of exception of the black market and the globalizing spoliation of the multinational Western. Ethan Hawk portraying a police Interpol which, tireless, this time it's pursuing and arresting Yuri. A species of Jiminy cricket that symbolizes our moral conscience, a species of rare, impotent bug in its tenacious fighting for a lost cause.There will be those who perhaps see here a slow or boring film. For me, it's a risky, thoughtful, virtuous, necessary and really fabulous work. The music is careful, the script still works despite not reaching the stature of "Scarface" or "Goodfellas" and visual invoice is much better that notable, it full of symbologies and black humor. Ultimately, one of the best films I have seen in recent years. A nice discovery with a single but, I have not done.</body>
</review>
