<review author="Bruji" title="Un engaño de lujo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tunisian Pierre Salvadori amounts to class warfare the ironic fight of sexes popularized Ernst Lubitsch, achieving an accurate ridicule of el universo masculino, inheritance of Hawks.</summary>
	<body>Tunisian Pierre Salvadori amounts to class warfare the ironic fight of sexes popularized Ernst Lubitsch, achieving an accurate ridicule of el universo masculino, inheritance of Hawks. Powerful reasons which require repair in this fresh comedy French, evocative of mythic American cinema titles, and driven by a couple protagonist of exception.The difference between a tribute and a plagiarism is, fundamentally, managers who practice the first, responsible, explicitly recreate situations reminiscent of the past. They are these films winks that are much appreciated. The plagiarist, for their part, are engaged in mask ancient scripts following the vanguard Word. There is no doubt that Salvadori, - who, on numerous occasions stated his admiration by master Lubitsch, coming to be regarded as the devil said No as "a perfect film"-, belongs to the Honorable category. His latest work, a delicious comedy with classical dyes, is a good proof of this.Prix hors (something like Carísimo!) is one of those movies that get the attention of the Viewer from the opening credits. The rotating sombrillita belongs to a technique that would be mainly used in American comedies of the 1960s. A claim, however, that was not exclusive to this genre, only have to remember the prodigious home created Saul Bass for Anatomy of a murder (Otto Preminger, 1,959).The romantic comedy formula (paragraph that, improperly, parking is this tape) begins and ends with the chance encounter that occurs between the protagonists. A succeeded in Manhattan in which Cinderella (Gad Elmaleh) soon becomes pumpkin. A new "muñequita of luxury", Pretty modern Woman, that persecutes its Richard Gere.A from this time, the story starts an upward trajectory, looking for the classics, manages to satisfy the movie fan memory. From breakfast at Tiffany's (Blake Edwards, 1,961), with the implicit note of cruelty which contained the story of Truman Capote, until the freshness that only reaches the impossible dreams that we met on holiday in Rome (William Wyler, 1953). We follow a well marked out path in each bend, makes us to marvel. From how to marry A Millionaire (Jean Negulesco, 1,953) until the peculiar "petit déjeuner" served on the Gallic coast, the tribute paid to the beautiful sites of Nice, which both reminds that Delmer Daves made the eternal city in more beyond the Amor.De Fund, the famous battle of sexes it proliferate in the comedies of the 1930s and 1940selevated to class warfare; and the tendency to ridicule the male universe, legacy of Howard Hawks, which reached its maximum expression with the girlfriend Era of 1949. However, the final set far, a lot of what we know by a "film round". It yearns for an effective soundtrack, Councillor of the highlights of the plot; a point of depth in the dialogues, the existence of sharp and witty phrases that feed the script of Benoît Graffin; the creation of new situations that not eternicen initials; and, why not? the inclusion of some memorable frame that had known to exploit the beauty of the lead actress. The scene in testers of clothes, with a close up of the back of a sophisticated black evening gown, clear tribute to Audrey Hepburn, is a good attempt that fails to complete.In any case, with a couple star of luxury, a coherent plot, and development with its frequent references to mythical titles of the seventh art, Prix Hors is, without a doubt, one of the best comedies of the year.</body>
</review>
