<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Odette" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The paradox is that it is the star who needs him arrope his admirer, and not vice versa.</summary>
	<body>Realism is a burden that is sometimes unbearable. "Our friends the logical" as he called them Hitchcock in the Truffaut interview, cling to any irrelevance to demonstrate that the director is wrong. I have a friend that told Indians of Western films to demonstrate that they had killed more than those who were missing. Why managers who want to get rid of the noise of "our friends the logical" wasps give them completely incredible atrocities and have them silent throughout the film. Odette levitates.A famous writer in low hours receives a letter from an admirer who returns the faith in life. He goes to visit her and stays to live with it a few days. The writer lives life who have chosen others, success, money, plastic women. Critics said that writes for hairdressers and employees of stores that have in their bedroom posters with a sunset. Odette is the paradigm of the employee of a few stores with one of those posters.In a society in which the famous known a fraction of those who know them to them, the paradox is that it is the star who needs him arrope his admirer, and not vice versa. The protagonist is her, although at the beginning it is not very clear. What can you offer a widow that collects dolls a famous writer? Either that is the happiness of the title? He has hand with their children, is happy with his son gay which brings many boyfriends home, but not with the tapped has chosen his daughter. It adorns the small things in life with cabaret numbers. Dance beautiful choreography while doing the household chores. Is that enough? Possibly not, but the attempt is grateful for. Her have compared with "Amelie" for its tenderness, but I her ideas with our Candida by its militant naivety. The result owes much to Catherine Frot, not because you do well, but because its 50 years, it is to eat.</body>
</review>
