<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Transformers" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Transformers works the first half. It works when no one knows they exist.</summary>
	<body>It has become fashionable talk about cinema popcorn, made for people who disconnects the brain into the room and cinema gafapasta, for people who want to show off. Example of the latter would be the incomplete "The lives of others"; as an example of the first thing worth us this film of Michael Bay. I have to say about this dichotomy that doesn't interest me. It tells me absolutely nothing about the film, I only speaks of as the spectators feel with regard to their own tastes.Yes I can say what I do not read the critics that say "palomitero cinema". They are not lovers, film snobbish. Dislike the film, mola les cache that gives praise to the big names and wear them in the tab as a medal: "I understand Dreyer", "I see movies by Buñuel", say. Just in case someone didnt read anything of what I have written, either does not know even my you aversions, give me the snobbish disgust. (I certainly like Dreyer, but not as much as the Farrelly brothers, for example).Made this point sociological, if I may, I will talk about film.The problem that loaded million and special effects producers such as Spielberg and Michael Bay should consider is do to what extent this waste affects a viewer? There is a scene in which the entire town is scene of a colossal sympathetic Autobots battle the evil Decepticons. If you want to hear an objective opinion, the battle is indifferent. All those billions in CGI arouse less interest than a conversation between a father and a son who wants to come out of the closet.Even though they intend anonadar us with his blockbusters, there is a path that leads to success, and that is the path the feelings that can not buy with effects, final firecrackers, or dazzling metal gadgets. At the beginning catches us the character of Shia LaBeouf, which is a common name in their land as here Jose, or Paco. There you shout "Shia LaBeouf!" and become twenty. The young boy goes to the Institute and not stands out. It is strained by the beauty of the class, which is easy to understand after seeing the actress have hired to interpret it, but she does not know that he exists, not even after you buy a second hand car, something husked, which he believes will finally break his celibacy.While the teenager plans to the way of approaching the bombonazo, evil robots, or Decepticons, they plan to as seizing land. The question is: has the second no interest! We accept the roll of the robots and the Save humanities because we know that upload you the moral boy, and gives you an excuse to kiss, but nothing more. It is the story of androids which must be at the service of the couple, rather than the reverse. Forget "Bay about basic things.""Transformers" works the first half. It works when no one knows they exist. The Pentagon knows they have killed one of its military bases in the desert, but do not know who (emotion). The boy knows that your car has something strange, but do not know what (emotion). Parents know that something happens in the garden, but do not see the four hidden (higher than the House) autobots (desparrame) behind the porch. The excitement of the robots is not the amount of things you know make or shoot at the final battle of the film. It consists of the face that is going to put each character when you to discover. Once discovered, the only thing that still retains some interest are the curves of the girl.</body>
</review>
