<review author="Jose Contreras" title="En algún lugar de la memoria" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The subject should really consider is the price of pain what is a daughter who died in a September 11 plane?</summary>
	<body>The character of Adam Sandler lost his wife and their three daughters in one of the planes on September 11. The question is: would we mind both if had lost them in a traffic accident, or on a train of the 11 M? I regret the cynicism, but the answer is no.There are pains and headaches. And Dr. Fineman suffers the pain of all sorrows, suffers from the open wound of a nation in mourning, suffers pain of epic proportions, the pain of a nation that he slept thinking that it was the largest in the world and woke up knowing that he was vulnerable.The argument is articulated in a narrative blueprint resembles that chose Wenders in "Paris, Texas". The protagonist is self-destroyed in a never-ending ceremony until that at the end you can talk and put back together with a speech the shreds of his life which has been showing in front of the screen.Why to Fineman you are consent to be everything. Why nobody lets only. The landlady, the friend, the administrator of the vast fortune that claimed as a victim of the 11-S, the therapist. all hold his extravagance and chase him for that. For what? Can so relate in front of the camera the suffering that was for him the loss of his family as if it were a television show?The loudspeaker of a confession is not enough for a pain so excessive proportions. It is necessary to go further. We need police to stop it and hold a trial against him and gets questioned his mental health. We need that attacked by parents of the wife and Fineman will become a victim of your silent pain (silent?). The collective catharsis, the bath of tears you both want to flood his bereaved victim is necessary for the public.But the issue should really think about is the price of pain as is a daughter who died in a September 11 plane? as is the brother died in the Gulf war? how much is worth a firefighter trapped in the twin towers? and a victim of Katrina?Actor and director worked already together in "Aggressive Executive". There worked the lesson of the rage that we all carry within, the lesson of not save anything. But already us her learnt well. Not a review was needed to show her, too, to the healthy dentist who interprets Cheadle.</body>
</review>
