<review author="José A. Peig" title="Harry Potter y la piedra filosofal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nevertheless, a very estimable film of fantasy and adventure, which stresses well above the current prevailing mediocrity in this type of film. But even so, it is too warm to be the story of a magician orphan facing the executioner of his parents.</summary>
	<body>With this film begins a long series of fantasy and adventures inspired by another melià series of books. Chris Columbus directed with deft hand this presentation and first immersion in a universe of fantasy that comes to be a revisitación of the classic icons of the fantastic: wizards, elves and Gnomes, dragons, trolls, sorceries and hidden treasures. Children are the protagonists in the work and in the enjoyment of the same, because in this first adventure emphasizes the anecdotal and a sense of humor that goes from the ludicrous in its first minutes to more inane in the further development, to the detriment of the dramatic possibilities of the story, a sentimental vein which is personified somewhat superficially in the daydreams of the boy protagonist, the orphan looking for his parents to the same time as he discovers his talent of magician and the dark intricacies of his past and evil represented in Voldemort.Pensada exclusively to amuse the children, the film certainly works pretty well and uses the magic and the magician as suggestive claim and stimulate the imagination of children: a magic wanda top hat magician, a flying broom, the dream that, in his time, we have all had when we were children. From this point of view, the film is delicious, a world of magic and mystery that it vibrates and unfolds in a decorated Gothic aromas, reformulation of the "other world" - such as the world of Oz or Neverland - in this case represented in Hogwarts castle, where there coexist as charming and the uncanny.In addition, the film stands out first and foremost in plastic resources; excellent artistic design and special effects to the required height. Magnificent soundtrack by John Williams. The characterization of characters also conforms to stipulations in a specific field like this of wizards and magic, but they really end up being too stereotypical and the film lacks a character evil with charisma, that Voldemort does not happen to be a puppet too decaffeinated, with clear reminiscences Darth Sidius or other representatives of evil seen thousand times in film and television. There are other interesting things, as ambiguous and enigmatic personality of Professor Snape or the histrionic caricaturing of the Potter child's "earthly" family, but none of them ends curdling by diluted of the narrative, as we will now explain.The same burden of always: the error you want to compress the novel in an excessive and/or untapped footage, everything is to satisfy fans of the book. And that cinema and literature are not the same, and when we are we inspired by a book the first thing that must be taken into account is that the film should erect on an idea of structuring and film structure has already been said, and if it is necessary to delete characters and specific passages, it must be done without fuss, everything is to strengthen the essential aspects and can it be developed in 140 minutes or two few hours. Narration is not over curdling none of its elements because it is intended to present too many characters and too much emphasis on very redundant passages or scenes. Discourse and the script should have reinforced the relationship between Harry and the memory of his parents (very beautiful mirror scene, great lyrical and sensitive moment between a sea of inanity), the enigma of Snape and the stone and the fight against Voldemort. These were the three major issues that fade without finding the proper strength in depth and development. Ultimately, the narrative is lost in flourishes and insubstantial anecdotes.Nevertheless, a very estimable film of fantasy and adventure, which stresses well above the current prevailing mediocrity in this type of film. But even so, it is too warm to be the story of a magician orphan facing the executioner of his parents. Perhaps it has to be understood as a project who, conscious and intentional, does not want to finish boot for the benefit of subsequent deliveries</body>
</review>
