<review author="Berto" title="Transformers" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you want to spend 2 and a half hour spectacular, with action, laughs, action, persecutions, action and special effects that you tardareis days in delete you from the head, this is your film, for everything else, you have other twenty films in billboard fixed colmaran much more your expectations.</summary>
	<body>Slowly fall premieres of the summer, and the waiting to arrive the fifth installment of the most famous Wizard of all time, here comes this weekend one of the premieres that more box office will raise around the world and that fixed that broken some record fund-raising, and that men spider and the pirates came strong this yearbut there is something which separates this film from the rest of premieres and is that this film has achieved something that however neither Spider-Man 3 and Pirates of the Caribbean 3 managed, is entertain me during all the footage from the film and I forget the clock during the 2 hours and a half which takes the film. It was clear that the tandem Michael Bay and Steven Spielberg would produce an authentic revientataquillas, but also the already mentioned previously that mission and did and however Spider-Man 3 is definitely the weaker of all, with authentic moments painful and quite desaprovechada, as well as pirates of the Caribbean 3 is the weaker due to its lack of new ideas and his intention to try to finish all the plotlines of two movies in too little time.In the film I took today, we find ourselves with adaptation to the big screen in a series of cartoons in which robots, grouped into two sides, good and bad, are fighting on the planet Earth, for an end to the human race and others for trying to save her, and is in this simple argument which was based the ochentera series and is on this premise that underpin Transformers in 2007. As you can see, the script is more simple, and let us not deceive ourselves, the film is simple in terms of script, is simple in terms of characters, and is even predictable throughout the film, but, since when a film and not can be enjoyed? We will enjoy at another time of Fincher or Scorsese, go to the movies for fun at the end and at Cape is one of their main reasons for existence, entertain, and this film is that it entertains. There a moment to relax, because from the third minute of footage the robots make their appearance, and fine appearance, and throughout the movie the pace and action grows until an end to slash the Pinnacle and you dry without blinking because if you blink you lose some extraordinary special effects second that wasted the film at all times and especially in the final half-hourone of the most impressive battles that we have seen in the film throughout its history, and that they are already more than 100 years. Believe me if I tell you that we will not see special effects and all that remains of the year, and probably take some more, to find a film that her equal or exceed in terms of perfection, eye candy and spectacular, and not worth me having the second part of Transformers, because Yes, friends, we have singing trilogy.Obviously, the characters in this film are nothing out of this world, and in this we have stereotypes of the typical normalito guy from Institute, its respective companion, very good to say enough is enough, the Group of American soldiers who fight and fight until the fainting by his country, the Minister of defence that does not hesitate to do anything to save the people and even the typical group of hackers slip of glancingvery good girl incorporated, with the head of a section of a top secret organization too paranoid to know for sure how he came up there. Among them highlights undoubtedly Shia LaBeouf, authenticates the film revelation and authentic revelation Usa, with a couple of released movies is becoming a mass phenomenon and after seeing the movie I understand perfectly, because LaBeouf, has charisma, and with its performance you get well into the first moments that comes on the screensomething essential to continue with a bit more interest the plot, and already posts, say that his choice of son of Indiana Jones seems perfect to me, you can give much freshness and be at the height of so highly anticipated role. Megan Fox is very normalita, is dedicated to show off Palmetto throughout the film, which is not little, and the fact that his character is very little used, almost as untapped group of marines, among which are Josh Duhamel and Tyrese Gibson, which can very little mention of them except that his performance is correct and little more. As for Jon Voight and John Turturro, they are not bad, but while Voight makes a more content role, Turturro gets carried away by his character almost to the grotesque and created one of the strangest roles throughout the film, that Yes, with their good moments and do not detract from his performance in any situation, we note that you rolling switched it pipe.Ultimately, Transformers is a real summer blockbuster, but the of a few years ago, those who were going to see looking for a good time of fun and widely improved your expectations. If you want to spend 2 and a half hour spectacular, with action, laughs, action, persecutions, action and special effects that you tardareis days in delete you from the head, this is your film, for everything else, you have other twenty films in billboard fixed colmaran much more your expectations.</body>
</review>
