<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Ladrones" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie is slow, sleeping and pretentious. Poor Juan José has behind him the weight of a failed movie what however in other hands, could have been a great movie.</summary>
	<body>Film label crappy Danger where is spoken of love, a mother, a girl, to a memory.I will try to be brief. Jaime Marques Olarreaga directs this stinky film with so little talent that I believe that if my little brother had charge of the direction, the result at least it would be bearable.The movie is slow, sleeping and pretentious. Poor Juan José has behind him the weight of a failed movie what however in other hands, could have been a great movie. The script lacks chicha, but everything that is argument think it has pull. The goal to achieve is that the Viewer is excited in such way that leave the cinema trying to steal wallets pq everyone who creates the director has overwhelmed it. However, what you want is to end the visual torture as soon as possible. I say that it is pretentious by Jaime Marquis tries to uses a pseudo-poético language through their images fails, is a tedious pace, slow.Reviewing the direction of actors, I have to say that they are all fatal, and when this happens it is the fault of the director, so is that an intensive cursito in coaching with Augusto Fernandes Argentina I recommend Jaime from here (which not Fernandez), because it is difficult that Juan José is loose interpretation.María Valverde that I loved in the Borgia, click here also and is that this girl when it comes to scripting, slow rhythms cadenciados intentions pulling to dramatic, always shows the same face and clear and tired. Ay! Maria Maria that see you the plumerillo with Juanjo, the girl was shaking and was not played XD. We are going I also temblaría to the irreverent Juan josé dust Ballesta.Me liked the soundtrack and Juan José (idyllic until the esquizofrénia), the rest in the trash.</body>
</review>
