<review author="Kiko de España" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do absolutely delusional with great dialogue, and above all, better persecution of cars seen in years in a movie theater, and that it's a sequence? classical and analog?, as the persecutions were shot 30 years ago.</summary>
	<body>Difficult to focus on something concrete to discuss the latest furor of Quentin Tarantino, Death Proof, and that always is good. I will leave aside the trailers, the double programme and all what is Grindhouse, not only because it was a historical bump on American soil (incomprehensible, would add) but because even beyond the double programme will be maintained and they reestrenarán both movies like that in Europe, in a director´s cut. In other words, because Grindhouse has been a dream that once we dream, but to awaken what we had were each movie separately. It has been both what we have heard these months with regard to the film event of the year (I personally put it above Transformers, pirates, etc) this is cinema that I will try to be clear now that we have seen a pass organized by the people of Aurum, its distributor in Spain. At the height of expected: outstanding.Stuntman Mike (Kurt Russell Ma-gis-tral) is a psychopath son of a bitch that runs along the roads with their racing car, a true killing machine, in search of girls to assassinate and, if they are well good, so much better. The girls are spectacular is normal in a movie of these characteristics, what is not normal is that friend Quentin has so many handsome contacts, because Miss Poitier (do go? legs!), Rosario, Zoe or Mary Elizabeth are they sparkle. Absolutely hilarious, with a few great dialogues (despite some serious kind claiming inconsequential, only as you look at it), and above all, better persecution of cars seen in years in a movie theater, and that that is a "classical" and"analog" sequence, as the persecutions were shot 30 years, something should learn the Wachowskifor example. Course, meta-realidades (the character of the Dawson takes "ringtone" "Broken nerves" of Herrman which already used Tarantino at his Kill Hill), shootings of films, a new dance to remember (rather more subidito tone than that of Travolta and Uma, or Michael Reservoir Madsen) and an absolutely timeless atmosphere eventually materialize in a perfect wayso foolproof, I fear not, because we are one of the great films of the year, but a reality test of any doubt, because many frega you in that goal, for many favors you do, by many garbage in which his name appears (eye, any Hostel or Running Scared would there), Quentin Tarantino is one of the guys with more talent that has given the American film in, its history? Death Proof is the debut of Tarantino as director of photography, and all I can say is that you note of Knoxville has worked with types such as Robert Richardson (do Kill Hill, the Aviator, JFK?) and that he has seen a lot, probably all, the slasher and acquired giallos and for having an encyclopedia on "as light a good movie of series B / Z". Another (very) important point lies in his filmography (for what was to be less?) with the music that accompanies the images, and Death Proof starts with a theme of Jack Nietzsche entitled The Last Race, there is nothing. Then I say, the best DJ of Hollywood is recreated as it did from Pulp Fiction, both in the music and images. Ah, by the way, before concluding I would like to stress that the better and more badass car wreck lives of middle, cinematically speaking, in recent times, is in Death Proof. And the end is simply unforgettable and memorable. The only negative note will be the question of the fake trailers, because it would be a pity to miss them and at the moment we have no official news (1), only the rumor that Planet Terror, which I have not been able to see in its extended version (but it is a sufficient zany retro-pulp with many good moments, but there is the problem, is a film 100 hundred Rodríguez)(, with which this entails for better and for worse) it will come with the Machete, directed by Rodriguez himself and that it could stretch until the long. Other titles are:-Werewolf women of the s.s. (by Rob Zombie) - Don? t (by Edgar Shaun of the Dead Wright and a narrative of "Arrested Development" Will Arnett that will make you cry with laughter)-Thanksgiving (by Eli Roth, an outstanding job.) (And gorno, of course) thanks, Quentin, thank you.</body>
</review>
