<review author="El mágico" title="Ratatouille" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pixar returns to position itself as a large factory which achieved a great victory over Dreamworks. As regards film quality, your product exceeds the Shrek himself, flagship of his rival.</summary>
	<body>Brad Bird has directed "The incredibles" in 1984, and his work had been very good. In general, we know that Pixar has better ideas than Dreamworks terms how working scripts for animation. "Ratatouille" comes to screens mounted in a hellish advertising display which made me much doubt its apriori values.Not be one distrusted, but you know that the big studios invest more money on advertising when you know that your product is mediocre? As Word of mouth will not work, they inject money media so that everyone is tienten and go to see your movie. Well, fortunately "Ratatouille" is not of this type. Now, the cast have to say that I was pleasantly surprised (rather than anything, I want to say that you as almost always, I saw the English version, so I will refer to the characters according to its original dub), is a film where the voices are accurate and good humor depends on the chemistry that occurs between images and those that provide their voices, in that aspect, the film is notable. But we move on to the story itself, Remy (featuring Patton Oswalt, precise tone and acting) lives in Paris, loves cooking and her dream is to work in the best restaurant in the world, has exceptional conditions to combine spices, ingredients and learn about the best product for their work. Of course, there is a problem, Remy, is a rat! Here is the first nod of the script.Our friend rodent seems to represent a case of strange, as if it were a "lower", subject who belongs to a social segment and for those things of fate stands in skills that characterize a layer higher than the suyo.y that seems inaccessible to their possibilities. Well, Remy is a rat that accidentally goes to such a Linguini (Lou Romano, sensitive and very funny), a young human who also wants to be a chef, but don't know anything about cuisine and above all, he is sent to work in a restaurant that had been owned by the legendary Gusteau (Brad Garret, ghostly!), Chef of prestige that was loved by all France until his death. There, his assistant is still directing the place and will accept to Linguini among its ranks, good.Remy and Linguini! There is a secret that could change the fate of all (which will not disclose here), and the plot is complejizando as it progresses in natural and well organised. Linguini gives with Remy and although there is no verbal dialogue between them, the symbiotic communication show is very well achieved. Between the two they will be complemented, any is fall in love (Colette in the sweetest Janeane Garofalo) and surprise you with excellent dishes to the amazement of his employer, Skinner (I said that it was the sober Ian Holm) who feels that Linguini is hiding something dark that could put an end to your business. "Ratatouille", did me not a film for kids. I mean, not for small kids. Your script is showing signs of sophistication ranging from the chosen place to unleash the conflict (a Parisian restaurant) until a clear problem of racism and intolerance (the subject of the clashes between humans and rodents). I think that there is much work in the history and adults really enjoy this addition to the history that is what gives the film flight extends its spectrum. In that sense, Pixar returns to position itself as a large factory which achieved a great victory over Dreamworks film quality, your product beats the Shrek himself, flagship of his rival. "Ratatouille" appeals to us with such candor with films where the search to find a place in the world is the primary subject. The best for the whole family, while not the laughter and extreme situations (although there are), abound this this is a very friendly tape for the casual viewer and a delight for the predisposed to sit at this table to taste this exquisite delicacy.</body>
</review>
