<review author="El vengador toxico" title="Historia de un crimen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An absolutely essential film this summer, without stridence showing us a complex portrait of characters around a violent murder.</summary>
	<body>Interestingly, this film has a more appropriate title in Spanish, in English. It's the follow-up made Truman Capote the crime of a family of rich farmers in the American Midwest. This follow-up dragged on for five years and led to us masterpiece "in cold blood".The film begins with a series of scenes that show the integration of Capote in high society New York at the time. During the footage, there are moments which shows these characters a kind of interview to qualify actions by the writer.I do not know as it was in fact the true Truman. Here occurs with an effeminate pose and a few "outfits" more picturesque, causing a dramatic contrast with the sobriety of a traditional American conservative city. This serves as a base to funny moments that are splashing the first part of the film, rather than the tone becomes more dramatic.When you stop the murderers starts the real core of the film, which is the relationship with them to reflect accurately in his book, and as emotional involvement is making a dent in the writer.The role of Capote is beautifully portrayed by Toby Jones (I have not seen the movie "Capote" of the añopasado, so I do not know if better or worse), showing a character complex, capable of displaying frivolous, incisive or tremendously sympathetic, as required by the occasion. Exemplary is the scene of food of Christmas where he began to creep into the closed rural society.An important pillar of the movie is the relationship with Nelle Harper Lee, childhood friend and writer of great success (what Truman causes a certain amount of professional jealousy). It is a support for the writer outside his high society circles. And is superbly played by Sandra Bullock, actress me has always fallen sympathetic, but to which I have never seen in a great performance, so far.But certainly, the other character is that of the murderer Perry Smith, with Daniel Craig also immense, totally away from her last performance as James Bond.Una absolutely essential film this summer, without stridence shows a complex portrait of characters around a violent murder.</body>
</review>
