<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="The host" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A true update of the genre of monsters comes from the hand of South Korean director Bong that, away from the digital approach to the Hollywood industry, presents the monster in the background to the main characters.</summary>
	<body>Nobody knows the face of the family, there are people who say that it is like a huge dog, or a black Adder with cat's eye, and they say that at night it goes through the reedbeds dragging a chain.[Jorge Lanata, dead of love, Ed. Alfagurara, Buenos Aires, 2007]That strikes something which oppresses us, us, us devora.ha State, is and will be represented in the film (as in any of the arts, literature to comics) through the figure of the monster. Our represented fears be indescribable. The monster as metaphor makes us prisoners of our fears, curtailing our freedom of action, causing flight, horror and despair. Film - will awake our instinct of survival, and only, the heroicismo - there we rescue from the absolute brink.The range is wide. Zoology surprises us in Moby Dick or shark. Devastating extraterrestrial, as Alien and predator. Friendly Gremlins. Classics such as Frankenstein and King Kong. Z series with a hero named the Toxic Avenger. And always the Japanese such as Godzilla and Godzilla. Our latino Faun. We desdramatizamos through the cast, with the monsters of Píxar and Dreamworks.Una jewel true update of the genre of monsters comes from the hand of South Korean director Bong, away, the industry approach to digital Hollywood (special effects above all), presents the monster in the background to the main characters. The really important thing is what happens to the protagonists, their emotions: how face that something and how change them, personally and in relations with others. Each of the members of the family will discover the monster inside and how do away with him.To this end, Bong builds the history from different angles. This fact produces pass comedy, to the terror of the family to an action film drama. Difficult task which the director goes away. And that is the happiness of this Asian cinema; that us disorienting and us held captive at the same time. And even, Bong gives an ideological tone. Political representation of the monster as allegory of any form of repression. And foreign interventionism, from the hand of the American superpower which, in the same way that bombs Baghdad will also launch chemical weapons on Seoul to stop the Monster (which, incidentally, themselves created), as they did on Monster Hirosima.Ese indiscriminately throwing bombs on defenseless populations is the most fearsome of all.</body>
</review>
