<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fincher has rewritten the classic patterns of the thriller. This is a sentimental, sickly, intimate thriller almost.</summary>
	<body>Thorough and suggestive to pornographic, overwhelming in their detailed dissection of a criminal investigation, Zodiac is not a commercial film in any way, although it contains traces of generous box-office because its quoted director, David Fincher film (Jeunet, Seven, fight club, panic room and the little The game) and its more than competent cast. Zodiac is a study on the obsession that descends from the purely descriptive (crimes, the relevant evidence of a case that alarmed the population of California during the last 1960s and early 1970s) up the sickly, representing by a series of characters encorsetados in a very ambiguous territory that is neither police nor journalistic. Fincher is not meant to miniaturize the plot; more on the contrary, what it does is hocicar his narrative in all the crevices talent so that the Viewer is being suffocated by a proposed excessive drama, perhaps too rigorous, not leaving his film character at any time and that explores with delinquent delectation in the aspects usually more hidden in this type of film Gadgets: inquiriesthe surveys that they are, at some point in the footage, tiresome and obviables, but without whose assistance the exquisite set is deslabazado, sluggish, as if he had stolen any minimum feature of credibility and we were attending any vulgar telefilm desktop on assassins in series and desquiciados policemen trying to hunt. As we have seen much film of this coat, it must be very demanding with Zodiac. The result? A masterful, almost overwhelming tape, in any case, perfect in their heightened sense of ethics and the epic because, well watched the final aftertaste that is: the of having swallowed a monumental sentimental outburst on justice, the right to find the truth and the obstacles that the time and the reluctance of the society has to give her when mediaauthentic depositaries of the mountains of data, have already decided to give sovereignty back. Zodiac dazzles for his hubris, which is also - in the view of some people--its largest says.It is not possible to reduce their excess: will require their two long hours so that no thread is without braid and, at the time, is the last thought that all threads to the abovinarse have not led to complete any Hank. Narrative never hit, Zodiac entertains at any moment and has the virtue of not licensing is perhaps perdonables: a more explicit truculence, a spirit to the Seven that Fincher is no stranger because that work teacher last entertainment film (commercial, say) is yours. What makes the director in this case is to rewrite the pattern on which address the gender of serial killers and reformulate his speech on the basis of criteria more literary, closest to connaisseurs models as all the President's men (I know that I am not the only one who has seen this similarity, in fact before see this was the only information that was in the film) or even JFK. His formal neatness, their lack of doctrinal enthusiasms and its marginal character in the thriller Zodiac make tape rather than recommended, is not the masterpiece that could have been (it has mimbres and incentives to be in those who thus consider it in their internal jurisdiction) but yes, and forcefully, one film more within the Fincher filmography at the height of Seven. Curious that his greatest accomplishments come from similar narrative foundations. Perhaps in the next foray into the genus give to man by listing view hundred and eighty degrees and dive in the melodrama or in the musical, and all without abandoning assassins in series, clear.</body>
</review>
