<review author="Caruco" title="Un engaño de lujo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do few masterpieces has given the genre in recent years, and?A hoax of luxury? It is not an exception. Nothing of genius, but at least, a more than decent so long-suffering romantic comedy genre film.</summary>
	<body>Make a comedy is not thing of laughter. Or resorting to humor easier and thick, to the more trite script or to treat most of the characters as if they were stupid. Few masterpieces it has given the genre in recent years, and "A deception of luxury" is no exception. Nothing of genius, but at least, a more than decent so long-suffering romantic comedy genre film.With a mise en scène as elegant as effective, is very consistent with the happy story of a fortune seekers (Audrey Tautou) who loves to flirt with billionaires pulling to lesbians, rather than to live well, to spend all what make you available to your Visa; and his? affair? with the bartender of a hotel (Gad Elmaleh) who will end up taking the role of Gigolo maintained by another ricachona widow (Adam Marie-Christine) only for approaching his true beloved Golden part of the Cote d'Azur.The touch Blake Edwards and almost (I repeat, what of almost) of other masters of the classical comedy as Lubitsch, plans in the mind of its director, Pierre Salvadori, which is converting, with the permission of Maya, in the great French hope in the field of comedy of entanglements and misunderstandings. It was unveiled with the estimable "You first", at that time with Daniel Auteil and Sandrien Kiberlain as protagonists, and here goes one step further in its light treatment, but not without good taste and talent.It gives us a little surprise that also boasts an Audrey Tautou willing to leave behind the lengthened shadow of Amélie and that, true to its name, the Audrey, seems newly out of "Breakfast at Tiffany 's". A delicious creature willing to sell his body to the highest bidder, be not his solitary soul, lurching and ignoring the pleasures of the heart.Audrey, the Tautou is splendid; his partner, the actor of Moroccan origin Gad Elmahed ("the game of the idiots", "The train of life"), knows to give the replica without resorting to the topical interpretive excesses grotesque grimacing, jerks verborreas or trompazos everywhere, but also all the contrary; and the side do not seem mere stupid comparsas. In addition, the invention entertains and works.</body>
</review>
