<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Transformers" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Transformers shows that the humor of our societies has changed: the impropriety of policy or the irony without blood have gone to audiovisual conservativism that although is more realistic in the staging of the action, soon becomes an empty show that chokes the emotion for the benefit of the box office.</summary>
	<body>I take the appearance - not enough but always necessary in summer - the refreshing audiovisual attraction of this Fireworks seller who is Michael Bay (the rock, island, are even their own infumables Pearl Harbor and Armageddon) to remember (perhaps this just more into years and engullidas movies public endure the 144 minutes this inconsequential circus and only bearable isolated scenes) the trajectory of a master of entertainment as Joe Dante, whose master to make fun and innocent movies still leaves a mark on those who we were lucky if teenagers back in the eighties.Transformers is good only when it smells like Dante, when their robots remind us of the naif irony and the antics of the Gremlins, or heroism without small soldiers dead. And the introduction to the first love through the crazy and amazing adventure has echoes of the prodigious chip and above all Gremlins. The scene in which the protagonist must go home to retrieve the glasses is pure Dante. The forced verbiage of robots that seem more about pets as the saviours of the free world is pure Dante (even if in this film runs all its freshness neglected by a script and a rhythm without the child naturalness of the master). In Transformers the exaggeration of some prodigious (and perhaps the best) FX dilutes the freshness and disperses the attention about the epic teenager Yes worked with Dante and came even excite.Transformers is trying to attract with cars (what a disappointment the conversion of the ramshackle and humanized second hand in a dazzling Chevrolet Camaro car) and girl removes the breath and other things (Megan Fox is so tasty in their as tasteless kinetics in his interpretation) to the young audience, which soon will feel identified with the protagonist, a smart guy with a sense of humor but two candles. However Dante magic is what you have; everything transforms him through the adventure and soon the young man in search of his identity will find her trying to save the world? (even in this Transformers is diluted in a 2 Armageddon). With Dante nobody wants to save the world; enough adventure. The eighties optimism of the mark Dante knew that, as in the indianescas films of Spielberg (for true, co-producer of the tape), while the character run, jump, flee, Kiss and rescue the emotion is assured. The rest is enough, even the digital FX. Why the character of Martin Short in the final scene of the prodigious chip does not return to his old life, but that runs after another mission that makes you feel alive.Transformers robs their characters for a famous series of Japanese TV that back in the 1980s became a sensation and anticipated what is now an explosion manga that trasversa film entertainment made in USA (including Tarantino). And it shy combines the coldness of the machine with the anthropomorphic irony that makes us accessible and exciting adventure of the robots. Although this I prefer the endearing rivalry of the R2D2 and C3PO, Grump even naïve teenager vitality of Johnny 5 in short circuit (John Badham, 1986), the Sayonara baby of the insensitive Terminator or the heroism of the endearing Buzz Lightyear (Toy Story, 1995).And is that Transformers demonstrates that the humor of our societies has changed: of the impropriety policy, the irony without blood or nudity without condoms of the eighties, have gone to an audiovisual conservatism which although is more realistic in the staging of the action, soon becomes an empty show that chokes the emotion for the benefit of the box office.The best: the scene in which the protagonist must go home to retrieve the glasses. Without a doubt, Shia LaBeouf. An actor without much transmitting a naturalness and incredible proximity. The more than obvious knowledge of mechanics of Megan Fox. The realism of the CGI digital effects, a prodigy of technique, imagination and pacienciaLa scene of the girl in the pool (very to the style of the King Kong of Jackson or girl with Shyamalan water). Perhaps Transformers would have been a great film in key to terror, perhaps.</body>
</review>
