<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Vecinos invasores" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Child film suitable for all audiences, from the smallest to the largest, to see with the eyes as dishes</summary>
	<body>I do not is that they have the zarigüellas, but they are fashionable. The two latest movies I've seen animation appear these friendly animals which in my life I shall be released. Incidentally, that rarest family, with a Patriarch turtle turtle, a daughter Skunk seeking love, a raccoon that trafficking to be adopted, an oscuras squirrel, a subfamily of zarigüellas and a few playful porcupines (who share family responsibilities, by the way). And the bad milk of humans who want them to exterminate, really. In the end.The film is a strange family of animals that rise from his hibernation and discover that they are surrounded by a luxurious urbanisation, where before there was a lush forest. As they have been without food, are advised by a raccoon to get eaten by humans, with the risks that this entails. But the Patriarch of the family, a turtle, fails to see the plan, unclear what does that the family unit tambalee.To me these films, by definition, I like a lot. And if they are also good, because I like more. In this case we have a film on family unity, diversity and equality, on the progress on the coexistence of humans with the rest of beings of the Earth, about teamwork, even about love. And is that we know that these films have to atufar moralina on all sides so that the elderly can say "see for the values it instills" and not that we enjoy with children's animation films. The plot is quite childish, which is very appropriate given that it is oriented for children. The argument develops quite agile, with few moments of narrated moralina, what is to be welcomed. And it has many moments of humor for everyone. Deserves special mention, in the Spanish version, the dub of Luis Merlo in the body of turtle. I think that it is the role of his life and that if that turtle speak, should be with that voice.In short, film suitable for all audiences, from the smallest to the largest. To see with eyes as dishes, in the same way that see it boys.</body>
</review>
