<review author="José A. Peig" title="Harry Potter y la cámara secreta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do the Harry Potter saga begins to be cinematically solid when at the charming and playful designs and their individuals? tics?, joins a content set out clearly, winning in dramatic force.</summary>
	<body>Following the steps marked by author j. k. Rowling, Columbus returns to lead in the new adventure of the boy magician most popular of all time, in a continuation and extension of the universe presented - lovely but too banal in the approach of history, as already explained-, rather than a progression of the previous story, is an extension of the information regarding the situation and the circumstances of the mystery and the threat that surrounds to the School of wizardry, Hogwarts. The film stresses the strange relationship and similarity between Harry Potter and evil personified in Voldemort, or rather, in how the past of both converge, the salvation of one was the defeat to the other, the power of Voldemort transferred to Potter at a crucial time. Harry discovers a common nexus linking it to the qualities of the House of Slicerin and the dark legend that drag in their powers and abilities. In it, Harry raises questions about his true origin.As for Voldemort, we discover is calling Tom Riddle in his teens, and that already he then conspired to eliminate all those, according to the tenets of Slicerin, which were dirty blood, i.e., children of non-magic people. This hechiceril racism begins to collect plot weight as a ploy to tell a story on struggles for power and influence in the world of Hogwarts, which, from now on, is no longer a world of enjoyment-based gossip and anecdotes mágico-delirantes, Pixies and other typical of the "Potter style" "tics", now a more sinister story begins, with a much more adult tone.However, the problem of "philosopher's stone" was not as a film, but his plot, weak and too scattered. On the other hand, in "Chamber of secrets", apart from being a tale dark and not without some macabre details, history gets progress on a very clear and pervasive thread: the dark threat of a conspiracy and terror kept in secret corners of Hogwarts. The writers and director, do not lose time with sentimental pretensions about the parents of the protagonist or football matches on horseback of a broom, or how does or is pronounced as or which spell, unlike its precedent, which force you want to show much, little chance of development there. "Chamber of secrets", on the other hand, role brilliantly his tale of mystery, a tale of mystery in a Gothic atmosphere and using a more somber tone, which translates into an increase in dramatic force, welcomed. "Chamber of secrets" not only have fun, also handles a smart suspense and it offers some chilling time. What in "philosopher's stone" not finished booting, that suggestive decorated product of one of the best addresses art that they have been in recent years but devoid of appropriate intensity and narrative effectiveness here expands its possibilities as an amazing visual folletín at times, lukewarm in others, but always interesting, never forget the story you want to tell. The myth-poetic elements - elves, magic wands, ghosts, memories in a forgotten book, a trail of spiders that guides us into the dark forest, healing tears of a Phoenix, etc - are no longer just a nice to see scenery, but is now the framework inherent in the history of Harry and his friends.That is why we have a good example of palomitero film with own soul and uniqueness. A narrative clarity in a story focused on a very specific leitmotif, is compounded by a mythological space which is a defining characteristic of the style. Contents and human profiles form a whole developed and coherent with the forms, both of artwork in the effective direction. We talk about the minimum payable in a good movie adventures, to continue dragging some problems, too much maybe the character played by Kenneth Branaght, participant of luxury, but as a frivolous character. In conclusion, the saga of Harry Potter begins to be cinematically solid when at the charming and playful designs and their particular "tics", joins a content set out clearly, winning in dramatic force. And we insist: Entertainment film does not mean "vacuous cinema". Entertaining films must also find its "sediment" of depth, their identity as film representation of a world. "Chamber of secrets" is not a work of art, but this requirement with moderate solvency. For this reason, it is a decent film, while "Transformers" - to give a current example - is cow poop.</body>
</review>
