<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>That could have been, taking advantage of the powerful argument of the book, the best film of the saga of Harry Potter has become a small bluff, with a considerably Orgasmic final Fireworks.</summary>
	<body>Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix is the longest book in the saga of the young magician (893 pages, are not feat), but however, his film adaptation has the footage more short movies inspired by the mythology created by J.K. Rowling.Y note an egg.Takes a regular in almost everything: the screenplay by Michael Goldenberg (debutant in Harry Potter) is poorly adapted, and the mediocrilla direction of David Yates (who will direct the next film, Harry Potter and the half-blood Prince) doesn't help much. It is full of incomprehensible facilones and resources that can be confused that does not know in advance the story (if up to me I had confused!), such as the creation of Dumbledore's army, the discovery of the room where the E.D. practiced, and obtaining the worst memory of Snape Harry. In addition, the pace is a disaster.I am aware that in a film adaptation will have to change many things, but there are some rather vital details of the book for the plot here have ignored completely. or be included without explaining what they are, only so that fans of the book say "Oh, this!", but first see them the film will stay with the face of moniato.Therefore, that Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix is the most short film of the saga film, taking into account that the book is the longest, it seems to me an error. The plot is not well defined, and has even half of half of half of the tension and the bad feeling that they had in the book: not feel at any time that something big is brewing within the magical world (at least until near the end).Now, the final act, the part of the Ministry of magic, is a joy, and fairly faithful to the book.Struggles between good and bad wizards is a very enjoyable visual delirium, although there are shots in which is not absolutely nothing, and the final between two of the greatest wizards, it is very well done; very electrifying.This final act and some other things that I liked a lot (Luna Lovegood, Dolores Umbridge, the cestrals, the twins Weasley, the first ten minutes, the new design of the death eaters.), give the approved justito, but very sweet and sour.That could have been, taking advantage of the powerful argument of the book, the best film of the saga of Harry Potter has become a small bluff, with a considerably Orgasmic final Fireworks.</body>
</review>
