<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Transformers" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Transformers has the ability of making me enjoy as a toddler in a movie theater, as any movie has done for some time.</summary>
	<body>Amazing. Transformers, the new comercialoide super virguería of Michael Bay (director of clunkers as Pearl Harbor, but also of real wonders as two rebel policemen 2), has had the admirable capacity of having transported to the past, to return to feel a kid of ten years enjoying a blockbuster summer as those already not made, for after leaving the cinemafantasize and play down the street on seen on screen and want to immediately buy the shift action figures.The characters are quite flat (despite the efforts of Shia Labeouf, which is huge), his sense of humor is sometimes too child and lead, and history is simpler than the mechanism of a Transformer (sorry for the joke xD). but it is rapidly entertaining, it has one of the best rhythms of the year (lasting more than two hours and gets you on a flight) and, best of all, not be takes seriously itself.Bay is aware that you have between hands is absurd to take him to the movies, a cartoon series about giant robots with its own life are transformed into things and are in continuous war only would have to stay in that, in a series of cartoons. Out of the top hat a roller coaster gruesomely entertaining and enjoyable, with great sense of humor and he is aware of this (in occasions too), sometimes even up to autoparódico (attention to the conversation between a very irritating COP, played by John Turturro!, and the two kids protagonists, in a car, on the Transformers!!), without any hint of pretentiousness (a part of wanting to sell many cartoons of action.) or delusions of grandeurthat up is allowed launch poisoned darts to the Bush administration!By far the best premiere big what you carry summer, and one of the most spectacular films of recent years. Pure cinema of evasion, full of fireworks good, is enjoyed, despite some too sudden camera movements in the action sequences, to the Batman Begins. Bay.Es tipiquísimos a genuine pity that many people be swayed by their prejudices, and her cane to the film because it is directed by Michael Bay, or simply because it is an action film. If the film, as he came, her signed James Cameron, another Rooster sing?</body>
</review>
