<review author="Bruji" title="Chuecatown" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tape full of absurdities, that start with a bad script, crowned worst dialogues; they reach a novice director, that anything you serve close-ups; to lead to some interpretations lamentabilísimas.</summary>
	<body>Between the "Percebe Rue" and an episode of the last season of "Here no hay quien viva", the writers of this free (and bad) adaptation comic of Rafa, forget that the creation of characters almodovarianos can only birth of La Mancha grace that they are unaware. The director, meanwhile, forgotten address. The actors interpret. The Viewer, what is the cinema. How is that of the new law?, for each Spanish film that we impose, will have to see three American to not forget what is cinema?, will someone ensure the quality of tax products?, are they at the height of the Spanish public?, what criteria governed the granting of State subsidies?, what subsequent premieres?.Is true that a good film, seen by anyone, and that only very lovers are able to swallow us any crappy, and write about them; but, even so, should not fill the glass of water droplets. You can come a time in which also "very lovers" abandon the screening room, a fact that has not seen in theaters since my earliest childhood, one that I started with titles like New York under the terror of the Zombies. For different reasons, Chuecatown is the typical film of which is that of it seems impossible that "is ispirado" something to someone other than the desire to run.And yet the thing not painted wrong remote initially. Divertidamente absurd situations, with a touch of black humour, accompanied by timely and effective blows of laughter. Characters who are struggling out of the marble that surrounds them, and could have been attractive to the Viewer. The frutera with literary aspirations, the aggressive Executive to the "Spanish Psyco", or the Inspector of police that collects all the unimaginable phobias, were inside the perfect mold. An original and coherent argument away from the typical comedietas of bed and tits to which we are accustomed, it tends towards the curious and unusual thriller. A proposal that dared to make funny allusions to Hitchcock film, with the animosity of Marnie (the thief) to the color red and the change of name of Anthony Perkins (Bates by Foster) in psychosis, which also parodies the famous shower scene. A pattern, in short, that would become a film unobtrusive and entertaining, especially recommended for a double session of DVD.However, the drawn line is not know keep beyond the first fifteen minutes of footage, proceeding to the resolution of the plot with pantomimes derived from mythical titles of the best Spanish films. I mean, of course, the quotations the League magic (Antonio Ozores, 1980), intelligent political jokes of El Cid Cabreador (Angelino Fons, 1983), and as it could not be otherwise, to great performances by Christopher Columbus, discoverer ex officio. These two last, belonging to the historical genre, that lot and well cultivated our film. Titles, all with one common denominator that remains undaunted in the history of Flahn, which gives different characters, equal records.The end result, discover us a tape full of absurdities, that start with a bad script, crowned worst dialogues; they reach a novice director, that anything serve close-ups achieved through mirrors (typical in the Filmography of Don Pedro Almodóvar); to lead to some interpretations lamentabilísimas. The characteristic of a deal doomed to a very bad direction of actors, which only survives, and not in all cases, Pepón Nieto.Llegados at this point that the crappy begins to emerge in all their addresses, the only possible solution to prevent the disaster would have been the recourse to an effective and misleading advertising, passed by holder product "The mystery of the dark room"offering an erotic thriller with nudity of Pablo Puyol. American cinema would have done so. They don't have the healthy habit of lying, but bad. More, as not that would work us, came to the conclusion, fellow filmmakers, that the only effective remedy so the public does not jump from his armchair at the minute forty-eight and exclame something as Spanish as go movie shit!, is none other than the put to work. that it is high time.</body>
</review>
