<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Harry Potter has lost the sense of humor and, at the same time, that art almost magical that it hooked to millions of viewers of all ages. We must encourage this guy that is doing most to forced marches, albeit based on Prozac or similar.</summary>
	<body>Harry Potter is depressed. And its writer also. Or at least that is the impression I got after seeing Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix, the fifth, and at the moment, latest film installment of the character created by writer j. k. Rowling children's literature and which opens tomorrow in the Spanish screens.Voldemort has returned from the darkness, while Potter - by use magic outside Hogwarts School of witchcraft and wizardry, in defence of his hateful cousin Dudley - can be punished with the possible expulsion of the Centre. Bad rolls are installed in his head: the death of a fellow student; the memory of his murdered parents; the thirst for revenge and personal contempt which is submitted by the director Hogwarts after having reinstated this in his Academy, will be making it into a sad, gray and lonely.David Yates, the director, for the first time facing the universe of Potter and company. And does so in a pesarosa manner, a bit under this abatement which marks the own Harry Potter. The film, apart from owning a pace alarmingly slow, is confusing and wrong narrated in many of its passages. His lack of consistency in the script, makes it look equipped with a number of characters in any developed and unnecessary. A good example of this is what happens with the ghostly presence of Helena Bonham Carter that, giving life to the tantalizing and evil Beatrix Lestrange, seems stuck under pressure in the history with the sole intention of having another famosillo to give a little more than brilliance to its, already alone luxurious credits. Things of the marketing and the box office, I say.Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix costs it a lot to boot. And when it does, it is halfway inks. All the (theoretical) tension that goes accumulating over your footage, explodes in his last twenty minutes of projection. It is undeniable that, at that time, the tape acquires a caliber more vibrant and interesting but, despite trying to trace this narrative heaviness with her has been developing, the situations of action that offers at its apex, remain dark and with little force.If something positive is this chapter, it is located in the good intention to break somewhat with the classic plot scheme defined by the four previous titles. In fact, the tape begins and ends in the city and the subsurface of London, giving less prominence to the familiar grounds of Hogwarts School, place in which unfolds the central part (and more pesarosa) of the same.A splendid and promising, prologue filmed outdoors and using a tone very close to the Steven Spielberg film; a wonderful and very visual scene inside of a gigantic overshadowed room, littered with shelves filled with balls of glass, and the delirious presence of an unbeatable Imelda Stanton in the role of a pathetic woman with dictatorial cravings, is more remarkable work that denotes the fatigue of a series that still missing two chapters ahead. Harry Potter has lost the sense of humor and, at the same time, that art almost magical that it hooked to millions of viewers of all ages. We must encourage this guy that is doing most to forced marches, albeit based on Prozac or similar. A visit to the psychiatrist would not go you bad. Someone has to get the pit which has sunk. And, surely, insofar as it is achieved, we will gain all face coming titles.</body>
</review>
