<review author="Jose Contreras" title="La sombra de una duda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What could do that Hitchcock felt so satisfied by a work like this?</summary>
	<body>When Hitchcock filmed "Suspicion", became known that was going to be one of its calvaries in Hollywood producers, and not him, would take key decisions in their stories. They rule the end. It had hired Cary Grant to mercenary husband a spinster, and Hitchcock could not shoot the end that he knew that it was important to this story, Cary Grant guilty, because Cary Grant was a star. "Shadow of a doubt" is in many senses "Suspicion" but written from another angle. The same story but as if Cary Grant had a niece who idolizes and gradually discovers his dark past. In the shadow of a doubt", Hitchcock hired not a major star, but Joseph Cotten, why could leave him the role of bad.Uncle Charlie (Cotten) flees from the police, and decides to take refuge in Santa Rosa, a Californian village where his sister lives. His niece Charlie idolizes him, but gradually discovers that his past hides something shady. Police investigating him and an agent falls in love with her. The detective tells her that Uncle Charlie might be a killer they call "the killer of the merry widows". That is why it does not want to hear the waltz when sang it the niece, and also a page of the newspaper that pulled. It also explains the initials of a ring which he gave to the niece."Police stop looking, because it is a false culprit, but niece wants his uncle abandons the family, and the guy wants to get rid of the niece."According to Hitchcock "Shadow of a doubt" is one of his most logical films. A film for 'Our friends our friends the logicians, psychologists' however it is not enough. The killer of the film is a killer of tambourine, a character without depth. Does make sense murder of a loved one, a naïve girl posed no danger, and that would in addition giving a million tracks to the police? None, except the have the audience in suspense. To enjoy hichcock must be set in its details and its plots, perhaps in his style, but must turn a blind eye to their human beings. what could do that Hitchcock felt so satisfied by a work like this? The favourite game of the master, the "who knows what" isn't squeezed to the maximum: niece Charlie, knows that Uncle Charlie is a murderer, the family does not know anything, the public suspected from the first image, police failed to investigate the case. I think that for Hitchcock could be stimulating the amount of things he says without getting to talk about them. Ring, the waltz and a visit rushed to the library of Santa Rosa put the niece to an absolute certainty. But the niece does not speak of it, not even with his uncle, only says: «leave». Two successive accidents make us think that the guy wants to kill the niece, but we do not see him work. Someone could give a plausible explanation that the guy is innocent. The game of Hitchcock is in the amount of things that is telling us, without showing any in front of our eyes. No dialogues, nor the images show us what we are seeing: that the niece is in danger and that the guy is a killer without scruples.François Truffaut: Know that Shadow of Doubt (the shadow of a doubt) is of all his films which you prefer. I believe, however, that if unfortunately disappeared all of his remaining films, Shadow of Doubt would give an inaccurate idea of the "Hitchcock touch». Instead, Notorious (chained) would leave a more faithful picture of his style.AFRED Hitchcock: Should not say that Shadow of a Doubt is my favorite film. If I have sometimes argued in this sense is because I realize that this film is satisfactory for our friends the credible, our friends the logicians.François Truffaut:. our friends and psychologists.AFRED Hitchcock:. Yes, our friends and psychologists. It is, therefore, a weakness on my part, because if on the one hand I intend not to worry about the plausibility, on the other hand I worried for her. I am only human after all! But, surely, the second reason is the memory so enjoyable that I keep working with Thornton Wilder. In England, he had always managed to the collaboration of the best stars and the best writers. In America had not happened the same and he had received negative on the part of some stars and some writers who despised the kind of work that interests me. That is why I was suddenly very pleasant and satisfactory to discover that one of the best American writers was willing to work with me and to take the work seriously.[.]Thornton Wilder had worked in a very realistic way, in particular for all that conierne to the city and decor. We had chosen a House and Wilder feared that it would be too big for a small bank employee. After an investigation we discovered the type who lived in that House was in the same economic situation as our character and then Wilder was satisfied. When we returned to the city, before filming, the type, so happy of his home out in the film, had painted her. We were forced to paint it all again ' dirty' and of course, at the end of the film is it returned to paint everything again.[.]François Truffaut: Shadow of Doubt to, with Psycho, one of the rare films in which the main character is the villain and the public much sympathizes with it, probably because not seen ever murdering the widows.AFRED Hitchcock: Probably, and moreover is an idealistic assassin. It is part of those murderers who feel in them a mission of destruction. Maybe that widows mereciesen what was happening to them, but wasn't affair do. The film poses a moral judgment, right?, as Cotten is destroyed at the end, albeit accidentally, by his niece. That is to say that not all the bad ones are black nor all the heroes are white. There is grey everywhere. Uncle Charlie wanted to much to her niece, but not as much as wanted you her to him. However, she has had to destroy it, because we must not forget that Oscar Wilde said: «kill what amamos.»»François Truffaut: A propósito de Shadow of Doubt there is a point of detail that worries me; in the first scene of the station, when it comes to the train that goes to descend the uncle Charlie, there is a huge black smoke coming out of the chimney of the locomotive, and when the train approaches, obscures the platform. I have the impression that it was a deliberate thing because, at the end of the film, in the second scene of the station when the train is going, only a little white smoke.AFRED Hitchcock: Indeed, for the first scene had requested much black smoke; It is one of these ideas that one bothers much without that then they realize secure, but here were lucky: the position of the Sun produced a nice shadow on the station.François Truffaut: does this black smoke can be translated by 'here is the devil that enters the city'?AFRED Hitchcock: Yes, of course. In the same vein, in The Birds, when Jessica Tandy goes in his truck after having discovered the corpse of the farmer, he got a real shock and, to preserve this emotion, I did leave the car exhaust smoke and dust of the road this also contrasts with the peaceful scene of arrival: the road slightly wet and without smoke in the exhaust pipe.</body>
</review>
