<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Obras en Casa" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unfortunately, works at home does not offer any special incentive that justifies viewing.</summary>
	<body>In the comedy, there are some very recurring themes exploited endlessly by the various film, but which by some strange whim of fate almost always achieve their goal: succeed at the box office. There is no doubt that one of them is the domestic reforms, something that in real life can be the worst of the dramas, but that on the big screen always acquires tone of comedy.By coincidence, that at the end of last year opened another French comedy that dealt with the same subject, the House of your dreams. Both were two separate taquillazos in the Gallic country, but in ours the first passed without penalty or glory. Now it is the turn to works at home, but the big question is will bring something new or is more of the same? Unfortunately, Brigitte Roüan film does not offer any special incentive to justify viewing. Instead, the screen parading endless supposedly comical situations that will make blush embarrassed the more painted Viewer. The scenes occur wildly, as if the argument were only the pretext that serves to fill between gag and gag. The script is nothing more than a mere excuse for the showcasing of a Carole Bouquet in full attack of hysteria, which should cause sound laughter among the French public. At this point, and given the type of comedy that comes from France, the most obvious conclusion is that one of the things that we do not share is the same sense of humor. However, the film has a good point, and is that not everything could be horrific. Works at home also addresses the issue of illegal immigration, and intended to convey a message of tolerance and coexistence in harmony. The key word is intended, that Brigitte Roün uses the alleged social complaint to illegal immigrants become victims of bad jokes.Works at home is a comedy that exploits a spent format, and does so without offering anything new. What is most amazing of all, is that after seeing tapes like this, one just to remember with affection and longing that prank of this House is in ruins, and miss the Tom Hanks ducks and clown.</body>
</review>
