<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Red Road" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Road network is first and foremost a film little honest with itself and with the Viewer, full of unnecessary artificial tricks that divert the attention of its chief virtue, history.</summary>
	<body>The theorem that reads "any reaction followed a consequence" is physics and philosophy, elemental. In recent years, the film industry has followed the footsteps of major productions full of special effects, by putting the spectacular and dividends at the box office to a good history. One consequence was the independent movement, innovative proposals, and another way of seeing and understanding the film.Road network is part of the Advance Party project, a proposal a priori very interesting, which consists of three movies based on the same characters created by Lone Scherfig and Anders Thomas Jensen. The directorial debut of Andrea Arnold, winner of the jury prize at the 2006 Cannes Film Festival, is the first of these tapes. Jackie (Katie Dickie) works in the city of Glasgow carefully monitor images from security cameras scattered throughout the city. One day, go on your monitor to Clyde (Tony Curran), a man who hoped not to see in his life again. Thus, slowly starts a story showing fully and openly the miseries of the human soul, which is gradually capturing the attention of the Viewer to immerse it in a spiral from which it is impossible to escape. At least, it would be impossible to escape if the film does not convey that so annoying sense of artifice. Amdrea Arnold tells the story sparingly, feeding the intrigue and anxiety of the Viewer, but does it jumping some rules. The script is full of tricks and blows from effect to cause confusion, to believe what is not, diverting attention from what really matters. When dissipates the smoke curtain woven by Arnold, there will be anyone who finds it deliciously perverse, or there will be who sits fairly cheated. And it is that Red Road right at the bottom, but fails miserably in the form.Road network is first and foremost a film little honest with itself and with the Viewer, full of unnecessary artificial tricks that divert the attention of its chief virtue, history.</body>
</review>
