<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Harry Skywalker has returned to postpone ineluctables plans of fate, but.... (are pending libraries, hamburger and establishments in the industry)</summary>
	<body>Francis Bacon said based they have that science and magic tended to the same goal. This complicity was broken when the Science left behind the magic to apply as a more efficient method to achieve this goal. All that knew J.K. Rowling when it began the saga of Harry Potter. I knew that a magician with a wand child needed a fabulous props and founded a dazzling universe of train stations false, verbal charms to the old-fashioned and worlds hidden beneath the apparent with its formidable battles Vertigo, litigation and even schools erected daunting landscapes. Literature gave the go-ahead to the film and was born a marvelous franchise, one of the best views recently, billed with imagination and desires of pleasing the teen eye than before, with greedy fruition had devoured hundreds of sheets. And the film has found in the adventures of Wizard Potter a robust, unaffordable to discouragement, well equipped Philo of the usual round of tricks that will delight the épila, albeit without neglecting the patient assistance of adults, not initiated into the mystery books Revelation and unrelated to the symbolic alphabet of the universe fundancional. But we have reached the summer five or six, I do not know now, Potter was and the product enabled the circumstances is not dark, as it was checked by Cuarón, or complicit in these technical watermarks so pleasant to the vicissitudes of the magician has strengthened with no new pirotecnica which encandile the eye.Everything that once was basically clean exercise fantastic, vitamin rich characters, good articulation dramatic and overwhelming visual imagery has been now diminished, reduced to a correct, but dreary, cumbersome film of easy assimilation and easier still evacuation.Already the fact that part of the bizarre propaganda machine of the film trust your hitch with the public prepubescent or already lúbricamente pubescent a stylized Kiss Harry good plant moza accomplice of their mystery Arts it scale. The reckless Potter, before his magical brain sort the deserving dramatic chapters of his childhood, does not find love: what has entered its ojito is the carnal passion, the pull of hormones to muscle his voice and ensures that the adult Wizard has entered into scene for the greater glory of future clashes with the Unnamable, true spiritual mentor of all the adventure and, apparently, brazen plot remake of another series already sufficiently known, Stars Wars. Potter is a Skywalker of darker legend with his Darth Vader-family Fund, which draws as the hero to the Propp obstacles common to invest as hero or villain all the sidereal Lucas pilot wielding a spectacular lightsaber, only candy of children around the world, and Harry wields a wand of spells and incantations arguments. Logistical support is the same.Fascinate, however, some specific episodes: the scene of the balls of the prophecies or the majestic and clean of unnecessary barroquismos final match. Mention apart the character of Dolores Umbridge, a sobreactuada, but effects Imelda Staunton. Or a sweet and captivating Ivanna Lynch in the role of Luna Lovegood (of the pudding, Yes, with the face and the voice closest to the ether of woman who is Nawja Nimri) the creature of J.K. Rowling has yet bread that cut into the table of these summers of big screen and terrifying tails in view of that the next literary installment (half-blood Prince) for the brass bands symphonic in press and similar. It is at the bottom of alfombrar following delivery, start preparing personnel in new initiatory rites and lead them with estimable style and naturalness to the next queue. We will be there.</body>
</review>
