<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good debut in the direction of Félix Viscarret, with a good script and some good performances.</summary>
	<body>"Under the stars" is the debut in the direction of feature film produced by Felix Viscarret, until now renowned short film maker, who also wrote the screenplay based on the novel "The trumpeter of the Utopia" Fernando Aramburu.La tape account history of Benito Lacunza, a sleazy waiter aspiring jazz musician who returns to his people to attend the funeral of his father. There he discovers that his brother Lalo has pushed girlfriend, Nines, a friend Benito knows of their adolescent revelries. Their lives and relationships will change when Benito meet the daughter of Nines, which will establish a very special friendship.Struck by the amount of good works of the Spanish film I'm seeing lately. Tapes in which note a fondness for characters in forms and in the background that are encouraging care. It is no stranger to this current emotional, sad and yet fun script Viscarret.Dicho script has strong characters, real losers that may seem rare, and even a few mamarrachos (as it is the case of the protagonist in the first half hour of the film) but that we must take them the dot to appreciate them. In this sense, I believe everything with a knob of a door as a visual metaphor for the characters.And as I mention about the pomo, say that all this gag continued (of those that work for accumulation) is treated with intelligence by the director so fails to never tire. A good demonstration of how to make a running gag narrativamente without sobreexplotarlo.But a script needs, inevitably, a few actors who know how to make them consistent without falling into excesses. Violeta Rodríguez, Julián Villagrán, Alberto San Juan and Emma Suárez are outstanding in this regard. I was not very fan of Alberto San Juan (pardon the rhyme) long but I have to admit that, with each job yours I am seeing, I will like more.It is not a perfect film, that much is clear. The first half hour is something weaker than the rest, partly because it takes enough to connect with the main character for his antipathy and his selfishness. It is joining the already game all characters when the tape is the right pace and engages the viewer until the end.What I've been suggesting in passing but I must make an express mention to the direction of Félix Viscarret which I consider to be very exciting for the future. From here wish you all the luck in the world?Although debuting with a good film, also produced by Fernando Trueba, it is difficult to improve luck.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 6.5 out of 10</body>
</review>
