<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film for all ages served with efficiency and without insulting the intelligence of young people or adults</summary>
	<body>After so many months of posters, trailers and comments that may have tired more than one comes to our cinemas the fifth installment of the adventures of Harry Potter, "Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix" and directed by David Yates.Una once again, courtesy of Warner Bros. Spain, saw the film in a press pass few days ago by what you come to tell you my impressions thatin fact, not different too of which I have on the previous film in the series.And it is that there is no big surprises in this new installment of the adventures of the young Wizard and I start to fear me that he won't never be. Fear to disappoint or excessively surprise your target audience prevents those responsible for taking risks and requires them to constantly continue longer paths.I do not mean that not worth going to see it, at all. The film is entertaining, can be seen easily and those who we've had more or less well with previous tapes of the series we can get to feel satisfied.But while it is true that one passes a fun time during the slide show, it is not less true that after leaving the room becomes inevitable to feel a certain distaste. The issue is becoming a little repetitive and, curiously, seems to be losing some of the magic of previous deliveries.Not deny that this chapter is quite dark and that reflected an evolution in the characters well interpreted by a few actors who have already made theirs, that makes the viewer feel as close to them and tracked without any problems with them. Interesting are also some of the new characters, such as, the light-heartedness and mysterious Luna Lovegood which would make any surprise in new releases.It is also true that already feels the nearness of the end of the adventure and that it shows in the film. Very efficiently, are creating tension in the viewer that is already anxious to know what will be the solution to all problems. I hope that the climax did not disappoint but there are a couple of scenes in this movie that made me worry, to suggest a possible outcome style "the Empire strikes back" that would consider it me quite little original.Needless to say that technically the film gives the stature, though I am surprised that at this stage a night flight by a city can be so cantoso as the Donner Superman flights, and the art direction is one of the strengths of the tape.In short, film for all ages served with efficiency and without insulting the intelligence of young people or adults. Already more than can you tell other successes of this, so far, is disheartening year of cinema.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 6.5 out of 10</body>
</review>
