<review author="Tyler" title="28 semanas después" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The photo is cruel, and the script is little well-meaning, which makes this movie a true madness of the macabre, with anthologies scenes, superb gratuitous violence and blood to GLUGs.</summary>
	<body>28 Days later was the film of "zombies" (but they were not) what version of Steven Spielberg's "The war of the worlds" film based on extraterrestrial invasions.Realism wholesomeness, echo from a point of view physical and primary, the movie took the issue seriously and was not taking the hair to the characters (which on the other hand does not have why be bad) If you imagine the months following the fine "The war of the worlds" also have an entertaining film. As well, "28 weeks later" mra as it would be London 28 weeks after the infection of the virus of the ira.The approach is simple and the movie too, and that is something of which you have to learn the film. simple. The movie is nearly perfect if it isn't already. I believe that it will become a classic as well as its predecessor. Not be if it is better or worse, and I don't care about, I think are pelisque debian exist, the perfect sequel and prequel to the perfect. I.e. it is not an unnecessary sequel to learn pasta that I gave the first, no, this movie had to happen. I wanted to know that it would happen after the first move.Danny Boyle decided not he directed, was too busy with "SUNSHINE", and he sought out someone saw the very correct "intact" and hit the touch to the compatriot our Juan Carlos Fresnadillo, that after several meetings he decided to access taking as a condition to tweak the script, Boyle was agree... and the thing started. Luckily.The movie has a fucking great rhythm with a morbid realization, necessary thing, the camera is infected, it's almost more from the point of view of the infection that's not infection. Influenced by the first but not like that, "28 weeks later" is more brutal, more violent, more kooky.It has little to do with horror from now, because it is not made as a horror movie, is more like a science fiction as possible. as a version to the beast of "JURASSIC Park".It is terror, but it doesn't. It has a touch almost of that film that is towards in the 1980s in Germany or Italy or USA. The MONDO film, extreme violence. The little care with what is said, the little responsibility with what he sees.Even though and that many smart people say, it has nothing to do with the war of Iraq. people see absurd Parallels. It is a movie, point. A fucking great movie that people who make films must learn.The secuenciacon that opens the movie is masterful, to learn from it, study it, watching. The rhythm is vibrating from the beginning, but has required moments of rest. rest not without tension, is as a bacterial film, as a biochemical weapon as that release in the movie. You feel great seeing it is not these films that leave you bad body. As part of the infection, the film is infection.The photo is cruel, and the script is little well-meaning, which makes this movie a true madness of the macabre, with anthologies scenes, superb gratuitous violence and blood to GLUGs.In addition to a nihilistic view of man as a waste of the Earth. actually, I think we should all die, diseases are actually necessary to put an end to part of humanity once. That one thinks when he sees the movie.A movie that is worth more than we think, a fucking great film and a flat finish that gives meaning to everything.</body>
</review>
