<review author="José A. Peig" title="Harry Potter y el prisionero de Azkaban" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spare not missing anything in the course of the narrative. Even in the scenes on magical teachings, screenwriter and director managed to prevent were spare parts of filling - a defect common to the two previous deliveries - and work here integrated into the main reasons: the mystery of Sirius Black, the Dementors and fears of Harry Potter.</summary>
	<body>Alfonso Cuarón is a filmmaker who uses a striking aesthetic, likes to play with the images and create planos-secuencias of great visual strength, or diverse frames that go from lírico-colorista to an ochre dark and macabre, emphasizing sometimes tragic situation with subtle expression. There is a fairly widespread misconception that defines it as "author" or "independent" director. But this is a mistake. It is true that film what counts is the singular vision of a creator who creates your world through the eye of the camera. However, a complete aesthetic works requires something more you framing suggestive and imaginative. Or combine in a balanced way the continent (images, framing, mounting, levels, chromatic resources, art direction, etc.) with the content (topics, development of characters and history, emotional connection, etc). With all this we come to say that Cuarón is a skilled and creative filmmaker in the Mise en scène, but weak when the question is to a regular and strong outline its dramatic look, the content of the story. In this same booklet explained that children of men is a sweeping visual spectacle, but too weak and irregular in the construction of a human set and a truly unique content. The prisoner of Azkaban is another example of the same. Cuarón maximized the potential of the universe "harrypotteriano": plays with images with remarkable lyrical sensitivity, Hogwarts is an ideal space to display the visual imagination and it shows that the filmmaker is in its sauce, creates images based on the circumstances without Miss or a single element; a flower Withers to the passage of the sinister Dementors, fall leaves a happy tree on depth of field which culminates with the castle of Hogwarts, introduces us to the paradoxes of time through a flat stream that runs through the bowels of a large mechanical clock. More that a strong Narrator, Cuarón is engaged in painting pictures taking advantage of the orography of the world of Hogwarts.Con a particular visual style is not forged a masterpiece. The root of the problem may not be in the work of J.K Rowling both the profile of the filmmaker. Taking into account that we are in the third installment, go 140 minutes to discover that Harry Potter had a godfather who was believed guilty but then is that he is innocent (go man), and that the real culprit is the rat of Ron, is fairly insubstantial. The plot and history are too flimsy to conclude that we we have a great fantastic film, despite the strength that give off many of his images and the laudable attempt to Cuarón to achieve a progression regarding the two previous films. It is intended that the third act the Potter saga acquires a darker tone, with testosterone making mischief in the budding teen age of its protagonists. We see Harry or Hermione hitting punching drop some other typical cry of acne, faced his uncle and the teachers, but with these gestures is she cannot talk of further development or complexity of the characters since they constitute the leitmotif on which basis a distinction with respect to the previous, but we cannot talk of any development. The only thing that could have saved the pitfall of a story so flimsy and repetitive with respect to provided in his two preceding (change of a child tone to a more teenager tone does any progression if history and context does not encourage the development of the characters itself.) Make sure the reader that the film insists on the subject of always: search by part of Harry, of the past and his real family), would be that Cuarón achieved to make your visual expressiveness was in an adequate match of the dramatic content of the history. But to this end, the gaze of Cuarón is too cold and impersonal. No mistake: Cuaron offers us a genuine look and staff own the universe "harrypotteriano" (from their physical elements and mitopoéticos), through its implementation in scene the environment and landscape. But is vulgar and repetitive in the flat dramatic: Harry, Hermione, Ron, and the remaining human background of the story, follow the same basic patterns in its precedents, are anecdotal and added costumes to the visual style, without consistency between this and that. And so there is no way to balance the product. Why "the Chamber of secrets" is a much more complete and balanced in its different strata film. Columbus is not - nor pretends to be him - an independent filmmaker. His sober style, following the classicism of Spielberg, combined quite well the expression and visual design with a story of mystery and Gothic horror very close to their characteristics.Cuarón, instead try to create poetry and Visual flourishes, but lacks the genius they possess the true authors of the seventh art: the ability to make visual poems inherent - concordant, sequential, parallel - to the deep beat the dramatic content or the meanings of the story. And what criteria used film critic to differentiate one from the other? How could prove that Cuarón visual resources are not properly conjugated with dramatic content?. Here we talked about the hermeneutics of art. It is somewhat intuitive, there are no fixed rules, it cannot be explained in ten lines. In any case, any spectator attentive and endowed with the necessary intuitive ability will see itself that "prisoner of Azkaban" is, at the bottom, and despite appearances, a film failed in relation to its claims.The magnificent use of the structure is its best asset, in any case. This is a film in which not enough or lack nothing in the course of the narrative. Even in the scenes on magical teachings (the classroom and the teachers), screenwriter and director managed to prevent were spare parts of filling - a defect common to the two previous deliveries - and work here integrated into the main reasons: the mystery of Sirius Black, the Dementors and fears of Harry Potter.</body>
</review>
