<review author="JohnTrent" title="Cuando un extraño llama" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>?When to call a stranger? It is, therefore, an elongated version of the scene telephone Scream but not as effective</summary>
	<body>I have a standard that I always try to meet, it's not to see a remake before seeing the original film that is based. I usually meet, although I must say that in this case I breached this rule. Anyway I do not think that he assess differently the original after seeing the remake that happened to comment on, and it is that "When a stranger calls", as I understand, just grab the original the first minutes to extend them for an hour and a quarter.In the 1990s, "Scream" had used for his spectacular opening scene the idea of that film of the 1970s which discussed. The scene in which saw Drew Barrymore be harassed by telephone by a psychopath until finally massacred, only lengthened one ten minutes but their effectiveness was absolute. "When called a strange" comes to be, therefore, an elongated that scene but not so effective version.Anyway, we are not in a movie so bad and expendable as they have committed to say many. The first thing that surprised me was the photography of Peter Menzies Jr, especially in the first fifteen minutes, where also highlights Simon West planning after the cameras, more solvent than expected. "After these first minutes the thing is divided into more or less disturbing moments, several scares and no surprise given that they already gut us everything in the trailer.""When called a stranger" is far from being a notable film, but does not damage your viewing. In fact, that it writes spent it well seeing this "slasher" without a punishment deaths not a drop of blood, and that already is something to take into account, because a "slasher" without those two aspects may have a fairly small interest. Simon West is a mediocre, but within what should be saved the ballot without excesses, without trying something more that see you a screen, i.e., a "teen movie" squishy and accessible to everyone, which is as fast as it is forgotten and where there is no seek nothing more than entertainment.Interpretations and the script does not have been mentioned over the criticism, as you already adored because there to give them the most minimal importance. Few performers coming out only are there to make gestures and, from time to time, drop a sentence that could be avoided and the script puts in the mouth of those performers these sentences that could be avoided and, incidentally, is a mere excuse to set up an approach and reach a "standard" length.I will try to get soon the "When called a strange" original and already I will give my opinion in this regard, but I doubt that it has great similarities with this remake. Anyway, "When called a strange", the remake, suffers greatly from that "air noventero" so clean and well checked makes no great favors to the film's genre, or at least to the "slasher" of series b that so many joys gave amateur beyond by the 1970s and 1980s. I.e. in this film is imposed at all times political correctness, being notoriously precast everything to get out of kitchen and serve without problems. The end result could be worse.</body>
</review>
