<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Isn't enough, obviously with a brilliant ending: the set confirms that the series is not at his best film.</summary>
	<body>Was to be expected: David Yates, the director of the fifth chapter of the Harry Potter series (and what is worse, the next delivery, as it was announced), was not the most appropriate for the strongest youth of early 21st century saga. Yates has a mediocre full curriculum of works for television, none of them evolved, so it becomes strange to know what saw in the Warner to hire him (and rebound, as in gymnastics.). Effectively, the first part is desvaída, no personality, relying the filmmaker in the knowledge that the Viewer already has the characters rather than a true progression of the plot. It is true that "Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix", in his literary version, is the weaker (along with the second installment, "Harry Potter and the Chamber of secrets") of the series imagined by J.K. Rowling, but is also that of bad novels have become magnificent films: the case of "The lady from Shanghai" is recurring. Yates is limited during the first one hundred minutes, put in images the new adventures of the little (well, no longer both.) Wizard: membership in the order of the Phoenix, after being attacked in the quiet streets of London by the Dementors; the ministerial refusal to believe in the return of Voldemort, according to Harry; taxation in the Hogwarts School of a great Inquisitor Dolores Umbridge, which will end up replacing the very Dumbledore, the father figure of the saga; the creation of Dumbledore's army, with adolescents Potter as a teacher; the first kiss with Cho, then the girlfriend of the boy Cedric, who died in the previous chapter, so close to Harry. All this happened in a tired way, without rhythm, without that tone between joyful and uneasy that characterized the first two chapters, and even the third. Thankfully, from the moment that the Weasley twins decide to make pointed sleeves (what is the point reached, in this case, such phrase.), Yates seems to cheer up and the last stretch of the film cobra force and vigour, as if he had been waiting to get their best clothes: then develop bright scenes such as the defection of twins in full tests of the SCAMS (which should be as the selectivity here)(, but with more potions.) and, above all, the key sequence that takes place in the secret room of the Ministry of magic, with a stage visually very bright, with towering shelves that make up a variegated store of prophecies enclosed in balls strange lit, and that will lead in the well-structured and easily seguible (both virtues so rare now in the action scenes) sequence of the fight between Voldemort and his death eaterson the one side, and Dumbledore and his army of apprentice Wizard, on the other. But not enough, obviously with a brilliant ending: the set confirms that the series is not at his best film. Daniel Radcliffe ratifies its limitations as an actor, much which obtained critical acclaim in his theatrical debut "Equus" of Peter Shaffer; Emma Watson, the face of a Hermione Granger already with girl curves, looms as that is probably the most talented new stars discovered by the saga; You can not say that about Rupert Grint pecoso and red-haired Ron, which seems to go to get very far in his facet as actor. Among the largest are happy always find a surprise, as in this case the splendid Dolores Umbridge that composed the veteran Imelda Staunton, a certainly odious character that makes it unforgettable. The rest follows the usual tall, with powerful people of the English scene like Michael Gambon, Maggie Smith or Helena Bonham Carter; that Yes, Emma Thompson appears out of a theatrical Institute course end representation. Was not there another piece of paper for this, otherwise excellent actress?</body>
</review>
