<review author="José A. Peig" title="Harry poter y el caliz de fuego" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The main setback in the style and the identity of the work is the mediocre display of director Mike Newell, superfluous and repetitive. Their close-ups and your lousy sense of rhythm (in fact, lacks visual rhythm) difficult to distinguish between his film and any Disney movie.</summary>
	<body>Goblet of fire is a story of conspiracy in which Harry Potter is the wizard of straw and the key piece for the achievement of a goal: the rebirth of Voldemort. The history displays various subhistorias, alternating sequences between a competition of magicians and the first conflicts in love and friendship. Whereas the saga as a whole, this gives confirms the evolution of the universe harrypotteriano from child towards the pre-adolescent. The characters grow, Hogwarts grows and becomes witness to progress towards adulthood, analogous to a few events that follow a pattern of drama "in crescendo" in space. We believe that the attribute more representative and remarkable of the saga is that progression of tones, from early childhood until puberty problematic. Seems its walls that enclose the landscape, the symbolism and the architecture of Hogwarts, the mysteries and events and surrounding valleys, is a reflection or metaphor of the insecurities, fears and hormonal changes in their human protagonists. It may not be very risky to say that, in future, the saga of Harry Potter will be interpreted as if it were a metaphor, in soap opera kistch key, on the passage of time and changes in the future.However, the fourth film returns to fall into the errors of the first. The structure is quite right, as we have said, underlies the central motif (conspiracy to resurrect Voldemort) of which the various sub-plots are constituent parts of it. What fails is the articulation of the various plots. Goblet of fire is a scattered and vague film because of the absence of some connectors to create a dramatic sense of set. In the course of minutes work disjointed pieces: Harry nightmares and his disagreements with his friend Ron, the flirtations of teenage love, competitions and tests to overcome, the conflict between teachers and other tics of the saga. Writer, in this case, wanted to develop too much information and in the end fails to the necessary cohesion between the pieces. And, specifically, do not get any of them to be interesting, except for the last twenty minutes, in a total of one hundred and fifty. How much untapped footage. The main setback in the style and the identity of the work is the mediocre display of director Mike Newell, superfluous and repetitive. Their close-ups and your lousy sense of rhythm (in fact, lacks visual rhythm) difficult to distinguish between his film and any Disney movie. And where deficiencies are most noticeable in the scene Summit - or which should have been scene Summit-, the return of Voldemort. On the one hand, confirm that Voldemort is a bad little chicha, and decaffeinated clear that little juice can be drawn with a very mediocre performance. It is a problem of mise en scene, first and foremost. In summary, very loose this fourth part of the adventures of the young Wizard, conspicuous only by sporadic anecdotes and moments. That Yes, the sinister end opens many unknowns that promise great emotions for the next adventure. We will be vigilant.</body>
</review>
