<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Harry Potter y el prisionero de Azkaban" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Does Alfonso Cuarón (specializing in slightly more adult film) has given another? touch? to the film.</summary>
	<body>Well I've seen one of the films of the summer and after taking in the door one of anecdotes more strange, quirky and funny way to tell my opinion, but first I'll tell it, is I when I was a kid was always to the cinema with my father or my sisters (I'm the youngest of 4 sisters) and I always carried film accompanied only? ever. do well when I went to see "Harry Potter and the prisoner of Azkaban" when I was at the door with my media naranja, making time to enter, more than anything by that I can't stand being late to not miss the trailers, I see a mother talking to the usher? And when you say that begins the film? And when tells me that you just? In this turns and tells the child that is not separate from the usher and make him in any case. do and already she withdraws from the tail to the cry-that release to leave the kid watching the this nonsense of Harry Potter! (it should be noted that the child was walking between 8 or 9 years)After entering the room and project us some trailers, including "Mar adentro" of Amenabar, based on the life of Ramon San Pedro, (the paraplegic Galician who finally managed to put an end to his life) and starring Javier Bardem and Belén Rueda, "The polar Express" that if the film is going to be like the trailer want to see it already! (premiered in Christmas) by that I swear I am excited and even a few tiny lagrimitas have suddenly leaned accidentally by my eyes; "Spiderman II" that is true that impresses almost as much or more than the first part, but it is also true that he looks a "whiff" of Superman films, as told me this afternoon my kinsman when spoke with him of the item. And "Catwoman" of Pitof, I've seen the Teaser and finally. for porn movie if, but for superhero movie. Uff, I do not know to say.After the trailers shuts down everything and starts to sound the tune I know of memory (more than anything by that took melody on my mobile phone) and appears the logo of Warner which we are facing and we planted 10 of Privet drive and begin to see what we have been reading in the book (it is true and I understand) that summarize a book is trickythat condense 359 pages in a film of two hours and 10 min. It is something crappy, more than anything that I know writers and know how difficult it is, here there is with the reader's imagination, everything here must translate it so that reflect it the sense of sight. Also the change of director, Chris Columbus (specialized in child and youth film) to Alfonso Cuarón (specializing in slightly more adult film) has been another "touch" the film.One of the things that more strange found me has been change of locations for Hogwarts, in the first two films were shot in a city and it was decided to change more than anything there it rained one exaggerated thing and decided to search for another site, so now some things have changed, the corridors of the school are distintintos to as them and the position of the hut of Hagrid alsoin fact before I was below the castle in an Esplanade behind forest prohibited and now, however, must be down a ramp to give with it and even Boxer Willow now isn't where it was in the second movie. You quickly enter the game but after two films it is shocking to see such a change of scenery.I have to say that the special effects are spectacular, highlighting the presence of Buckbeak the hippogriff (ILM has surpassed itself) and in this case is the visual spectacle of the film including that "moment Titanic" has Harry on the back of the same. I would also highlight the Dementors that when I saw for the first time I was reminded to the spectra of the ring of "The Lord of the rings" Although in special effects the saga of Harry Potter has never faltered and since the first film until this most of them (the Elf Dobby in the above) have been excellent.Alfonso Cuarón, as I've already said is an accomplished director of young actors and in this (well known is complicated a film with kids) all work excellently well, additionally Ron Weasley is no longer the comic comparsa (dubbing is also excellent at last!) and Hermione Granger is also taking almost both prominence and Harry Potter. By the way, there are two details more than I want to highlight that there is a change in uniforms that make them less colegiales and Quidditch clothes finally seems sportswear (with name and everything behind) in this film although there are party in all is a pity that it lasts so little. Also I liked to see the players more time dressed in street clothes.By the way, the score conducted by John Williams is excellent and sometimes puts you goose bumps because that the Union between images and music is nothing short of magic! In a film of this type.Now only remains for me to read the book again (my favorite of the Potter) since that long ago that I did and I have quite forgotten memories of it already and I think I will try to see the movie a couple of times more since that has seemed excellent.</body>
</review>
