<review author="José A. Peig" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Like episode? hard? and murky saga, works pretty well, the direction of David Yates is vulgar, but very effective for the achievement of the purpose.</summary>
	<body>"While the characters have grown up, the stories also, leaving behind innocence and confusing us with arguments so labyrinthine that required a PhD at Hogwarts to follow him." (.)" Roger Ebert, Chicago Sun Times.Nos striking this comment of Robert Ebert. Harry Potter not only is a series of fantasy, also is a story about childhood and the transition to adulthood housed in a space metaphorical to call Hogwarts, continent of the threats that can affect the lifestyle of a teenager. "The order of the Phoenix" features a key character in this sense, the inquisitive teacher - with estimable versatility - starring the actress Imelda Staunton. She symbolizes the traditional authoritarianism against the air of freedom of the boys better than anyone, and his energetic pose while the false condescension that hides his true evil, become the best of the function, a histrionic character it brings new things to a series that was in danger of stalling because of a scheme so repetitive.All the Harry Potter films to follow a same and iterative scheme and that in five installments barely there is much more that more of the same (forgive the redundancy) is a fact. But if we are careful, we discover that what is of the story progresses in a dramatic progression structured in concentric circles: is not adding information, but increase the emotional intensity and nuances relating to Harry and his disturbing resemblance to Voldemort, at the same time that Hogwarts - as a metaphor for the púberes fears - becomes a more sinister place. What, in short, is to have always the same but under different perspectives and different shades dramáticosY thus arrived at "The order of the Phoenix", the muddier episode filmed to date, with clear references to the Galactic saga of George Lucas, because history could be summed up with something like "Harry Potter against its reverse scary", and in the final scenes, some may think. that was just missing that Voldemort was the father, uncle or brother of Harry, which would explain the similarities between the two (there is a very clear analogy: Voldemort is Harry Potter that Darth Vader is Luke Skywalker, at least at the symbolic level). That is something which, in any case, will decide the pen of j. k. Rowling, still remain you two deliveries to invent anything.How "hard" and murky episode of the series, works pretty well, the direction of David Yates is therefore vulgar, but very effective for the achievement of the purpose. I.e. modest claims are adjusted with the final result, which in addition has the proper structure, focused on the essentials, an interesting portrait of Harry Potter in solitude, misunderstood and victim of his own findings, facing the responsibility – and the duty - to become the leader of new quarry of wizards willing to fight against the forces of evil. On the contrary that in "Goblet of fire", here there is a dramatic meaning that encompasses all the history. It has several flaws: the first fifty minutes are a repetition of the same, the same theme in mouths of different characters, but the narration is reduced to a static address. It shows, too often it is an adaptation of a novel and there are parts badly explained, as if it were assured that the viewer has read the book, although it is true that they are secondary details and the attentive spectator can follow the plot without any problems. Separate chapter deserves the final stretch, the scenes in the "Department of mysteries" are magnificent, imaginative and sinister, handles very well, the tempo, rhythms and the presentation of sinister masked characters. The duel between Voldemort and Dumbeldorf or the death of Sirius Black help raise the dramatic tone in a very fitting end for his climax. So worthy that it seems it is worth support more than one hundred minutes of a more or less regular narrative to see resolution. and begin to guess where goes the saga of the Magi. A saga that, in this new episode, and in General, us is not offering any wonder, but have to see how holds the type.</body>
</review>
