<review author="Vsancha" title="Jarhead" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the best anti-bélicas films from the metallic jacket</summary>
	<body>The latest film by Sam Mendes (winner of the Academy Award for best director for American Beauty) not disappointed, Jarhead is at the same level as his earlier work. In this, his new work, stresses above all in the way to tell the tale, it away entirely from above that we have seen in any war film. Mendes returns to show the more human side of the characters as it already did in "Road to perdition" and makes him do in "Jarhead", which is not a war film in itself, at least not the concept I war film, is a drama about a naive soldier innocently enters the army and that every day that passes regrets having done so masterfully. Leaves behind his life, family, friends, girlfriend, I work? something that will cost to recover because of his experience in the war. It is inevitable think "Metal jacket" Stanley Kubrick when one sees the beginning of the film. The style of the film recalls much more to European war films (see Stalingrad, enemy at the gates?) where it is given more importance to relations between the soldiers than to the war conflict itself. Highlight, once again in a movie of Mendes, the impeccable technical aspect, the picture returns to be great, with those perfect images of the desert. The direction of Mendes returns to be perfect, camera is where it should be, is not dramatic nor looking for shocking scenes type saving private Ryan, perhaps even the history tells Mendes, on the soldiers and the war is more impressive than any scene of saving private Ryan. The BSO again magnificent, perfectly accompanies the film, initially when I heard some themes before seeing the film, not identified him with a war film, but then in the film fit perfectly and make a round film Jarhead. The performances, the casting is phenomenal but I must highlight the main Jake Gyllenhaal (Donnie Darko), which makes a deep and complex, almost perfect performance and which reflects his feelings perfectly at all times. Jamie Foxx gives life to the sergeant major Sikes, a non-commissioned officer who feels comfortable being what it is, a professional soldier. And also a great convincing performance as Peter Sarsgaard. No doubt Jarhead is one of the best anti-bélicas films that have been filmed from "Metallic jacket" and that we can identify its anti-war message with works by the likes of "Without quiet on the Western Front" or "Paths of glory". A film which shows the stupidity of the war, as they have evolved the wars, where now fight "at a distance" where you don't see the face of the enemy and where soldiers are trained as killing machines and at the end their unique shots are open-air fruit of his frustration. Soldiers who live unforgettable experiences, leave behind all his life and then there is no possible return will always remain a cabezabote whatever you do. This is especially seen in one of the final scenes when a veteran of the Viet Nam gets on the bus when they get home, receiving them as not received you and as they see what they will turn with the passage of the years. His life will always be linked those moments lived with your classmates in the trenches with a few classmates who become brothers, "blood brothers". Welcome to the suck!</body>
</review>
