<review author="Taliesin" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Count Alberto San Juan for an opera prima is an authentic lujazo and under the stars its director, Félix Viscarret, wanted to maximize. Perhaps too much.</summary>
	<body>Awarded as best film at the Spanish Malaga Film Festival, as in paragraphs of best direction and best male performance, the truth is that I had some expectations with the first feature film of Felix Viscarret. I can not say that under the stars it had proved me disappointing, but I expected something more. And it is that this film stands almost altogether in a superb work of Alberto San Juan, it proves once again that it can move in other waters other than those of the comedy. However, if we take your interpretation of the equation, the end result does not has much to offer.It is a story that should be tragic, but that ultimately it is friendly. There is no shrill in the argument and the Viewer is always with the feeling that the plot is going to break somewhere. The truth is that it breaks, but less painful hand and although it sounds masochistic, this is one of those movies that should give direct to the liver and then deliver something sweet to not leave wanting to commit suicide. The mimbres to hit the viewer are, but finally remains in the tale of the prodigal brother who discovers in the rural world everything what had stolen the city. It is true that the fact of being based on a novel closes the path to plot more interesting variants, but I am sure that you could have done something better. In the end, everything is wobbly wobbly and I guess that the endearing rogue who gives life masterfully Alberto San Juan has a lot to do with this.The alma low stars is the transformation of the character that starts being an alcoholic trumpeter surrendered to nightlife and is gradually approaching the Viewer. Keeps ramalazos that make it insignificant, but when she begins her relationship with "puerquita" the tone is more comedy than you might expect at first. In any case, Alberto outboard his character and has great chemistry with small violet Rodríguez, which makes his scenes maybe that gives us the tape. Emma Suárez as Julián Villagrán are discrete in their roles, but probably more because of the script that by itself says.In short, under the stars is a great movie that could have been much more if they had opted for a few characters more strongly, at the expense of subtracting protagonism to the main. The general tone is could have sharp enough changing some scenes that are almost filled by others to give the viewer the opportunity to want more characters. Nevertheless, another shows more than there are professionals capable of bringing to the screen stories close and able to touch us chord, which we already have Michael Bay for the Transformers in the Spanish film.</body>
</review>
