<review author="JLO" title="El aura" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film which reconciles us with the romantic idea of those who believe that money is not the solution, or the only option. And that even, does not change anything or anyone. A thought so dark and pleasant as the Aura.</summary>
	<body>After this miracle that was nine Queens, being an opera prima of critique and superlative public, at the head of the director successfully passed probably many things. Why took five years to ponder his next step. Which coincidentally, was an own project dating from long time and that the success of nine Queens has changed his tone, to make it more grim in his birth. The bet was swift and proved to be confirmation of a new star of the direction argentina, talking exclusively about talent, demonstrating that any chance was not done.It is, this time the best Argentine player - Ricardo Darín - not it becomes more inclusive of the film, you don't have to deploy all its expressive background with this exclusive merit, epileptic taxidermist of the director, which even seems to tell us that her first film was only an excuse to perform this.Also in the films of Fabian it is very rare that any actor clash. The Aura is the perfect antithesis of its precedent, but is also like that, round, with a solid script where you look at and is excellently filmed in all their items. But it is dark and relies more on their climates than in rhythm, paused without being slow; just the beginning refers to nine Queens with the scenes of the cashier and dream theft, filmed with the precision and the timming trademark already of Bielinsky.Hay references Yes. The use of classical music and the beautiful frames refer us to Kubrick, climates to classic Hitchcock thrillers, thick forests to the same as for Shyamalan. Up top, with its sorry and static protagonist mounting, reminiscent of the great Buster Keaton Las 7 times. Details just a dash of watchmaking, but more relaxed. Only a "lapsus" would be disposable, that is when the protagonist tells his experience with their attacks. A debtor of the explicit Argentine cinema scene. A film with several layers, escaping in a unique look.A scene of theft averages the film and the party in two. Both by the atypical form of deal with, almost absent - a theft who feels more than what he sees - and that adds a dose of "chance" to the script, nor it hurts anything to it. Bielinsky ultimately not only not disappointed, but that is exceeded. Just have to wait another five years will not be. Thank you for a beautiful open end, almost unprecedented detail in 30 years argento film.A film which reconciles us with the romantic idea of those who believe that money is not the solution, or the only option. And that even, does not change anything or anyone. A thought so dark and pleasant as the Aura. Another new Argentine cinema classic. The death of the director will be difficult to overcome loss.</body>
</review>
