<review author="JLO" title="La Novia Cadaver" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A too complacent final - one always waiting a little more than madness in Tim Burton - or risk not ruin 76 minutes of total enjoyment. If true is the saying of a that a great director are always shooting the same film; We cannot be completely satisfied...</summary>
	<body>The imagination of Tim Burton is so amazing with both the animation and human beings. As Beetlejuice you deployed all his imagery touted as charming continuing in that masterpiece darkie/romantic called the young scissor hands.Creator of classics, theirs passes through the pure fantasy without fall - generally - in the false message moralist, so present in the genre that he passes. Corpse bride is another example of his touch and good taste, its pace for the comedy, the pleasure of simple stories and an amazing animation (almost two hs. for a second movie!). With each gragea TB, one returns to being a child, entranced by his stories as did the character of the big fish with his father. Fables not exempted from that grim, characteristic touch as necessary and harmless.Its genus is fun and pleasure in its purest form, almost childlike, with that dark and melancholic touch which is so obvious even in his failed works, which has, and lately are becoming increasingly less spaced. When it was a little bit seriously - the great fish, the planet of the apes - his gaze was diluted by lack of depth or too seriously. With this the comparisons with the world of Jack Skeleton(de_la_que_fue_coguionista_y_productor,_no_director) are inevitable. The similarities now depart from the characteristics of the characters, as if TB had been wanting to go that already turned classic total. The music is still a valid vehicle to quickly present the story. I.e. where Disney bored TB is teaching. THE pleasure of death all of his films are full of life but his vital reason is admire the death. Already at the beginning of the young. with the death of his father, with Jack and his MicroWorld, Beetlejuice returning from it; death flies over triumphant and without fear all the great moments of his filmography. With great presence also in the Headless Horseman and in it, the death - even more than the love that also stands out course in his films - is the true engine of his vision. Not for nothing the world of the dead is painted with joy and color while the real world is in grey tones, almost grim, and even the more amoral characters of this story. As the shy and clumsy Vincent deficit not awakening empathy that instantly woke Jack, as well as songs from Danny Elfman - another fetish of the director - of that film (which was also the voice of Jack) are insurmountable. (With the voice of the repeated Johnny Deep - stand-in for 80% of the films of TB!) This Vincent seems the antithesis of the explosive Jack. On the other hand his corpse bride is a mirror - perhaps more sexy - of the also detachable Sally.Esta repetition or similarity leads us to think that TB this comes from taquito, automatic pilot type. Then we wonder: do there would be to ask a little more than risk? It did in any of his films and why they are the most unsuccessful of his work? It is necessary or with these clones is enough just for the happy outcome? Perhaps the degree of admiration/enjoyment of his work of the response. The imagination of TB is one of their strengths more praised mentioned above, but there are those also wary of it as commented Renoir quoting her father and that is beside the point: "Paint a leaf of tree without starting from a model and run the risk of monotony, because the imagination does you nothing more than some models of tree leaves." Nature provides million on the same tree. There are not two equal sheets. "The artist who paints himself soon arrives to be repeated."A too complacent final - one always waiting a little more than madness in TB - or risk not ruin 76 minutes of total enjoyment. If true is the saying of a that a great director are always shooting the same film; We cannot be completely satisfied.</body>
</review>
