<review author="JLO" title="Al límite de la verdad" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting, concise and daring development at times - as several attacks on their lives between actors - with a final - uf - with all possible concessions pro-mainstream that we did not expect to see even if it is for the one and only time.</summary>
	<body>A chance encounter as it can be a car accident serves as an excuse to portray the current madness of the inhabitants of New York and its known individualism, played in this time in lawyer Gavin Banek (Ben Affleck) and an insurance salesman named Doyle Gipson, played by Samuel Jackson always yields. The class struggle and the hysteria post 11-9 with their inevitable stereotypes, lawyer successful, corrupt, without nor moral ethic contrasted with an insurance salesman alcoholic with emotional and economic problems so as to not be able to solve his own family and inevitably black. By the clash Doyle lost valuable minutes and the trial for the possession of their children, while Gavin leaves forgotten a vital folder for their future at the hands of his recent enemy unleashing a fierce struggle to regain its recent past. We must stop in a valid although uneven acting counterpoint between a Samuel Jackson vigorous and real, in one of his best roles then of the well-remembered Jules from Pulp Fiction and a tasteless, although quite right Ben Affleck in a race in ascent, being them the best and salvageable from this film. Isn't that its director, the South African Roger Mitchell responsible for the failed and trumpeted A place called Notting Hill, comedy not demonstrates in his first foray into American cinema ideas and a firm for the drama, if not pace that his gaze is somewhat banal and superficial, depicting a society which he notices others, sucked by the machinery that everything devours it - see John WooJackie Chang and several more - accentuating is this with the faintness of the passage of minutes. This same the torna at times slow, mainly in the Office scenes a bit anodyne and with the plus of having aided by an excellent cast secondary, such as Sydney Pollack and William Hurt while emphasizing development interesting, concise and bold at times - as several attacks on their lives between the protagonists - a - uf - ending with all possible concessions pro-mainstream that we did not expect to see even by a single and only time.</body>
</review>
