<review author="JLO" title="Kun-fu-sion" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A work of absurd humor, which so hip with the Spanish Javier Fesser, creator of the excellent El milagro de p. Tinto (1998) and Mortadelo y Filemón (2002). I.e., a Chinese and a Spanish as highest regard of this genre.</summary>
	<body>Stephen Chow is today after seven films, the man no. 1 film in China. The popularity did it Star, but also in their films is the director, producer, screenwriter and the total brain behind your product. As did also the old glories such as Charles Chaplin and Buster Keaton. And to them is precisely - among others - to who pays tribute to Chow with his fresh comedies and dancers.Slapstick, this physical form of humor he returned with him. A primitive and anarchic, ideal mood for the pirouettes of kung fu; a territory that Buster Keaton did great, creative chaos in chain as this beautiful Kung fusion. Ojo also Chow shows a care of the aesthetics and forms (see the picture of this image), in the Assembly, makes us to agree on both the frames of apparently, another of their direct influences: Stanley Kubrick. If not see the opening scene and the endless travelling backwards. In previous Shaolin Soccer, is the beginning with the soccer ball and a head of shaolin "aligned" as the famous planets, to the sound of classical music, which shows. Here is an obvious reference to the shining. Pure cinephiles. And respect for the classics. All this is really no surprise. Shaolin soccer (2001) was a zany comedy and showing all the imagination that Kung fusion confirms. The surprise is really that Chow is exceeded, which in this case makes his last film in almost a masterpiece.A work of absurd humor, which so hip with the Spanish Javier Fesser, creator of the excellent El milagro de p. Tinto (1998) and Mortadelo y Filemón (2002). I.e., a Chinese and a Spanish as highest regard of this genre. Ja.El more accurate example of what can be Chow movies, I gave the Critic Roger Ebert of the Chicago Sun Times: "Imagine a film where Jackie Chan and Buster Keaton meet Quentin Tarantino and Bugs Bunny". In fact, the choreographed fight scenes, were made by the same team that failed Eastern parody called Kill Bill (and also of Matrix). Both poor imitations of the oriental culture. Step and unwittingly, left to the now Hollywood Jackie Chan, a little ancient and on the verge of retirement. And here it shows the difference, because any of several Kung fighting. they pass without disheveled, to the big and numerous of Kill Bill. Only one could compare them in skill and imagination, with some of the animated series Dragon Ball!.Telling gags – which are hundreds – not only would be boring if not impossible. The script, with endearing characters and without falling into the dreaded kitsch, is a little simpler. The struggle of common people against the mafia, no underline. Smart and pure fun. Up the own Chow is kept in the background in the film despite being the protagonist. The scene of persecution - worthy of any chapter of the Road Runner - the fight with the musicians and the final battle; they are the high points of a film with a steady pace, redondísima, with excellent performances of mostly older people - some are operation Dragon Bruce Lee!-, with romance, action, humor and without weak points. Anything else?.Buster Keaton from somewhere in the sky, after seeing Kung Fusion, will be smiling for the first time.</body>
</review>
