<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Ghetto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about one of the Nazi ghettos in Lithuania during the occupation of the second world war. Very interesting to see, with its point of tension is maintained and that ends up exploding you in the face at the end. To know that you can cry.</summary>
	<body>Several very weird things have happened with this film. When he was preparing the critique, I searched a little bit of information and I have encountered there is almost nothing. For most, this film does not exist. On the other hand, and this is not so unusual, the official synopsis and of what I think is the film have absolutely nothing to do. In the poster leave the same actors, if it wouldn't is another. In the end.The film is about the German occupation of Lithuania, specifically of a ghetto under the command of a young nazi officer. In its effort to maintain his plot with the greatest possible encouragement (and the Jews to do productive actors) to have a good coexistence decides to reopen the theater, so that all Jewish artists can follow their performances (and incidentally not amtarlos). On the other hand, a clever Jew, opens a business with the nazis to repair the costumes coming from the front. And I swear that the film is this.Well, look at it did me not do much see this movie, I do not like those of penalty. But found me this very interesting. Input, is not a film especially hard, if not runs with a kind of calm that makes you expect the worst. The setting is "curious" without large decorated, but sufficiently effective (most of the action takes place in the Theatre). The characters interpreted roles very different and strange, being the peak of all the girl puppet.In short, film about one of the Nazi ghettos in Lithuania during the occupation of the second world war. Very interesting to see, with its point of tension is maintained and that ends up exploding you in the face at the end. To know that you can cry.kisses.</body>
</review>
