<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Bodas y prejuicios" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about casaderos topics in the India, with a modern woman who does not want a marriage of convenience. If you are one of those who likes that they sing and dance in the films, while they talk about insustancialidades that cover bleeding truths, is your film. If not, do it for love.</summary>
	<body>It was the other a day server looking things by the modern Oracle, when it told me my medium Zucchini "Come love". Thinking it was something erotic, I ran as to the appointment. Bad choice, given that I sat on the couch and said "Let's see a Bollywood film". Heavens, one of those Indies that dance and sing during the footage, while they speak of insubstantial things. And without sleep, he put it to all estrozo. And the worst, the worst of the worst, is that it is not even of Indian studies, which is English made with that style. Virgencita, virgencita. Is like the beer without alcohol, exist the with, for what this abhorrent invention of the devil?The film is a Hindu mother whose obsession as good traditional mother, is to marry off their daughters. Total, one of them says that before dead than a marriage for convenience. In these, they are there to pretend her a crazy Hindu which has made fortune in the U.S., a rare "jipi" and a rich owner of a chain of hotels. Obviously, the entire fabric is in relations with the latter, seasoned of the stuff from the rest. And the film is so called because it is a strip and tug of war between the typical clichés and social reality.Mother that laughter we spent. We had our eyes a kind of musical, romantic comedy with dialogues and situations somewhat loggerhead and simplistic. My average Zucchini spent the entire film telling me that this was for children and that neither had given a kiss. It has many nice moments, but of course, if put you half footage of Hindu traditional dances, so you can give a telele.In short, film about casaderos topics in the India, with a modern woman who does not want a marriage of convenience. If you are one of those who likes that they sing and dance in the films, while they talk about insustancialidades that cover bleeding truths, is your film. If not, do it for love.It is not my style.Besitos.P.D: To put that movie I liked. Of those that you see and you have left the impression that everyone is good and that the news are bad shot films.</body>
</review>
