<review author="Bruji" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the realm of the PlayStation, the adventures of Harry oblige dust off the imagination, encourage reading and enact fundamental principles such as love and friendship.</summary>
	<body>In the Kingdom of the PlayStation, it was multiple technologies, universe in which the subject of human being; continues pending the adventures of Harry oblige dust off the imagination, encourage reading and enact fundamental principles such as love and friendship. With debutant director and new screenwriter, the magical saga brings us closer to a fifth installment, almost perfect.Even for those who possess the "emotional capacity of a brick", resist the Potter-mania is highly difficult. Stairs that molt to pleasure, Hogwarts and its millennial emblem "Draco Dormiens Nunquam Titillandus" (never do tickling a dragon that sleeps), "Alohomora", mirrors that show what you want to see, flights in broom, "Wingardium Levi-ou-sa", night breaks to forbidden forest with layers of invisibility, thinkers, trasladores, "Petríficus Totalus!", Centaurs and unicorns, paintings with its own life, platform 9 and ¾, talking newspapers, Siriux the Godfather, "Specto Patronum!", changing labyrinths, black lakes, the room of the necessities or the Nimbus 2000, are some of these things that make reborn fantasy that, at some point, we lost."!!!" The boom in the British writer, however, seems to have fallen into an inexhaustible well of imagination. Film adaptations, for its part, emerge as much magic as the pages of his novels, while reaching one major achievement, which is none other than an accurate incitement to reading. Obviously, no one can expect to the Warner rolls the final outcome. The response if J.K. Rowling will be able to get rid of the protagonist that her has catapulted to fame, as he did his compatriot Agatha Christie with some famous Belgian detective, only found in a book. The Muggels, meanwhile, wonder at what exact point a perfect story develops.The secret of success would have to be found in the comprehensive construction of a parallel world, interrelated with which we all know (only must know that the Ministry of magic is situated just below the English Ministry of defence), in which, far from insulting the intelligence child (common practice in film and literature), decided to develop it. In some characters, based on imperfection and involuntary heroism, inhabiting both scenarios, for which magic does not constitute a way of escape from reality, but a quality of their own personalities with which they have to learn to live. In the issuance of precious messages, start with that derived from the love of a mother, the only one capable of overcoming the evils of mankind (also "to that not must be named"), and culminating with the assessment that "all have light and darkness in our interior, depending on us the choice on the side that we want to promote", to say that "those who want us to""always remain". And in the constant evolution of the saga, which adapts to the different ages of their protagonists. In this sense, and in a progressive manner, Iran disappearing adventures focused on the acquisition of school supplies in wonderful shops, uniforms which both remind us students of Goodbye Mr. Chips, the recreation of the typical dining room which, similarly, Sam Wood shot in 1939, innocent contests in which the fellowship and friendship, advantages richly options the famous phrase of the director wise: "In the light of recent events.", in a magical chess game, or skirmishes against Lord Voldemort (oops, I wrote, without wanting to, his name!) extremely weakened; to make way for other situations requiring maturity.The order of the Phoenix, so surprising as the previous installments, represents the culmination of four courses of sorcery, the moment in which the obligation to study becomes a necessity; or what is the same, the point at which starts to grow. Our Harry has to multiply to adversity, because it is not the famous magician that everyone admire, but the "Plotter", the liar conspirator, ignored by his mentor, victim of a slander him over. Imposes the self-esteem, commitment (training in Dumbledore's Army) and the uprising against the dictatorial methods of Hogwarts. A few stages that form part of the endless School of learning which is life itself.With such fertile conception, followed by a sound development, it matters little who is after the cameras. Either the Alfonso Cuarón himself or a television Director, the success is assured provided that the spectacular production design has the special effects in the service of the argument, and never vice versa; as well he has been so far. Even misses the original soundtrack of Williams, nor the photograph of the first films, in a few stories that, primarily, dominates the screenplay, overseen by its creator. A skull "previlegiado", which I would say Valle Inclán, who, however, you forgot indicate something fundamental. In holidays. How are these people contributing?, by ordinary mail?, with OWL?, by email?.</body>
</review>
