<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Next" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very good idea, badly exploited that loses both bellows arriving to stop at all, a penalty, but can not ask more of a summer release of such ephemeral features.</summary>
	<body>Well, well, now come to understand the reason why "Next" has taken so long to release in our country, while it is true, that summer is time conducive to this type of tapes, however, the film, a story of the mythical and famous (after his death) Philip k. Dick is a more than so many, and even dare to match with another of the same author"Paycheck" which starred in the ineffable (which not infallible) Ben Affleck, lol and without having it prepared went me a couplet.It is true, the main idea is wonderful and the first act is masterful, leaving one in the armchair, wanting more, however, the film which had begun masterfully hits a sudden halt, just at the beginning of the second Act and becomes sosa, at times predictable and simplistic in its final execution.Nicolas Cage in his line, start to believe me that this man has a kind of curse toward the movies he starred in, and is that, however much that my lady loves, project this man plays, project that he fails miserably and it is that this film, has just raised $ 45 million, a figure almost excasa quantities that nowadays moveincluding box office and on DVD in the States.Tanto Julianne Moore, Jessica Biel as they are quite normalitos, the Moore was note that you enjoy being a bit "out of the water" (lease dramatic cinema) and Biel, despite being vase women (metidita Casita I te espero.) sometimes seems that you think more about the cheque going to charge once the work is completedthat give him something, he more than packing his performance.Special effects, I would say that almost, a character in the film, are normal, fairly simple, so we are going to cheat, and the direction of tamahori quite excasa, this director was what brought us one of the most loaded with 007 action films? (not recognize you).In short, a very good idea, badly exploited to lose both bellows comes to stop at all, a penalty, but you can not ask more of a summer release of such ephemeral features.</body>
</review>
