<review author="Bloody Will" title="Next" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is consumed as fast as the medium popcorn cardboard. Even in a cinema session of Terrace, with prices in half and the possibility of seeing two followed, this film is perfect.</summary>
	<body>Who said that this summer was no mutants?. Do after enjoying / punish with?Spider-Man 3 &#8242;, and waiting for two weeks to come here?The 4 fantastic? with its sequel, the surprise of halftime occurs: Nicolas Cage, the visionary alias. He has caught the taste to this powers? and now step to the side of bland in their roles. ?Next? It is not a film: is a short story with just duration, and actors that do what they can to ensure that it does not become the most crappy 2007. The thing did not give more than the 88 minutes that lasts the tape.Does lee Tamahori has already forgotten the aesthetics of film printed to his best work?Do Mullholland Falls?, to focus on the worst of their ways, repeated like hotcakes in?It die another day? or?XxX 2 &#8242;. With a solid as a short story by Philip k. Dick (?) 1954(The_Golden_Man?), and whose work as prolific has given wonders as?Blade Runner? or the semi-decente?Does Minority Report?, the director has due meets this time with the worst of his enemies, the typical writer of Hollywood that adapts and destroys one idea that seemed fairly consistent with a hobby that is becoming a classic of our times: make up for failures of script with a succession of scenes of action dressed with the latest in digital effects. Voila, we already have the film for release.The main premise is what would you do if you knew what is going to happen in the next two minutes?. To me I would not be much, but Chris Johnson (Cage), a magician from Las Vegas, given to be all one piece hunting desired by a get smart national security (Moore), and somewhat disorganized terrorists. After one sequence more than stupid that presents us with the powers of the subject in question and causes the warning illogical federal, the following is the race against time to stop a group of villains who, after stealing a nuclear bomb, intended to destroy everything, and who incidentally also want to apprehend the protagonist I don't know very well why. Between all, Johnson began one relationship rather than unnecessary con una chica, Liz (Jessica Biel), who will be trapped in the heart and will serve as insulting piece of exchangeable meat.(Only) to highlight all the scenes where Cage Dodge bullets, da esquinazo agents that lurk, or causes real avalanches where zafa controlled way by mm and that serve to hinder the rest of their persecutors. Did the powers of prediction that initially shows Johnson give to much and that? vision of the future? that only covers two minutes is a better gift than flying, be invulnerable or some good x-rays that pass through the clothes of Biel. Do as a good Bond, Cage ends by guide towards the Elimination of terrorists in a tour of a few stores that are more entertaining in the film good? and here is over all positive, the rest is to forget.If you ask an explanation about the powers of the protagonist, ye shall not have her. If you want an explanation of the obsession with national security by Johnson, you will not have her. If you want an explanation of the suitability of starting an affair when you are in search and capture, you will not have her. Even if you want an explanation of why Liz alert Johnson of the intentions of the Feds when they have told him that he is a criminal and knows it one day, not her you are going to find. And if you want an explanation for one of the endings more firecrackers this year, I have not. And what about Nicolas Cage. Do do this man begins to be a classic in our list of? the worst of the worst?. His choice of work in recent years is unfortunate or the less than deserved rebuke, because I say I do to read the scripts before you sign?. Again the face of cardboard in the situations of action, again the same ways and again his face of lap dog in the scenes with girl sharing level. I already begin to tremble each time that presents a film with Cage as the protagonist, and is not anything good. Julianne Moore is not to sign their best work, but to do so regularly exceeds vengeance to Cage in the scenes that share. Biel is a mere pretty face ever, and as they had to include scenes with a girl good looking, what better than she.If there is no further remedy and you are not equipped to take two hours in the cinema?Next? It is consumed as fast as the medium popcorn cardboard. Even in a cinema session of Terrace, with prices in half and the possibility of seeing two followed, this film is perfect. If not, refrain from such loss of an hour and a half little of his life and they expect that in three months it will be on DVD.</body>
</review>
