<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="The Queen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>That if it is a devastating portrait of our current society, that ideology of a political crisis, which are of the sign, do always the same: succumbing to the tentacles of power. Once they arrive to rule they feel like Kings.</summary>
	<body>As the piece of chess, you can walk by the Board as any of the other pieces, with the exception of the caballo.ah, but we do not give greater importance, H.m. Queen Elisabeth II has more appreciation for the deer. The news of the death of Diana in 1997 that shocked the British people nor the bothered. but if imported you at the time in question the its distant attitude to the tragedy. This should not arise the soundness of an institution, as it is the monarchical, anchored in the past. Stay calm. They are politicians. He was Prime Minister Tony Blair, newcomer to the power, who intervened to let him know the Queen who had to set aside his coldness, arrogance and indifference, and share the pain with his people.Stephen Frears builds a caricature of power. Imitating each of the characters involved in the story (from the Prince of Wales to the very same Blair family), splendid starring Helen Mirren as Queen, winner of several international awards. A caricature of the ones above, which represent a country, so if they have been democratically elected or not.In this way, the monarchy is portrayed. You are interested in the people, nor its responsabilidades.sino go hunting, take tea and the Protocol. And not to speak of it, let the good quiet. Frears makes it from within, from the everyday. Concluding that the sole objective of the monarchy is their survival as an institution in a "supposedly" modern world. The death of Lady Di was an earthquake. And who was going to say. The Savior of the monarchy was the labour Blair (the supposedly modern politician who came to the British Government, after years and years of conservatism). It, along with Bush and Aznar, proposed "Save" to Iraq with an invasion. If the monarchy is advocate of their values, with politicians who come to govern a country happens the same. There is the real critique of the film, focusing on the political class that we chose.That if it is a devastating portrait of our current society, that ideology of a political crisis, which are of the sign, do always the same: succumbing to the tentacles of power. Once they arrive to rule they feel like Kings.</body>
</review>
