<review author="JLO" title="El caso Bourne" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the achievements of the script is that everything is held not by the action scenes, but by the relationship of the two characters in a linear fashion, slowly and without false steps or sentimental.</summary>
	<body>Police thriller brought to the screen by Doug Liman and performing with tasteful, true to the book and rate sustained in your footage. Adaptation of part three of the novel by the renowned Robert Ludlum died recently and is also one of the producers of the film. A road movie set in the streets of Paris, the beautiful landscapes of Prague and the North of Italy, enhancing its landscapes with an excellent photograph.The film tells of Jason (Matt Damon) temporary amnesia and the search for its own personality with the help of Marie (Franka Potente) initially reluctantly, suffering persecution and rediscovering him with forgotten skills - and very useful - to discover his past. It is not a common film addressed as the old serial TV, but in a manner uncommon to today so prone movies of the spectacular nature, having a healthy kinship perhaps with the series mission Imposible.Con all ingredients into perspective and realistic and is: fighting hand-to-hand, spectacular persecution of cars, duels with bullets. Everything with sobriety, credibility and relentlessly. One of the achievements of the script is that everything is held not by the action scenes, but by the relationship of the two characters in a linear fashion, slowly and without false steps or sentimental. In the manner of a modern James Bond but without glamour, Matt Damon plays a good work by content, for a secret agent role without unrest and almost touching the deadpan. Following the analogismo, the powerful German (without the sex appeal of the Bond girls) shows once again how good actress who is more than a mere being partner of the hero. A final scene which is surprising because it breaks with all above realism, but not blurs a good smaller - action film that yes - but with good characters and well worn, something small and welcome in these times.</body>
</review>
