<review author="JLO" title="Los 4 Fant치sticos y Silver Surfer" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The first was a kind of movie kitsch, playful and cheerful, amounting to an approved scraping by its naivety, rhythm and grace as a catchy pop song by radio. This new shows of the Fantastic 4 Silver Surfer, or becomes only a good guitar riff.</summary>
	<body>The expectation really wasn't much. The first was a kind of movie kitsch, playful and cheerful, amounting to an approved scraping by its naivety, rhythm and grace as a catchy pop song by radio. This new shows of the Fantastic 4 Silver Surfer, or becomes only a good guitar riff.Another scene of dance at the beginning (as in the ill-fated Spiderman 3, seems that dances are not going with the superheroes) and an anticlim치tica intro on the Reed-Sue relationship, anticipated us that we are facing a problem of rhythm and script.The same cast class B of the first part, does what it can with a 침o침o script, which leaves no room for big surprises. In the spirit of an episode of any series of science fiction in the 1970s. Too little compared with the existential problems (and more rich) colleagues comiqueros like Batman and the same as artificial as clear contact lenses Spiderman.Todo and the blond hair from Jessica Alba, as Julian McMahon as the Dr.Doom (again this bad) and the eternal Stan Lee cameo in project marvelita.Marvel has a gallery of great characters untapped in the film, all of excellent personality: Punisher, Daredevil, Ghost Ryder, Elektra, Hulk, these same Fantastic 4 and now Silver Surfer. Films that disappoint by their lack of depth in the psyche of the heroes.If not for Raimi and his Spider-man, Blade 2, and some X-Men, Marvel would already be up. Although we are not naive and know what sends here is the box office and not the film quality.If it were not for the digital Silver Surfer (character powerful if any) we would be talking about an unhappy film. But Silver is. Even if it is only that.</body>
</review>
