<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential movie in its genre. By far, the best of the series.</summary>
	<body>Before you start with criticism, rather the bathroom of praise of the film, said that with Harry Potter nor am I nor I will be objective in life. I have read and re-read all the books. I have deleted the bytes of the DVDs of the times that I've seen, and I've been expelled from forums for criticizing aspects I liked or that have not been rounded. So, if you are looking for a sincere review, where you critically have the film, long passes. I would begin an arm before you criticize the peliculón I of ver. 24 of the night of July 19, 2007. Again the film with his eyes still drenched with emotion. I doubt that you can best start on my birthday. I am in front of the computer with a small glass (of paint) whisquito that has left shivering the Glenrothes. I meditate two or three seconds what I am about to say. I remember the entry into cinema. As I cried, I laughed, I am excited, I pulled popcorn at the screen, and I has not missed the usher for that there is no such figure in modern theaters. Than 20 rather exploited euros, so the popcorn were tasty just point of salt.The film is a teenage kid that is magician, not as the Tamarisk, if not rather throwing Merlin. Not giving to be a teenager, already quite problematic, it is also an orphan, why their parents mato les a more evil dark magician that quina. Total, that Harry and his cousin les attack some bad bugs like black ghosts called Dementors. As our hero drives away them, is judged by magic and seems that you can not attend the magical school. Well, and then they go to so many things interesting and vibrant that I soon cut a finger that reveal them. Or not?Today we have changed the usual format of criticisms of nonsense - synopsis - comments - summary, one more extensive. Let's see, the film I has enthused, and that the book seemed very weak, with some sub-plots (such as the Dolores in height) that I people bored Presidency and put bad milk. Here nothing from that. Pretty solid, without the usual gaps, and very consistent with the general history has created a script. Earthly problems take weight, while the classes lose it, very unfortunately. But has not lost that touch that was lost in the fourth installment of splash each frame with a magical flowers, subtle. Despite perfectly know me the history, and as he was going to conclude, as if he knew nothing of the history have vibration. Maybe he had to see that you expected me a flojota movie. I am glad to have gone with this mindset. Let's see the characters (sorry for me that I do not lift looking for the book to make the names well) Moon Lovegord. Damn that girl faintness, more hits in movies of fear. It has been hovering between give fear and give a lot of penalty. They could have made a tad more cheerful, that it seemed that you owed him money for the writer.Dolores Umbridge. As he imagined. For kicking him in the intestines until leaving him by the mouth. That tirría that have it, by God. I am grateful that they have cut their torture.Bellatrix. After having seen in the films of Tim Burton, the truth that not him it hit much the role of bad very bad. Although Act well, that I would not dare to deny it.Voldemort. He has grown the nose to this boy? More evil than evil.Longboton. Fuck that most heinous child. As in the last book does not change will be the most absurd character ever invented.Kracher (home Elf). As you imagined. A little more of prominence it had not been wrong.The said. Made me one out black, given that in the books never mention race (thing that feel me great). It has made me funny not to be black, if not for the strange role that they have given, entirely on fill. The girl who changes her hair made me laugh much the moment of glory that has.Dumbledore. This man has less glamour and presence to the mats for the tele of crochet. Why it takes a serviletero in the beard? Removing that, a crack total and more stylish than the host. OLE by him.Hagrid. Her scene with the giant reminded me the cat of the this movie of animation of a green OGRE (not put names of other movies that does not give me the win). Little paper.The giant. They have changed you, very rightly in my view, the role he had in the book. I made him as much more horrible, and at the end is a good-natured of care.Ron and his brothers. Very good the final scene of the brothers, although it has varied with respect to the book (which feel me sorry for her was not able to imagine reading it). Ron is much more mature as a person, always next to Harry.Hermione. That big is this girl I like. As always, giving the point of sanity, although it has been seen as less important in history. Say, that very well in his second discreet flat.Harry. Very well. Nothing more to say.Comment on something else, the patronus scenes have been very good, with much magic. The fighting has nothing to do with books, with a much more powerful good. In addition, the fight scenes are very successful and bestial. The apotheosis, and very sentimental, end with a Harry showing how wonderful that is friendship and family. Very curious House where meets the order, especially the scene in which enter it.In short, essential film in its genre. By far, the best of the series.And by that I do not have 6 stars.Besitos.P.D: If I had not to stir Rome with Santiago to to see her again, her would go to see it again tomorrow. I'll have to wait for the DVD and its good extras (I hope).Pd2: The beginning of the letter "Dear Canute" made me cry of laughter. It seemed that Harry Petas would make it the porros and dismissed in this way. Great name.P.D.3: It had never spent half an hour to criticism.</body>
</review>
