<review author="Berto" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie which although not you can remove the etiquette of entertaining, for my is the weaker of the saga, and glimpse into the series as a great movie, I think that we we have the movie that serves as a link between the development of the previous films.</summary>
	<body>We have here the almost "eternal" apprentice magician, in a fifth installment originally proposed major changes and challenges. These changes and challenges are directly based on the adaptation of the longest book of all the of the Potter, and seeing the length of the other films this wanted eternal when adapting, although seen so it seems that have opted for the tijeretazo directly to skip chapters and more chapters, to leave only a main plot follow during all the footage. Secondly, the changes relate to that middle adolescence that already has our Harry, now entering full amoriles issues, and which will also finding increasingly more alone and with a character a little more rough the sweetness that distilled at the beginning of the series. All this would be quite well and it would give a breath of fresh air to the saga, but I have to admit that this movie has disappointed me a little. Firstly, to focus only on the main plot of the film, something that wouldn't be too bad, the problem is that when watching the movie, it gives the feeling of many things are left in the dark, in search of a narrative a bit more agile and spectacular, and so a simple example, because now that I'm reading the book in questionthe piece that I read, until their arrival to Hogwarts School are almost 200 leaves in the book, whereas in the film 10 minutes is already coming to such an exceptional College. Secondly, the much-heralded darkness of Harry Potter, which does not become such, simply a couple of voices that stick them to their friends, and a sense of loneliness throughout the entire film, but fails to imbue the character of Harry, which continues to be brave and determined when it is up, and not a step back by many "ghosts" travelling on their thoughtssomething that in the book it is also better spot and looks, but which fails here, because here the only thing dark comes to observe throughout the film, is the use of all keys more off color, very much in the line of what did Alfonso Cuarón in the third installment of the saga, the prisoner of Azkaban, that if that seems really dark in approach than this.Another problem is the use of characters. Some characters appear and disappear as if by magic, and never better art, and it seems that they are simply there to say a couple of appropriate phrases, or simply to do bundle and join the excellent roster of actors. I do not know how to develop his characters in the book, because still not reach that part, but the roles of Bellatrix Lestrange, Nymphadora Tonks and Luna Lovegood simply appear from time to time, and above all the role of Bellatrix, with Helena Bonham Carter playing it, I think it will be a bit more decisive in the next film in the series. As I say, Daniel Radcliffe, Emma Watson and Rupert Grint are exactly as in the previous films, but a little more creciditos. Only say that the only with something for the future I see the trio's protagonist is Emma Watson, and but at the time, because I think that we we have a new case Luke Skywalker with Radcliffe. The other characters also appear very in passing throughout the film, with the exception of the great Gary Oldman in his role of Sirius Black, without doubt the very best that we see on the screen, together with Imelda Staunton, whose role of the repellent Dolores Umbridge is very accomplished, resulting odious almost from his first appearance, the other characters, as I already mentioned, albeit with much too untapped name, such as for example 3 lines of dialogue that Emma Thompson has throughout the film, the three sporadic appearances, although conclusive for the history of Helena Bonham Carter or even Ralph Fiennes in his role of that which may not be appointed, and that although stands out mythical qualities of bad filmcan't you appear everything which would have to give shape to a role of magician so bad as he would be entitled.With regard to the director, it brings nothing new to the show. While Chris Columbus started the saga and her endowed of the spectacular nature that characterizes him, and then some other director contributed their bit, as for example the great third superbly shot by Alfonso Cuarón, here simply David Yates is dedicated to placing the camera and try to maximum possible levels where you can use some special effect and thus add a spectacle that only with the plane could not be achievedwhich says very little in his favour and showing me that it makes one of the most flat and devoid of personality of the Potter works, and worst of all, is that this chosen this director to shoot next movie, the half-blood Prince. He would only save the beginning of the film, that begins with enough force and gives hopes for a film that will follow this same style all the footage, but can not deceive ourselves in better way, because until the final battle between wizards, that as I said people that if the book has been read is quite faithful to the book, for a viewer accustomed to special effects of the caliber of TransformersPirates of the Caribbean, or Spider-man will seem anything less spectacular. It is fortunate to have been able to take advantage and see the film in Imax format, since those last 20 minutes in 3 dimensions, adding that spectacular of lacks to the film, and that that end is not shot to be exploited in the 3Ds, but hey, if you cannot be both.In short, a film which although not you can remove the etiquette of entertaining, for my is the weaker of the saga, and glimpse into the series as a great movie, I think that we we have the movie that serves as a link between the development of previous films and the end of the sagaIt occurs with these two latest films remaining Harry, in which hopefully recover the narrative agility, better use both the main characters and the unused side long, and regain the strength and even the darkness had already marked in the previous films.</body>
</review>
