<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Kun-fu-sion" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To start the chest to laugh and have to download emergency to what they sew you.</summary>
	<body>The humor they do in Eastern countries rarely we like in the West. The nearest to us thanks was one program "Yellow humour" which was really fun thank you comments of presenters. By the way, now not be could cast in television, given that they were a little uploaded tone and potentially xenophobic. But other times they were. Who does not remember of the breast chicho, the ay to heat and other retailas of Manakin nipple nipples? To those times.The film is a band of evil called the axes. Of course, they are named because their main weapon is an axe. For reasons which are not the case, they reach a poor area of a large city, where she lives in curious harmony a large neighborhood. In this neighbourhood live an explosive mixture of characters, all dubbed with Spanish accents, making hearing a genuine I messing. Andalusians, Basques, Galicians, etc, are represented by jumping Chinese experts in martial arts. And the entire film is of the band's fight against the neighborhood.Indeed the film is a joke. Impossible is that not you rias, or by to do grace scripts or because you seem so pathetic that you laughing. The characters are the cane. There is a goalkeeper with perpetual curlers who flees to the minimum, given that you don't want to use your hipoeruptohuracanado (such as pepepótamo), a huge screeching. Her husband, a carrot of volume and loin, expert in the most hidden of martial arts and calzonazos grade sumo. Hairdressers gay, also tremendous fighters. And a long etcetera. To highlight the bad very bad, is a Lord who got into the insane asylum because he was not rival who fight. His secret tactic is ridiculísima.In short, that the movie it is worth much. My medium sweet potatoes and I we start box literally. At the beginning we we looked with strangeness, but as soon as you assume the translation, the rest of the tape is shot. That Yes, asumid that the movie is total nonsense, that the Chinese do not fly and that if you tread they head you not up. You are very stupid and you what you all think.To start the chest to laugh and have to download emergency to what they sew you.Besitos.P.D: The asesiones of the Chinese guitar are the Peel.Pd2: Because there is a character that teaches us the ass all day?P.D.3: There are winks to multitude of films, as a Matrix (with the Smith gentlemen with axe) to Asterix (by the absurdez of the blows) and more I do not remember now.</body>
</review>
