<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Madagascar" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you have small kids, lead them to it to see animals and colorful on the screen. If it is not the case, not gasteis money, unless you have a so infantiloide mind as mine.</summary>
	<body>See this film reminded me my earlier years, in which I spent summers playing risk. If things were going well, you had half the world and Madagascar gave you more or less the same, given that it was yours and no one could attack. If things went wrong, and you were lucky to have this region, you agazapabas you waiting for better times. Well, because the movie has nothing to do, but I was reminded of this nonsense.The film is about a few animals that live in a big city in a modern country. The star of the zoo is an a little bit proud Lion, that every day makes a show of ROARs and poses. His best friend is a zebra, which is neither as artist, nor wants to live where he lives. She wants to live in the wild world and have fun. Then appear a few penguins who are graciosísimos on par with bastards. A few monkeys that not is what paint but have its dotted. And a burning llorica with a hipopótama which is the unique string in the history. And then go them to things and at the end it ends well because it is a film for children. ALE.como well say, the film is for children. It's not like Shrek or the incredible. This is for children children. Do not go ugly bugs give fear, there are no scares, no complicated talks, or nothing at all. So if you like animated films for adults, nor are you happen to go. To my personally I liked. The main plot is a little roll and moralist, but the secondary plots are good. The Penguins are cachondísimos, and a little bastards. By the way, remind me of some folk, not be why. And the appearance of the lemurs is grandiose. Itself are stupid bugs, but they have a song that is very catchy. The lion and the Zebra are quite dull. The filetarías Zebra and lion you would give a kick in the crotch.In short, if you have small kids, lead them to it to see animals and colorful on the screen. If it is not the case, not gasteis money, unless you have a so infantiloide mind as mine.Besitos.P.D: That grace make me the problems of the lion because it is hungry and want to eat his best friend. And to solve it, they eat fish. That pussy have done you to the fish? They could have made the vegetarian lion and leave alone the fish. And when eaten juicy steaks at the zoo? Oh, we deceive children with tonteces. In the end.Pd2: Greet and sonreid. Greet and sonreid.</body>
</review>
