<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Harry poter y el caliz de fuego" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I was expecting too much for the little that I found. Possibly, if you're going with moderate expectations, you'll see a peliculón (as my medium kiwi) but if you go with large illusions, you will be slightly squashed. In addition I it has become short.</summary>
	<body>My small chicks, the tito Chinchan will give a d.o. for free, just for reading this criticism. If you want to go to the cinema, Tuesday is an ideal day. About 30 people, were seeing Europe's largest screen so only us has lacked the blanket to be at home. The downside is that the service is far and that he can't stop. In addition my medium kiwi has not left me see the movie in gayumbos not be why.The film is about one year in Hogarts, the fourth, in which Harry already have hairs in some pubic area and Hermione have left you breasts. Begins with the world of quidich competition (as written), in which some strange events do not finish as expected (no, not kill Spain in the quarter of irregular way, more rare I mean). This year in Hogarts seems that they do not give classes, given that other students in two foreign colleges have come, a French girls school which release petals of flowers by walking and other rough Nordic more gross than a "Guillemot". And that is all about.I will not say that the film is the darkest and the most adult of all, given that says it all over the world. What if I say this is the one to less magic. It is not not have large doses of special effects, which you have everywhere, is that it has no worldly magic. To not appear only in class, don't these tricks which gave it a very magical air films. The usual characters do not have almost appearances, or Hagrid, Professor, Professor Severus or almost none. Focuses almost entirely on Harry, Hermione and a new teacher who has an eye for everything to 100. Moreover, incredible landscapes and amazing, special effects of scandal (the scene of the Dragon will be difficult to match) and an incomparable environment. But I is not over fill.In short, I expect much for the little that I found. Possibly, if you're going with moderate expectations, you'll see a peliculón (as my medium kiwi) but if you go with large illusions, you will be slightly squashed. In addition I it has become short.Besitos.P.D: Hormones and pheromones floating in such a way in the air that have left me breasts.Pd2: I'm a superfan of Hermione, it should be called "Hermione, Harry's fool and the calyx of fire". I think Mania I'm picking up.P.D.3: by the way, that leaves "that your already know" which seems that it went through Corporation dermoestética.P.D.4: Hogarts has undergone certain changes, especially structural.</body>
</review>
