<review author="Albert Puyuelo" title="Next" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The script there is no grab it even if it goes with the best predisposition, and if were not enough the tape where is extremely cheat. And if not, eye to patch this way, which will leave with your mouth open more than one Viewer.</summary>
	<body>The day in which an Executive came up that could be used the expression "do inspired in?" rather than "do based in?" was a great day for Hollywood. An ideal subterfuge with which cover the backs to the public by the myriad of outrages carried out with novels, works of theatre or even actual and historical facts.Science fiction has been one of the main victims, as there are countless cases in which a good idea becomes a vulgar action film. This is the case of Next, freely inspired by a free Philip k. Dick story titled The Golden Man. It is a Wizard of third in Las Vegas, which puts their physical Nicolas Cage and little else, has the gift of seeing their future with two minutes in advance. Such quality makes that an FBI agent, played by Julianne Moore, ask you for help to avert nuclear catastrophe. But oh, the poor Devil just wants to live a happy and quiet life with a woman, that the vase of Jessica Biel puts its curves, with whom he is obsessed. Who wait to see a work of science fiction that addresses critical and philosophical topics already can go to forgetting Next. On the other hand, those who are looking for a film in which the argument is a mere excuse to give way to an endless sequence of action and Visual effects will enjoy nice with Next. The script there is no grab it even if it goes with the best predisposition, and if were not enough the tape where is extremely cheat. And if not, eye to patch this way, which will leave with their mouths open to more than one Viewer, and these, in a vain attempt to seek an explanation fairly reasonable, brought the screen without leaving their astonishment.Who had the gift of seeing the future as Nicolas Cage's character. With such capacity, many disgraces which we support in a movie theater or on the couch in our House we could save us.</body>
</review>
