<review author="Cp" title="El señor de la guerra" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Much criticism of American cinema, but while movies here are stupid there have movies like this</summary>
	<body>Is who the villain of the piece? Or maybe that you've still not seen. Then, do not do case of film critics that you talk about the pace of the action of the characters, and other topics, which as it is not a minority Iranian movie, was not lowering to extol. They are actors in Hollywood, famous, handsome and sold many tickets. But who have had the courage to accept a script against your own country (so clearly, the film attacks hard to the USA and its Government) without being a Michael Moore film, that if cool, this cool, and European critics applaud, when it isn't more than canned demagoguery, but changing the political sign, although it is still cheap and stylish short made in demagogy it uses. A film, almost documentary, where the excuse of the life of an arms dealer, is the hook to catch us and continue listening to a real summary of atrocities and absurdities that have crossed our planet these thirty years, while we did you case, something which incidentally, also tells us the film. It may not be a wonder, and not stop 30 minutes to explain to us in detail by that character trauma child hates the Strawberry ice cream, but for that you already have those movies that you recommend your film critic. Here are going to a class of history and politics, when your thought that you were going to watch a movie.A detail. In all written and filmed trash that surrounds us, the phrase: based on a true story, appears at the beginning, to achieve an effect on the Viewer. In this case, it comes at the end. Your thought that this were exaggerations of a few writers. No, boy, welcome to the real world, and without red pill.Much criticism of American cinema, but while here are movies stupid to launder money, on the other side of the Ocean have movies like Syriana or Lord of war, which may not be artistic wonders, but they tell us stories about how is our world, without giving us a moral judgment, without telling us who is the villain, just show us the reality, so that each one can decide it, provided that it does not need a mental nurse, this clear, that if not, better resort to Moore or Bush, depending on your creed politician. who is the villain of the piece? If you've not seen it, think that the protagonist, or the evil African dictator, and better not stop reading until you see her. If you have seen, maybe you think the same, or maybe you're agree with me. The villain is the woman from the dealer. One that does not question, does not look, does not challenge, to live in a Fifth Avenue penthouse with a high gear life, etc, etc. But that is it outraged when they put him in front of their noses, and she gets naked, refusing to put their garments paid for by the blood, but that even with all the evidence front, you do not report the traffic of weapons, but it is followed by the security forces, and leaves her husband when this is imprisoned, not before. That character, are almost all in our society.As for the film. Best thing is the thoughts of Yuri Orlov, the arms dealer, played by Nicholas Cage, who accompany us and guide us, or its dialogues with the character of Ethan Hawke, the policeman who chases him, a whole class of real policy. But also the moments of black, very black, almost sadistic humor, that appear during the film. Publicized as almost a comedy, when a black girl, in the middle of the night of Liberia asked Orlov if his amputated arm will return to grow, or many other scenes well, confused who expected a Rambo movie (also mentioned, XD) I do not think that they laugh much.In short: Better to understand our world, unless you like reading, then you have a lot of books that tell you what is happening in the world, and those who drink this film (for example, diamonds bloody Greg Campbell, to name one). Nevertheless, a quick and entertaining way to learn above all this.</body>
</review>
