<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="Whisky Romeo Zulu" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Controversy. It is the word that best defines the life of the complainant film, containing flammable material. It also the first film of Piñeyro as director.</summary>
	<body>Take this document called WHISKY ROMEO ZULU, after the tragedy which led to the crash of the TAM plane at the airport in Sau Paulo, with 200 dead, on 17 July as a warning.At 20: 54 on August 31, 1999 the failed takeoff at Aeroparque Jorge Newbery (Buenos Aires) a twin-engine Boeing 737 (registration LV-WRZ) of lines air private Argentinas (LAPA), whose destination was the city of Córdoba (Argentina), culminates with a dismissal at the South head of the track. The aircraft destroys the beacons of track, the perimeter fence crosses Avenida Costanera, where runs over three vehicles, destroys the coastal wall, assails a crane and a stand of gas for finally finishing uncontrolled embedding in a slope of land that serves as a limit to a crowded field of golf driving range. 67 People die.Enrique Piñeyro knew what could happen. In fact, denounced it much before that tragedy to occur. You've not heard him. and cast you the company in which it was pilot: LAPA. Terrible fulfilled forecast. The maker became director of film to tell their story and, incidentally, was erected in hero. It is not the Superman flying layer or intergalactic sword. but the brave human, which has enough courage to confront the company for their professionalism. "Piñeyro directed Whisky Romeo Zulu (WRZ, relating to the registration of the aircraft)."In the company's interest the chanta wrong unionized. The serious professional is a figure that is opposed, break you the balls, he complicates flights, generates costs, they have no interest. "Is as saying, my selection of staff does not point to your efficiency or to your professional quality, but that points to your ability to be bowed by the interests of the company."[statements Enrique Piñeyro in the lover, April 2005]Controversy. It is the word that best defines the life of the complainant film, containing flammable material. It also the first film of Piñeyro as director. Previously, it had participated as a producer and actor in Garage Olimpo (Marco Bechis, Argentina, 1999). Between a style that airing American classicism, and the skill in making use of direct images without going through the documentary, and combine a shocking sound at the climax of the film, arises a powerful film that takes the Viewer from the first minute of footage. The film is an exercise in practicality and simplicity. In this case, the media (film) justify the ends (get to the audience the facts), and a person so far, had been out of the Middle, but that she knows his marvelous power. A miracle. And we speak in the first person, because this is the film of the hero director.del.Argentine production of 2003. Piñeyro takes almost three years to shoot her, through his production company. He participated in the 2004 Bafici, winner of the audience award, it opens in Argentina a year later (April 2005). That same year at the 11th Mostra of Cinema Llatinoamericà of Lleida, the Argentine film won the award for Best Director. It is the only presence of the film at Spain. No one knows more. When land WRZ? In 2006, Piñeyro premiered force Air Corporation. The end credits of WRZ unfold in this interesting documentary, which alleged the incompetence of the Ministry of defence in the management of airport traffic, civilian. Such is the stir that hours after its premiere the Argentine Government decides to transition to a civilian management body. Almost nothing.</body>
</review>
