<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Transformers" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about robotos that is tranforman in vehicles and vice versa. Palomitera one hundred per cent, has the problem that you are going to be the mouth as esparto of the amount of exploited corn that gives you time to eat. Less roll and more call.</summary>
	<body>Your dear Special Envoy in Toledo has gone to cinemas in the periphery to inform you of the this movie of the car that transforms into robots. Not a month ago that it premiered, and a Friday at nine in the evening we were in the film five people, plus two of those put at four in the afternoon in the film and will be changing rooms until ending the session. Me I don't even imagine if I get in a room with Spanish film, they would be to plant these dry West movies.The film is a kid his father he subsidizes half a fardón car but made a shit. The boy what he wants, as it is logical in the late teens (of these American adolescents who do not already meet the 25), it is put it in marinade with the girl of the captain of the football team (which is as a cheese ball, everything is said). Total, resulting in what the boy is with triggered pheromones in the ass of the world, the most powerful army and Savior of free Nations is brutally attacked by something that dismantled it in two seconds. So while one fight that the human race is not extinguished, the others do the same. The eternal dilemma of the make love and not war, but with robots.Let's see, the movie is very long and becomes hiperlarga. Why? Let's analyse it in a nice list of things surely that clarify you everything: fighting robots-> Mooooooolan maaaaaazo.Robots that are tranforman-> Mooooolan.Robots that give the sheet-> Bueeno, come, for freedom and stuff.Comic robots-> funny touch necessary and essential.Explosions and special effects in two words,-> im presionantes.Soldiers-> in his role.Elders who make stupid-> to exterminate them and take his remains to the sharks.Teenage kids-> mortal coil.Scene girl that repairs car while guy lifts the car without cat-> wow!Footage-> excessive. We want more robots and less human.Final-> as should be, Fireworks.As you can see, everything to with robots has been plated. We can get you a couple of drawbacks. On the one hand, the stubbornness to the sheet with the goodness of the human, which is fine, but bored. And on the other hand those fights occur too much speed. That is, if the fighting were bad, because that move them fast. But it cannot be that as the Minister helicopter they slow down and then the struggles are at full blast. There was needed more detail for tired eyes.In short, film about robotos that is tranforman in vehicles and vice versa. Palomitera one hundred per cent, has the problem that you are going to be the mouth as esparto of the amount of exploited corn that gives you time to eat. Less roll and more call.I did not understand the puerile winks that do not contribute anything.Besitos.P.D: The robot Scorpion scene is great, in all senses.Pd2: The little robot I love.</body>
</review>
