<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="28 semanas después" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This sequel will delight fans to the genre and all those who want to see a proposal interesting and consistent with what it purports to.</summary>
	<body>Juan Carlos Fresnadillo returns to theaters and manages to leave through the front door. If already with his short film "Handcuffed" was released, and later with "Unbroken" showed what was able, with "28 weeks later" gives us a sequel that could well be included in the select club of "second parties better than the first".The argument is simple, and tells us the situation in London twenty-eight weeks after the outbreak of "Wrath" that ravaged among the population, and who saw in "28 days later". With a start of film frantic, fast and harrowing, Fresnadillo puts us in the shoes of Don (Robert Carlyle), and how he lived the outbreak and had to leave behind.This boot show us some images very stunning and with great force, as the race that has to give Don the Plains, as hundreds of zombies Chase you. Subsequently already is presents the current situation to the other characters and we are living the events unleashed after the new outbreak.Leaving aside the potential readings on the situation that happens in England, and the problems that arise in families, Governments and other moral dilemmas, Fresnadillo opts for showing us a very fast film, which abounds on the camera in movement and the grain in the images, giving a close touch at times.Another virtue is the use of the subjective camera that puts us in the vision of players, especially in the scene in which women and children fall down the stairs of the subway, totally in the dark and only serving to see infrared of the weapon being the peephole. At that time it reminded me to "The Blair Witch Project", tape that achieved a realism and anguish rarely achieved previously.The script and story flojean in some situations, but Fresnadillo manages to save without the film suffer excessively.The absence of people, crowds, decisions of senior and snipers, the trip by a desert London aboard a moped or the carnage of the helicopter, are some of the sequences that make up "28 weeks later", and that make the zombie theme to continue its resurgence after recent good proposals that we have been finding.This sequel will delight fans to the genre and all those who want to see a proposal interesting and consistent with what it purports to.</body>
</review>
