<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Superman returns" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Popcorn, giant Coke, and a cushion for the moments of torpor. Many special effects, but little script. Was it necessary for her to return?</summary>
	<body>Watch that to me this Superman never caught my attention. For starters, it is very limited as character, given that is invincible. I.e., that in every episode I need Kryptonite to defeat him. Then he redo and melts at the bad based on call. Their love problems find me stupid at not being able to. And then, the topic that your great costume is remove the glasses from timorous reporter to superhero damages human intelligence. No, I do not like Superman. I prefer to Spider-man, that always they creak you, to Hellboy who is a bitter life, X-Men that are variaditos, etc.The film is an extraterrestrial Superman that after five years of retirement looking for the remains of his homeworld, returns to Earth. Falls, quickly resumes his life of journalist in the Daily Planet, hoping to return with the woman of his dreams. But not everything is as he hopes, given that she has partner and a child, for it focuses on two things, save the world from the evils which torment him and try to bind to its reporter. On the opposite side, Lex Lutor (the bad very bad) has escaped jail on grounds of form and is redoing his empire of evil and terror. -Against the new threat that fly over on the United States, may Superman I say on the world? This. Let me think. well I think that if.Buff, this is a hell. Let's start with the good stuff. The sets and special effects are delicious, with the culminating point in the scene is that Clark followed with his supermirada to Lois through the elevator. Everything is assembled with great care, especially in the city. In this aspect I really liked. In the flat negative is the script, which is a turn of the screw more a character which I consider to be very limited, to the only to be defeated by the Kryptonite. For starters, what you intend to Lex Lutor teaming up with this bunch of incompetent? In addition, to urbanism Councillor to earn money, there Superman gets no hand. Then, I can understand that Superman fly and be invincible, since for that I'll see a fantastic film. Now well, Lois shake on a plane hitting against everything and leave without a scratch I think not. It is simply absurd. And what I say layer of Superman? It has its own life. If low, the layer remains steadfast waving it. That is in space? It therefore trespasses as a flag (although there is no atmosphere). I like science fiction, but with a bit of reality. And well, the final crushing of the film is not where to take it. Oh, and do not you espereis action as well the type X-men, which is more reminiscent of Hulk and their problems to achieve that the package fattening you in the same way as the muscles.Speaking of packages, it is rumored that you have had to cut digitally the said actor main, since they say that in that regard if it is Superman. And I say, a Superman shouldn't have a super Member? I think that if. By the way, led to this Superman to a level much more metrosexual, fleeing from the aesthetic muscled of the comics. Would that have even aflautado you too, with the Crystal face that.In short, drum large popcorn, giant Coca-Cola, probe (which are well served 150 minutazos) and a cushion for the moments of torpor. Many special effects, but little script.</body>
</review>
