<review author="Taliesin" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Move a 800 page book to the screen is an almost impossible task and with the order of the Phoenix have not achieved. Although it sounds strange, this new installment of Potter have left the magic in the book.</summary>
	<body>Five films in six years. The same characters, the same routines and an almost copied structure. It is almost a paradox, but the truth is that the Harry Potter films increasingly have less magic. This fifth delivery we can rescue scenes, but as a whole does not seem a great movie, for readers of the boy wizard, or for those who only know him through the film. What maintains interest in the Harry Potter novels is not anecdotal in each volume (we all knew that Voldemort looking and we all hope the great final battle between Potter and his nemesis). What really hooked to the reader is the growth of the characters, the evolution through the years and the possibility that this gives you know them better. If it wasn't for this, am sure these billets of more than five hundred pages to would be in bookstores catching dust. The problem is that in a film of something more than two hours is almost obligation focus on the anecdotal, that at the end and all is what moves the saga, to the detriment of what really works in the books.Only evolution that we appreciate the characters is that they're all more creciditos and have something revolts hormones, but little else. While through the books the reader can know the motivations of the characters, it is impossible to know is what moves on the screen. And at this point in the series, things have been difficult so much that it is difficult to understand that it is what is happening without all these references who have stayed in the role. In the end, everything is a great outline of what the book has to offer and I suppose that it is not only the writers fault, it is that it perhaps an impossible task. The case is that on-screen order of the Phoenix does not work and the story becomes boring, disjointed and repetitive. Even the smallest can withstand a weary rhythm which simply give strokes here and there, offering only a few more or less spectacular scenes on the way to a desquiciante finish, that have been resolved in five minutes.Another problem is that the actors who hired six years ago because they were funny to the House have evolved differently. Now some are up to, and others are simply bad. However, the selection of new players if it is correct and both Imelda Stauton, in the role of Dolores Umbridge as Evanna Lynch, giving life the lovely Luna Lovegood, they are really well, to the point of leaving before the shortcomings of the rest.Ultimately, Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix is pretty mediocre and more which aims is to be entertaining at times. At this point I guess it is late to change some actors, and perhaps should have done for a couple of films. What we must recognize is that, with the wealth in important details that have a more than eight-hundred page novel, it is virtually impossible to move to screen all the magic of Harry Potter. And that, when the protagonist is a magician, is something unforgivable.</body>
</review>
