<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Next" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is mild for vain attempts to Tamahori by astounding the Viewer to pretend you do enter a game where really current and possible future alternate, in my opinion, in a repetitive way.</summary>
	<body>Entertaining and enjoyable action movie and much imagination, not in vain main history is the innate power of the protagonist to find out what will happen in the next two minutes. It's an adaptation of the novel "The Golden Man", in Philip k. Dick.Tamahori moves skillfully during the first third and in scenes of great spectacle, as the attempt of escape from the protagonist of the House of the mountain. A long scene shocking, done with computers, which is noticeable in excess, but that is nonetheless true that it enjoys power and intensity.The rest of the footage, especially once it is coming to the end of the tape, is pure action with shots, explosions, beatings, adventurous movie not too well achieved. It is not that it is wrong, but it is more or less apparently thousand and one times, although it is true that "skills" of the protagonist are added to make them more surprising (multiplication by six or seven of the protagonist), thing that, at this point in the film, they have lost luster.In my opinion it's a film that is not very convincing when viewed in its entirety, for, it is undoubtedly clear that it could have been better. It contains ideas and situations requiring a greater narrative skill as well as a greater emotional intensity. Thus, the love story between the protagonist and the girl (a beautiful Jessica Biel) lacks credibility, especially if we take into account the decision of the girl once visit of the FBI and comment you something of the boy. The truth is that not be believe anyone, as they tell us and the data we have.Instead, the moment in which, at last, both are known is really funny, thanks to a successful Assembly where show us quickly different and alleged attempts to approach.Ultimately, that "Next" okay as mere entertainment, but it is mild for vain attempts to Tamahori by astounding the Viewer to pretend you do enter a game where really current and possible future alternate, in my opinion, in a repetitive way. Therefore, this formula to manida over the footage, can finish by tire. That he is great in the end, including the final credit titles, which is however totally in tune with the spirit of the film.</body>
</review>
