<review author="El vengador toxico" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film progresses smoothly, flowing through the course and stations without sudden jumps. I do not know if it is that I expected something worse after read criticisms, but to me I liked and I I recommend to all.</summary>
	<body>You know all that premiered the fifth part of Harry Potter. In my case the first three saw before reading the books, the fourth almost simultaneously and this is what I see enough after reading it. So the first thing is going to be abstracted from the book to avoid comparisons. Obviously, given that a two-hour film script are about 120 pages, cannot be expected to be the "entire" book. Important thing is to see if the script has its own entity or advances to catch-up.As you know the readers of the saga, and imagine fans of the films, the story begins in the last days of summer and runs throughout a school year in the school of wizards of Hogwarts.En this case is highly recommended having seen the previous, to know the outcome and to understand the references to it in this film. And according to this, those responsible have been eliminated completely return to explain the small "ordinary" magical things that have been seen in previous films.To be able to put the criticism, perhaps it is good to put my opinion on the previous movies (again, about the movies, not on whether they are more or less faithful). The first two are highly recommended films, with a target audience of children, but that others moved as the vision of a boy who discovers a magical new world with surprise. Good movies, the pace is somewhat calm. It is the third where Alfonso Cuarón think more tenebrist Gothic surroundings with a much more dynamic and absorbing script. For me an absolute peliculón. The fourth in the series grew in spectacular, but the script wasn't so round and progressed to saltos.¿Y how is the new? Sure you read criticism saying that it is loose. However for me not moving in the fall (great news after the fiasco of sequels of this year) and even I liked a bit more than the fourth, even without reaching the level of the third.The film focuses on the decision-making power of the Ministry of magic on Hogwarts, maligning Harry Potter and Albus Dumbledore to say that Lord Voldemort has returned. The seizure of power customize in the odious Dolores Umbridge, fluted voiced, his eccentricities and his cruelty focus on Harry. This, with a number of colleagues, will try to prepare for the return of the Dark Lord.As I have noted, the film progresses smoothly, flowing through the course and stations without sudden jumps. The progressive weakness of Dumbledore and his followers will guide us towards the spectacular end.By the way (a subsection about the books), the lack of explanations of the spells in the film makes that the fighting are more "balanced", without that annoying feeling that flies in the books that good magicians are Patsies (you can read my opinion in Harry Potter and the half-blood Prince).As for the actors, sadly Ron and Hermione decrease its prominence, even playing a role of novel teen flirting. The role of Dolores Umbridge (wonderful Imelda Staunton, is completely odious) reduces the role of common characters, such as Sirius Black, Severus Snape or the own Dumbledore, but also of new (as Helena Boham Carter). The truth is given time to have less paper many of which were common, but is what we have to pay to maintain the agility of the film.I do not know if it is that I expected something worse after read criticisms, but to me I liked and I I recommend to all.PS: Supposed her they shown in Imax 3D, but yesterday certainly wasn't on the Bulletin Board of the Imax Madrid.</body>
</review>
