<review author="Caty" title="Magnolia" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Magnolia becomes one of the best works of 1999 (and see this year was prolific), as well as my conviction that this film will become, over the years, one of the great classics of cinema.</summary>
	<body>After surprise half a world with the excellent "Boogie Nights", the young director Paul Thomas Anderson, was a challenge to front, that persons who had vibration with the previous film, find in Magnolia something really stimulating, writing an innovative and complex script that counts the events in the lives of nine people during a period of twenty-four hours in the city of Los Angeles. In this regard, Magnolia begins in a manner less original. In its opening sequence, in a rather ingenious way, it addresses three narratives of deaths that have incredible coincidences. From this point, the tape delve into the lives of the characters, creating a tangible expectation of discovering as everyone in the viewer they intertwine at the end of the story.The greatest feat of Paul Thomas Anderson is perhaps its ability to achieve the Viewer to be involved with all the figures which cross the screen. Interspersed with various frames, the director manages to maintain a steady pace. Thus, at the same time we accompany Earl Partridge his convalescent dying of terminal cancer, we discovered that his wife is stuck in a kind of "crusade" of self-destruction by having misled for years to her husband. In the Middle, we get to know Frank T.J. Mackey, a "guru" of self-help that teaches insecure males to flirt. Meanwhile, we are informed, that, in reality, Frank is the son of Earl (which they find out the nurse in the second, Phil, at the behest of the dying). In addition, Jimmy Gator, the presenter of a programme you extensive starring gifted children - including the small Stanley, always under pressure from his father-. Gator is the father of Claudia, a young woman brutally hooked to cocaine at the same time and that by chance know the sensitive police officer Jim Kurring. And can we not forget Donnie Smith, who in his childhood was one of the great stars of the Gator program? and this is only the beginning, friends.With a gallery of characters so interesting, it would be injustísimo to highlight a single performance, because the distribution of Magnolia is fully competent: If on the one hand we have Philip Seymour Hoffman, whose look of kindness and understanding is exciting, on the other hand have Tom Cruise in one of the best roles of his career, intense and exaggerated. Do on the other hand, John C. Reilly shows us that he deserved a place in Hollywood to keep a perfect chemistry with the talented Melora Walters? and at the same time that the young Jeremy Blackman demonstrates a talent in the making, the veteran Jason Robars rubrica one of the most intense roles of his extensive career. We have also always competent William H. Macy, who is representing an individual pathetic and confused with your own feelings. The only disappointment, in my opinion, is that of Julianne Moore(y_mira_que_esta_actriz_me_suele_gustar_casi_siempre), which starts the hysterical tape and will deflate slowly.With 188 minutes of footage, Magnolia not weary, because there is always something to look at the screen. Always intriguing, the film has two scenes worthy of praise: the first occurs when Jason Robards remembers his first wife and regrets the mistakes made in the past, doing a poignant speech at the same time that all the characters through their own moments of difficulty. The second is even more exciting if it should be, since it represents the climax of the suffering experienced by all, that just linking to sing a single song.Full of messages, the beautiful script of Anderson, emphasizes issues such as love and the disappointments, the complicated relations between parents and children? and are, to name just two issues of this superb film.For me, in conclusion, Magnolia becomes one of the best works of 1999(y_mira_que_este_año_fue_prolífico), as I am convinced that this film will become, over the years, one of the great classics of cinema.</body>
</review>
