<review author="JLO" title="The bank" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A script in any obvious moment, with one interesting twist towards the end, well led by Robert Connolly in her first film, demonstrating good use of lighting and shadows in a cold environment, with a predominance of steel and computers everywhere.</summary>
	<body>Film by other timely for brand new in our country, to try an expensive item in these times of financial crisis and playpen, bringing a bit of justice - even film-, against the feared banks and their shady dealings (apparently by the film, universal).Tells the story of Jim Doyle (David Wenham, correct) a mathematical genius that along with its Japanese partner, they succeed in creating an attractive software for the Centabank Bank. Led it by an ambitious and unscrupulous, Manager wanting to use the system not only for the benefit of the Bank, but to have the pleasure of ruining all the competition and satisfy their enormous greed.Everything is intertwined with another subplot, that of the marriage of Wayne and Diane Davis, affected by the troubled bank and adversely affected handling with a credit; being the emotional - and tragic at the same time - part of the film (with some coup also bass) everything to get more in tune with the desire for vengeance upon the Bank in question.A script in any obvious moment, with one interesting twist towards the end, well led by Robert Connolly in her first film, demonstrating good use of lighting and shadows in a cold environment, with a predominance of steel and computers everywhere.An interesting thriller, with all the condiments and couples performances, highlighting "the bad": Anthony LaPaglia (sweet and melancholy), without excesses but with the appropriate charisma and also best parliaments: "People to look after herself", "I am as God, but with a better suit". The girlfriend of the protagonist (Sybilla Budd) brings naturalness and self-assurance being the richest of all character. Released in Argentina in the month of April at the independent film festival, another curious fact is that the climax (the banking collapse) occurs in the film an on October 25, the day after its premiere here. To exit and quickly make the endless queue of the Bank.</body>
</review>
