<review author="JLO" title="Simone" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Satisfactory with good doses of humor as see comedy to</summary>
	<body>Owner of a personal look demonstrated in his three films, the New Zealand director Andrew Niccol is responsible for the screenplay of the famous and successful The Truman Show and the director and screenwriter of Gattaca, another good film with partner Thurman/Hawke. And also Simone, who also produces and is the weakest of the trilogy interesting point. It is not by what has been achieved in this film but because it dare not go one step further in the critique of the society described, yes he did on the stabbing Truman. Victor Taransky, Al Pacino in his accustomed good performance, is a director been less with failure including box office. Despised by his fetish actress Nicola Anders - Winona Ryder, good performance though brief - and recently fired by his own ex-wife. Through the admirer Hank, a crazy computer genius, achieved by Simone. A virtual woman incredibly beautiful and hypnotic, ideal vehicle to achieve its cinematic resurgence. Her had been promoted as a real digital character being an unknown model, Rachel Roberts, responsible for "body" to the situation. Added virtual scenes seem more a joke on the subject of the film. Fable Frankenstein-style, attacking the system itself Hollywood and excessive ambition of its components. Actors, directors, press agents, parodied and banalizados as mentioned superficially, without ever becoming a serious complaint. Walking on the thin line between story and reality, even being at times trapped between the two as the unlikely scene of the holographic recital of the protagonist. Comedy satisfactory with good doses of humor as see Pacino complaining of the ego of the actors. Nothing in this film would argue without a figure of stature, with green light for the showcasing and including a monologue, which turn this tale moralist and too conventional, a bit too slowly and too explanatory.</body>
</review>
