<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Wes Craven signed the original. His mark is visible in this version, the heroic solution of the fear in the boy who knows things that nobody wants to hear, in the end...</summary>
	<body>The Carter family crosses the desert of New Mexico to get to the California coast. The employee of a stinking petrol station indicates a shortcut to save a few hours, but that path leads them rights to an ambush. This area of the desert the habítan the human monsters that caused the test from the middle of the last century.By arbitrary that they may seem from a bloody movie deaths, the author always leaves a pattern. And the viewer leaves the room with this imprint in the head. If the family would have not got that shortcut to go to the coast would have not happened the tragedy. If the father fails to enter the House of the charge of the petrol station looking for her dog, responsible not had indicated them the road of death. I suspect that viewers we submit to the cruelty of cinema of terror in exchange for lessons of this kind. The characters who die first trace the line. The strategy that they have followed her, cry, beg, flee, does not help us. Those who survive only will be saved if they try another.Carter, Bukowski, family son-in-law is a pacifist who repudiates firearms and seeks explanations for the massacre as a good guy. He is the character who most has to change if he wants to go out live from hell. Minors have to overcome their fear.It is a battle for life or death among normal people physically and morally, against egendros are two-way. Contrary to Tim Burton, this type of film teaches us to hate what is different. AJA much slows the response of civilization. Your invitation to join in the orgy of blood is made with all kinds of delays. When the good guys decide highschool is, the public takes hours asking for it. Asians are less sanctimonious when it comes to delivering these banquets.Wes Craven signed the original. His mark is visible in this version, the heroic solution of the fear in the boy who knows things that nobody wants to hear. In the end.</body>
</review>
