<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Follow the free fall of the poor OGRE. For my taste it is the worst of the three parties with difference. A loose, recommended film for only boring adults and children.</summary>
	<body>Follow the free fall of the poor OGRE. There was an irreverent, crude and sarcastic Shrek which are only shadows. There was a donkey tontorrón, heavy and graciosete which only is trace, and something similar could be said of Fiona (never had too much joke, everything is said) and even el gato con botas, which becomes inseparable from our monstrous friend friend.With Shrek the third is definitely lost the magic of this tale, which should be already finished. The writers stretch and stretch, probably at the request of those who smell and handle the money, but no longer know where they go. Resources have been exhausted and the characters are becoming softer, less striking, more. boring. In addition, this time there is no new characters. at least none that stand out, which will bring something new. History, on the other hand, is relatively entertaining, but very focused to a child audience. Ran the Tinker and any other output tone. Everything is politically correct, no animal suffered damage while it is filming this movie and blah blah blah. Anyway, that adult you can entertain the plot, but that has never been the major asset of Shrek. Genuine, authentic in this tale of ogres, was the absurd gag, the nonsense, the bizarre situation. All that, in my opinion, began to lose in the second installment, and finally dies in the third.Anyway, for my taste is the worst of the three parties with difference. A loose, recommended film for only boring adults and children (was my case). Anyway, but it has nothing to do, if your partner or your children are determined, see it. Not bored, and this is already something. Pity that the film has made 7?. If her he had seen in DVD perhaps would not disgusted me.</body>
</review>
