<review author="Caty" title="La Casa de los 1000 Cadáveres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not espereis see neither good nor bad, this film is, as all that takes references, a description of the American Midwest rural, families of sadistic murderers and cannibals, lost in the middle of nowhere, of desolation in the middle of the field, and roads of tons of black humor.</summary>
	<body>The House of 1000 corpses is an unusual film, shot with a budget of laughter, with unknown actors and a director, Rob Zombie, debut behind the camera as director of this film of horror, gore and black humor. First and foremost must begin describing its Director: Zombie, rock singer and leader of one of the bands more originals from the scene of the 90s: White Zombie, (whose concerts and release live were spectacular, with monsters, screenings of classics of horror and other paraphernalia), is the typical adult American who has grown up reading comics, watching horror films of series bcollecting figures of action, assassins stickers and becoming the paradigm of the American subculture of the freak. Therefore, if he has followed this character throughout his career as a musician, winks of life in this film can be seen and even things will be recognized and scenes which he used to include in the work of the group, and therefore will not find strange in no time the concept of the movie. It took 3 years to release (had been filmed since 2000) due to certain scenes that the director had to cut because of the harshness of these and that made less suitable than already it of if is for the general public.United States both here in the old continent, the reviews were for all tastes, same thing her has been classified for "masterpiece of terror of all time" as "crappy infumable", and before this, and so that the viewer can decide which definition you want to adopt, would have to explain that this film is anything but conventional. Drinking directly from "The massacre of Texas", Tobe Hopper and all of the late 1970s and early 1980s B-movies, leave aside all the current horror films. This tape is not recommended for all those who wait to see guaperas adolescents fleeing the killer with mask on duty with aesthetics of music video of Britney Spears, that they have sensitive stomach and do not possess a sarcastic and cynical sense of what might be the gore and terror, or those who do not support the end that leave you "half". Arriving, as it came to exhibit in theaters dedicated to public accustomed to consume multi-million dollar productions, not me it surprised nothing nothing to find me at the exit of the projection faces of disgust, disappointment and perplexity.Not espereis see neither good nor bad, this film is, as all that takes references, a description of the American Midwest rural, families of sadistic murderers and cannibals, roads lost in the middle of nowhere, desolation in the middle of the field, gas stations run-down with characters coming out of the underworld and tons of black humor.Unknown actors interpret well its role of victims and executioners, not being a feature of this type of film the interpretative qualities, but other elements such as music, the way of filming or the argument.Rob Zombie handles the camera excellently in many moments, using flash-backs, effects of camera negative, freezing the action really tense shots, demonstrating that, with true talent, it do not need much money in bringing creativity to the celluloid.For many it will be a breath of fresh air to both adolescent she already doesn't know who or who flees (follower of Tobe Hopper and cinema of George a. Romero, those who think with nostalgia that the times of the best horror movies have gone down in history like the tape, or at least understand his philosophy), and if they continue the game will enjoy a very risky film, a show rundown cinema, in line with the sordidness of the argument, adjusted the eighty-eight minutes that lasts. Not advisable, therefore, to the enemies of genre cinema (which rather than "Scream" or "I know what you did last summer") and those who like to sit in front of a screen to see a nice Ribbon, flat and without much thinking.</body>
</review>
