<review author="José A. Peig" title="El vuelo del navegante" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If one believed that this is a good movie, all blame it on the hormones. Watch it now has the same value and meaning as the magdalena of Proust: a powerful evocation of what we felt and we were in the 1980s, sitting on the couch and rewinding tapes with VHS.</summary>
	<body>A while ago a reader of this notebook made us the suggestion I talk of this film, a small sample of the family film of the 1980s, of which many people (which now has twenty-five years of age onwards) keeps a very good memory of insurance because we saw in the early childhood and preadolescence and few things are as evocative (and misleading) as memory and its imaginative potential.Directed by Randal Kleiser, is a child of its time, and its merits die beyond this. It premiered in 1986, and comes to be a remake and remix - very akin to the tastes of the era--from classics like "Back to the future" and "E.T". He tells us the "dream" of a child, which travels through outer space aboard an alien spacecraft. When he returns to the Earth - ralentizador effect of the speed of light - eight years have passed and he does not remember anything of what happened. The film, at least respects a few fundamentals of storytelling based on "the journey of the hero", and the transformation it induces in the life of the protagonist. At a metaphorical level, the "dream" of David serves the purpose to reconcile this with his family, especially with his hated brother. The story is told through too simple, often ñoños and stupid, resources with a treatment of the elements into play more like a telefilm that a product which was broadcast in cinemas. A telefilm of pleasant view, no doubt, sympathetic approach to the modern myth of the UFOs and the abductions, some touch of successful humor, ochentera musiquilla of "can" and electrodes and little else. Special effects are a tacky that they sing even at the time of its filming, although the design of the spacecraft is quite successful, with those changes in a manner according to the direction and rhythms of flight.If one believed that this is a good movie, all blame it on the hormones. Watch it now has the same value and meaning as the magdalena of Proust: a powerful evocation of what we felt and we were in the 1980s, sitting on the couch and rewinding tapes with VHS. On his film role, the film is absolute nonsense, not for the story, which as we have already pointed out, started an interesting proposal, but by banal and plumbous the scenery and the characterizations. At the time he had his grace, but it has aged very badly.</body>
</review>
