<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Locos por el surf" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>High technical quality, stresses in each and every one of the possible aspects. Being a film to an audience often, has plenty of funny winks to the elders, making it essential in this summer.</summary>
	<body>The other day my friend Rafa called me and told me that if we passed through the release of crazy by the surf, which was in the afternoon. Certainly, with that name, and after seeing the poster, I thought it very much, and after staying no excuses give it, I had to say Yes. Hey, that hit big. To begin with, that like go to the room that has Sony next to industrial in the Castellana. Seats-ready wide back fat, a tiny room with a screen that fulfills its mission. In addition to giving us a complete cd with the movie data. Very happy with the people of Sony.La film is about a small teenage Penguin named Cody who since that he met the greatest surfer of Big Z history, just want to be like him. His family mocks him, especially that live in Antarctica, until that day comes mounted on whale turn, a great surf to worldwide competition. After quite a few problems, our Cody manages to get to the contest, but before it receives a strong drubbing, makes him know a fat Penguin with a strange philosophy of life.Great movie, if Mr. And I do not come with the roll that I see the movies of animation with too many good eyes. To begin with, the technical section is spectacular and impressive. They have a very rare thing, which is that the effect of water and character mix perfectly. And that is not at all simple. The effects of the sand are also destables, in the same way as the hair of the characters. Let's say that plated for the effects. The plot level is a bit experimental, given that it is recorded as a documentary film. I.e., we see the film through the camera of a journalists recording everything that happens. This gives rise to very funny situations, such as the small penguins talking about. Speaking of funny scenes, flat comic is great, with a very memorable shot. And not just for children. Finally, the soundtrack deserves separate mention. At all times it is more than adequate, and gives a cache for very important film.To sum up that today is very necessary, documentary film about the life of a penguin who wants to be champion of surfing. High technical quality, stresses in each and every one of the possible aspects. Being a film to an audience often, has plenty of funny winks to the elders, making it essential in this summer.Besitos. information adicionalYa have given me a cd full of interesting information, a couple of notes. For starters, the website is complete, giving us an idea of the magnitude of the project that we have from manos:http://www.locosporelsurf.comteneis games to piles, screenshots, trailers, and plenty of information about the characters and the film.Finally, the choice of characters is very large. On the one hand we have the typical graciosillos of all the movies of this style, a patilargo bird and a chicken fumeta me mondo with him. The bad ones are tad prototypical, until delve a little in his life, where begin to give more unfortunate that fear. Good, there is everything. Since the fat with its philosophy, until the impetuous, passing through the pingüinil beauty small. And not to mention the "extras", as the Cody family, the participants in the competition, indigenous or toddlers who are the Peel.And not I roll it I up more.PS: The cover of the Anglo-Saxon version I like much more than the Spanish, so I put.</body>
</review>
