<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="La heredera" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Intense drama that avoids the conventions and that offers a different view on romanticism. Great duel worlds confronted, openly opposing interests and values.</summary>
	<body>Set in New York in the mid-18th century, heiress puts us squarely in the bowels of American high society of the time. Catherine Sloper (played by Olivia de Havilland, which would receive an Oscar for this role) is the daughter of a wealthy doctor secretly tormented by the lack of sympathy, grace, and beauty of his sole heir, who constantly reminds the virtues of his deceased mother. However, the ingenuity and candor of Catherine her remain in an aura of happiness that was only threatened by the demands of a fully straitened social class. His life flows without large insides until in one of the many festivals that are forced to attend meet Morris, a young gallant followed shown crazy for her. After a brief courtship, Catherine falls definitely exhausted at his feet and the two decide to marry. However, the humble origin of Morris and the suspicions of his father, who from the beginning sees therein a Hunter of inheritance, make that everything is complicated and that the life of Catherine change forever.The heiress, based on the novel by Henry James, is without a doubt one of the summits of William Wyler and 1940s cinema works. Awarded 4 Oscar (actress, art direction, costume and soundtrack) and other 3 nominations (director, film and supporting actor) is in my opinion one of the films that has portrayed the evolution of a character (in this case the Catherine) with greater brilliance. Naïve, Candida and insecure creature, the heiress turns into a cruel, cold and strong without that no one or nothing can prevent it. The loving failure, disappointment, have felt despised by his own father and another set of circumstances end up becoming gradually a person has nothing to do with what was to be. Rarely a character suffers this evolution, from sweet to sour, from the best of the human being to his darker side. And rarely a spectator can feel so many different emotions to observe him: pity, sympathy, hate. But not only the character of Catherine shines. Although more planes, the characters of Dr. Austin (his father) and Morris are other two great bastions for this drama. On the one hand, the hatred restrained showing Dr. Austin by his daughter, always uncomfortable in his presence, ashamed of his way of being and anchored to the memory of his wife, and on the other the mysterious behavior of the young Morris, as soon it seems Romeo as a white-collar thief, do that tension is maintained at all times and that one suffers by the possible outcome of each meeting two or three bands.In short, intense drama that avoids the conventions and that offers a different view on romanticism. Great duel worlds confronted, openly opposing interests and values.</body>
</review>
