<review author="Caty" title="Memento" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do it is gratifying to be able to see a work as a Memento, which amuses, suggests and? hooked?. Does an excellent, and above all, story? he dares? be a film told in a way never seen before.</summary>
	<body>After harvest a critical success in half the world, the experiment which is "Memento", conquers the public by its originality and boldness, features absent in most of the major studios films, unfortunately, and where many times films are made as if they were in an assembly line, mechanical, without feeling. but "Memento" is a parenthesis in this vortex in the film industry. It is difficult to understand, difficult to understand in a first viewing, but made with so much talent and passion for the seventh art, that it is impossible to not stay hooked to the story, despite the convoluted in its approach.As it is already known to many, the story is told in an inverted manner. That being so, we started by the final scene and we are going backwards in time, until that we discover how started the film. But do not you think that you are going to see dialogues upside down or people walking backwards. The film is divided into several segments, and suffer these segments the temporary investment. The beginning of each segment is the end of the next. At first, it may seem complicated for the Viewer, but after 20 minutes of projection, it is easy to get used to. This investment is not only a resource estililístico of the film, the director and screenwriter Christopher Nolan wanted, with this investment, make the viewer feel as much as possible, through the head of the character of Leonard Shelby (Guy Pearce), who suffers from a condition called "loss of recent memory" from the brutal murder of his wife. That condition is the inability to recall more than ten or fifteen minutes straight. Any event that took place before the death of his wife (childhood, work, family, anecdotes, friends) is well remembered, but since the incident, he is unable to record a memory in such a way that it has no exact consciousness when he died his wife, how long has been suffering from this ailment in his mind. because the last thing they remember is the brutal murder. The only way that has Leonard having knowledge of what is happening is taking pictures of everything what he sees, of persons with which has contact (behind these photos, write characteristics of the individual, such as your name or if you must trust him), record everything, do tattoos all over the body with the information more important. So much concern is not in vain. Leonard looking for the killer of his wife and plans to kill him when you are face to face with him. But the murderer could be anyone, and Leonard, due to his illness, runs the risk of being manipulated and deceived. Just knowing Natalie (Carrie Ann Moss) and Teddy (Joe Pantoliano), that, as it is moving (or moving backwards, as you look at it) the plot, good people are changing to pusillanimous beings.Nolan used the temporary investment in a very smart way, because we only discover the "truth" with the protagonist. In a more graphic example, the feeling that is watching the tape is that we are recovering the memory with Leonard. Thus, the sense of suspense is guaranteed until the end (or beginning, according to this approach). The laps of the script are so constant and so well-constructed that frequently the Viewer is rethinking everything. and the end, where the beginning of the story is revealed, is open to as many conjectures and so many possibilities that it is difficult to find two people with the same theory. The script, therefore, is a true watermark, and I can assure you that history would work just as well if the chronological order not vice versa.The activities, which are very marked in this plot, are exceptional. Guy Pearce goes very well and manages to convey all the anguish and stress the role demands. The characters of Joe Pantoliano and Carrie Ann-Moss (which, again repeated film, after the successful Matrix) are also very well exploited, both actors are very careful with their performances, since the true intentions of its characters change several times. The music is very melancholic and accompanies very well the feeling that everything seems new and old at the same time, that all fades, paraphrasing to Rutger Hauer in Blade Runner, "like tears in rain". Also he called me much attention to some particularly important details, are filmed in black and white, as for example the memories of Leonard prior to the murder of his wife.It is gratifying to be able to see a work as a Memento, which amuses, suggests and "hooked". An excellent story, and above all, "osa" be a film told in a way never seen before.</body>
</review>
