<review author="Robgordon" title="La casa del lago" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>New snapshot of American romantic drama, governed by the same rules and common topics you</summary>
	<body>Since their first minutes of footage, this new drama romantic "made in america" reminds us specifically to "City of Angels" and generally that "modus operandi" which has the yankee film to tell us one of romances. "Even the fact of being directed by Argentine Alejandro Agresti, makes"The Lake House"that something, that bit of personality, which he differs from films like for example"message in a bottle"and carer.""The Lake House" is a story of impossible love. But in these times, the impossibility of love on the big screen should have a fantastic touch. Nothing of poems of love with characters that are searched and not found by chance, luck and destinations. "The Lake House", as also was "City of Angels" (with whom he has numerous points in common) are love stories with fantastic pretext, a mixture fuck in clips and usually evident gaps in his scripts little to analyze them. "Far away is not to love for logical reasons and verosimiles seen in"Letter from an unknown woman"(wonder of the seventh art) or without going beyond in" lovers of the polar circle "by Julio Medem, masterpiece of the loving misfortunes.""The Lake House" is the debut Hollywood by Alejandro Agresti, director of "the wind what" or "El sueño de Valentin". He joins Walter Salles or Fernando Meirelles, directors of South America are cared for in the North to make products in its industry. Furthermore, "The Lake House" means the on-screen reunion of (one entered in years and some that another kilo) Sandra Bullock and Keanu Reeves, twelve years after finding a bus without the possibility of brake.The story told in the film tells of two lonely characters (Bullock and Revees) that maintain correspondence between the two through a mailbox located in a House on a Lake, where the two lived. Presumably witty, is that they are written at the same time but live in different years, exactly with two years of distance between them, which means a burden for her, ever increasing love.That plot excuse is the base to show us the love they profess Sandra and Keanu, and the tricky thing will be that can see. A usual manoeuvre of the American romantic drama, seeking rapid effect on the Viewer, of impotence by the amorous encounter. An excuse plot is not, nor much less, original Hollywood, "The Lake House" is another remake, in this case a Korean tape of the year 2000 titled "Siworae" and known throughout the world as "Il Mare".However, "The Lake House" takes place without penalty or glory during his footage, with flat inconsequential lurking songs accompanied by abuse and a constant feeling of tragic victimism in its protagonists (notably Bullock). There are numerous close-ups of Sandra Bullock, which consists a sad character as little expressive. The side are of low status and participation and we found Christopher Plummer to doing the same role that makes four or five times each year, in different films. A film that not clear a pinch of personality. In addition, it is preferable to not enter in the game of spatio-temporal of the film approaches, because you will find so many gaps in script. Do Porque.¿no could be Sandra Bullock known location and the State of Reeves in 2006, only to find his name in the guide of phones or even write it in Google, as this is a well-known architect that easily will appear in the search engine?. Instead Bullock if that it explores on the day on which he died the father of this or any other irrelevant data. That makes the Ribbon can extend at the 1: 40 minutes that lasts. "In other words, in the logical, just it would happen the minute of footage way.""The Lake House" is, therefore, a new sample of making American romantic drama, governed by the same rules and common topics, regardless of whether its director is imported in Africa, Latin America or Europe, denoting that from time to time imposed by the large producers and need of a film as well that offer the Viewer.</body>
</review>
