<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Lucky You" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apart from the opening scene, the most notable of Lucky You are poker games. The rest is to forget, which will not be easy because the two hours of tape.</summary>
	<body>The shadow of Steve McQueen and Edward g. Robinson in the King of the game is very elongated, and therefore Poker has been almost a stranger to the film. In poker, when your opponent bet, if you want to see your cards, you have to see the bet or upload it. Fortunately, when went to watch a movie only pays the amount of the entrance, and there is no cover no preconceived bet.But, and if I had to bet on Lucky You, what would be suitable? Bet by the brilliant Curtis Hanson's L.A. Confidential and young Prodigiosos, or the mediocre Curtis Hanson's 8 mile and in her shoes? But with our heart we wish Lucky You it were the first, evil that despite us is the second bet. Eric Bana plays a professional player who seeks desperately to participate in the World Championship of Poker and prove himself and others is at the height of his father, a two-time world champion that Robert Duvall gives life with solvency. And among these complexes sneaks the character of Drew Barrymore, most vase seems the typical annoying Bumblebee. Lucky You starts with great force, with an opening scene that sums up the essence of what is Poker a thousand wonders. film endures the type the next half-hour, but from that moment will deshinchando over its excessive footage until you reach a very predictable outcome which leaves anyone unsatisfied. Between, the spectator attends a double cheap melodrama: on the one hand we have a paterno-filial conflict would blush of shame to the same Sigmund Freud, and on the other we have the sweetened relationship between Eric Bana and Drew Barrymore. There is one detail that of really funny, and is placing the action in 2003. It is supposed to add more drama to the script load, to oppose to the veteran players with new technologies and new ways of understanding the game. Which will be quite incomprehensible to all those who are not versed in professional poker.Apart from the opening scene, the most notable of Lucky You are poker games. The rest is to forget, which will not be easy because the two hours of tape.</body>
</review>
