<review author="Caty" title="El Experimento" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is the type of movies returning to those films of suspense that made you will not move the legs in the projection or not the hands of the arms of the Chair or armchair, soltaras full to nervousness and impatience.</summary>
	<body>"Seeking volunteers for a social experiment for a period of 2 weeks, high remuneration;" refrain go those which can withstand extreme situations "with this disturbing announcement begins"Das Experiment"(the experiment), a sultry thriller inspired by real events (the experiment of the prison of Stanford in 1971, remembered as an aberration and a few events that ended in tragedy), directed by Oliver Hirschbiegel, debutant in the film but with great experience on German television and that"removing some defects, typical in the operas premiums of many directors, resolves a film where his Totem is the story tells us quite well. All items (music, sets, costumes, actors), dance around the chilling plot. Das Experiment won all possible awards in his country, Germany, and caused a sensation beyond where it happened.Tarek Fahd is a taxi driver, former reporter, while it ojea newspaper with apathy, found of face to face with the announcement of yore. With the idea of infiltrate, he attends the newspaper in which he worked and proposes to make a story with hidden camera everything living in that period of time. Enroll in the experiment, in which 20 men are divided into two groups, prisoners (12) and watchmen (8) an experiment where they have to live 2 weeks in a simulated prison, taking the roles that are assigned by lot, either prisoner or guard. It is easy money, and the participants of such experiment is normal, everyday, people people wanting to earn money. The problem comes when one of the rules to participate is to waive certain civil rights and when they warn us that we will be constantly monitored by cameras. Only with stand two weeks, you have your award, but you have to resist to the end.The first days are considered a joke, nobody takes his role seriously, but as they go through the days, everything changes brutally. Increasingly climate (aseptic, too "clean", it gives the feeling of being observing laboratory rats by a window), is becoming more claustrophobic, more heavy, and finally participants are becoming aware of the roles that have to play part of the experiment. Since they remember all the first day, peaceful coexistence so that everyone can reach the end and take their reward, they are happening, in the course of time the formation of leaders both on the side of the prisoners and the of the guards, small quarrels, which will increase, grow, up to become a monster that everyone escapes Manus and in an explosion of violence final, and converge in a belief of his roles, in such way that come to believe that this micro-mundo in which are living, is part of the reality.The only black point of the film: the somewhat absurd story of love has the protagonist made from flash backs and memories, that diverts attention from what is the main argument and really adds nothing interesting to the end result.Is of those movies returning to those suspense films that make you not pairs of legs move in the projection or that you not drop the hands of the arms of the Chair or armchair, full of nervousness and impatience, therefore, quite entertaining, with a surprise after another who manage us inmiscuyamos completely in the movie. Made to embarrass us, to draw conclusions about human behavior in extreme situations, and how about seemingly normal people in day to day they can become tyrants, cruel and aberrant beings.</body>
</review>
