<review author="José A. Peig" title="Los Goonies" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We are all agree that the film by Richard Donner is a toy to have some fun on a silly day. But it will also be true that there was no nor the moment there is a film like this, so magical and fun despite its flaws.</summary>
	<body>We are looking for the explanation of certain myths and we run into small masterpieces that have marked a generation. We never went Goonies, and nor had a map of the hidden treasure in the attic, a magical corner of life in which tears and exorcise the misfortunes of the child that will always be child. The soul of the story (better said comics), Sean Astin asthmatic and charming, look at the landscape of the Goon docks (! hence comes Goonies!), detached houses between the pines and the cosy port terrain, and a sea that extends on the horizon. Here never happens anything fun, he sighs disconsolate as drops in the mattress of the bed. He even imagine, is that at the end magic takes the form of a pirate ship whose silhouette hides shadows because of a Sun that dawns on the waves. They are dreams only cinema can materialize. Important thing is not to find the treasure. What matters is to be a Goonie, i.e., living the dream of adventure that delivers us from external reality, the back up, which we expected to ascend through the well of wishes.Steven Spielberg and Chris Columbus raised a story that combined to Indiana Jones with the pirate archetype (nice tribute to Errol Flyn) and worldwide Freak of the dreamers and the abused, in humorous key and under a teenage impulse which traps without complexes derived product kitsch tontorrón and often corny, but vertebrate with a characterology of profiles and situations that succeed in creating a unique style and genuine. We are all agree that the film by Richard Donner is a toy to have some fun on a silly day. But it will also be true that there was no nor the moment there is a film like this, so magical and fun despite its flaws. Its flaws may be its virtues, by the sincerity with which is catching a grotesque ridiculería tones. We all know that the scene "Gordi" and "Sloth", saying I love you under a bright blue sky (and with the Superman shirt!!!) (I might add that Sloth is one of the more ridiculous characters that have never seen), it is one of the most pathetic moments that has given birth to the seventh art, but tradition sends and in the memory and the imagination of the young film lover endures the idea that, at the end and after all, that is part of the magic, the chemistry that arises between the ducks and marginalized gordito and the "Monster" cave, equally hated and detained in the world.The film, then, is this freshness that makes it timeless in the unique synthesis of elements Freaks and the casual comical whereby the writers are entailed the comic with jokes and several winks, some quite stupid, others more fortunate and some not free a restrained sense of the macabre. Perhaps the best explanation for the fascination aroused by even today after more than twenty years, and despite being a very simplistic film is the perfect use of editing and visual rhythm. The successive "gags", "traps", jokes, are sequenced so that the half-heartedness of the story ends up being absorbent, rhythm, if the narrative is insubstantial, this is disguised by the tremendous visual fluency, austere production design and a soundtrack that evokes the dream of the protagonist: Sean Astin looking at the waterfall of the well of wishesdiscovering the map under the dust over the decades, confraternizando with the skeleton of a centenary pirate; Your were the first Goonie. In this scene, in particular, (emotional game plans and contraplanos of the face of Mikey faced the skull of Willie the one-eyed man) the film is their dignity, which justifies the other nonsense, the resolute return to the initial here never happens anything fun. They, along with the image of the pirate ship away on the waves, and the stunned púberes and adult gaze, film in its purest form. Or how a mediocre film gets to be really good.</body>
</review>
