<review author="El mágico" title="Cocalero" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>At the beginning, "Grower" seems one documentary... But with the evolution of the course we give account that Landes managed to capture something historic: the coming to power of a common subject, outside of the traditional Bolivian aristocratic stablishment.</summary>
	<body>In general, while I see documentaries, I try, or avoid commenting on the blog, simply because they do not in general have massive and people seek primarily to the film as a refuge to entertain. Costs, therefore, if they are not familiar with the genre to make time to see documentaries, even up to me, I see a few cost me! On that basis, you will wonder, after such introduction. For what to read criticism of "Grower"? It seems to me that this proposal of Alejandro Landes is more than a classic documentary. Landes is writer, born in Brazil, raised in Ecuador and graduate in the U.S., a restless spirit that after participating in the production of "Oppenheimer presents" (the American TV show) decided to follow the last months prior to national elections in Bolivia, where competing with serious chances of victory a singular character. "Grower" is, then, a tour about the rise to power of Bolivian President Evo Morales. Landes accompanies portable camera in hand, to Evo in multiple places in your country in political acts, intimacy with their colleagues and friends, in the heavy fighting with the right and the military in each media exposure. At the beginning, "Grower" seems one documentary. But with the evolution of the course we give account that Landes managed to capture something historic: the arrival to power of a common subject, outside the Bolivian traditional aristocratic stablishment and popular phenomenon that was for that people achieve this fact. From the point of view of the edition of the tour, it is full of funny moments, (wit that makes Evo leadership military on respect for the hierarchies is anthological especially in the context in which da!), offers many spaces for rest and reflection (comments from the candidate to Senator alternate slope of Morales are very interesting) and there are clear enough in the picture showing the society. Perhaps Landes not implied at the time in which accompanies Evo that his material would have a momentous and historic value by the conjuncture encountering, but the truth is that this proposal contains many elements of interest that bring it to be a more massive than others traditional product of the genre. Beyond of your political ideology, "Grower" attempts to plot the moment prior to the consecration of a popular leader, but not just any leader, but a citizen of aymara origin Socialist arriving for the first time in the history of Latin America President supporting values of integration and respect for the pluraridades that exist in their land and with the hefty task reintegrate Bolivia to a framework of economic stability that urgently needed. By Landes (who now resides in Buenos Aires), very intelligent people of Hoyts by including it in its programming (had much impact on the BAFICI of this year) and congratulations people of INCAA Tita Merello by its new projection equipment (not know him) and the image quality with which plays in an acceptable size copy DVD which had. A very interesting product to learn more about political roots and brotherhood, "Coca", great debut of Landes.</body>
</review>
