<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Gritos y susurros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Masterful film exercise: impressive catalogue of emotions, perfect interpretation....</summary>
	<body>I did not understand cries and whispers when I saw her for the first time and perhaps now not been reached, in depth, understand the film speech by Ingmar Bergman, their panoramic devastating pain and death. There are occasions in which seems boring and tiresome of the history of the cinema director and others where it is inevitable admire his talent, and conclude with certainty that it is one of the major filmmakers of the 20th century: which raises lit adhesions and causing maintained yawns.I myself to watch Bergman movies when I read that Woody Allen so admired. He came to Kurosawa in the same way. I also so heard Bach with interest when I knew Keith Jarrett, pianist that he supervised undertaken in my income in bartkowiak jazz in the mid-1980s, it had as their favorite music. These things tend to happen: one reads a tale of Cortázar, stays took and want to read the complete works. He is marked up a term. At the beginning, in honor of the Holy truth, not I saw in the films of Swedish director nothing to wake up my astonishment.Cries and whispers is the story of a woman that matrix cancer devastates and beautiful still life family who entertains his last days consisting of two sisters and a maid. In the wrong hands, barrunto that this episode of absolutely dramatic dyes could have billed a film of sensitive but banked involuntarily to yellow, to true impudor show pain as if cuasierótico were of an object. In this case, Bergman makes a sober study of pain, a visual document that cuts the sleeping modernized vision of the spectator, in excess fueled by narrative solutions of less intensity. Faith, the death and isolation, the major issues of the Bergman, appear here, but aren't written with the metaphysical incontinence of yesteryear. What is told here is the evolution of the disease, the oppression of the family Palace, red as compulsion to the soul. Bergman goes from reality to fantasy, the imperturbable present to the past as propeller which still actuation mechanisms of the frustration and the visible conflict. Women escorting Agnes to death are also dead, cast, bereft of all vital breath and admitted in a grey tenebrism, able to make emerge secret hatred, wickedness, the foundations of fear to confront the vision and the existence of the other, albeit the sister, which has grown in its interior and has made all the vicissitudes of life in a single page of a newspaper.Bergman films with Audacity the faces of their heroines dead, women doomed to silence and the glittering splendor of a bourgeois life seeking no spiritual happiness. Cries and whispers is a stark journey to the heart of disenchantment: there is no love, there is no humanity in these spectral characters exude misery who exhibit behaviour typical of those who have lost everything and know that they will never recover as crave. The review of the tape has hurt as before he did: perhaps makes that the subliminal or blatantly explicit message, I dunno, Bergman: the offer of a neat inventory of emotions only translatable if age or experience of the spectator has the appropriate reading instruments. I imagine that if I give you a third revision in thirty years I will find new meanings: good cinema is this, the luxurious possibility that every film is different everytime we face to it. The good movies or good literature or good music, art, ultimately.Photography just deserving Oscar at the ceremony of 1972: Sven Nykvist, usual Bergman, apabulló the jury with his genius in creating oppressive atmosphere.</body>
</review>
