<review author="José A. Peig" title="Réquiem por un sueño" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A spiral of psychic turbulence with a hypnotic effect that catches the viewer and makes it part of the bitterness.</summary>
	<body>Images. Sounds. Music. Words. Making art is to create a structure through the imagination, "double vision" of the artist, poetic visions that emerge in the interaction between the world and the intuitive eye of the creator. A Requiem is a composition, Darren Aronofsky composed with images and words to express a whirlwind of ideas and sensations, dreadful reflection on the problems of social or, better still, on the human being alienated and lost in an empty world is filling up with virtual realities of daydreaming. Dreaming of what you want, everything serves: drugs, television, sex, food, are the ways to an artificial paradise that immerses us in what we are not.The story is heartbreaking, not original, but for the perfect balance between form and substance. The parallel installation and Visual tricks configured a musicality in the succession of images that saves more than the intention of leaving "cao" to the Viewer. It is not effects, but cash. Aronofsky camera creates a penetrating vision of each psychological moment in each of the characters, using images of a sensuality sickening, using elements such as drugs and sex to emphasize the addictive drive that oppresses them. In this film, the spectacular visual artifice, bombastic psychedelia, they come to be the technique suitable for the representation of a conglomeration of individual hell articulated in an expression of collective tragedy, a drowned heartbeat that is moving towards the dream final, desperate flight forward. The death of the dream the same dream. Depending on the title, therefore, the basic idea is the lament to the underground of society, human frailty, the little that we are and how much that evil hurts us not to be more than what we are. But it is not only the pain, the gaze of Aronofsky composed various tones: pathos (represented in the character played by Ellen Burstyn, simply unforgettable), (the loss of the past with the consequent loneliness) melancholy and satire on American institutions, uses and customs. In short, an overwhelming composition encompassing both sensations such as concepts, impeccable balance between the emotional effect and the expression of an idea, a spiral of psychic turbulence with a hypnotic effect that catches the viewer and makes it part of the bitterness. Do not write more because there is no time, and also because there are no words to do it justice.</body>
</review>
