<review author="JohnTrent" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This?The hills have eyes? It is one of the best proposals that have reached us of the genre in recent years</summary>
	<body>In 1977, a still maiden Wes Craven directed the cult film "the hills have eyes", shortly after having led another small cult classic as it is "the last House on the left". In these two films we found ourselves with a marked use of earthly and realistic, so stark as cold violence. "The hills have eyes" is not a film of terror in the strict sense of the term but rather what have come to be termed "films about and/or cruelty". And it is that in that proposal, Wes Craven we stood in a deserted space lost anywhere, in full light of day and with some maniacs willing to feed a family travelling by Caravan. This was "the hills have eyes", and his result was more than right, being one of the most notable films of its director. In full fashion of the 70s horror film remakes it was hoped that late or early, we got one of "the hills have eyes", and this has been.The project, as well as hopefully provided that emerged a remake of a cult movie, was initially greeted with few expectations by many fans, but little by little the new news about the names involved in the project were thinking something good could come out of all this. It is that, as soon as you confirm that Alexander Adja, the director promising of the notable "high tension" was going to be after the cameras the expectations were growing, and no doubt the wait was worth it.Once seen the movie, one is left feeling that Adja has had a free hand to do what has given him the win, and that "High tension" was not any display of quality lost in time. And is that, "the hills have eyes", remake, joins the also brilliant remake of "Dawn of the dead" as only two revisions of cult classics of the genre that they have managed to overcome their original, despite who gets upset. What is more, this "the hills have eyes" is one of the best proposals that have reached us of the genre in recent years, and certainly an exercise in cruelty collapsed in its final stretch of moments that will delight all amateur to the most brutal genre, al gore and the same original Wes Craven.Como saidthe brutality of the film before us is difficult within a today day commercial production. Without going any further, the recent "Hostel" which though to be entertaining and correct not far reaches elevations of sadism and violence that so high announcing its managers, stays as a tale for children compared to this film. Perhaps, more fans to genres such as al gore and several brutal movies, not impact us much or at least not to the degree that can impact viewers less accustomed to this kind of films, but I think that anyone who sees "the hills have eyes" certainly was not indifferent to images.At the beginning, "the hills have eyes", remake, after a spectacular prologue is dedicated to follow almost basically what we saw in the original. Therefore, we enter at the gas station and later in the shortcut to a family into a hell. But shortly after this when Alexander Adja takes the reins of history, presenting us with the family of manic, which this time are mutants you deformed because of the army tests. From the first moment that appear the action is triggered in a "in crescendo" of cruelty, sadism and torture that not apiadan anyone, tracing the attack on the Caravan that we saw in the original almost to the millimetre, but this time even more cruel. But it is shortly after this when this remake extracts an ACE of manga, which will take place in an unhealthy place where the horror will grow beyond the version Craven.Todo in "the hills have eyes" has a spectacular visual aspect, a composition of levels very carefully, good work on the resolution of the key moments and a disturbing rhythm makes us prepare always for a new event.Now if we can already say that "Dawn of the dead" was not an isolated example and that even though sometimes cost us to recognize it, a well done remake may be superior to its source of influences. Everything in "the hills have eyes" is an "improved, extended and uncensored" from the film Wes Craven, a gift for the fans of the original and the genre in general.</body>
</review>
