<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Transformers" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pure and great commercial cinema. It has all the perfect ingredients to become the success that it is.</summary>
	<body>Shhhh puuum! Graaaskc, ñiuuumm, oisfff. This could be a good summary of Transformers, the last film by Michael Bay, and who raised (and rightly) $ 250 million to date, worldwide. The Bay film is the epitome of palomitero and commercial over not being able to film. But starting from this premise, and only on the basis of it, it is a great movie. Tremendous special effects, sound spectacular (and deafening), funny scenes, good music and young protagonists.Thus, it has all the perfect ingredients to become the success that it is. If we join the realization of a director characterized by spectacular images (Armaggedon, Pearl Harbor), is not simply to sit in the Chair with your popcorn, your drink, and enjoy the explosion of light and sound. Outstanding commercial cinema.However, the film saturates. It overwhelms. As the last 20 minutes of the film, although they sell us it as the final climax and it really, becomes weary. Too much explosion, a lot of sound (become cry). It is as if they decide to show us what you have given us during the rest of the film, but raised to infinity and for a period of time certainly something excessive.Shia Labeouf, in his role of 'boy-who-falls-bien - al - Viewer', Megan Fox as 'attractive-girl-turned-in-heroin' and the other characters are at the height of a film of this kind, and that the film has its funny moments. And the rest? No more. But you can not expect it. Who is a good script or deep in this type of film dialogues? Does not own the film nor the viewer should not either. 'Transformers' one will entertain themselves. And this gets far. And if you can let yourself go at the pace until the end, it will be one of the films most enjoy. Without a doubt.Palomitero cinema in its greatest exponent. It is this. Nothing more.</body>
</review>
