<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Pathfinder, el guía del desfiladero" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Remake of a Norwegian movie of the eighties, which tells the story of a young Viking expelled for his people. Lot of action type Conan, in a dark I do not understand, and with a predictable storyline. Popcorn.</summary>
	<body>Strange thought me of this film which has reached Spain by the puertsa back after a tremendous fiasco in its American premiere. Apparently it is going to be very far get retrieve the millionaire cost. And the truth that I do not understand as it cost a lot of money. On the other hand, the promotion that has had here is quite sad that not goes far beyond a couple of posters at bus stops.The film is about a young Viking lad landed on the shores of North America. Given that it is considered to be of the tribe of the Dragons (bad balls, ole rhyme), Aboriginal people that you are taken you with suspicion among them. When it grows, their distant relatives landed again in the area to crush as many skulls as possible (another objective not grasping). And he that sucked the sword of the breasts of his mother, has to defend his people.Well, the movie itself is not bad. It has spectacular moments of fighting, has a little soporíferos ratillos, and maintains a more or less continuous pace. In general, as it atisbaba in the trailer, it is a very dark tape, and this becomes a tremendous problem in the action scenes, which can not see anything. The behaviour of the actors, at times becomes a bit strange, touching the absurdism (as in the scene of the trap). The costume is tad excessive, with a horned Vikings with more skins to peleterías Martínez, from the Aboriginal despelotados semi.To sum up, remake of a Norwegian movie of the eighties, which tells the story of a young Viking expelled by his people, who later has to defend his adoptive parents of their real families. Lot of action type Conan, in a dark I do not understand, and with a predictable storyline. Popcorn.Besitos.diferencias with the originalPara start, they have said that it is a remake that has given them the win, given that history is simply similar. In the original, all the action takes place in Lapland and the kid is the Earth. In the remake, we have an exiled Viking fighting his native people in North America. Then the plot starts to go hand in hand, as it should be. The action, of course has nothing to do, given the first more interest to the plot than in the second, more focused on crushing skulls.As for credibility, of course that the first is much more. The history can believe perfectly, while in the latter there is who creates many of the parts of the story. The blood does not know moving the sword, not. Finally, do not understand as in the present they have ignored the essential scene of unnecessary naked in the sauna of Norway. An incomprehensible error from every point of view.Hey, and where is the first snow? And crossbows? And sensual female breasts? (This had already said, but if you do a remake do not forget the pechis)Page web webLa is pretty little curved. It has the least to justify the expense of a domain. A few photos spectacular (but small), your video clips and little else. The only thing remarkable is the Viking chronology, anecdotal way.</body>
</review>
