<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Pathfinder, el guia del desfiladero (1987)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Original film about a kid whose family is murdered by the Vikings and decides to avenge either way it. With that childish taste in films that have more than 20 years, we have a nice story for a tedious afternoon. Recommended with reservations.</summary>
	<body>Taking advantage of the passes Pisuerga Valladolid, and they premiere a remake of this Norwegian film opted to Oscar, I have thrown resource and I've seen nothing less than Veiviseren. By the way, do you remember the Yulupuki grandfather? Does not leave in the movie, if that notes us that Lapland it is cold. That certainly. I have to say that I'm getting used to see before major productions, those which are the source of inspiration for directors with little desire to pay for a writer. First it was the lion of Sparta (the 300 Spartans), and 300. And now this one.The film is about a Sami community which is attacked by a few Vikings. After exterminate his family, only is I live a kid, ending in another community, which is forced to flee. The young can the thirst for revenge and decides to stand against the invaders.The thing has not been bad, but the truth is that it seems that it has caught me too resabiado. I.e. If this catches me at age 12, corro by a bow and I mess to kill Icelanders to arrows. But over the years, and with the eye used to great effect, since I know little. The story is very linear, perhaps too, with characters that appear in the life of the main character one by one and without apabullar him. Very little real, although it is not poorly resolved. The action is very realistic, with fight scenes that seemed real and very believable situations. The actors do not seem to all professional, but gives by far the pego. Soundtrack seems it didn't, and the Vikings locker room seems removed from the remains of Matrix.Resumiendo, original film about a kid whose family is murdered by the Vikings and decides to avenge either way it. With that childish taste in films that have more than 20 years, we have a nice story for a tedious afternoon. Recommended with reservations. Many consider cult film, what does that which visione it has to be.Besitos.P.D: That lasts the life of the Sami.</body>
</review>
