<review author="Caty" title="Olvídate de mí" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Carrey inhibits all his comic energy to the role of a man attracted and repelled by the free spirit of Winslet at the same time. Amazing and very original.</summary>
	<body>Amazing film of the multifaceted and histrionic actor Jim Carrey (which has as many detractors as followers), which makes us to demonstrate that it does something rather than to make gestures, exaggerated in front of a camera. It tells the story of Joel Barish, a writer who one day rises and meets the situation that his ex-girlfriend Clementine (Kate Winslet) has gone to a clinic that erase you the memories of her relationship with him. Angry with the news, Joel decides to undergo the same procedure and erase memories of his relationship with her. in full "blanking" of these memories he repent and decides he does not want to forget that piece of his life with another person. It is at this point where starts real surrealism of the film, with Joel trying in every possible way flee within their own mind with Clementine. The argument we have Patrick (Elijah Wood), which serves as the clinic worker, and drawing on the memories of Barish, tries to conquer Clementine, which has fallen in love with Stan (Mark Ruffalo) Assistant and worker along with Dr. Mierzwiak (Tom Wilkinson). Then we can also see Kristen Dunst as Mary, who is the receptionist of the clinic, and that at the end of the movie is going to play a decisive role in the argument.The film is divided into two "realities", one is in the quarter of Joel Barish, where Stan and Patrick, together with the subsequent visit of Mary, make a party with the food and the drink of Joel lasts while the procedure of erasing memories. Patrick just confessing he fell of Clementine to display the memories of her on Joel. The thing is complicated when, as we have mentioned before, the patient is resisting the process and they need the help of Dr. Mierzwiak. That brings us to a second reality, in the minds of Joel.Conforme memories of Clementine disappear, the given account that is going to miss her much and then tries desperately to save her memories in places of his life in which she never was present.One of the rather argued parts of the film is when the characters are not known and are discovered yet again because there is something that attracts them. Carrey inhibits all his comic energy to the role of a man attracted and repelled by the free spirit of Winslet, who changes his way of seeing life as you change your hair color at the same time. We also highlight Wilkinson, which gives the doctor a calm intelligence almost makes us forget the dreadful machine borra-recuerdos of his invention.Even with this plot with very superficial touches of science fiction, "forget about of my!" not surrenders to the ease of special effects. Its strong points are the characters, very well built and very well interpreted.</body>
</review>
