<review author="Caty" title="Alejandro Magno" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film entirely on the lot. Good special effects and good costume, but the script makes water everywhere and the characters are not located.</summary>
	<body>Who was this Alexander the great and why is so important from the historical point of view?. This is a question that many people will be when you are finished watching the film after attending life in the Macedonian conqueror film directed by Oliver Stone. Why was Alexander a military strategist so bright? What it differed it from the other generals of his time? What were your dreams, aspirations and frustrations? Why does it aroused so much fascination among his followers? In its attempt to humanize an important historical figure, the screenplay written by Stone, Longipedunculata Kalogridis and Christopher Kyle, get barely portray the character as an insecure and weeping subject whose sole purpose military was reaching the end of the world. Yes, there are references to his concern for culturally unifying East and West, but this is in the background, giving this place a "geographical" curiosity and a desire to avenge the death of his father, allegedly entrusted by King Darius of Persia.Comenzando already with a grotesque historical error, Alexander has, as one of its major failings, poor narration by Ptolemyplayed by Anthony Hopkins, although they serve to summarize the viewer various facts that would occupy hours of projection, explanations of Ptolemy fail thanks to the inexplicable events selection by the three writers who simply ignore most of the key incidents in the formation of the nature of the character. An example: despite having been responsible for almost all of the education of Alexander, Aristóteles is only seen in one scene, in which seems more concerned to justify - for the public - the future relationship between the protagonist and his friend Hefestion, than in teaching the young.More that later, after illustrate the conflict of Alexander at being divided between the political machinations of the mother and the brutality of the father, the film jumps eight years in time, preventing the Viewer to see, for example, participation essential of the hero somewhere that another battle next to King Filipo, when their ability to conceive strategies was revealed. The battles, mounted in a somewhat confusing way, can even impress thanks to the air intakes and the use of a huge number of extras, but unquestionably pale if compared with similar sequences seen in "The return of the King", for example. On the other hand, the second battle contains the level more beautiful of the tape: one in which Alexander, mounted the horse Bucephalus, is facing an enemy that is on an elephant. Hitting in rescuing the admiration that Alexander felt by Achilles (which included the love of Achilles by Patroclo). Unless the film has the value not hide what was between the protagonist and Hephaestion, as happened in Troy, where Patroclo was transformed into the "Cousin" of Achilles, naturally portraying relationships between two men of the time (the concept of homosexuality simply didn't exist). Stone includes various levels in which we see soldiers kissing during feasts and Orgies, but inexplicably acobarda when dealing with Alexander. If it is clear that Hephaestion (portrayed in a manner too archetypal) and the main character they love, but they do not give a paltry kiss in the projection. On the other hand, the sex scene of the hero with the beautiful Roxana, is shown in wild form, reaching the point of ridicule, thanks to the exaggeration in the interpretation of Rosario Dawson. But accuse Dawson of exaggeration becomes an injustice if we compare his character with Angelina Jolie, passing the film alternating two looks: seductive sorceress and villain stars. Apart from that, the simple fact that they try to pass as mother of Colin Farell (is only one year more greater than the real-life), is enough reason for not see you sense to his election as Olympia. Val Kilmer is the only convinces with its character, leaving the interpretation of Farrell in something very normalito with the same tone of voice throughout the film and a histrionics that exceeds normal.Finally, Oliver Stone reveals a disappointing tendency to melodrama than I ever had observed in his works anteriore s-basta count the number of times a character shouts a novel "NOOOOO" during the slide.Therefore, and in my opinion, a film entirely on the lot. Good special effects and good costume, but the script makes water everywhere and the characters are not located.</body>
</review>
