<review author="Plissken" title="Patinazo a la gloria" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>'Blunder to glory' is a very effective comedy of thick stroke, with moments of true embarrassment and delirious (some even improvised) dialogues conducted by the owner of the role, Will Ferrell.</summary>
	<body>Yes, I admit I liked 'Talladega Nights' (brilliantly translated here as 'Last lap'). It will not be a classic comedy, but I had enough funny gags, some excellent secondary scratching surrealism (Gary Cole, John C. Reilly, Sacha Baron-Cohen) and an acceptable recreation of paleto American NASCAR scene. It is not one of those unforgettable movies, but more than enough for a warm afternoon of summer.With those expectations started to see 'Blades of Glory' ('blunder to glory' in North Africa), the last product of the factory Ferrell. And once again not left disappointed experience: 'Blunder to glory' is a very effective comedy of thick stroke, with moments of true embarrassment (looking at the dress of Peacock of John Heder, for God's sake) and delirious (some even improvised) dialogues conducted by the owner of the role, Will Ferrell.La history, for the umpteenth time, responds to the cliché of the genuinely American genus of overcoming, sports subgenus (baptized correctly as "hero-to-zero-to hero"): mass idols fallen from grace must learn to work as a team to return to the top. Variations, two: the sport chosen this time is the ice rink (which already had been brought to the screen in the cutronga 'Passion for the triumph') and the number of heroes, two in the absence of one: the angelic novels Jimmy MacElroy (absurd and funny John Heder) and the rebel addicted to sex Chazz Michael Michaels (unstoppable and delusional Will Ferrell). Both, world figure skating champions coming unless, again to fight for the gold in the competition for couples, where await them their archrivals, Stranz and Fairchild Van Waldenberg siblings (brilliantly ridiculous 'Arrested Development' Will Arnett and Amy Poehler 'SNL'), to prevent his victory by the usual means in this beautiful sport.The truth is that the film does not stand a serious dramatic nor stylistic analysis. But the truth is that it matters little, in this case. In the hallucinogenic choreographies on ice of the protagonists, with its priceless pints and macarrónicas chosen songs ('Don´t wanna miss a thing' of Aerosmith, 'Flash' of Queen, or Marky Mark &amp; The Funky Bunch!), the horterísimas comments from sports reporters, even by computer effects, all raya at high altitude during competitions, pity there is no more. It also has other really big moments like the surreal persecution on roller skates ice or the presentation of the technique of the "iron Lotus". Tremendo.Resumiendo, 'Blades of Glory' offers nothing more nor nothing less than fun at the expense of one of these sports naff in themselves and in charge of the number one of the time American comedy. Look no more cause to see if you'd or excuses to loathe it if you don't like (you know to what they were).</body>
</review>
