<review author="Noa" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An entertaining, with many clichés of the genre well avenidos savagery and an unpleasant outcome</summary>
	<body>With the heat of the summer, evening parties and other sinful distractions have advanced without want to (avoid) holidays. Although officially I will close temporarily the snack bar next week. Quiet, there will be dinner of farewell and botellón to everyone. Pagais you. That Yes, we stayed in a place surrounded by ethyl zombies, not from each other, and nothing to go to a desert to make grace such as the Carter family. Pleasantly satisfied I am. (I Jane, your Chita). Alexandre Aja is the man of the function. "High voltage" positively surprised me and that I was almost a year looking at the cover of the dvd and returning to put it into its corresponding shelf. Well, sometimes her left behind "The Aviator" that I got closer to the counter. "High voltage" turned out to be a good horror film, with winks and homages to classic titles are essential. The end, many criticize, I do not bother me at all. According to the critical acclaim of the film Hollywood didn't look at Aja, seeing in him the next Carpenter, Craven or Hooper. "The hills have eyes", remake of the 1977 Wes Craven classic is the hope of good horror film.Partly topical and somewhat boring, we know an American family, which included caravan travels through places of the desert inóspitos again Mexico. Someone will convince them to change their route and take a shortcut. In the middle of nowhere will find a human with very bad milk to which will have to deal with a struggle of blood and guts and deformed cannibals.AJA do not skimp on close-ups of pure carnage and a visual dirt infuriating and well done. Obviously it is not suitable for all kinds of audiences, in which not myself, and am part of female gender network (nod without malice). The film is an entertaining, with many clichés of the genre well avenidos savagery and an unpleasant outcome, i.e. well. Despite all the successes of the tape, the plot blunders are also evident although in this type of movies they do not acquire such importance if the result is effective.As a recurring example are the main characters or tasteless figurines, a woodpecker that matter to us. Except for the baby and the dog, doing the best moments of the film, along with the deformed humans and sequences in the radioactive village. There are also things of MacGyver retirao, as some explosion in some caravan or the ability of some to be immortal. Despite everything, I recommend "the hills have eyes" to all lovers of the genre.</body>
</review>
