<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="Wolf Creek" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Under the direction of Greg McLean, notably the final section of the film. In full light of day the Hunter chases its prey. And, in the absence of film, viscera. And the Viewer is still digesting as much cruelty, until when?</summary>
	<body>The bar is very high. The viewer accustomed to see anything on screen, cruel and sadistic scenes have crossed the horror genre (only remember the final scene in HANNIBAL, semi-closed brain of Ray Liotta). The public expects more novel, stranger and more intense impact. arriving a moment in which it is not surprising, nothing surprised. In recent years the horror genre has revisited successful formulas of the 80s, with al gore's background and the remake as airy way out of a crisis of originality. So, in the absence of new stories, the main goal is to impact (as does the television or internet).With the exception of JEEPER CREEPERS, the vast majority of semi-independent productions opted for classical and better-known story youth lost in an inhospitable place and that, inevitably, have to deal with crazy or family of crazy, thirsty of flesh and blood. The current horror film baby directly of emblematic works such as 2000 maniacs, the massacre of TEXAS and the hills have eyes. Thus arises, for example, the HOSTEL endiablada. And time when Australian cinema (as an extension of any American production) brings its bit to gender. Unique proposals were in his day films TOTAL calm and Highway to hell. WOLF CREEK, it is not the same. The same story: three friends who decide to spend their holiday in a place called Wolf Creek, they have a mishap with the car and accept the help of the strange man named Mick Taylor. From there, you can already imagine. And if to all this we add about "based on a true story", which it raised at the beginning again. Horror film in particular is making use of a purely media, away from the film (sadly) language. In this case, it conveys the idea that what we are seeing is reality (as it happens with the big brother television). Nothing beyond reality (forgive the redundancy). Under the direction of Greg McLean, notably the final section of the film. In full light of day the Hunter chases its prey. And, in the absence of film, viscera. And the Viewer is still digesting as much cruelty, until when?</body>
</review>
