<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Turistas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Provide or not a good, bad image or real of the gentilicio of Brazil doesn't really matter: the fear of everything that is not "our home" is perfectly embodied.</summary>
	<body>Three Americans, an Australian, two English and two Swedes traveling backpacker Brazil. After a night in a lost paradise beach with easy sex and alcohol, they wake up realizing they have drugged and robbed of their belongings. After a few hours of anguish, are starting to disappear one by one. It does not take long for will realize that they have been the vícitimas of a trap set by locals, and its first worlders lives are at stake.To read the synopsis of tourists (2006) becomes evident why many her rated as a Hostel (2006) of the poor: both were in billboard (at least in the United States) more or less during the same period, and both saddled with a fairly similar initial situation: tourists from the first world in strange lands and, suddenly, it face to locals for its survival. However, despite the fact that they share a same premise and, in some ways, the same "message", the truth is that the two films are very different. While the Eli Roth film wallows in a horrifying "Theatric" more typical of a horror of the whole film life, tourists points more towards a realistic sample that best expresses the verisimilitude of your scenario. Not always succeeds, but almost.And it is that for me, at least, the greatest achievement of the film lies in those sequences that can feel the real situation. During the first half hour was a bright and spacious natural paradise where you can access all kinds of pleasures, becomes a desolate trap surrounded by an oppressive jungle. That piece in which the protagonists, stripped and dams of anguish, walk the streets of a village Brazilian plunged into misery follows an immensely real flavor. What is a decoration nor a set; the people through which passes the camera is real by %, as it is the people inhabiting it. Provide or not a good, bad image or real of the gentilicio of Brazil doesn't really matter: the fear of everything that is not "our home" is perfectly embodied.Unfortunately the tape is not always maintained in these paths. Those passages in which abandons his realism aren't very interesting. The villain of the story, for example, is so bad that it becomes cartoonish, and even has a (completely absurd and surplus) scene in which punishes one of his henchmen and he delves into the grounds of the supervillanía of the comic. On the other hand, the final sequence of the underwater persecution, if well very effective and claustrophobic, not seems to be very in tune with the rest of the tape, although I acknowledge that worked out particularly well with me.What wants to tourists is very clear: show a moral fable of retribution on the meat of those "predators" of the first world that, although innocent, receive theirs by the outside world that have used for decades. This point her certainly matches with Hostel, only that here the moral is too explicit and on top of that is literally explained in the main and most unpleasant scene of offal of the footage. It also shows which is why they have to kidnap the young visitors, one I daresay not here although you can easily guess from the beginning. But despite all these flaws, we talk about a highly recommended tape. It is not nowhere near a movie without bugs (its aesthetic, as I noted then, is sometimes inconsistent, and the reactions of certain characters are by little credible moments), but has very successful sequences that make it a respectable entry into this sub-genre of "dead tourists", bringing it beyond the typical and hackneyed story of psychopaths preying young innocent and unsuspecting. In the end, is appreciated some originality in these times in which this kind of movies are produced like hotcakes for the "enjoyment" of the staff.</body>
</review>
