<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It would have been a real crappy if it would have worried the sub-plots of teenagers and he had quit this dreamlike and terrifying part that characterizes both. Perhaps fails to the mastery of the third part, but yes I think it is the second best in the series.</summary>
	<body>When premiered Harry Potter and the prisoner of Azkaban everyone looked forward thinking film saga of the young English magician had matured since it was darker, more adult and intelligent than the previous two of Columbus (the first, however, I liked quite). Alfonso Cuarón, therefore, marked a new stage, that soon faded with the infant and weak quarter, of Mike Newell. Fortunately, as we all expected, the fifth installment again that style that Cuarón left marked, leaving children's arguments and focusing on what really matters, gloomy. I think that Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix would have been a real crappy if it would have worried the sub-plots of teenagers and he had quit this dreamlike and terrifying part that characterizes both. Perhaps fails to the mastery of the third part (the script is what most reeling), but yes I think it is the second best in the series.It is not as irregular as the Newell's (or less!), but notes several times that there something is missing. The biggest problem is that they have tried reducing 800-odd penalties pages in a two-hour and little (this is the shortest of the saga film, also). And this reduction, despite being generally correct, lacks some (somewhat secondary) plots to follow the thread throughout the film. Anyone who reads the fifth book I am well insurance that would take it from beginning to end, but who has not yet done so will cost a little more. Even and thus the script not just be quite well, as several times the film is repeated and leaves other loose frames unfinished resolved (as the "gags" Filch, who are too repetitivios and the already boring end). This would be his biggest mistake, but without doubt, Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix has many more successes than failures. The second and final flaw that I find is his cast. It is not that the players are wrong, is that they look not so much like pudiésen. And that, in part, is because of David Yates, the director. Especially the side that barely have time to say a couple of phrases (the characters of Lupin, Bellatrix Lestrange, Nimphadora Tonks, Moody and even the already not as secondary Lord Voldemort, who only appears in the final part, and not too much). At least the young protagonists are the focus of the film, so yes appear often, and the new and excellent incorporation, Imelda Staunton looks like any other character. But I shall leave it to the cast later. Only comment that the tape missing minutes, both to eliminate entire complete argument that secondary actors look as in the previous installments. I forgot to comment that there are a couple of scenes that could have been refined enough, such as the death of Sirius (all know that right? died,) or the final battle, which could have been lengthened several minutes more, since it is somewhat confusing and too short.But as I said, the result of this film is more than satisfactory, so I shall begin to comment on the aspects which have most attracted me. First of all, highlight the setting. The darkness and the whole tenebrosidad is more appealing, for me, this movie. Also highlight the technical section, which no wonder or the least receiving a nomination for the Oscar next year. There are a lot of scenes unforgettable (and more emotional all common thing which I think is great) and that in addition they resemble how the book reflected them: the struggle between Voldemort and Dumbledore, while missing some minutes to be spectacular; Dolores Umbridge forcing write to Harry with his pen; the kiss between the magician and Cho Chang, much more daring than I expected; Harry dizzy while the Weasley brothers escape and the public applauds them, and consequent Hermione look (this girl becoming best acts); Snape and Oclumancia lectures (pity that flash-back that you all know has changed of place in the film and is too short); Harry teaching her "Army" to exercise the most dangerous magic, in that room very well reflected on the book; everything related to the Ministry of magic (very attentive to the asensor-cabina); Harry nightmares, very well made; and many more scenes which I can not remember exactly. It is clear that Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix has really prodigious sequences, but I must also highlight various technicalities as photography (very, very good and intelligent), excellent music by John Williams, suitable for each of the scenes, and the always outstanding effects, this time does not exceed such uncontrolled way in the fourth and are very well placed (look at the brother of Hagrid).As discussed above, the cast of the film not just take. Moreover, virtually all secondary (with the exception of Dumbledore, Umbridge and Arthur Weasley) are quite untapped, because they are only a few minutes and don't have time for reciting witty dialogues, as they did (all) in the Cuarón. Ralph Fiennes (Lord Voldemort), nor appearing too (only in the final part), just fight and drop screams, so no you can see his terrifying appearance at all (as it did in the fourth). However, there is an actress that looks like none, and this is Imelda Staunton, who plays Dolores Umbridge, the new Inquisitor for Howarts is out of danger and more disciplined, although this do so in their own way. His performance is superb, full of nuances and looks that only she can do. It gives up more fear than the own Voldemort, punishments are terribly unpleasant and voice (in English) is priceless. She is the strong point of the film, which does not fall at any time. As usual, the trio protagonist just does not get it wrong, but I think that Emma Watson and Rupert Grint are even better than Radcliffe, which remains the same agonies as always, even when not so bad (like many young actors today). Other young people have good moments (pay attention to the new addition, Evanna Lynch, perhaps the girl that does best), and especially Michael Gambon, as great as always. Nor would like to mention the actions of Emma Thompson (his scene is one of the more emotional) or Robbie Coltrane (very good, but also short appearances in the cabin and the forest). To end, say that the incredible opening of the film leaves that the Potter family (uncles and his cousin) will look as well as the third, showing their cold, arrogant and distant you facets. Harry Potter and the order of the Phoenix is a good movie, full of magic and darkness, and, moreover, is entretenidísima. Some small plots have been changed (or deleted) of the book, it is somewhat repetitive and many side do not appear enough (some seem even cameos), but her however, put in second place after Cuarón, either by its enormous ability to catch the Viewer by its elegant design of production, for being more adult, by the tenebrosidad of the set or the grandiose Imelda Staunton. Those who have not read the book they are very attentive and think that here things are missing, and those who have done, enjoy both as you did with Azkaban.</body>
</review>
