<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Ratatouille" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not more than a dinner served with a taste of first quality, with a most perfect script and endearing characters. Nothing missing, nothing is.</summary>
	<body>Like small star of this film, its director Brad Bird has a delicious smell to choose themes (or in the case of the mouse, food). First designed for a family with superpowers really incredible and now a mouse who travels to Paris to finish "Chef" at a famous restaurant. No doubt, this man not may be denied the imagination. Ratatouille to her she would describe as delicious. Following the line of the Incredibles, this film begins with an incoming dish, apparent simplicity and a somewhat cold taste. To encourage the thing, its outcome is like a second exquisite dish that provides a trip through education. And finally, the dessert, no less exquisite, with a final climax really overwhelming. As you will see, the film Bird is not more than a dinner served with a taste of first quality, with a most perfect script and endearing characters. Nothing missing, nothing is. It is perfect, although obviously it is not deep enough to be one work teacher. The message, which never lack, it is impossible to clear: If you want to achieve something and put you effort, you get.At a glance, already is that the film is going to be nice, classic air and with touches of intelligent humor. And I am not disappointed. Moreover, apart from all this, is a very entertaining film, sometimes topical (and surprisingly does not bother, because it is not repetitive or pretentious) and inevitably unforgettable. Already the main batallita home of this lady shows us, somehow, what is going to be. During his stay in Paris (or virtually all), our protagonist is evolving in a progressive manner, while the young chef makes it (also it could be called protagonist). And is that both protagonists (now yes) are, in fact, one's own. Does not need to say why, already see you. At a glance it seems the typical film for children and no one else, but this assertion is wrong. As increasingly the case, this film of animation can enjoy it equally adults and children, although this time gags are not as sophisticated or hidden as in others (ahem)(Homer). And the truth is that we would appreciate a film like this to be less pedantic than some others (Shrek 2 seems to me great, but find that some of their adult jokes abound). In Ratatouille adult intelligence is not noted, because the Viewer already knows that it is there. However, it is also intelligent in the technical sense. The quality of the animation is really impressive (only have to observe the movements of the characters or sequences of action (with the camera in "hand"), which increasingly surprised me more (if you have luck, maybe you can see in the film the teaser trailer for Wall-E).) I must admit that Pixar has surpassed once again with this impeccable Odyssey of this tooth called Remy and its relationship with the environment of the kitchen (well done).The characters are all credible, endearing and intelligent. From the outset that Remy, mouse, you like and is therefore more pleasant to follow the plot of the film. Not wasted at all the young chef, who also, along with the other Cook, get us we create them and we made nice. But for me, the greatest achievement of the film is the food critic, a sleazy character who initially acts as bad but the tastar recites one of the best thoughts I have heard in theaters for some time, the famous "ratatouille" on the art of being critical and all the consequences. Ratatouille may not be the perfect work mouse creates at the end, although I don't think he meant it to be. This is a great movie, but unfortunately fails to be perfect because it is animated, and therefore can not be as deep and complex as a footage for no animation. But if we focus in the field of the drawings, we could consider this, best film seen in long and, without doubt, the best animated film of what it far this year. Absolutely essential.</body>
</review>
