<review author="José A. Peig" title="Indiana Jones En busca del arca perdida" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>That same ease and freshness in the treatment of the characters and situations is pervasive throughout all the footage, so smooth and strong narrative that one reaches the end credits with a thought: just seen the total adventure, paradigm of the seventh art as a recreational tool.</summary>
	<body>According to an original idea by George Lucas, Steven Spielberg signed here one of his films more round, paradigm of the modern adventure film and presentation of Indiana Jones, the model of adventurous hero that has most influenced the minds of fans over the past decades.The intention was to recover a classic style taking as a reference the film and comic of the years 30 and 40. The result was indeed a return to adventure movies, Furthermore, managed to reformulate the style and the myth of the hero in tune with the new demands of the emerging culture of masses, and a film industry ready to exploit the new possibilities. First and foremost, "Raiders of the Lost Ark" is the expression more forceful that has ever had the film in its more profitable field: the show devoid of any other intention than that of entertain the viewer with a succession of passages filmed in such a way that they excite and cause amazement, not only by a visual delight which is of impeccable handling of the tempos and the pace immediate consequencealso by the perfect structure to be linking a few situations with others, in a cluster of action scenes that become pure film to be at the service of a simple narrative and seamless. In this way, the film not demanded anything the Viewer, we are talking about a product consumption easy, but done with art.First bars: a group of travelers in a jungle, a mysterious character with jacket and hat leads the retinue, always behind or above the camera, we will not see his face until moments later, when one of the companions intended to betray him, then hear the hum of a whip and from the jungle shadows emerges the face of the unsung hero. The presentation of Indiana reinforces the subtle and mysterious halo that is (should be) own all charismatic hero. The subsequent sequence before the idol of gold, the approximation to the objective attitude of barely disguised reverence, stunned and fascinated expression in the gesture of Harrison Ford before take the relic, in a few short moments Spielberg characterized the character and makes a simple but powerful drawing which will be protagonist and winner in the great quest. He is passionate about the campy archaeologist who transmutes his appearance of erratic traveller in a respectable University teacher dressed in a suit, "gafotas" and object of desire by some of his students. Reflection of the hero, once hanging the whip, jacket and hat, appears to be one of the lot.Already said elsewhere: the narration is an art of synthesis, and above all, "in search of the Lost Ark" is a story in which all the characters (despite being quite one-dimensional) are characterized with effective stroke, without unnecessary details that could impede the pace of storytelling. Spielberg - along with the commendable work of that great screenwriter named Lawrence Kasdan - summarizes the action of the show with a succession of acts perpetrated by consistent characters and in the service of such action. From Belock, antithesis of the hero, to Marion, passing through Shallá (gesture unforgettable his farewell from the docks before heading on the boat of Katanga) or repulsive secret agent who deceives us with a hanger coat which home looked like a flogging instrument. Everybody's looking for the Ark for a few reasons stated with clarity.Simplicity and conciseness, this is the key to the good cine-espectáculo. Add is a configuration of profiles attractive and claw.Some critics have wanted to see flaws in this film, and often refer to the inability of Spielberg to create complex characters. Indeed, the characters are fairly one-dimensional, but in this particular area is not necessary to have characters with complexity (depending on the intentions and contents of each movie, that would be analyzed). And - conclude these clueless critics - the movie would have been much better if the characters have other shades apart from the archetype "the movie boy", "girl from the movie", "the bad friend of the bad guys", "good friend", etc.Well, all this is nonsense according to the scope and the intent of the product. Synthesis. Synthesis. Synthesis, damn is. That is to say, in this case, which, supposedly, the film could win with the (unnecessary) effort by director and screenwriter to create more complex characters, would lose it the pace, pulse and narrative momentum, continuity of action without respite and dialogue serving essentials. That is, the very essence of the film would be lost. This being one of the few times in which claims are couples with the final result, sobran all considerations that are being demanded product something that does not form part of its scope. What matters here is to provide the history of a characterology of characters akin to the structure of media and content, not depth. Moreover, it is a film that moves by land arquetipales, prone to the topic and the sentimentality, but never falls into such defects. Perfect example of this is the scene of Marion and Indiana in the boat, the kiss between the wounds of an Indiana battered and grumpy, a time to love, but without falling into the as usual sentimentality in scenes of this type.That same ease and freshness in the treatment of the characters and situations is pervasive throughout all the footage, so smooth and strong narrative that one reaches the end credits with a thought: just seen the total adventure, paradigm of the seventh art as a recreational tool.</body>
</review>
