<review author="Tony Astonish" title="La Novia Cadaver" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without being so fascinating as "Edward Scissorhands", I think the story that presents us with Tim Burton is a delight well designed, well established and that doesn't let us indeferentes...</summary>
	<body>The universe often submit Tim Burton in his films always has that strange mixture of sadness and joy, and in "The corpse bride" expression of their characters in both sets is very well defined.In the "mortal world" everything is grey and dark; the faces of the men that inhabit it are sad or show anger; everything is monotony and they move to the beat of the "ticking" of a clock. In contrast, the "world of the dead" is inhabited by skeletons and cadaveres which seem to have not lost their lives; the colors both of the sets and the costumes are clear and alive; residents smile and sing jovially, welcoming the newly arrived to make his long stay not "eternal".The tale is about a very trite theme, "true eternal love", and introduces us to a couple of young, Victor and Victoria (embodied by Johnny Depp and Emily Watson respectively) are forced by their parents to marry by the economic interest pure of these. Two young people are apathetic and cold at a marriage of which do not even know your respective partner (how to marry someone that you're not in love!!!)(-wonder). By a misunderstanding, the young Victor "undoes" the spell of Emily (Helena Bonham Carter), a woman who was murdered just as he was going to marry. This event will change his life and the rest of the film's characters.The movie includes twists and very funny gags, such as for example references to the mythical movie "that took the wind", as well as take a joke a taboo as the death. And, of course, missing the macabre touch that characterizes the movies of its director. I loved the attention to detail in the movie: one might say that each drawing or each scene help, in greater or lesser degree, for something that is going to happen. The length of the tape is fair, perhaps too to explain such dramatic change in the way of thinking of the main characters.Without being so fascinating as "Edward Scissorhands", I think the story that presents us with Tim Burton is a delight well designed, well established and that doesn't let us indeferentes.</body>
</review>
