<review author="José A. Peig" title="Indiana Jones y El templo maldito" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It has almost everything to be a bad movie, but it is not. The good work of Spielberg, the magnificent work of mounting, production design and the overwhelming musical accompaniment by John Williams manage to make this film a very worthy divertimento.</summary>
	<body>The temple damn situated action a year before the search for the Lost Ark, so can have the nickname "prequel", a kind of marginal adventure hero Indiana Jones is involved in a plot around dark rituals of the India. The prologue, at a restaurant in Shanghai, is anthology and mark the boot of a rhythm unwavering in one of the more frenetic films in the Filmography of Spielberg, without giving respite to the Viewer, is sequencing situations to each more zacchia, without losing the ability to entertain, but with less style in the Ark lost.Its predecessor, as we already said, had virtues in abundance in the different facets that can offer this type of film. A show articulated through a simple but vivificada story based on characters - model handled with ease, some of them too stereotyped, and yet the film never fell into a ridiculous or topical saturated binge. Unfortunately, and is something that both Spielberg and Lucas have said with regret, in this occasion were not so fine.We said that the important thing was not the complexity, but characterize characters with claw and without falling into cliché. Kate Capshaw, unfortunately for all Queen's function, not only is a stereotypical and annoying character by their expressive excesses, it becomes a figurine of ridicule in the form of crazy that happens all the time hitting screaming and saying stupid number. The character of Willie is a major setback in the style, which ends up invading most of the sequences. On the other hand, the new companion of the hero is a child that contributes little apart from having tear re-examine, in the line of the weaker Spielberg and helpings, and also knows kung-fu. With all this we have the film loses bellows because there is not a single charismatic character accompanying to Indiana Jones, unlike that in the Lost Ark, where the set of profiles accompanied perfectly, configuring a collective spirit of adventure. Here, instead, the mouthed blonde and the child make mere anecdotal comparsa, are not integrated into the style that characterizes to Indiana Jones and was held singularity of a paradigmatic work. In short, the tone of the adventure degenerates in banality and circus vulgar, if we look at the action scenes.When the imagination is scarce, it is natural to resort to designs and spaces of park attractions (or game), riding to the viewer in a roller coaster, as we see in the persecution carried out by the henchmen of Mola Ram in a scene, however, equipped with a frenetic pace and infantiloide humor. Forced and too contrived situations with which the writer is seen the Duster: plug always stomping and puts his hand where it should not at the time just., Willie puts the ass in less place. They are stereotyped and easy tricks that banalizan the overall tone.On the physiognomy of the elements in game - topical, situations and characters too stereotypical and devoid of imagination - the Temple of Doom has almost everything to be a bad film, but is not. The good work of Spielberg, the magnificent work of mounting, production design and the overwhelming musical accompaniment by John Williams manage to make this film a very worthy divertimento. The scenes of the ritual in the interior of the temple are impressive, the choreography, the presence of Mola Ram (a bad circus and topical, but has its moments), the brilliance of diamonds in the interior of the sacred stones, the transformation of Indiana in henchman of dark power, and the liberation of enslaved children, preceded by a frame in which we see Indiana with omnipotent expressionAfter herding the proper punch. A scene which expresses eloquently the resurgence of the hero and the supernatural character that is own.</body>
</review>
