<review author="Doris" title="Cars" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Display of design and meticulousness, one creation of the geniuses of the Pixar House</summary>
	<body>Perfection is impossible, I'd say that. But Pixar hovering ever closer; do that Yes, what? MOM? Disney lets you. Cars, the latest in animation for the big screen, is a display of design and meticulousness, one creation of the geniuses of the House which, however, suffers from little imagination in the message, something what is regrettable after a past full of intelligent wonders of the drawing. However, the triumph is assured, especially among children and the lovers of racing.Do Lightning McQueen, the protagonist racing car, is in danger of becoming a cocky champion only worried about the triumphs and the? Flash?. His biggest dream is to win the piston Cup of California, a title in the great power that would make him a young star of the racing. But going way of the competition, you lose your phone and will stop in a small town in the legendary Route 66. There he will meet his future friends and will understand that life is not only to win?All very predictable but possibly necessary given the characteristics of the product. Humanize a car is not an easy task, and to compensate for the lack of expressiveness, which is however very accomplished, pulls the always ready sentimental appeal. Need an affordable moral but without going and, of course, a nice ending. Do the tradition is not going to change at this point, but at least is to be welcomed that we have avoided by all means some? topicazos? irreversible.Does taking advantage even the pull of formula 1, figures such as Michael Schumacher and Fernando Alonso (stuck to shoehorn in the Spanish version), are left? see? in a round? cameos? It included some that another surprise. Something of everything squeaking, as well as the so-called love story, whose sole function in the script is to make time, and crane? best friend? McQueen. Do about which the? well of truth? history is ugly and silly adds nothing (what such, any time, be a friend of? bad?).Despite the ailing development and an excess of localism which runs the risk of being ignored by some part of the respectable of Lasseter not disappoint as winks and double readings refers. And, of course, his wit manages effortlessly redirect the sudden sweetening of the moment, including the central song of the indispensable Randy Newman, Our Town, starring this chronicler as a mockery outright towards type Pocahontas ballads in several sequences. Everything is possible.But what really excited to see the machines in action. It is a real pleasure to appreciate the game of textures, colors, reflexes and precision that Cars boast an impressive superiority. The movements of a camera that does not exist do the rest. So enjoy with the speed and are not lost, as I have to know, the opening credits. Nor the short of the principle, the man Orchestra, a delicacy that is almost worth more than two hours of projection. Just a few minutes.</body>
</review>
