<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Planet Terror" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Planet Terror is new delirium of one of the most personal Directors has given Hollywood industry in recent decades. That, to enjoy it entirely there to immerse in the fantastic world emerged from the prodigious imagination of Robert Rodriguez.</summary>
	<body>These are not good times to find something original and different in a film which in recent years has saturated us remakes, remakes, sequels, prequels you or any other term that defines a rampant lack of ideas. However, some filmmakers are fighting against it and continue to make proposed fresh and innovative, as Quentin Tarantino or Robert Rodriguez and his Grindhouse project. It must be admitted that it is the less ironic that a project emerged as a homage to a type of outdated film is one of the most innovative and original of the year proposals.The cinema of Robert Rodriguez, although at first glance it may seem otherwise is very personal, and since then does not support average, or you love or you hate. The argument of Planet Terror is nothing out of this world, is one of terror in which a strange group of people fighting for their survival against an army of zombies infected with a virus. What matters in Planet Terror is not telling the story but how the story. And it is that Rodriguez is a true master of storytelling, a filmmaker who masters perfectly the language and film tempo. The film is a frenzy delirious from beginning to end, and has some truly surreal moments that will cause multiple laughter in the audience. And it is that between all the blood, guts, desmembramientos, shots and explosions that contains the Ribbon hides a sense of subtly macabre humor. It is true that Rodriguez will goes hand in hand in some scenes, but all the geniuses have their excesses, and it knows in what occasion may move from the line and which not. But before all this, and to open mouth, the audience can enjoy with the madness of the fake trailer for Machete, which aims to Rodríguez become full-length movie.Planet Terror is new delirium of one of the most personal Directors has given Hollywood industry in recent decades. That, to enjoy it entirely there to immerse in the fantastic world emerged from the prodigious imagination of Robert Rodriguez.</body>
</review>
