<review author="Bruji" title="Next" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With a legacy development of Femme Fatale of De Palma and a perfect open outcome, their multiple successes get hide the continuing inconsistency of an obsolete script.</summary>
	<body>Excellent tape action in which only compliment the pelucón of Cage and, in not few moments, sobreactuada interpretation of Moore. With a legacy development of Femme Fatale of De Palma and a perfect open outcome, their multiple successes get hide the continuing inconsistency of an obsolete script.They can not deny. The USA worship be in constant and imminent danger, and the public loves it. Even dare to assure that those yearn times of the cold war in which a tangible enemy of USSR name was always willing to undermine their vast Empire. When, at last, this happens (Fortunately, only in the best theaters), and the nuclear alert extends to Southern California, from San Diego to Los Angeles; all doubts about the potential incompetence of their Government, are met; the security forces are declared ineffective and insufficient, and a lone (on this occasion, guessed in Las Vegas) manages to save the Humanidad.Con so ridiculous, outdated and absurd plot, collected based on a novel by Philip k. Dick, inspiring of great movie titles like Blade Runner (Ridley Scott, 1982), challenge Total (Paul Verhoeven, 1990) or Minority Report (); Tamahori amply meets the fundamental objectives of the best action genre. Agility in the narrative structure - which soon dispenses with a voice that does not need-, spectacular scenes and a development of rapid pace that creates and maintains the tension; tucked behind political safety an accurate soundtrack and some well-intentioned interpretations, are the main advantages of this production of considerable budget. Although undoubtedly its greatest success lies in the ability of the filmmaker, proven irreproachable and impeccable in the way of directing, to alleviate the many inconsistencies of the script. It matters little that the FBI focused all its efforts to locate the wizard of the 39 steps, rather than attempting to dismantle a gang of international terrorists of mobile and origin unknown, if this relentless persecution is drawn with brilliance. Nothing is concerned the shameful cellular mitosis which undergoes the protagonist, nor his bizarre way of avoid the danger, if after the cameras is one of the best craftsmen of our time.The result translates into a notable exercise of pure entertainment, for an hour and a half, has the virtue of invading the senses of the spectator, preventing him blinking, seducing you from the first frame, forcing him to archive the inconsistent unreality of an exploited argument and up - who knows? - the reality of its existence.Within the cast, we find a reviled, reviled, and often mistreated by critics, Nicolas Cage. An actor who always did what came to him in WINS, producer of his own films, which is at that point that can afford the luxury of making his cloak a sayo. It is not alone in doing so, does perhaps was not Robert De Niro "The father of Ella"?. Julianne Moore, the eternal promise that never ends shine, is convincing when his roles involve not transcendence; to fall apart if you know that your interpretation will be object of praise. Surprisingly, his naturalness in the hand that rocks the cradle, as well as its ridiculous atavism in Lejos del Cielo, or his overacting unconscionable in Las Horas.Jessica Biel, for its part, will achieve a perfect interpretation in its task of good aunt, altruistic master of an Indian reservation, whose charms will not leave indifferent.And, as "know the future remains spontaneity", "freedom means responsibility" and "beauty is the sum of the parts working together in such a way that no required add or alter anything", is possible? and even likely - that this movie manages to make us forget the matters. at least for the next two minutes. Who said that this is not the film?</body>
</review>
