<review author="José A. Peig" title="Indiana Jones y La última cruzada" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A superb exercise Classicist adventure and adventure as a metaphor for the spiritual quest, a spectacle of appalling Visual rhythms, humor, some of Wagnerian romanticism, excellent characterization of characters and anthological description of the hero.</summary>
	<body>Many years passed until these days - motivated by recent news about the new adventure of the archaeologist of yore, which reach the screens around the world in May 2008 - who writes this and his troupe of thinking minds, they decided to review the three pieces that have forged a timeless icon, and this third - is by ignorance or forgetfulness - discover with great satisfaction that hides a masterpiece", perhaps, never as sufficiently proclaimed, and since then has nothing to envy to a work of art as it is"in search of the Lost Ark".""Indiana Jones and the last crusade" is one of the best adventure film in the history of cinema. If we look at a classic pattern - a pattern that synthesizes the bases of what should be the art of narration in images-is one of the most perfect movies ever made. It is model and CANON, at the height of the great adventures filmed by John Houston or John Ford. You can add also something of the spirit of Howard Hawks. Spielberg, borrowing a bit of each, makes his personal synthesis, appropriate to their times, and proclaims himself - with merits and justice - master absolute entertainment.The first images are already an evocation to the classicism of John Ford; the Paramount icon gives way to a mythical landscape, the steep arid mountains in the State of Utah and the Colorado Valley, winds that drag sand and far a convoy of riders that ride in a row. It seems that we are back to the golden age of the Western. The pace acompasado in the succession of long and general plans in harmony with the first notes of John Williams, transmit the sensation of a spirit and a way of making films that, unfortunately, now seems to extinct. Then we discovered that the riders are a group of boy scouts, and Indiana (our teen Indiana) is among them. In one of the caves, Indiana discovers a group of looters, whose head leads the future hero attire. Suggestive evocation of a Genesis; the theft of the cross of Colorado and the consequent persecution until the train, and resolution, defined from the prism of the saqueador anonymous which then "baptizes" our hero by placing the hat, the fate of bold, amoral adventurer: that smile of pride and satisfaction when he sees the boy flee with the precious object. It seems that he sees in it a reflection of himself. The beginning of the future hero.When young Indiana arrives at his home looking for his father's support, it makes a gesture of rejection so a latent conflict because of a too inward in his archaeological passions and indifferent father of Family Affairs is established, and by reason of this future criticisms will come.Once the hat falls on the face of River Phoenix, as in a wonderful fusion of the past in the present, the teenager that emerges is already adult, faced his former adversary, at a first level which culminates the genesis of the hero in a continuous temporal not devoid of beautiful meanings. With so much hot air just try to say this: that those first ten minutes of footage are a masterful lesson in cinema, example of synthesis, and exquisite by narrate taste. And, incidentally, shows a great respect for the created character, which already in 1989 was part of popular culture.The following sequences raise a return to the scheme of "In search of the Lost Ark", again Indiana as University Professor, returns Marcus Brody, Christian mythology returns to be the excuse to start the adventure. Venice, a library with its secret passageways, boat chases, conspirators fundamentalist, and her presence omitted the father of Indiana as a main driver of the quest for the Grail, until finally appears in an Austrian Castle. From that moment, the film becomes a journey of action accentuated with blows of parody and sarcasm. The relationship between the Jones the Jones and father son this drawn with a sense of humor that covers both the cold and distant communication between them as a disguised feeling of mutual admiration and respect, as well as the criticism and opposition from ideas: Indi materialism against the faith of Henry. And the relationship between one thing and another, presents an eloquent ambiguity. In short, the chemistry achieved between Henry and Indiana Jones is one of the best orchestrations on the characterization and connection between two characters, who have been in the past thirty years, worthy of anthology.And to this tale, there is a key phrase put in mouth of Walter Donovan (Julian Glover): find your father and you will find the Grail. The Grail as a literal element of a spiritual quest and personal fulfillment. Between father and son, as we have pointed out before, there is a conflict whose origin goes back to childhood. The "Junior" nickname used by Henry to appoint his son has a contemptuous connotation, as an effect of this conflict in which the father does not end value to his son into perspective. Then, in the final scenes, when Indiana cuando Indiana está is I note from falling into the abyss for wanting to take the Grail beyond the label which limits the eternal life, in a moment of understanding, Professor Henry Jones pronounced with emotion the word "Indiana", which comes to heal all the wounds of the past that redeems the hero of his sins of greed.There are several outstanding action scenes: persecution in motorcycle, mounted in an aircraft, through the desert and to the beach, in which we see a feat Sean Cornery, skewing a flock of birds with an umbrella, making his own army and evoking, umbrella in hand, the words of Charlemagne, while the face of Indi draws a gesture of admirativo appreciation, but always back to his father, which is a constant (the love content or disguised, a certain emotional isolation) on the relationship between the two, except in extreme moments.Excellent mounting allows a collective story, in which the characters are its constituent role of rhythm and narrative claw; Donovan, Elsa Snaider, a German soldier with very bad milk and penetrating blue eyes. Anecdotally, we see Indiana face to face with the very Adolf Hitler, giving him a book of secrets that will go unnoticed. The gesture of Indiana to Elsa Snaider, at the ceremony of burning of books in Berlin, taking him neck with fury, and the response of it, the content between the two, hate maybe beating also is a mutual respect, in spite of the circumstances and the lack of scruples by some and others, a network of relationships forged through an excellent construction of sharp dialoguesin which premium the sarcasm and irony. Goes without saying that the main action scenes are all an example of master in every moment and problem viewing, superb handling of the rhythms, the profiles in a flawless structure which ends up joining the whole way in the battle in the desert, between tanks, horses, camels and fundamentalist guerrillas, there where all parties involved come together in the resolution. Pure spectacle and narrative structure that becomes a timeless classic taste.Excellent chemistry provided by Harrison Ford and Sean Cornery reaches a point of Ecstasy in the last steps to enlightenment. Donovan shoot Henry, and is then when Indi another option that does not fit the go in search of the sacred water that can save his father. The scenes in which Indiana is surpassing three final examinations acquired an intense dramatic meaning through the proper use of the Assembly, alternating the fear the lack of faith in Indiana with the agonizing gesture of a Henry Jones who urges his son to a State of faith enabling it to achieve the Grail. The magic returns at the end, after the last leap of faith, and father and son recognize the mutual discovery. The four adventurous ride towards the horizon while the solar disk invokes the twilight of the gods, we see the silhouettes of four horsemen who move away in one of the best frames, evocative and meaningful from a farewell, farewell of an adventure film made with love and craftsmanship.In summary, a superb exercise Classicist adventure and adventure as a metaphor for the spiritual quest, a spectacle of appalling Visual rhythms, humor, something of Wagnerian romanticism, excellent characterization of characters and anthological description of the hero, nostalgic, tender, as well as parody and easy-going. And Yes, in reality, and despite the fact that the Lost Ark has taken all the fame, this is the best of all, still not valued enough in all its complexity. Do we change mind from here to a few months.?</body>
</review>
