<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Volando voy" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Many things happen but you do not learn well why. The actors are quite loose, the remainder drama. And follow the plot is very complicated, for the continuous ups and downs (and because it is incomprehensible why the acts of the PEAR).</summary>
	<body>Flying go, flying I'm here, by the way I I entertain. (Kiko Veneno 1979).The film is the life of a child, nicknamed the PEAR, from age nine to eleven. Only brother among five sisters, from very small is dedicated to steal cars and drive them. Their continuous assaults and persecution, United friends of wrongdoing that has, it makes him flesh of presidio. Parents attend totally powerless to as your child becomes a myth among juvenile delinquents in the South of Madrid.Al seem everything is based on the real life of Juan Carlos Delgado "the pear". Look, it will be truth that did all this, but I script so I do not believe neither of coña. It may be that the chosen actors are not the most appropriate, but I think that very little credible is plot. I suppose it's a case of which reality surpasses fiction. Not I learned well if it was a comedy or a drama, as the father of the PEAR (el peral, juas, juas) has no dramatic record. And it is that when you're bad actor and you're pigeonholed in the role of goalkeeper's series of humor, badly you can leave it. This film would have needed a dramatic actor of truth, and not to this gentleman. They could have made a very good movie with good actors and transitions between scenes clearer, but done so the result is loose.In short, many things happen but you do not learn well why. The actors are quite loose, the remainder drama. And follow the plot is very complicated, for the continuous ups and downs (and because it is incomprehensible why the acts of the PEAR).More than anything what could have been and was not.Besitos.P.D: do Kiko Veneno will have something to do with "the poison" (of sharks)?Pd2: There are poorly resolved very violent scenes.P.D.3: The only one that is saved is the director of CEMU (students city boys) which seems to me to be acting very credible. And what is incredible, but true, is that there is people like this in the world. Here I give you my most heartfelt congratulations.P.D.4: Once I was with a tarao in the streets of Toledo imitating the PEAR and I almost small on top.</body>
</review>
