<review author="Doris" title="Memorias de una Geisha" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In reality, it is a story of love more than a miserable biography</summary>
	<body>The Asian cinema has become already what the whole of their countries of origin, into a giant. This week opens in Spain with great anticipation the adaptation of best-seller memoirs of a geisha. And is certainly a superproduction full-scale, above all by the fact that the head is that made Chicago (dot were Spielberg or Spike Jonze) and because the Bill is American. And in addition, includes in its cast to more flashy movie stars: Michelle Yeoh, Ziyi Zhang, Li Gong and Ken Watanabe. By the way, that only he is Japanese, because the great Yeoh was born in Malaysia and the other two in the Chinese millenarian. Curious. Also appear around Cary-Hiroyuki Tagawa, Koji Yakusho, and Randall Duk Kim, surely they have seen in some other movie.The recreation of the Japan of the 1930s and 40 is fantastic, and that is all decorated less, I think, the gardens of the tea room, an explosion of colour and peace (Yes, the Zen philosophy me has invaded). And the story is almost epic. In fact, it is a love story rather than a miserable biography, which is well known that the own and real protagonist, Mineko Iwasaki, not congraciaba, so decided to write their own version later. It is interesting, however, contemplate how entrenched culture moves the everyday life of women since the girls are and how these are prepared to be the most desired and envidiadas. Because it also shows the greed and decrepitude which at one point invades the hearts of women. All very metaphorical, very rhetorical and highly decorated, as you can imagine. But however nice and without being heavy, that it is true that some Eastern productions sin of this.So, despite some other sober loose and the overwhelming and little Cape that is the development of the narrative occasionally (Incidentally, in voice-over, a very Resolutive resource), not to put too many objections to memoirs of a geisha. And since then, the actresses I liked once again. Pretty as they alone. Mr Watanabe is seen more, what going you to do.If you want to see something else this mysterious world, two Councils. My dear Moriarty has strongly recommended me you see Zatoichi, of the illustrious (says he) Takeshi Kitano. That, talking about another thing, back to see you soon in one of its more crazy facets, says Gadxeto blog. And one more thing: if they can contemplate a day most ancient Japanese traditions, as the ceremony of tea or the placement of a kimono (thanks to Sony). Nothing more.</body>
</review>
