<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Absolutely unmissable film with images which must have done to the American censors falling from the Chair</summary>
	<body>The hills have eyes (2006) was defined by Richard Roeper (the second most popular film of United States critic) as "an ugly piece of splatter-porn". It is the kind of movie in which your girlfriend leaves you, the type of tape to which people refer when it leaves the multiplex, furious, saying "but if I come to the cinema to have a good time". If this does not convince you to go to see her, I don't know that it can work, because without doubt are dealing with the terror of the year piece. The Gaul Alexandre Aja has not only understood perfectly what makes great original Wes Craven film that brings this concept to the absolute limits.At the beginning, Aja displays the history making almost a copy of the original Craven, following exactly the same storyline of a family who suffers from an "accident" in the hills again Mexico is attacked by a horde of mutant cannibals. Differences between the subtle (apart from the geographical location and the fact that the accident is caused on this occasion) is the greater emphasis on this occasion in the origin of mutants: the harmful effects of the product of decades of atomic test radiation. However, the similarities just in the moment in which the Carter family is finally his deformed pursuers dam. The brutal attack is shown by Aja in splendor, without reserve or a detail, and abuse suffered by women Carter at the hands of their attackers is, in my opinion, very difficult to endure, especially an image in particular that must have made American censors falling from the Chair. These details are not free, only showing us the savagery of the mutants (which on this occasion, thanks to the unique work of Greg Nicotero and Howard Berger, seem to actually mutants, special mention for the new and spectacular Pluto, and forgive me Michael Berryman) may Aja show what is undoubtedly the essential point: the reaction of the protagonist family. After all (and here is where it shows the effectiveness of this remake) really horrible movie is not the suffering of those who die, but what happens to those who survive, the bestiality that arises in those seemingly timid beings who must choose between death and become authentic inhuman monsters. AJA twists and expresses this idea in the figure of the timid Democratic that everyone mocked and ending converted in a beast covered with blood and thirsty for revenge, whose actions are to make matters worse accompanied with an epic music that makes one, as public, do not know if the director is doing a chant or a critique of bestiality. It's funny, in addition, be garnish this with a somewhat jingoistic profile (the American flag becomes here a cynical instrument of destruction). You can make this a trip of my pot, but now that I know that the father of Alexandre Aja is a notable politician of French socialism, I'm not so sure.Another huge success of this remake is what refers to their antagonists. The new mutants in the hills have eyes, apart from its repulsive ugliness, are real animals who have been deprived almost entirely of dialogue (something which in my opinion due to the original). In addition, their numbers already not confined only to a family clan (though Billy Drago makes a great Jupiter in a brief cameo) but that its history extends to mythological levels in what for me is the best sequence of the film: a visit to a ghost town inhabited by the race of cannibals and their offspring. This, coupled with agoraphobia that produces this immense and hot desert of which there is no possible exit, and that tremendous final table of survivors, makes this an absolutely unmissable film. And I wonder: what Alexandre Aja can do in the future? Whatever it is, it will have to see it.</body>
</review>
