<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Harry Potter y la orden del Fénix" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>On the basis that "could not concetrarme completely in the movie", this new delivery seems very forced, so many things are that have wanted to translate that the pace is abrupt and at times bland.</summary>
	<body>After watching Daniel Radcliffe in Equus (play by Peter Shaffer, in which protagonist) naked, and with that tail between legs it is certainly hard to believe that it is once again Harry Potter. Let us not forget that the Potter is aimed at children and as such his characters even if they have an evolution and maturation, always keep that veil Heinberg (minimum how), clear that in the case of Daniel, such an "appliance" removes completely the veil. So it is that you on the basis that "could not concetrarme completely in the movie", this new release seems very forced, so many things are that have wanted to translate that the pace is abrupt and at times bland. At least I do not have enjoyed this film both in the past and that we had a Helena Bonham Carter (God I love) and Evanna Lynch (Luna Lovegood plays) as sinister touch of this installment (don't know if you you realize that increasingly is pulled more sinister item, introducing characters Dark).For my best thing about this film is it "without a doubt", Evanna Lynch (August 16, 1991) is an Irish actress of 1, 52 m of height. She plays Luna Lovegood in the fifth part of the Harry Potter film series. In the auditions for the role, he defeated 15,000 applicants. Even before given the role, was already a big fan of Harry Potter; This is his debut on the big screen, my God and that debut, is undoubtedly a future replacement of Helena Bonham Carter and we'll see if new musa Tim Burton along with others of his style as Chirstina Ricci. Only to see it already it is worth going to the cinema.For the rest, the visual theme remains spectacular, as the excellent production which are already being a seal in the saga. The world of Potter nevertheless continues to be fascinating.David Yates, director of this delivery, will also direct the next Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince which began filming in September of this year and intends to release at the end of 2008. With the exception of the protagonists, the rest of the cast is not confirmed. If you think that this stayed here were wrong because in 2010 we can attend at the end of the saga: Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, moment in which the artistic careers of young Portas will fall sharply for some time.</body>
</review>
