<review author="Bruji" title="Turistas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Taking advantage of the good reception of shit I like?Do Hostel?, and with zero geographical and historical knowledge, the American writers, once more, insist on insulting the international intelligence. Disappointing, even for the most ardent lovers of the subgenre.</summary>
	<body>Kind of project of end of career which, inexplicably, obtained financing and subsequent distribution. Taking advantage of the good reception of shit like "Hostel", and with zero geographical and historical knowledge, the American writers, once again, they insist on insulting the international intelligence. Disappointing, even for the most ardent lovers of the subgenre. Based on the typical formula of "what seemed a paradise vacation, became a nightmare," in the paranoid obsession of Americans by found always in danger, especially in those places where the magic words "I am a citizen of the United States of America" mean nothing, and the exploitation of international fears; Tourists is not any horror film.In reality, it is not more than a crude collection of all kinds of situations and dialogues inherent in this kind of stories, based on the classic faces of "die" all that, by its improbability, lead, inevitably, to the tedious mock.Do so in quite a few passages, the tape of John Stockwell (the air in his youth Idol) does not reach the category of "movie", translating into a kind of project of end of career which, inexplicably, obtained financing and subsequent distribution, perhaps, to make use of the pull of clunkers as the saga of Hostel.Su script? from beginning to end - not only is the paradigm of unbelief, but that consistently, persistently in insult the intelligence and common sense of the Viewer. In this aspect, we accept the unlikely possibility that a group of mindless teenagers, after suffering an accident that puts them in the middle of nowhere, focus their energies and concerns in the way of enjoying the sexual and gastronomic delights of a place unknown (significant level of a used condom). "The occurrence" to be executed by eight cuarentones, however must be the lemon pear. By the same token, we accept the existence of a luxurious mansion which is located in the interior of poverty, although it belongs to the uncle of a humble young man found on the beach. Clear, that the cottage is equipped with security cameras of latest technology, rich delicacies, ron añejo and jeans of the exact one of the protagonists, size must be reasons more than enough to start suspecting its inhabitants. It gives the feeling of that USA children never read the House of Chocolate. As the Swedes did, these are them leads bound and muzzled, in the purest style of Apocalypto. On the other hand, would not be more Stockwell is devoted to explain at what exact point of Brazilian geography join the sea and the jungle, why in ten hours of hiking the intensity of sunlight remains unchanged and in what historical time the Swedes, Australians and Americans sack Brazilian rubber and sugar. (This last assumption, fear would have to give the Spanish summer in Latin America). Without the bad taste that situates the action somewhere in Brazil, as if the Bush Empire did not exist this type of practices, psychopathies and "altruistic" nationalists. For this reason, even convinced the alleged social criticism that proposed, nor the original twist seen in the mythical indent of Coma, the famous story of Robin Cook, which carried Michael Crichton screens.The development of the plot, for its part, fruit of an accurate and infuriating irregularity, crowned by the uncertain measurement of time, contributes to finish an ill-fated product, totally dispensable to the history of the cinema, that should never cross its borders. or see the light. Surprisingly, the simplicity with which is approached the outcome, as well as the brazenness with which truncates the factor surprise, the sickly natives rear recreation, painful events planning. Given the fact, moreover, of even the magnificent underwater scenes to lose his brilliance to be repetitive, incurring another error of script, which makes it possible that foreigners get poke fun at the locals in their own caves.A film, in short, that does not convince you to lovers of suspense, terror, or the followers of Peter Jackson, master of al gore. A history that not even the addicts and unconditional of some of these genres can be defended.</body>
</review>
