<review author="José A. Peig" title="Ratatouille" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entertain with little recourse to extreme simplicity, golden rule to build a product aimed at the immediate divertimento, without worrying about if in 20 years someone will remember of this film.</summary>
	<body>Entertain with little recourse to extreme simplicity, golden rule to build a product aimed at the immediate divertimento, without worrying about if in 20 years someone will remember of this film. History of a rat who dreams of becoming something more than a simple rat, raised to the status of human gourmet and change the vision that human have the old clan, a clan of rodents beginning of petty thieves in a cottage, living on crumbs, and end up tasting culinary delights, by work and art of the rat who wanted to be different. Pixar Animation emphasizes the design and the visual force on the plot, something that is usual in their productions, and is convenient to emphasize that cartoonish character that combines very well the ingenuity in designs with a sentimentality carried with some dignity, since those levels which show an idyllic Paris in the eyes of a rat who was excited seeing the landscape, or the setting of the large dining room which makes the role of focus of the dramatic tension, because there comes a time in the plot in which fortune - or misfortune - actors, depends on the opinion of a culinary critic that even on the eve of the final recites a speech on the role of the critic as gourmet specialties (something applicable to various areas of creation)(, in this film, under the point of view of the above-mentioned critic, the cuisine is art), and it's worth saying that this characters is without doubt the most interesting, that the antipathy raised in principle by repulsive his characterization, derived in sympathy when, in a passage proustiano, a sporadic return to childhood because of the rustic flavours recovered by the ratIt transfiguring his sullen and malicious bearing an image of innocence and rediscovery. From that scene, the gesture changes and also the vision of things. There are certain parallels with Dickens, and we certainly have a film inspired by the good intentions, as it could not be otherwise.Little more can be said; a very correct film and you have a very effective characterization of characters functionally speaking, well structured, at times witty, and that keeps the interest at all times. It has good humor coups, although at other times it is something spectacular and wasteful. The resolution to the role of some characters is little inspired, and often plays too with topics, ideas and feelings we have seen nauseam in other films of similar intentions. Use the topics, by Jove, here at least not gooey.</body>
</review>
