<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Blowup, deseo de una mañana de verano" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Atypical psychological thriller: a masterpiece converted a tape of cult or vice versa. Metalinguistic outburst, a tumble of ideas without excessive rational seat and a surreal parade of tronados characters.</summary>
	<body>Julio Cortázar handles a Remington or a Contax. The typewriter and the photo machine. Blowup, desire for one summer morning is the film a tale that cannot, in any way, reporting no history and simply runs, impassive, by the always fallible byways of language and Orthodox mechanisms on how to tell a story. The conclusion is that the story can not be counted because the reality is not unproblematically or Cortázar admits that their settlement in the world is accidental and subject to vague random contest. What is questioned is the fidelity of the narrated, the veracity of the literature, which is both address the substance of the time or the appropriateness of the language. In all this mess entirely philosophical or semiotic or cryptic nature, Antonioni makes a thriller and a lasting document on the London of the 1960s which, today, is left to handle without loss of contemporaneity, become a model set of images rather than a film. Antonioni filmed a delusional City: a touching, intriguing, strange London. All the characters who traverse seem unrealistic or are on the verge of entering any unreality more in line with the dreams to life. And it turns out the only thing truly real is a picture or series of pictures that have registered a murder. Cortázar/Antonioni aims to delve into reality for lowering of verismo. The film is a continuous manipulation. The colors of the buildings are subject to the fickle moods of Thomas, the carefree, frivolous and cynical fashion photographer who, in his spare time, free camera on his shoulder, it subtracts the reality its fringes, their threads, translatable in photographs. What is a picture at the end and all, but a robbery to the reality? The invisible crime is a perfect mcguffin: an excuse to argue for an hour and half a reflection on the automation of the senses and how confident this to the point of not to put what offer us filters more demanding that can reveal the true as seen or in the figurative sense. The camera, the Contax of Cortázar, becomes deified object that is capable of reliably inventory the chaotic world offered to our eyes and that we accept without questioning its essence, its Vertigo.Blowup has justifiably been converted to tape of worship for some sector of film and criticism perhaps also justifiably converted tape misunderstood for a certain sector of the audience that sees therein a metalinguistic outburst, a tumble of ideas without excessive rational seat and a parade surreal characters tronados, at that time, in the cerniente cultural boomfound in the rock, sex and rock an incentive to find happiness. I have no doubt that they did so.The own Cortázar saw in Amsterdam and recognized have enjoyed the translation into images of his story (Las babas del diablo). He noted that the film is a machine Stakhanovite make money: he received a few thousand dollars by consent to the use of his account and Ponti, producer, grossed several million. As always added detail is curious to see some young Yardbirds (Eric Clapton made a muchachote) liven up statuary assistance that not pestañea to sound tear which are still objects. Jeff Beck breaks a guitar in the style of Who and Jane Birkin appears first in a film.</body>
</review>
