<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Planet Terror" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Planet Terror will come to become a cult film, it has all the ingredients to be although perhaps the mass public is not prepared to assess the real magnitude of this project.</summary>
	<body>Planet Terror is part of the GrindHouse which they carry out R.Rodriguez and Q.Tarantino and consists of two parts, Planet Terror and Death Proof, latter is which directs Quentin. We all know how well that take these two, well I as a result of a night of sex, drugs and alchool, is born this project that has not garnered the success expected.As you sit in the armchair and started to put the trailers you enter in the eighties world of the movies in series B. I think that I am not the only one who has been astounded with the trailer for "Machete", is more I assure you that more than one (among which I include myself) would be willing to see it. The effects of noise in the frames of the movie, uncredited, the absurd stench of the eighties and its Z series. It is increñible. For my Robert has emerged from the peyejillo with this film.Planet Terror is a caviar not suitable for all tastes. It must learn to appreciate it and understand it in its enviroment. "Isn't a poorly made movie of zombies" as I read somewhere. It is an important tribute to the horror of B series of the 1980s. The dialogues, the plot, everything is perfect.I have to show my weakness by the divine Macgowan Rose (Ex Marilyn Manson), being his film career with effort and intelligence. One of the examples of overcoming. An actress that deserves a place on Hollywood Star System by all his talent that she herself has been forged that nobody has given absolutely nothing. From here my wholehearted support to this great woman.Rose is the soul of Grindhouse and especially of Planet Terror. Represents the mythical character who discovers by chance its true but entregandose to him and upon his own existence. Do something more pure and true?It is absolutely raucous and sometimes heady time "Pata de Palo" and when I wanted to die of excitement is in the amazing "Submachine gun foot" moment, go Super heroin friend Robert has been created. Of course Rose has taken all the juice to the character. It is full of sensuality, claw and audacity.Two against the world. the love story is fabulous.I think that Planet Terror will come to become a cult film, it has all the ingredients to be although perhaps the mass public is not prepared to assess the real magnitude of this project.</body>
</review>
