<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Lucky You" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Light world of professional poker. If it had not been directed by Curtis Hanson, it would not be wrong, but he being the Director of "L.A. Confidential", the black gender absolute masterpiece, you know little.</summary>
	<body>Entertaining and enjoyable film about poker players, where this sport (many not so qualify as well), goes to second place when human feelings between father and son comes.Although perhaps not pass into the background, but that both are complementary, becoming the same thing, since that father and son carry the game to their lives and vice versa.The film lasts more than two hours and not noticeable. This means that bored not the slightest and interested enough to maintain the concentration of the Viewer. But that isn't enough to convince at all.The tape is not only far more light than one might assume in advance (the opposite of the excellent "Rounders"), but that would have required given the undeniable harshness of history.Although there are at all times emotional tension, there is no scenes with enough nerve to stay in the memory.All trasncurre assimilating gradually until you reach end in tone with the set of the film, that is, quite calmly, Miss claw and spark.Best thing is its great prologue with the excellent scene of dialogue between the protagonist and the owner of the House of endeavours. In those five minutes or perhaps something else, know how is the protagonist. And we also have the good moment of the poker game between father and son in the cafeteria, where they are on the table, in addition to the letters, the feelings between them, what unites them and what separates them.The rest is easily digestible, with successful moments as a golf bet and others where we would like more emotional involvement and where some characters only are drawn, as Charles Martin Smith or the own Drew Barrymore, that sometimes is a simple comparsa.In definiva, if it had not been directed by Curtis Hanson, it would not be wrong, but he being the Director of "L.A. Confidential", the black gender absolute masterpiece, you know little.</body>
</review>
