<review author="Bloody Will" title="Planet Terror" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This hour and a half of pure and simple savagery deserves a couple of mixed drinks accompanied by that friend who has all the ballots to finish in Carabanchel.</summary>
	<body>I must begin by saying that give an opinion of this film in the way that premiered in Spain is quite difficult. The botched the Weinstein brothers and the distributor have committed to split in two a product like?Do Grindhouse?, who had his grace to pass by double terror program, has finished with the sense that had to attend a festival of gore and guts that Robert Rodriguez and Tarantino had prepared for their unconditional.As always, the box office ends up being the main objective of all, and with the collapse of this invention in American theaters have thought about money we the Europeans. Will it pay in the future, that certainly outweigh.?Does Planet Terror?, as independent film, is a product of B series conceived from the outset to be so, without more script to go to maim and blowing his cast and finish through you the hand the face if you has spilled something. The story is so bad that it is made on purpose, actions are so bad that they are made to order. The special effects are so crude that they are made to order and blood is so false that it has been purchased in bulk in a whole hundred. With all that is fun for the most part, irreverent, and though it makes heavy towards the Middle, ends with an apotheosis end of fiestas, all very thing Rodriguez.A this point I do not know if I liked to be a hodgepodge of volume and spine, but it has all the ballots to be the most unbearable summer movie for a good number of unsuspecting viewers who do not know very well where they get and believe that they will see a few Undead to the Romero.Claro, the spark of all was in insert with fake trailers and compare it with the later?Death Proof? Tarantino. He had to see her knowing that we we have the two directors more personal in the Yankee picture: do as they please and as they want, and they can afford licences wishing. Do do with this scam split in two, trailers are still there, but seem to be stuck with a shoehorn, and when it ends the film you have that feeling that? I see cold at home for this?. ?Planet Terror? recover to this Robert Rodriguez from?Do open at dawn? and which had nothing to do with the most meticulous aesthetics of?No City?, but intended to give all the situations a point of absolute nonsense and an air of bad 1970s footage becomes vulgar when it has pulled out of context, and the context really, were the three hours of?Grindhouse?.It is the second film of the zombie genre that we are this summer (previously,? do 28 weeks later?), but the mutant zombies of Rodriguez in anything having to do with the rest. In addition to crumble very rapidly, the troperías committed by them are vomitivas, (care to Tarantino scene in the elevator) and with that I think that many people will be close to the cinema to see her. In this story there are no moral or lesson to be learned in life, only one dead after another. Do some situations, as I said before, make no sense, but do not need it because everything is a tribute to the bad films gave us the? exploitation? 70. The style is the of?Cleopatra Jones? and the bad ostia is Rodriguez.Los actors have done what they had to do: stop killing. They are basically stereotypes which puebla this premeditated slaughter, that we have the bad cabr ** (Josh Brolin), the military CA ^ ** (a spectacular Bruce Willis), the hero cool of the story (Freddy Rodriguez), the companion of the cool (Naveen Andrews) and the girl stripper and cale ** survives to everything, even to an amputation and its subsequent replacement by a submachine gun. Then there are las tontas which are falling like flies, including my hated Fergie, singer of?Black Eyed Peas? and seen in?Poseidon?. Do the script is a calamity that lines of dialogue are taken from the compendium of? more phrases than manidas? in the history of the cinema. It does not matter much, because the important thing is not what they say, but what it takes to open the mouth before they cut them any limb.Do continue talking about the film would finish telling the key scenes of the film and giving you your point, so I will finish by saying that?Planet Terror? It is a bad film of gore made wanting to be bad. There is an absurd accident and an aunt that triggered by his leg, do you think that we should take seriously something?. Al gore is abundant and everything put in this film, so if you don't like al gore did not go to see her because her you pondréis green, and knew what was in the jar. To this it must add all the violence that Rodriguez is a specialist mixed with drugs and sex (scene interruptus). If you are sitting in the armchair and start to lift eyebrows and turning the eyes do that c ** expected this?.Without showing my preference for a distillery or another, this hour and a half of pure and simple savagery deserves a couple of mixed drinks accompanied by that friend who has all the ballots to finish in Carabanchel.</body>
</review>
