<review author="Yul B." title="Ratatouille" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Brad Bird has succeeded with Ratatouille a movie honours. Cinema 5 forks.</summary>
	<body>Ratatouille is for me, without a doubt, the best movie of the summer so far.Well, to calzón got, I begin this criticism with the apparent risk of confrontation with the view of many of you to write a few words so strong. But, my friends, there is no risk to say open heart that this film is the second best of the Disney/Pixar tandem after?Toy Story?; its high quality is appraised clearly evident with only enjoy the first 10 minutes of footage.And the strangest thing of all is that this film not only noted for its technical aspect. Gone are those times in which we maravillabamos with the almost perfection of digital molded the characters we taught so ilusionadamente these magicians of the animation.All of that is out of date, because such is the mastery with which Pixar already represents, and in this case, the characters human and ratoniles, mixing way superb reality and caricature, that we forget completely that we are dealing with a work of art animated and allow ourselves to cajole for something invaluable to have the tape: an absolutely captivating script.You raise your hand to go to the movies without wanting him they excited with a touching story, either because it contains moments of fun to navigate, with laughter that housing the eardrums of the public in the Hall, go bust or heart-warming moments worth to be calmed with tons of clinex. ?Ratatouille? you have all that, looking for more sensitive side of the Viewer, in the same way as has always done it the Disney with his eternal classics. And the main cause that we stay rendered with this spectacle is Remy, a rat with a special gift for cuisine that is not rated by their peers. Virtues such as tenderness, humility, generosity, going through situations of helplessness to be prosecuted as the biggest enemy of all clean restaurant that boasts, or having moments of euphoria manifestly to be a chef first, are represented with so much emotion and commitment that there is no choice but to fall in love her madly. It is the typical dreamy and helpless character that everyone we love in thousandths of a second.All their adventures are told with the ingenuity of Pixar who had inexplicably lost in earlier work: bizarre arrival to the most important restaurant of Paris, the Gusteau? s, which was run by the late Aguste Gusteau; the need to hide inside the hat of Linguini, a friegaplatos which by various causality becomes a marionette of Remy considering him to him wrongly critics as a revelation of the kitchen, and so we can have a means to cook without being seen; the success that can not enjoy; or the litmus test to lift the restaurant, after the death of its founder and disastrous management of the new chef Skinner: surprise Mr. Ego, the most famous food critic of Francia.Todo flows with complete harmony, extraordinarily extolling such heart-warming and moments of fun that I talked about. Each of the characters in this story has a mission that fits perfectly in the history, but it is worth a special mention of Mr. Ego, professional culinary critics who feared any chef that had the largest number of Michelin stars. Relentless, hard palate satisfaction, get nervous turn the public with their ruthless opinion articles.Never seen a villain so fearsome whose evil should be based on the word. A clear slap to critics with his ego can destroy new talent, for very rare (a rat) that are.By this a sublime moment of the film, which I cannot speak widely, it is where the crux of the footage offered Mr. Ego a very simple dish called?Ratatouille? for its sampling, and on which depends the re-invention of the restaurant. We will now comment on the thread of this criticism, but during those wonderful final 10 minutes put me the willies.There are portentous scenes but as these last no.For all cash I am completely surrendered at the feet of Brad Bird who, with his work in the writing of the screenplay and direction, and with the help of the great Disney/Pixar elite team, has managed a film honors. Cinema 5 forks.</body>
</review>
