<review author="Tyler" title="Planet Terror" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A way of seeing the film that we have never seen, a way to feel at one time through our. A way of discovering a filmmaker that promises things that makes.</summary>
	<body>Because there is no possibility of more stars, that if not, left no place to write and only satellite wonderful ponia brilliant this film Cine.El Maestrísima work may not be an art, or can, but which does have to think that what he does he is not; You should carefully consider the film in terms of handicrafts, Robert Rodriguez movie is therefore a genuine enjoyment, a tape so fun as violent and brazen. The move happened with GRINDHOUSE and its European Premiere, we all know that move to separate it into two to get more money from a movie designed to be a double continuous session. That is a mistake, because it not only movie is a tribute (and in it I will talk about later) to a certain type of film, is also a tribute to a way of looking at it.Much has been said of Robert Rodriguez (and God TARANTINO) are large "homenajeadores", which is not true. them not homage, they steal. they are thieves of celluloid, ideas and material, which occasionally recycled and sometimes simply copied and stick (Tarantino always, incidentally, with a lot more success than Rodriguez). This may be the only "movie tribute" Tarantino and Rodriguez. But let us focus on Rodriguez this time, is the time.There are people that has not seen the film that is exhibia in the GRINDHOUSES, but sure not many have seen and do not remember or do not know. The Weinstein say the movie have separated in two by the reason that Europeans do not know what that way of seeing movies, a real bullshit, my father (great movie buff in his juvetud years ago) saw movies in continuous session double "convois" or adventures and "cates", in late 1950s and 1960s. Authentic double sessions, which had rolls screwed by the use, rotten rooms in which people meaba and movies, to go in several rolls, is they saw in a disorderly way because to the projectionist is you had gone hand in hand with alcohol last night and placed them in the order were not, I remember that my mother (this time she) told me that once saw giant way messy in a summer cinema. What I am here to say with this calving esque sartada the reasons for the producers always are hidden, which we should import relatively little to the public, but to the "geeks" as I we like to know.The Spaniards know perfectly this way to see movies, our generation, the mia, which today are between 20 and 25 have not seen shit, and 40 not the truth, but earlier if. What is truth esque gender who saw Rodriguez and Tarantino, did not have much to do with us, they are the film of the 1970s.. the movies gore, the vampires and zombies, the spaghetti western instead of classic westerns. but the way of seeing them was the same, with lost rolls and like dirt.PLANET TERROR (Finally I am a bit specific!) is a movie with a devilish pace. It pays tribute to and copy to the movies by Fulci, Bava (Lamberto and Mario) Fleischer film and the 70s and eighties slasher. Picks up a bit of everything and beautifully blends it to make a product, such as who makes a gazpacho of those with "tropezones", of those that do not pass at all. (comparison to possibly understand only the Andalusian)It is normal duration and of action and horror, in the purest style Rodriguez, shot at full speed and video. It has a magnificent cast with a cast of side perfect, thing that lately Rodriguez does better than anyone else, look at SIN CITY. Rodriguez also makes one thing only is towards the 50,60 and 70 and now he and his colleague Tarantino, who is repeating characters, in this case the Earl Mcgraw of Michael Parks, also seen in KILL BILL and open up the dawn, which produces an interesting temporary vortex. If Earl Mcgraw died in open up the dawn means that this movie happens after KILL BILL and PLANET TERROR, but in PLANET TERROR the character Bruce Willis (an actorazo that we recognize in years and to which the film owes a lot) talks about Bin Laden in a dialogue that I do not want to disclose. something really strange.PLANET TERROR was written before overcoming the dawn of the dead and 28 days later, it is can people creero not, but the truth is that it has nothing to do with them, this movie is not serious and takes very seriously.It is not a parody, but it is not a serious vision of the zombies, is a CINEMATIC vision, through the same cinema.The actors all have very well caught the tone. especially Josh Brolin and the subvaloradisimo and great Michael Biehn, I hope that now jump-start as it deserves. the Reese in TERMINATOR.If you want to have fun at the movies, which is for what is invented, you see it and rent movies type four minutes, which I'm not saying it is bad, but it is better to see something of the style of PLANET in the film.The movie is witty, full of winks that people will see. The machine gun of Rose Mcgowan in the leg. It is an image that will go down in the history of the cinema, matter what people say. If you see the movie, accepts a tone from the outset and if stays, no squeaks.It is difficult to maintain a tone and break it with something quite different and not chiirrie, only comes a title to the head, EL man QUE NUNCA ESTUVO there, which has the extrañísima output of tone of the UFO at the end... and is wonderful, perhaps because we are talking about people so perfect as the TERROR Coen.PLANET must see, with this trailer at the beginning of a movie that seems to be that it will be, but that is not made... MACHETE. Perhaps I spoke little specifically for the movie, but alomejor is better, because you have to see it.</body>
</review>
