<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film about the most famous family in the U.S. has not followed the path easy to do a chapter of an hour and a half, but that they have gotten innovations that do not have seemed to me interesting. Even so, the result is good, but not outstanding as pretendiamos to see.</summary>
	<body>So many years waiting out the film the characters these yellow, and when he arrives, you realize that 90% of the jokes you seen in the trailer. Man, that is good that create excitement, which has created much up with false press releases, but not us destripeis the film before seeing her. If sold alone. In the end.The film is about a typical American family living in a typical town called Springfield. Pollution of the Lake has reached a point which is unsustainable, so the mayor decides to take action on the matter. But as always Homer, the father, cause a catastrophe, forcing the US Government to put a dome around the most polluted town of the country.FAQ, FAQ, deeply bothers me the film I see. It is not it that grace, something I made, if not me is feeling a tad sad. With how easy that was to make a long chapter, with many plots to assist the main reach fruition. And nothing more. That is what we wanted. But no, they have decided to innovate. And they have presented us a few decorated in 3-D when the series always has been flat. And not content with that, have mixed us two types of textures of life drawing, and a more realistic that not sticks. Otherwise, the argument is nice, giving a bit of cane to the Church, to the environmental situation and putting a peculiar US President that I hope that we will not reach never see in that position. But the issue is not over curdling for nothing.In short, the film about the most famous family in the U.S. has not followed the path easy to do a chapter of an hour and a half, but that they have gotten innovations that not found me interesting. Even so, the result is good, but not outstanding as pretendiamos to see.Spider Pig, spider ceeeeeerdo!Besitos.P.D: You still have good moments, like the pig above all.Pd2: And the brain of Homer, no doubt.Web site: the web is a total and absolute wonder, it shows that they have spent much in the promotion and they have been unwilling to let loose. They can be many things to make your own character. If the have not seen, already tardáis:http://www.simpsonsmovie.com/</body>
</review>
