<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Primeval" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a dentudo bug which denounces the lived and current situation of a country representative of black Africa. If not liked by that expect me a shit or that really it is good. Add the benefit of the doubt.</summary>
	<body>To sit at the cold and insulting blanquedad of the monitor, to write criticism, I was reminded of a joke that is very beside the point with the film. This is a company that hires a group of cannibals to your human resources department. Total, past a few months thrown them into the street. Will the leader of the cannibals, and says "we spent months and we have eaten 10 managers, 4 heads of personal and 17 project managers without no one realized, who was the idiot who has eaten the fellow who did all the work of the company?"Muahahahahaha, send your donations to my Switzerland account to continue the festival of humor.The film is about a giant crocodile called Gustave who makes the mistake of wanting to expand their diet based on Burundians with a white girl of the UN which is investigating a few graves of civil war. To make a report about the lizard size boat motor, start a beautiful and attractive girl, a presumptuous jerk, a mulatto camera with face that you are going to eat, a supporter of animals with the same look as above and a hunter with somewhat different to other purposes. Arriving there, informs an officer must go in the way of a local leader, autollamado little Gustave, with bad fleas.Hey, that pleasant surprise. I thought me that the film was going to be those with the kind of Anacondas bug and the like, and nothing to do. Well, a little bit. The argument, even if you have background to the reptile, is a bit denounce the genocide in Burundi as well as remind us how people live in sub-Saharan Africa. We have two basic plot lines, the search for the crocodile, and the small Gustave being persecuted by a subject that is not the case. Special effects, based on the bug are average achieved, given that the digital stone cardboard gives the pego, but removed to such a speed that you can not enjoy with the deployment of bytes. Only in one scene is seen as God manda, ending very nice, by the way.In short, film about a dentudo bug which denounces the lived and current situation of a country representative of black Africa. If not liked by that expect me a shit or that really it is good. Let him the benefit of the duda.¿Tendremos a second part in which combat the anacondas? Who knows.Besitos.P.D: That I don't say it is based on a real event that puts the hair like hooks only read that label.Pd2: The scene of the girl in the Lake made me jump like a cat when get you into the water.P. d:3: who has made this film the name of crocodile: a serial killer? Pathetic. web page: the web is sad, tristísima, something that here you have for your delight visual:http://video.movies.go.com/primeval/Trailer:Os thing put to English, given that say three words and the rest has nothing to do with the movie. If they then say that if people put to give birth movies, they put a trailer that has nothing to do.</body>
</review>
