<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Planet Terror" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ochentera aesthetics and blood pouring in the new production of the overrated Rodríguez.</summary>
	<body>In an experiment that will surely have no continuity, due to his stupidity, and with an aesthetic characteristic of the B-movies of the 1980s, premiered in Spain Grindhouse: Planet Terror, next to Grind House: Death Prof, composed a vulgar history of zombies, whose shooting have been distributed between Robert Rodriguez and Quentin Tarantino.Dos directors greatly overvalued and with an almost unhealthy devotion to violenceblood and organ meats. Two jewels are going. The part that touches today analyze is the first, Planet Terror, whose synopsis is reduced to two doctors checked that the town is filled with undead and in a more normal reaction lían shots, palos, navajazos and shoving with regard to hand. To make an idea, something like (although to the beast) to what one can find in the street the day of the ** Erizada. The struggle for survival, the claim of the resistance of the human being and the overcoming of the same capacity, are some of the characteristic of the genus usual nonsense are also here present. The poor image quality, aesthetic imperfections and some other details, get further accentuate the premeditated image of two decades ago that the film already by itself conveys. Even though I know that they enjoy a great Pleiad of followers, I can not finish without saying that Rodriguez and Tarantino, cinema except some exceptions such as Kill Bill I and II and Sin City, seems to me incongruous, vacuum and more like a disposed to the genius that some see in them. In any case, the viewing of this monstrosity can apologize if this one passes a couple of hours a fresco of the air-conditioning of the sala.* La Erizada is the event traditionally opens the Carnival acts in Cádiz, which consists of thousands of people eating sea urchins and drinking non-stop through the streets of the neighborhood of the vineyard of Cádiz.</body>
</review>
