<review author="José A. Peig" title="La noche americana" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The enormous capacity of Truffaut to build characters equipped with a humanity so real and dynamic as life itself and the ins and outs of the art of representation, provides the documentary a metaphorical power constituting the dimension more emotional, romantic, and ultimately, deep of a speech encouraging between the tear and smile.</summary>
	<body>When life ceases to make sense, the film has the power to prolong the illusion with its expressive potential, as a game of representations as a catharsis. Or perhaps, cinema and life are the same thing, we are interpreters of ourselves in the great theatre of the world. The universe posed by Francois Truffaut is watching us through three eyes: the eye of the viewer and the eye of the camera facing camera which is representing another universe. If we include the Viewer, we have three representational realities synthesized into a whole film that drift in a metalanguage for discussion between any lover of the seventh art.It is obvious that in this film prima the intention and style documentary, and therefore is a movie buff treasure given to many lectures on cinema understood as a product industrial and subjected to trade rules, or as an aesthetic expression, or a divertimento for their perpetrators, as part of their personal fulfilment. In fact, the greatest merit of the film, and it is in this sense where the mere documentary reaches the State of dramatic work that symbolizes the emotional problems and the disappointment of the characters, is its ability to synthesize life depicted with the "real" life, the effort to improve the work of interpretation with the effort to improve human (or better)(one thing leads to another). It is a film about people and characters, which, with a mask or without it, remain what they are, or what we are all. The enormous capacity of Truffaut to build characters equipped with a humanity so real and dynamic as life itself and the ins and outs of the art of representation, provides the documentary a metaphorical power which constitutes the dimension more emotional, romantic, and ultimately, deep of a speech encouraging between the tear and smile, in which performers themselves are called into question their instincts vital with regard to the requirements of the Office of actor or Director.Great film by Truffaut, though perhaps it extends too in some passages that do not end of reach significant port, and instead leaves a little in the air other aspects that they could have gotten more juice. It won the Academy Award for best foreign film in 1973, and is the best movie of the French author according to the opinion of an important sector of the critics.</body>
</review>
