<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Everything that happens in the movie is incredible. If you get to think about the amount of things that go from the first to the last frame, is to flip it. The amount of winks, jokes and laughing.</summary>
	<body>The moment where Homer gets up, pissed, in the middle of a film by scratch and Pica and says do not understand why an entry of cinema has paid to see something that could have tasted free at home, turning towards the camera and calling pringá you to all those who were in the film, marks the style of a hilarious filmNice, acid, scathing and scoundrel, which is exactly what we always expect the yellow family.I not follow regularly the Simpsons on TV, which did not have very clear if something particularly important had happened in Springfield in recent years it conditional me viewing of the film. But not. Everything seemed to be equal: Moe, Homer, Bart, the tontita of Lisa, Marge pragmatics, the detestable Burns, etc.Therefore, to enjoy playing. To enjoy seeing an EE.UU. txaranga and tambourine, always lucid eyes of Matt Groening, by evil that is, you can always go to worse. The protagonists? In addition to the usual - that in a display of script, leave all - it is the lavish and all-powerful President of the United States, Arnie; and or subject so concerned about the environment that could be a paranoid transcript of the argument relates to the Gore.Y, as not, above the theme star of all agendas in the world: climate change. Watch the heavy environmentalists take years and years giving grilled with global warming, the ozone layer and the melting of the poles. Because now, suddenly, ranks high on the agendas of everyone in the world is? or is intended to be - someone.And Groenning does not lose occasion of sticking the finger in the eye of both enrollao welfare, Homer becoming an environmental cuasiterrorista, Springfield in a sort of town of South deep American, with its akelarres and hangings. There is a flight to paradise lost, a love story, a tremendous confusion of personality, the return of the hero.Everything that happens in the movie is incredible. If you get to think about the amount of things that go from the first to the last frame, is to flip it. The amount of winks, jokes and laughing.For example, do commented something about the poster that appears at one point, with the legend "Hillary 2008"? And without any kind of criticism, a single frame of subliminal advertising.And, in the end, because all so happy, joyful and festive. The bet to move the series to the big screen has left either to a Groenning which remains in a State of grace and that, possibly, see reinforced ratings of his series on television around the world.They deserve.</body>
</review>
