<review author="Plissken" title="Wolf Creek" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Wolf Creek is fiction, but as experience in horror of the real you can find.</summary>
	<body>I don't know what is more absurd, if brand new Wolf Creek two years after its premiere, or talking about it when any good genre fan her must have already seen, thanks to new technologies. But if you're perhaps lost among the new wave of "slashers" that flooded the screens and do not know for what you decide, the magnificent Australian Greg Mclean film is the very best has done by the genre in a long time.The starting point, however, is not surprising at all: Kristy and Liz are two young tourists English in Australia, accompanied by the villager Ben, travel to Wolf Creek, a huge crater located in the middle of the desert which is 90% of the Australian country. What promised to be a placid landscapes worthy of National Geographic trip becomes a dramatic struggle for survival, with no one to assist trainees of explorers. Because they are alone in the desert, or not?The great merit of McLean in Wolf Creek is to build a tremendous tension around the actors, using the few inches (but powerful) means at its disposal, namely: a few players above the average in terms of charisma and intensity (special mention to a poignant Cassandra Magrath); the imposing enormity of the Australian desert, which from the outset is presented as a place as beautiful as little right to escape from people who want to kill you; above all, the effectiveness and coherence of the script, who plays the trump card of realism reliably much more that things such as Hostel or derivatives. And incidentally, plays with the spectator "veteran" subtly changing the roles and behaviours of protagonists and secondary. Everything with a slow pace, but that cala hondo and makes you worry, really, about the fate of hikers suffered. Greg Mclean films with the precision and patience of an expert, and is his first feature film. Chapeau by him.Another of their distinctive points is MIME which has been on the technical Bill and the setting, both through the image (courtesy of the unknown Will Gibson) and the sound and, especially, a music that perfectly accompanied changes in the script (in charge of the more unknown yet Frank Tetaz). The natural scenery accompany and are perfectly set to give as a result that mixture of desolate landscape and wonderful trap for unwary.To give you some but to the magnificent Opera prima of Mclean, a couple of moments they are resolved to the old and foolish style of the American "mataadolescentes", what removed you something of seriousness to the proposal; and the tagline of "based on a true story", well, then I guess that it will attract to someone else, but I think that it is not necessary. Wolf Creek is fiction, but as experience in horror of the real you can find.</body>
</review>
