<review author="Dragon negro" title="Ratatouille" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ratatouille is a classic of the factory from viewing as they already are Toy Story, Finding Nemo and the Incredibles.</summary>
	<body>Pixar proves once again, and with astonishing ease, the because it is the Queen of the cinema of digital animation, no longer by a visual quality increasingly achieved, but also by the quality of his scripts, which confirms again that the comedy in the classic style is still possible without having to fall into the easy joke or be irreverent and also makes it clear that it can be emotional and extol values such as love, friendship, family, or personal improvement aside from the typical characteristic of Disney.A ñoñeria through the steps of a very special rata attended the pursuit of a dream, the chef, achieved through a human being a loser who suddenly see their fate change to become of the overnight in an expert chefa reputation to immediately come big and that will jeopardize the team formed by the two inseparable since that one depends on the other. Exceptional success story which involves the relationship between these two characters and as establishing the communication between the two, although it would have been easier to opt for a more traditional path, the bet here taken is risky, but also brings consistency to the film and a different point of view.Punto y aparte is the technical and visual quality of the film where Pixar manages to overcome again and outweigh the "harder still" posed by each film. One of the major challenges was to represent food and meals of realistically, texture, color, form and movement. And go if it does, although not abused, if we can see numerous vegetables such as onions, celery, potatoes, and more, all them almost real and clearly defined, as well as cooked dishes, sauces, etc. Perhaps the unfinished even to get some more realism in people, instead of opt out so cartoony faces, I guess it will come someday that will be making an animated film where the human characters come to seem real.After that with Cars the Pixar flojeara a little, very little, this Ratatouille again to study at the top and its director Brad Bird as one of the best directors of animation at the moment. Ratatouille is a classic of the factory from viewing as they already are Toy Story, Finding Nemo and the Incredibles.</body>
</review>
