<review author="Plissken" title="Desmembrados" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The budget was not precisely the Transformers, but the sympathy of the whole makes it forgive all, between laughter and handful of popcorn</summary>
	<body>If you have worked in one of those large corporations who are concerned that the employee kept his motivation based on annual trips to strengthen the spirit of team rather than pay you more, the starting point of Desmembrados will be very familiar: a diverse group of employees of an arms company on a bus headed for an exciting weekend in Central Europe where will learn the value of camaraderie and cooperation with snowballs Paint. Really idyllic, if it were not for the questionable operations camp location, in the heart of the Balkans. A place say little suitable for practices of tyre and the guerrilla because there always are better players than you. And of course, do not use painting precisely.Christopher Smith, the author of the Creep failed, register within the genre and directed quite a few doses of messing with success what it looks like a cross between Deliverance and The Office. The characters do not pass the pure cliché, but are inevitably fun from the inept leader of the expedition (always solvent Tim McInnerny) until the black secondary topic (maiden Babou Ceesay), passing through the druggie, the ball, the brave, the Raritan or the cynical smartass. Oh, and two "ladies of company" of Eastern Europe, of course. All we have seen already die in similar productions, and it won't be here the exception, but the British touch of humour and hilarious scenes as the trap for bears (classic and effective gag), the effects of hallucinogenic mushrooms or the flashbacks with the possible explanations to the threat that surrounds them get Severance not be another "mata-mata" of the lot, but one of the fun, that worth seeing.In the technical aspect, the truth, and apart from the usual effects of makeup, little to tell: photography normalita pulling to cumbersome and music that goes unnoticed, except for the right song at the end. Note that the budget was not precisely that of Transformers, but the sympathy of the whole makes it forgive all, between laughter and handful of popcorn.A 7, ideal for a summer movie night.</body>
</review>
