<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Ratatouille" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fascinating exercise of film of great height that, without being her masterpiece many critics (read the Introit of the review) believe see, becomes the best movie of the summer: inapelablemente.</summary>
	<body>4.3.1The work of the critic is easy in more than one sense. We risk very little, and however usufructuamos a position located above those who submitted their work and his person in our view. We prosper thanks to negative criticisms, which are fun when you enter and when is the lee.2Pero the stark truth critics must face is that, in general terms, the production of average garbage is more valuable than what our articles are intended to point out. However, sometimes the critic truly risks something, and this happens on behalf and in defense of something nuevo.3Anoche I experienced something new, an extraordinary meal made by someone unique and unexpected. Say that this dish and its chef put to test my preconceptions would be tantamount to committing a gross underestimation, when the truth is that both were able to touch the depths of my ser.4Antes of this event, I never hid my disdain for Chef Gusteau's motto: "anyone can cook". But, I realize, just now I understand his words. Not anyone can become a great artist, but a great artist do come from anywhere.Anton Ego, the critical gastronómicoPor all that, even if only to see this character, must go to the movies and enjoy two hours of an exceptional animated banquet, a blatantly commercial gimmick, written and designed to engolosinar to the child and youth, plataea but covered with a patina of unquestionable adult honesty. It is not enough that the animation techniques are amazing. That action Cup good part of the footage. There are occasions in which this reliable and expected arsenal of cinematographic benefits do not guarantee a round film (Cars, put for example), but Ratatouille is a fascinating exercise in film of great height that, without being her masterpiece many critics (read the Introit of the review) believe see, becomes the best movie of the summer, time of weak favors entertainment intelligent and usually nourished of pastelazos without (Next) possible defence or Classics (by repetitive) artifacts of great acceptance and minor aesthetic integrity (the fantastic 4, Harry Potter, the jungle.)All that sweet lightness which is attributed a priori films orchestrated for the benefit of the child racket exists in Ratatoille. It has the outstanding merit of matrimoniar form harmonious and almost imperceptible (that is another point in their favor) the brochazo of universally accepted cartoon and the subliminal line of lucid text, well built and, above all, educational. It is the film that would have made Frank Capra have enjoyed these times of impeccable technique. And James Stewart would have excited in the armchair. (Now UB-40 song assumes a new significance).</body>
</review>
