<review author="Plissken" title="Ovejas Asesinas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>King made his debut in the direction with a nice splatter full of references to their live on film, the memorable Jackson Braindead.</summary>
	<body>The second plate of the double programme of horror Manga Films brings us this summer is sheep killer, a title which is a synopsis.Filmmakers, after exhausting the Noah's Ark in almost its entirety (crocodiles, spiders, sharks, snakes, bees, piranhas, Lions, slugs, rats, dogs, cats, frogs, ants, monkeys, rabbits) are finding it difficult to put the nickname "killer" to an animal. But it had to be in New Zealand, the land of the hobbits, the All-Blacks and Braindead, be given where the next round of nut to the argument "nature comes from the man". The culprit: Jonathan King and his directorial debut, black sheep, a fun corderil desmadre.Life is beautiful in the bucolic the Oldfield farm: Oldfield dad cares for his sheep with the help of his son Henry and his friend Tucker. Meanwhile Angus, the eldest son, develops a few brutal jealousy towards the Benjamin of the family cuasiperfecto. A tragic event changes everything, Henry becomes a trauma than good we might call "ovejofobia" and he goes to the city. Angus, for his part, becomes the master of the farm, and years more later, in a kind of Josef Mengele of sheep, in search of the perfect sheep, sheep Oldfield. Henry decides to return to the farm at bad time: just as genetic research gets rid of their "failed attempts", just as some tambourine environmentalists decide to give the blow to the unnatural methods of breeding of Angus, just when Oldfield race occurs in society. This mixture of factors leads to a shock therapy for poor Henry and the rest of the people, which already will never return to count sheep to sleep.King made his debut in the direction with a sympathetic "splatter" full of references to its more direct on film, the memorable Jackson Braindead. Aided by the tireless boys of WETA, converts to harmless and tontorrones cattle in machines to eat human flesh, and the absolute stars of the function. Each ovejero attack is more fun if possible, with authentic tackles and Kreutz flights resembled with the killer rabbit pythoniano. In addition, their bites become hombres-oveja their victims resource allowing King begin with a film of murderous animals and end with a woolly zombies. The truth is that seeing these sheep in action is a delusion, and is already worth approaching black sheep only by them.The major drawback is that Jonathan King not hides many more ACEs in his manga. Once submitted the black sheep, the plot follows foot juntillas already old roads of the genre, and actors do not pass than usual in these cases, with the exception of the villain Angus (a great Peter Fenney which seems the evil brother of Bruce Campbell), and show no more, although the script allows some really funny moments. On the other hand, the technical Bill is careful, makeup and FX both in photography, sound and music, but only shine really these threatening sheep.But in aggregate, I guess at the end you miss accounts and you have left an impression of a job well done and without major pretensions, thinking of a public that wants to have a fun time. In that Jonathan King and his sheep play to spare, ensuring 90 minutes of laughter and varied offal.6.5, That with what falls in the genre already is enough.</body>
</review>
