<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Fast food nation" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In fact, it's a "small" film despite the argument and the important quantity and quality of performers involved therein.</summary>
	<body>Interesting film of Richard Linklater, always willing to put in solfa various estates, allegedly untouchables in the United States. Fast food chains, food called trash, are one of them.Linklater here, addresses the issue of pollution of burgers, from different points of view. Perhaps too, which makes the whole not round which would have been necessary.Sins of ambitious, so to speak, to the mix, perhaps because they go hand in hand especially in the border with Mexico, work in factories in preparation of the product, with the inhuman, humiliating and very hard work of Mexican immigrants working in it as cheap and silent workforce (most works without papers).The film, however, is entertaining and interesting at all times, and there are abundant good scenes and dialogues. Moments like the work in the food chain, the conversation of the Executive with the link in the factory (excellent Bruce Willis), or the last ten minutes, manifest clearly the excellence of this important film, criticism of a corrupt system that threatens public health.However, it is clear that the film is uneven, and the somewhat erratic events. The employee rate is Linklater House brand, but it makes that few, has but recognizable downtime.In addition, not all characters have the sufficient importance in the plot. None left, but there are important differences between them.In general terms, "Fast Food Nation" to spare fulfils its role, which is the State a fact which should be changed immediately. But of course that it will fail, both because it is impossible the film to change completely the public awareness of, and because it does not, for my taste, the force required. Since, in reality, he is a "small" despite the argument tape and the important quantity and quality of the performers they involved therein.</body>
</review>
