<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Cars" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pixar stays true to his style, and proof of this is the hectic pace that has the movie from the first second.</summary>
	<body>A few days ago in the morning I went to the cinema UGC Ciné Cité of Madrid to see "Ultraviolet". Upon arrival, my surprise and joy were capitalized to discover that a preview of "Cars", the new and highly anticipated had film from Pixar. Unfortunately I had no essential invitation to enter. But behold, Providence in the form of friendly Lady, nice and with an entry of over did the miracle of let me see the movie (I have to highlight also the kindness of workers of cinema that sent back me the money from the entrance).Once sitting in my armchair and before seeing the film I could enjoy the teaser trailer of "Ratatouille", that on the big screen is a joy, and "The man Orchestra" short film that Pixar always shows before their movies and rigor that deserves comment apart.But let's go to the grain. "Cars", directed by John Lasseter and Joe Ranft (emotive homage to the deceased film director during the closing credits), account history of Lightning McQueen, young and successful racing car which by avatars of the destination and on the eve of the race of his life, is lost and trapped in a village on the route 66.Me would like to stress that dubbing does not seem as awful as I expected after hearing the news about the famous that doblarían some characters. Such eventually famous appear rather little and not come to bother too much, although I would have loved to see in original version to enjoy the voices of Owen Wilson, and above all, Paul Newman. Temáticamente the film is quite topical: cocky and selfish character that falls in an environment different from the usual and has to learn to be better. Along the way he discovers the importance of true friendship and the power of love. Fund, the typical singing the honesty and the beauty of the traditional village life with accelerated sophistication of the modern world (in this case symbolized by the racing world).But there is something that you cannot be denied to Pixar is that each new production manages to beat the previous visually. They are world leaders in animated 3D film and difficult it will be to lose his throne if they have to compete with films majas but lacking brilliance as "Neighbors invaders" (see critical) or "Ice Age 2" (see critical). If in "Buscando a Nemo", those responsible for Pixar reflected as never the marine environment now have decided by asphalt and races, with equally brilliant results.Pixar stays true to his style, and proof of this is the hectic pace that has the movie from the first second, which makes it one of the most entertaining films of this year. Nor are lacking the emotional moments than not sensibleros. And it is that occasionally the camera movements and images reach beauty and perfection that excited alone. All this seasoned, as it could not be otherwise, the humor brand of the House and with the waste of imagination to create a world that is like ours but which is inhabited exclusively by car.It is true that it does not reach the spectator as other tapes of Pixar. This may be because it is not so easy to feel identified with a car as a superhero or a fish (although saying sounds so ridiculous) or to that feeling of déjà vu that has the story. But all that gives just because once the projection, one leaves the film with a smile from ear to ear and with the conviction of having passed one of the year's funniest moments in a movie theater. And to raise the hand that can boast of having released a film as well in recent times.</body>
</review>
