<review author="Dragon negro" title="Planet Terror" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Planet Terror is like a bad joke that always explain with your friends and that always makes grace and understood among that small group who knows that going while the rest of people looks strange and are wondering where her pussy this grace if the joke is old and bad.</summary>
	<body>They already warned us that the GrindHouse project was intended to recover the essence and spirit of the films of serie B, and since then that Robert Rodriguez has succeeded with this first film that has reached us. Planet Terror tells us as a species of virus begins to infect the population becoming a human blood thirsty zombies, we, the typical movie of zombies, but in this case as last thread and so absurd that one cannot applaud such audacity to make a bizarrada so much fun like this.And is that if something is Planet Terror is that at no time taken seriously if same, and the director takes the opportunity to get scenes of action, already not impossible, but completely unthinkable, dialogues to which more jam and some memorable phrases stuck with shoehorn and meaningless, and above all a mise en scene and a deliberately crappy and homemade special effects. Until the actors acting badly on purpose, and also note that it has a couple of memorable cameos.Such prospect one not surprising that the commercial failure has been sound and is Planet Terror is like a bad joke that always explain with your friends and that always makes grace and understood among that small group who knows that going while the rest of people looks strange and are wondering where her pussy this grace if the joke is old and bad. So is this film a bad joke that only fans to the genre will know understand, find grace and enjoy it as what is a bad film, but which in reality is not, because that is what you want to be, and here is where lies his greatness. It is clear, that which it approaches the film without much idea of what going to see and expects to see a topical action or horror film and is confronted with such nonsense, because it is normal to not make him or fucking grace, and is that surely not he has learned that goes the joke.</body>
</review>
