<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Planet Terror" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I still see Robert Rodriguez as an ingenious type that has managed to surround and learn from friends from the world of cinema with more talent and best ideas that he.</summary>
	<body>The double session Robert Rodriguez and Quentin Tarantino have prepared us for this summer was one of the projects looked more forward. His aesthetic and content of eighties revival constitute an explicit tribute to a kind of cinema of terror and action, popularly known as B movies, of which this couple of friends and irreverent directors have both drunk in their careers. Grindhouse, container name which brings together the two films by this double session opens with the premiere of Planet Terror, the tape of the identifiable Mexican instantly by the powerful symbol in its poster embodies the beautiful Rose McGowan (charmed) with his Orthopedic fusil-pierna. I imagine that, due to the commercial dictates of today day, not been able to brand new Grindhouse which would have been more appropriate and coherent format: in one of the longed double sessions of our childhood. &lt; but going to the grain, the tape of Rodríguez happens what to his previous other works. Provides good ideas, sequences of magnificent Bill (the closing credits of this film again you endorsed as a great filmador of stripteases after her uncover in this aspect with the legendary of the Hayek snake in ready), brutal beatings of humor (the joke about the Pope or the fake trailer for Machete is depart) and moments of action shot with simpar originality. However, when one scratches on its attractive packaging, the package that they reveal is rather poor. For the moment, I still staying with his fidelísima translation of the vignettes to celluloid by Miller Sin City, where the Mexican was a step forward in the adoption of digital technologies in the service of a very specific aesthetic idea and, at the same time, improved her good skills in the composition of scores; which also is noted in the original soundtrack of Planet Terrror, with a sound clearly indebted to Sin City.Debo recognize that Planet Terror not excites me too much because nor did it at the time the kind of cinema that it intends to pay homage. I end up tired exaggerated blood with humorous desire baths or the annihilation of zombies / infected plan video game console. Do yes I like quirky characters such as the pair of brothers? the police and the owner of a ramshackle road bar? in competition lifetime to achieve the best sauce barbecue in the State of Texas. And I also like Rodriguez, Tarantino-style, to recycle in his films known actors of the past that we can now rediscover in unsuspected facets (such as the great Michael Parks, a regular in the recent work of the couple Rodríguez-Tarantino).However, after having viewing Planet Terror, I still see Robert Rodriguez as an ingenious type that has managed to surround and learn from friends from the world of cinema with more talent and best ideas that he. Somehow, still find me a promising disciple starts to chisel a style (such as the indispensable Hispanic touch of all of his works), but which lacks free from so many outside references to offer something more unequivocally theirs.</body>
</review>
