<review author="Bruji" title="Planet Terror" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Rightly, bad. Divertidamente vomit. Absolutely brilliant. Robert Rodriguez leaves us one of those lies that have always contributed to enlarge the film.</summary>
	<body>Rightly, bad. Divertidamente vomit. Absolutely brilliant. The exact point in which the impossible, anomalous, Chavacano and absurd converge at the counter of the casquero, to unleash that another way of understanding the film which is the series B. Without a doubt, the film that only Robert Rodriguez could conceive, understand and shoot without fear to lose its prestige as a filmmaker.The Grindhouse project is a tribute to the American cinemas which, in the 1970s and 1980s, projected low-budget films. Those that, according to Robert Rodriguez, "had good ideas, but lacked the means to materialise". I guess to them that, later, began to populate the first albaceteños video-club, who was assiduous. It is composed of two films, which we discussed today and Quentin Tarantino's Death Proof, among which are inserted four fictional trailers of films signed by usual genre directors such as Eli Roth, Rob Zombie and Edgar Wright, and the own Rodríguez., non-existent in reality, the invention is not new, nor when is about to make a parody of horror films, see (or better, not) stupid saga Scary Movie; or when a homage to the double session is proposed. Let us remember that in 1978 Stanley Donen filmed Movie, Movie, consisting of two other films, a drama that revolves around a boxer, title dynamite hands, and a musical called the beauties of Baxter, 1,933; precisely, to honor the double session of the cinema of the 1930s.In countries like Britain, United States, or Australia, the Grindhouse lot Debuts complete; in the rest of the world, it is decomposed, because we would "not we understand this type of format". When is the truth that, to understand until we understand that we will have to pay double for what others have acquired in a two for one, and that, under the guise of its extended duration, one tries to justify his dramatic failure at the box office.In this way, and waiting for the exciting pursuit of car that promises the history of Tarantino, we are left with the genius written, directed, photographed, mounted and "music" by Robert Rodriguez, the idea that only he could conceive, understand and filming, and that will keep the viewer out of orbit since the appearance of Machete, to be unspeakable in version X, until the culminating moment in which a go gó of disco fires with a machine gun being false leg.At all times, Planet Terror is intended to be a series B horror film, and succeeds thanks to the effects of digitization that they simulate the damaged celluloid, with frames that are striped and spotted, with the loss of color and sound, aderezados by an infernal Assembly, if you are interested in. Similarly, both the argument based on improvised heroes fighting against an army of zombies as characters, pursue identical goal; reaching the misplacement of the scroll issue 4, that in Spanish cinema would have never lost. But in the midst of this soundtrack of poor quality, that picture impossible, their repetitive and intentionally painful, dialogues of the indecent atmosphere that recreates external flat assumptions gathered under economic hardship, emerges "useless number 12 talent" to make way for a brilliant script, a careful editing and special effects that have little to do with the Grindhouse that pays homage.Against the typical scenes drawn from those unforgettable movies, decidedly bad, we love so much in the past, in which "the good", empty look, was detained when he tried to save the world, and the cable of an electric saw is always desenchufaba to avoid the massacre; We find the sequence Summit filmed George Romero in 1968, the achievement of a truck to escape from those infected, and the fuel pump that breaks out in the air. We also recognize in the blue eyes, Bloodshot, of untold tears of the scared blonde (Marley Shelton), situations that Giorgio Ferroni invented for Teresa Gimpera (the night of the Devils, 1,972).To configure the rest of the cast, as did the producers of night of the living dead, but for different reasons; Rodriguez becomes surround its nearest surroundings. Some relatives (his son and his nieces, the twin Kangaroo), the members of the technical team make-up (the veteran artist Tom Savini), and his collaborators and friends, leaving the roles actors for actors from television series, Rose McGowan (charmed) and Freddy Rodriguez (to six feet under). It is interesting to check the insistence that shows Tarantino, the last of the classics by Ava Gardner.Puede to be true, that "to the goals they will force when we talk about them", but is a fact that the bruja-metralleta already is an incono of the fantasy genre, and that Robert Rodriguez is not only removed a thorn to shoot a zombie, but that leaves us one of those lies that have always contributed to enlarge the film.</body>
</review>
