<review author="Bruji" title="El último rey de Escocia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The big difference that a history of history fall into expert hands or reaches the producers of 28 days after, resides primarily in that, in the first course, I could be talking about a masterpiece; While, in the case before us, it is only hear about the interpretation of Forest Whitaker.</summary>
	<body>That that history judge each and every one of the dictators of the world, okay; but it would be much better if, in addition, be brought to each and every one of the all-powerful who, at some point, smile at you them. The butcher of Kampala accesses the power of Uganda following a military coup which is supported by Israel, while the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, British he defines as "a splendid type and a great football player". A few aspects which, like many others, not transcend in a film of "historical genre".The big difference that a history of history falls into hands experts (I can think of Mr. Spielberg) or reaches the producers of 28 days after, resides primarily in that, in the first course, I could be talking about a masterpiece; Whereas, in the case that concerns us, you only hear about the interpretation of Forest Whitaker.No is strange. We have a film which is lacking too many essential elements, such as depth and historical rigour, a solid script, an effective arrangement, and an intensive course on what was meant by "measuring time" in the narrative of a footage. And that, on the other hand, has to go camera moves sea, scenes that do not fit and inserted artificial way (due to deficiencies in the script, in the montage, or both) and, above all, the claim that places it within the historic genre. The director of the film expresses his desire for the Viewer to a remote location, such as Uganda, for? assume - bring the socio-political reality of this country in the era of Idi Amin, "Given". (I say OK, we suppose). We are assuming that, being a November documentalist, success is assured; and we were wrong. The only thing offered is a film of adventure, "Doctor in Uganda", and a superfluous panoramic view of an imaginary country, ruled by a bizarre tyrant that coexists with English characters which do not explain his presence, which are episodes of kidnapped flights without clarification of the positions of anyone, and where is sensed the brutal repression against a few opponents of unknown provenance. Said with other words, the filmmaker turns into one of these travel agents which provide idyllic destinations in paradisiacal circuits closed, away from the harshness of the place you visit.Which is a real shame, because there are valuable ingredients that do not have managed to explode, as they are the attractive story of Giles Foden; the presence of a personal fictional, medical advisor of the dictator, who is representing the civil population seduced by it for later, suffer the revelation of his true personality; and the possibility of filming in the heart of Africa, which is only used to show the different types of existing mosquito, under the rule of a torturadora soundtrack.A clear example of what happens when it fails the "approach" which dealt with an argument, which leads us to wonder how different this film would have been if he had used the novel to deepen the historical episode, as did Steven Zallian in Schindler's list or Tony Kushner in Munich or even manages to capture the essence of the slaughtererwhich is brimming with of affability (which certainly was), but which not been attributed explicitly those other aspects which expressed his schizophrenia, which led him to appear in the Court of the Queen without prior notice, to make a telephone call to the President of the very USA at five in the morning, or to rebuke his admired Hitler "for not having murdered enough Jews". Some details that make, leaving the film, 1,500 doubts that assail the Viewer, having gone to the incredible history and, at all times, forced approach.In a product aimed at the satisfaction of a nothing demanding audience, it pleasantly surprised the extraordinary leadership of actors that develops the documentalist. Not only is worthy of praise the work of (deservedly award-winning) Whitaker, physical resurrection of the "King of Scotland" filmed in 1974 by Barbet Schroeder; but also they are interpretations of James McAvoy, Gillian Anderson and David Oyelowo. As much as the right picture of Anthony Dod, sober and sharp within the British Empire, intense colors in Ugandan territory. Which leads us to believe that the next time a filmmaker decides to venture into the African continent, will have to flee (as if it were a hungry Tiger) of the cynical message that release products like blood diamond, as well as well as the historic grey created by MacDonald. I am sure that the famous acronym AEAEA (this is Africa) are still pending to explain.</body>
</review>
