<review author="Bruji" title="The holiday" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nancy Meyers does not comply with the basic purpose of the romantic comedies, but knows defeat the shallowness inherent in stories of this genre.</summary>
	<body>Nancy Meyers does not comply with the basic purpose of the romantic comedies, which is love, but manages to excite telling two stories that are full of references moviegoers. With them, moreover, known defeat the shallowness inherent in this genre stories, break with numerous established topics and create a movie with heart, especially recommended for those who are in the process of "desenamoramiento". Does that?.The confidences are made at midnight, but anytime is right to confess an addiction, mine, to the romantic comedies. Based on it, say that eighty percent of the stories that make up so sweet universe in recent decades, are cut by a common pattern: "they are lying and they forgive". By forever never happened in Manhattan, I have never Besado. A dangerous formula that makes the genre stalwarts leave the cinema with a terrible remorse of guilt of others and, what is worse, with a strange feeling of false love. Obviously, we have allowed ourselves seduce by non-existent beings, with qualities such as understanding, tolerance and common sense, that are incompatible with the masculine gender.Things change when the script writes it to a woman. Old topics are reviewed and are rejected and, in their absence, the four species that compose the peculiar fauna that lose us sleep, are portrayed accurately. and with objectivity. In this way, appears insecure narcissistic, that needs to fall in love with other women to keep their own self-esteem; Peter Pan, unable to engage in his bloody life, eternal interpreter of the U2 song: "neither with you nor without you"; Mr napkin, which displays all its tenderness and its seductiveness to convince you that you're the perfect woman. to be the mother of his children; and the addict to the work, which necessarily has to be your favourite hobby.It is possible that someone thinks that the only thing that has made is to create new topics. Personally, I think that it is futile to look for in other directions: this is what there is.In any case, Nancy Meyers knows very well what he is doing. It was a major challenge to create two independent stories in the same film, and it has stood the test, relying on three fundamental aspects: different narrative structures, continuous cinematic allusions in both stories, and a full success in the choice of actors actresses.Behind of a comedy, seemingly inconsequential, holiday hides a tribute to the classics of the 1930s and 1940s. Shown in their long sequences, in the theatrical sunsets in Cameron Diaz scene, in the purest style of Carole Lombard; in the recurring "sexes struggle" with its corresponding discussion with slap, as well exploded William Wellman; and the delicacy and elegance inherited master Lubitsch, connoisseur of feminine nature. Remember, for example, the disease of Psychosomatics of one of the protagonists, and the hiccups of Merle Oberon, what you think women, 1941. but the Director goes even further, and creates two different narrative structures, because, in reality, what you are doing is telling two stories which are not interrelated. To do so, to treat the English adventure, used to the pace of British comedies, quiet and cozy, present in four weddings and a Funeral and Love Actually. A rhythm that disappears in the images of Los Angeles, where the American characters involved.They are continuous references made to the cinematic firmament of explicitly, including a cameo by the graduate, a list of classics with female protagonists of weapons to take, and a joke about the color red that uses Scorsese. In addition, Nancy will recreate various scenes that have been extracted from films such as The Mexican (discussion between Ethan and Amanda, she on top of a balcony), Titanic (the reaction that causes the name of the protagonist in his male partner) or brief encounter (the form know Jack Black and Kate, with a "char" in the eye). A few aspects that desatarán the nostalgia of lovers.Kate Winslet and Cameron Diaz have a single point in common: both have been kissed by Leo DiCaprio... and they have been able to tell. The Director knows to take advantage of the comic the first registration and the dramatic vein of Kate, which comes from the English Theatre; but he was aware that it would be a mistake to do both share scenes. The superiority of the British is more than evident. Thus, each in place and without being mixed, manage to excite and making people laugh, separately. We miss, however, some genius in the Assembly. It would have been convenient to altering its linearity absolute, only interrupted by the sequence of the spaghetti (linking the two accounts), and the plane of the splash in the bath, which gives way to a puddle.In short, a round romantic comedy, encouraged to prepare a different holiday. How sound that "you to Albacete and I to Acapulco"?. Not even there to worry about which sleeping in your room, remember that Iris leaves the dog in London.</body>
</review>
