<review author="Bruji" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do no one better that Milos Forman knows that? the horrors of history repeated? all too often.</summary>
	<body>Something supernatural happens when Milos Forman is behind the camera. Suddenly, the viewer feels like the protagonist of the Purple Rose of Cairo and is that, when he directs the technical barriers that separate reality from fiction, the screen of the patio of armchairs, disappear. At that time, it is no longer strange to concur with the head before the revolutionary speech of Javier Bardem, give back a smile to Stellan Skarsgard instinctively, nor that this hiele on the lips to look in the eyes of Natalie Portman.En reality, is not necessary to be brought "question" to sign and say that in the difficult task of transmittingCzech filmmaker has no rival.Goya's ghosts is a story of history, which well might being chosen at random, where religious fanaticism and the tyranny of political rulers lead to military intervention by neighbouring (or not neighbouring) invaders, in the name of freedom (safe-conduct attractive and recurrent), committed all kinds of abuses and committed against the population. It happened in Spain, and there was the painter of the King to immortalize the facts; but, as the director said, the horrors of history are repeated, so it is possible that this argument does not convince in the States holding of America. in any case, we are faced with one of those gems that resist all analyses of Gemology. The technical virtues of this film are innumerable and unbeatable, the composition of the levels is spectacular, aesthetic beauty is, frankly, amazing. Without resorting to clichés of camera, has been able to take care of even the most insignificant detail in every scene.Shows clear inheritance of pictorial mannerism of Stanley Kubrick, and his obsession with the unrestrained MIME of environments, costumes, lighting and sets. Milos Forman camera movements are still austere, and the "shaken" to which we are accustomed, creepily. The photography is excellent, exceptional mounting.But, perhaps, the greatest attraction of this footage is in the direction of actors, in his memorable performances that make up unforgettable sequences. The eyes of Natalie, the smile of Goya, the reprehensible aspects of the personality of genius, the extraordinary portrait of characters, situations and behaviors.It is important to note that each and every one of these roles rub the perfection that even Martínez de Irujo is credible and his wife, a Rodeo madrileña. However, I still do not find adequate adjectives to describe the performance of Mademoiselle. Portman in his triple register; and it is that I am afraid all the compliments of the Castilian language are declared insufficient to do justice. On the other hand, I have no doubt that who will be Yes batteries from this moment will be "the photocopy", his eternal impersonator, Keira Knightley, without being aware of that the bar is already too high.For posterity, are valuable samples of master, worthy to be studied in film schools. The interrogation which undergoes Bilbatúa Inés; talks that keeps the painter with his muse, in which hard to decipher if the protagonist is the deaf or its partner is silent; the translation that is, effectively abstract concepts, such as Liberté, Égalité and Fraternité; popular revolts, absolute chaos.Above their immense successes, what most surprised of this tape is a director of another nationality has received so much clearly the essence of Spanish, the mocking spirit of a people that is still called a "tag" to which many historians consider that it could be a good monarch; and why not say it? capture this ancestral trend of "whores", who continue to sell their services to the best client. Clear that, in all cases, is a matter of appreciation this historic episode has been told in the way that is done, leaving patent that this country was the subject of a spoliation unprecedented.In his latest work, Man On The Moon, he spoke of someone who did laugh when he himself had no own smile. On this occasion, shows those who are striving to appear normal when stability is absent, in a world that falls apart in a stage in which the courtyards of public performance is situated directly on the place where the pasodobles are danced. Devastating, heartbreaking, poignant, and with those eyes... Goya's ghosts is another masterpiece of Milos Forman.</body>
</review>
