<review author="Bruji" title="El velo pintado" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of those stories that revitalize with the passage of the years. Its failure at the American box office will then only anecdotal data that typically surround the great works of the cinema.</summary>
	<body>"Memoirs of China" that brings us closer to a thrilling story dated in the 1920s. In it, Somerset Maugham uses his unconditional love not correspondidos fixing and inexorable punishment ensuing reprehensible behavior. A film of high technical and artistic quality. A tribute to the romanticism within an essential title.But what little seriousness!. They measure them the film at the box office and American producers blame it to the Assembly of the Chinese. Why not directly to blame the American public?. It is possible that while others only repair in a heartbreaking love story, they sit warned before the popular clamor that joins the unanimous cry of: your House, imperialist pigs!.Better still, why not blame Norton, sole architect of the political dimension acquired the frame?. In the film of recent times is dangerous to show "the barbarian invasions". Only must be set in the ghosts of Goya, in their problems to find distributor.Up the inks against the synopsis offered by own producer, the trailer that sells and the label of "Romantic film of time", condemning it to the tedious saga is not could load. Fortunately, has nothing to do with the soporific works of the sleepy James Ivory.Como meaningless reproach arriving at the wrong time,? the legendary Mankiewicz Cleopatra failed miserably without that the Chinese to participate in the co-production-, we there a thick painted veil and will analyse the aspects that make it, despite everything, in an essential title.Firstly, it has an interesting raw material, the novel by w. Somerset Maugham. This author has been brought to the film on 24 occasions, being, perhaps, human bondage his most significant work. The same John Cromwell became work teacher under the title of captive of desire at the time discovered Bette Davis as "the bad" of the seventh art. On paper, El Velo Pintado is an x-ray of feelings that dissects perfectly the real reasons that feed and preserve the love.Secondly, are available to overcome all the obstacles that come from the adaptation of a story that is obsolete, to turn it into an elaboradísimo script for flawless structure, which has, moreover, a remarkable and select narrative pace. In this sense, it works in the style of the best classical writers, those who were writing, revising, supervised and retell relentlessly. In this way, on a material from the screenwriter of Philadelphia, involved another excellent writer who, systematically refuses to figure as such in the opening credits. Its mission is the extend the scenic spaces and break with the emotional Hermeticism of the initial story for the film glory, away from sugary contemplations that lead to the most tiresome of the aburrimientos. The unquestionable merit is Edward Norton. The third fundamental pillar it find in the dialogues, as smart as attractive, perfectly constructed, once again, in the purest style of the classics. Only the authors of the 40-50 decades were able to keep the attention of the viewer in long scenes? sometimes, entire movies - which were being carried out without major events, only two characters in claustrophobic somewhere. Those responsible for this film are not recreated in such situations, but know exit carry the day when pose them.Following major classical productions, requires the presence of two big stars. While that Norton - actor performs a discrete interpretation, Naomi is sublime. She showed her best dramatic record in 21 grams, hypnotised in The Ring and convinced to wear the clothes of early 20th century? such as 34 - King Kong. Without a doubt, the best actress of the last generations to embody the romantic heroine who give life Greta Garbo and Eleanor Parker. Both are wrapped by a successful cast of side of jutting Liev Schreiber.El fifth attractive element is extracted from a correct address which brings the various technical aspects to the category of characters. Thanks to some levels of the filmmaker, the viewer will experience the need to travel to Mei-as-Fu, even with anger. For its part, Dryburgh photography incorporates, at all times, the threat of the polluted river. Without forgetting the surround soundtrack Alexandre Desplat, the evocative piano, or the inclusion of this beautiful song: "do Il and longtemps that je t? aime.", that frames the crowning scenes of the film. The point in which the nostalgic remember the end of that "I had a farm in Africa".Maybe that "China is not place for a woman", but it is certain that this is one of those stories that revitalize with the passage of the years. Its failure at the American box office will then only anecdotal data that typically surround the great works of the cinema.</body>
</review>
