<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los chulos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Yet another film of this Spanish comedy duo, with a facing the demon Esteso Pajares Pius. Social criticism on the Spain of the Egyptians (that the left hand doesn't know what the right) decorated with typical topics and, of course, tits and ass.</summary>
	<body>If this were the bulls, we could say that there is a good sign. Three women in porretas in submissive positions, Ozores mafia smiling white suit, and lofts with the face of a giant fart be enduring. Not to mention Ricardo Merino, Juanito Navarro, Alfonso del Real, María Isbert and Jenny Llada (do not know anything, which I assume it is despelotará). They are no longer posters like these, which summarized us perfectly what we are going to see. Pity. the film is about a businessman in the sector of Vice and the so-called fornication Felix Rebolledo (Esteso), who decides to open a House of mental and physical relaxation in a village of the deep Spain. As we know that you have to be good with the forces of the same, through bribes, good carnal, either tangible, get have them all eating of his hand. But ete here the problem, which appears a such Arcadius (Pajares), nephew of the Bishop (Juanito Navarro), who has been expelled from the seminar by excess of Pius. It quickly leads a rebellion against the local festivals, supported by the women of the living forces.Give joy to your body Macarena, which your body is pa to give joy and good thing. Eehhhh, Macarena, ajú!. This has nothing to do, but as the film does rhyme or reason, because it is consistent. Let's start with the script, quite sencillote as it should be. Ozores wants that catch Pajares in unseemly position, so it covers of tits and ass to see if pica. It is rumored Pajares required doubles for this type of scenes, given that in the essay he preñó three. The action is fast-paced, from tit to tit, get us some chistecillo and enjoyable joke. And rare is that the end is very consistent with the rest of the film.In short, yet another film of this Spanish comedy duo, with a facing the demon Esteso Pajares Pius. Social criticism on the Spain of the Egyptians (that the left hand doesn't know what the right) decorated with typical topics and, of course, tits and ass.Good material for the visual.kisses.</body>
</review>
