<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Cars" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not carried their pipiolos to the cinema to see the movie! In addition to get tired and give them the afternoon, won't let enjoy the film his armchair companions.</summary>
	<body>I had my reservations about how Pixar was going to give life to something as inanimate like a car, the truth is that the project I loved it since I started having the same and perhaps news, and along with Superman Returns has been of the films of this year 2006 I've waited with more impatience, a similar phenomenon lived with Big Fish ending haunting me in such a wayIt appeared even in my dreams.Because Cars the seventh film in the House of the Flexo (Pixar), however, does not leave indifferent, this so well done, so well defined and so terribly animated characters that one cannot remain indifferent before such magna creation.Even its controversial dubbing (with the voices of Antonio Lobato, Fernando Alonso, immaculate Galván.) inferior film, since that is until an incentive more than tape discover who is behind the character we see on screen, until the mini-cameo of Michael Schumacher.Por elsewhere, there are 2 factors that does not make the film a perfect tape, one is the downturn this gives to the middle of the second actwhere not know very well why the tape seems that it stagnates, thank God, manages to recover quickly progress; But if Gets a tad tiresome, the other reason is an excess of moralina Disney were not in the Incredibles (Pixar previous tape) and here seems to load the inks in excess and is that you okay a small dose, or load of morality, but trying to translate lessons to every 20 frames becomes a little weary.Leaving aside the 2 negative factors of the tape, would like to focus on the well that this reflected the world of the engine, from the first minute of the movie until the end all are tributes, ads, brands, even the world of NASCAR (that in Spain we do not know) are reflected on screen with a mind-BOGGLING sophistication, and it is that John Lasseter is a lover of the culture of the 4-wheel drive and this helpsquite to the making of the film, by the way, the short that came with the tape is the funniest I've seen Pixar from the acclaimed For the Birds (birds), and the end of the movie with this homage to Lasseter tapes well deserves some laughter (such as which I suffered in my flesh). Ah! I forgot; parents of creatures of less than 4 years not carried their pipiolos to the cinema to see the movie! In addition to get tired and give them the afternoon, won't let enjoy the film to his fellow armchair, because between their snot, crying and "mama/papa I am pis" tarnished the enjoyment of the film, go, you go to the cinema and the kid you leave with the grandmother, aunt or Kangaroo! I said.</body>
</review>
