<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="2 Días en París" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The main failure of 2 days in Paris is the obsession by Julie Delpy in emulate Richard Linklater and her work, which to be honest is not that it was no gem.</summary>
	<body>It is ironic to think of the number of actors and actresses who in recent years have decided to make the leap to the address. Not by the fact itself, which is a natural step, but by the surprise and even indignation that this causes. Here we have Julie Delpy showing us his directorial debut, a story that looks suspiciously like his works on the orders of Richard Linkleter. The irony is that prior to becoming an actress, Delpy studied direction and script writing, and in these years has failed to financing for their projects.That the success of before of the sunset, including its nomination for the Academy Award for Best Original Screenplay (the own Delpy was partly responsible for), has led to the realization of 2 days in Paris is more than evident. It's a story with clear similarities and parallels with that, a couple as epicentre of the plot that wanders by a city and their emotional troubles. Such troubles become tedious after few minutes, reaching the audience a profound boredom which is difficult to recover. The tape is full of worn-out clichés and as expected adds nothing to an obsolete genus and endangered. Only the appearances of the characters of Albert Delpy and Marie Pillet (the best of the film) succeed in improving the scene infusing him some much-needed small doses of humor. Through the film, Delpy offers a portrait of part of the current French society, but fails in his attempt to become Paris taxi drivers their unique samples of study.The main failure of 2 days in Paris is the obsession by Julie Delpy in emulate Richard Linklater and her work, which to be honest is not that it was no gem. It will have to wait to be able to see the real Julie Delpy Director, in a more personal project and not a commercial commissioned as 2 days in Paris.</body>
</review>
