<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Los 4 Fantásticos y Silver Surfer" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The fantastic four and Silver Surfer is not just another clear example of the regrettable condition in that is action cinema and fantasy of Hollywood.</summary>
	<body>One of the basic laws of physics is that it is a reaction of the same magnitude to each action. This law can be applied to much of the activities of the human being, although in many cases the reactions tend to be disproportionate. The film was not going to be less, and the reaction to a success at the box office is devise a continuation of the same to perpetuate the streak.And so, here comes the sequel to the fantastic four, decent movie super heroes whose sole purpose was the entertain the Viewer without incurring too many errors. Facts that at another time would be common in action movies today are difficult to find real virtues. The history of this new release continues at the time that stayed the previous one, with the heroes turned into stars media which beans are gained through the promotion and advertising, such as David Beckham any. Everything is ready for the wedding of the century between Ree Richards (Ioan Gruffud) and Susan Storm (Jessica Alba) in a ceremony which will leave in mere village and palette pachanga to link cienciólogo Cruise-Holmes. However, the idyllic picture is altered by the emergence of a new and strange villain that is dedicated to agujerar the planet (and no, it is not the Mayor of Madrid aboard the Tizona). To all this we must unite the gruesome Hollywood fashion introduce dramatic elements in action films. The script, despite efforts to achieve it, does not have the slightest depth. Before such script, you do not know what to do, if take it to banter and laugh alegramente its coast, or weep bitterly for torture so go unpunished. Some of the dialogues of the film are truly pathetic, although less sonrojante is not null interpretative capacity of Ioan Gruffud and Jessica Alba, who will stay in cute girl for debris, or permitting the surgery and botox. The only pleasant surprise that awaits the Viewer is the funny cameo by Stan Lee.Los fantastic four and Silver Surfer is nothing more than another clear example of the regrettable condition in that is action cinema and fantasy of Hollywood. What was entertaining and worthy in the first film has become boring and embarrassing in the sequel.</body>
</review>
