<review author="El mágico" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is to spend a moment nice, if you are not a fan of the series, otherwise, what can you say? I certainly odiarás for writing my opinion! Acceptable but nothing out of this world...</summary>
	<body>The first thing to say is that "The Simpsons" is a film of difìcil evaluation. Me I crossed with fans of the series in the corridors of the multiplex cinema complexes these past holidays and all of them were bursting of happiness to see her favorite family on screen, arengando to see the tape and mercilessly attacking his detractors acusandolos say lightly without in-depth knowledge of the history of each character brings. Difficult place of critical eh? I must admit that I have intimidated! In part at least. Actually, don't see cinematically the value of "The Simpsons" to take place on any bulletin board, except the honor their adaptive capacity to be the most-watched of the planet cartoon series. No one can argue the Simpsons as a product: they may like you or not, but they are good, they have lot arrival and a legion of fans of all ages. The question es.su movie worth to go see the film or is a long chapter of 87 minutes that might be on TV if one could? Mmmm.complicado question not? It must be said that this is the first feature film of this famous family, since that it broke into our homes in 1991 it has garnered multiple Emmy Awards and as we know is a satire which criticizes society American in all its aspects, with emphasis on the family environment and in the relationships of his characters. It is a creation of Matt Groening, brain responsible for having kept this series 2D at the top of the most popular programs in the history of global television. His cunning is always incorporate new side-shaped elements, while respecting the essence with which viewers are identified. On this occasion, its creation is directed by the interesting David Silverman, who already has chapters in the saga for television and has been responsible for Monsters Inc and The Road to El Dorado, subject who knows a lot of cartoons and how to bring them to the big screen and it shows. The plot in "The Simpsons-(the movie)" is a simple excuse (there is an accident which pollutes Lake Springfield, an isolation of the place by the Government, a persecution to those responsible, a struggle to restore order-?- and regain the place of the city and of the own family in this story), seems that the book (screenplay) plucked thinking gags first, and then generating in base to the storyline. This means that viewers will shake with laughter in their seats most of the time because the film features humor in successive waves intended not to let glimmer as to doubt the effectiveness of the proposal.But the film is empty of interest for those who do not seek more of the same, but some kind of different approach, where the central idea has more flight and the action is not entirely spasmodic concerning the infinite succession of jokes at several levels. May they say that "The Simpsons" is environmentalist, critical of American politics is correct, pero.a his followers that cares? The Simpsons offer a similar show (dangerously if we think that this is not TV and film) to the offer in Fox or Telefé everyday, fun, likable and very clever. Now, from there to think that this is quality cinema.I think that there are differences! In any case, should be the film as one moment in the course of the Simpsons legend in one larger 42 "screen and a room with accompanying the tribute. Is to spend a moment nice, if you are not a fan of the series, otherwise, what can you say? I certainly odiarás for writing my opinion! Acceptable but nothing out of this world (movie buff, disappointed at the lost opportunity).</body>
</review>
