<review author="El mágico" title="Los 4 Fantásticos y Silver Surfer" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I really liked, and I think that if you are unprepared to see it, stripped of prejudices, it love...</summary>
	<body>I remember that "Fantastic 4" was one of the early criticisms of this blog a couple of years ago and perhaps for that reason also remember clearly that it was not a good movie. Much money invested, an expensive advertising campaign, a mixed result. So, to be the sequel to the saga went to the cinema with some degree of skepticism: same director, same cast, same result? But not! This is positive from the movie world, that the phrase "never the second parts were good," not always is confirmed. Here Tim Story decides to play for the visual deployment instead of working the emotional characters and the tape WINS in entertainment and conviction with the new format. "Fantastic four: rise of the Silver Surfer", may not have much to offer for those who are not followers of the factory Marvel Comics, however, what it proposes is a story direct, intense, full of action and excellent special effects that will delight any average viewer. Not encotraremos subtleties in this part, the script is quite simple and the four protagonists move history demonstrating a great predisposition to the resolution of conflicts through little subtle means, but okay. Sequences of fighting against the Silver Surfer are fine and scenarios that runs the production make us remember to any movie of 007. For those who are interested in the plot all starts when an enigmatic intergalactic Herald, the Silver Surfer (character that combines the work of WETA - Lord of the rings - special effects company, with actor Doug Jones - Abe Sapiens in Hellboy - who put the body to interpret it and nothing less than Lawrence Fishburne who contributed the voice!), comes to Earth to prepare it for destruction. But of course, in this path of destruction will find an original ally in the central villain of the previous delivery Victor Van Doom (Julian Mac Mahon, reliable in every chapter of my favorite series, Nip/Tuck) who recovers waiting for revenge of our heroes. While this villain runs (Silver) the world generating strange craters, Reed, Sue, Johnny and Ben (Ion Gruffudd, Jessica Alba, Chris Evans and Michael Chiklis in similar line, complying with the script and not much more) must solve the mystery of of the surfer in a context complicated for the group where the main couple wants to casarse.y not only that but have a normal family! As they embarrassment, this is the nice side of the film, with some discussion isolated on the responsibility and the harassment of the media. But it is the least. What is worth the price of admission are the action scenes; the most interesting are technically of the persecution in Manhattan and the attack on the amusement park in Londres.Aunque to be fair, there is to say that the film proposes something simple and met: there is guarantee of entertainment. Good by Tim Story, by writers Don Payne and Mark Frost that adpatan a story from the middle of the 1960s and the business to an attractive content for the public that today fills the rooms around the world; they are fantastic. I really liked, and I think that if you are unprepared to see it, stripped of prejudices, it love.</body>
</review>
