<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Ratatouille" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>?Ratatouille? It is a beautiful song to tolerance, understanding and coexistence, peaceful and creative, with a finish so superb that rarely has given me so much punishment is completed a film and the cinema lights are lit.</summary>
	<body>"It was created out of necessity." Because it is a way of understanding life, live and express themselves. "As a chef I don't understand my work without investigating, inquire into the restless spirit that defines the human being."Writes it this Quique Dacosta, factotum of El Poblet, one of the most famous restaurants in our country and, by extension, in the whole world. But if they ask him, sure that his words would be subscribed by the very Gousteau, the celebrated Parisian chef with name of submarine commander and gastronómico-revolucionarios desires.And, of course, would be subscribed by Remy, the protagonist of this masterpiece entitled "Ratatouille" rat. And well write "rat" because the protagonist of the last Pixarada not in a nice little mouse, a sympathetic Micky Mouse or a cute Hamster. No. The protagonist of this film is a rat hairy, ugly and repulsive. What shows that Pixar does not be walking with nonsense or with half-measures, which should be very clear ideas and a self-confidence bomb-proof for the arriesgadísima decision to become the protagonist of a film to a rat.Having said which, pay once to the wonderful story of "Ratatouille" and kneel before a film that is prodigious from his boot, old-style of the wildest cartoons of hinojos? this adorable snowing kills - the sequence of the flight of rats by underground channels, pure adrenaline unleashed. And, later, the tenderness. And the message about radical otherness, on the claim of the other, which is different. And on the value, the recognition, the love for the well done work, the love for the craft, the recovery of children, solidarity, family, teamwork.It is incredible what has "Ratatouille". And, above all, it is incredible how account you. It is a narrative prodigy. And the ability to convey emotions. And that Paris, more real than the truth. And that kitchen, these stews that can practically smell. And these side. And those winks. And the perfect combination of humor, love, friendship, passion, anger, etc. And these rats. Let us not forget those rats who run, climb, jump and climb. Some rats that sometimes give disgust, sometimes cause laughter. And tenderness. And, above all, respect. Respect for all those beings that being different, are there. On our side. On the floor of the side. In the bar where breakfast. In the streets that we walk. "Ratatouille" is a beautiful hymn to tolerance, understanding and coexistence, peaceful and creative, with a finish so superb that rarely has given me so much punishment is completed a film and the cinema lights are lit.The question is simply, when it comes out on DVD Edition for collectors?</body>
</review>
