<review author="José A. Peig" title="Planet Terror" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film with a very clear aim of mimicry desvergonzado, imitate the garbage without any reformulation but not sustained in a greater imagination or creativity. With which the objective is accomplished: garbage is and should be treated as such.</summary>
	<body>First segment of a divided into two parts production has been developed with the sole purpose of recovering and remix all the flavor and the aesthetics (?) of the so-called "z series" films, including the imitation of the structure in the typical "continuous session", including trailers of films similar in theme and purpose, both at the beginning and at the end of the narrative basis. Robert Rodriguez opens this díptico-homenaje to the trash cinema, which moves in the field of the evocation of subgenera and clichés "undergrounds", especially in the horror film starring the zombies that appear here a go-go in an "anything goes" that will not leave indifferent any viewer who go to theaters with or without knowledge of the facts. Obviously, a film in which Rodriguez does not intend to otherwise have fun recreating a frantic show of hemoglobin combined with science fiction, sex, black humor and parodic post-apocalípticas allusions, can not ask him to provide intellectual or artistic values beyond this scope, but done not longer a recreation carried out by two filmmakers capricious and master of the revisitación kisch; all pose is a hyperbole of a subgenus forgotten by industry for several decades. At times, such hyperbole reaches the magnitude of a macabre wit and a sadism that nothing they deviate from the conventional model and that we have seen in hundreds of equally bad films.Film for cutre-rocambolesca fun, film subjected to treatment under the legitimate nostalgic inspiration dump, and is reasonable to think that much of the spectators will emerge in the film with a smile of satisfaction. However, for aesthetic purposes, should also be recognized that it is a nice joke that some idiots her sold us as a work of art if it were. Extraordinary claims require impeccable arguments. Some unwary will say that the absence of claims is a trump card in its favour, which is totally wrong. It is a film with a very clear aim of shameless mimicry, imitate the garbage without any reformulation (all it does is multiply the effects and the sensationalism, but not sustained in a greater imagination or creativity - saving some timely point, say, for example, the unforgettable "girl pata palo-ametralladora" - but in a more economic budget). With which the objective is accomplished: garbage is and should be treated as such.</body>
</review>
