<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Planet Terror" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is likely that the continual allusions to other cult films complete bored spectators on average, but it is because we are talking about a tape that is simply not designed for that kind of Viewer.</summary>
	<body>Two films comprising Grindhouse are the apotheosis of these times of simulation in which we live, the orgasm of the culture of the copy and the referential freak, the same ultra-revisionista spirit that makes every two to three us remakes of old classics or blatant plagiarism claiming to pass by the GLib label of the "tribute" or "parody". However, in the case of the two tapes that make up this strange experience, it shows the good Office of this pair of onanistas geeks named Robert Rodriguez and Quentin Tarantino, who to date have not had problems to recognize that his films are pastiches of other films, mosaics impregnated with his personal style and that they allow them to showcase their moviegoers tastes each time that it gives them the win. In this sense, Planet Terror (2007) as Death Proof (2007) are two samples of this trend that is gives so much lately of "Let's play I do _ film" (replace the blank space by any genre that want). The difference is that, contrary to most of those who have participated in this re - re-recycling of past ideas, these types know what they want to achieve and (most importantly) how to achieve this. See 'Planet Terror', one of the first things that come to mind is the second half of open until dawn (1996), film that (confess) has always seemed to me a tape of the heap whose excessive cult not ever understand. However, on this occasion, at being free of his colleague Tarantino style and with carte blanche to develop a history of zombies to your tastes, Robert Rodriguez has been rid of the ballast that inhibited his previous story of vampires, to get to gloat in this absurd that both abounds in his filmography and offer a correct display of cinematic sources that has earned. And it is that almost everything in Planet Terror takes the Viewer to a reference or allusion to which no choice but to receive with open arms. Those who read this know (obviously) that the iconic image of the film, the go-go dancer on the leg of submachine gun, is the female complement to the figure of Ash, the hero of the Evil Dead 2 (1987) facing the undead with a chainsaw attached to the stump of his mutilated hand, but that is only the tip of the iceberg: here from the minimalist music style John Carpenter to passages taken directly from Lucio Fulci or George Romero, without of course forgetting that range of characters as likeable as absurd (the go-go dancer with aspirations of comedian, the sadistic anesthesiologist, the mercenary with the jar full of human testicles, the demented Kangaroo twin or that fearless villain played by a priceless Bruce Willis with knob). These references, however, are not simple filling: are the soul of the film (1).And it is that if we add to that the technical deficiencies intentionally incorporated into the tape, we realize that Robert Rodriguez has gone for all in its segment of Grindhouse, creating not only an experience the sea of entertaining, but also one of its more round films, regardless of their similarities or not with a film phenomenon that we only know of ear (without wanting to sound pedantic)(, I believe that it is necessary to remember that both I and 90 percent of the people who read these lines is too young to have witnessed this type of shows).It is likely that after an hour and a half of footage, the excesses of Robert Rodriguez can be somewhat cansones. In the same way, it is likely that the continual allusions to other cult films complete bored spectators on average, but it is because we are talking about a tape that is simply not designed for that kind of Viewer. As all private joke, Planet Terror is only valid within his tight circle of freak, and only a spectator to abandon any cynicism at the gate can enjoy jokes, the incogruencias, the chaotic Assembly, casposos dialogues and that distilled blood for comic effect. The new creature from Robert Rodriguez may not be for everyone, and can also be very far (in my opinion) deserve the enthronement which has been given months before your arrival, but there is no denying that it is one of the more enjoyable this season premieres, and by far.(1) There is a scene which for me sums it up very well: is the time in which one of the military (not coincidentally played by Quentin Tarantino), after seeing on TV a fragment of this pillar of the "sexplotación" prison called Women in individualizing (1971), decides to rape the girls that keeps prisoners, and interestingly enough you can see in the monitor of to the side. Without much effort, this scene shows much of the explotativo spirit of the Grindhouse experience.</body>
</review>
