<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="28 semanas después" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fresnadillo faces the challenge of continuing a product and not only exalts but which enriches it, fleeing from the typical winks of cinema of terror and, in particular, viscera and blood.</summary>
	<body>His optics has led him to relate the craving of beings infected with a lethal virus, a drama that comes from afar. The principle of a catastrophe has resumed, but we warned, then we fall the trickle: is not suitable for all tastes, much less if we talk about the most refined. It is true that to withstand the footage from this film, still closing their eyes, should be stomach, but who likes cinema with rhythm, the scares and the epidemiological Court, that it can "enjoy".End of 2001, unbroken gave the surprise: a script with substance, a methodical implementation and actors like Monica Lopez and Leonardo Sbaraglia, dancing to the sound that made them a novel director. He did not know, but it wouldn't take long for the eyes of the iconoclast Danny Boyle setting in an orchestra conductor that same introduces us to the more hard rock that delights us with sounds of new age and avoids the hackneyed clichés of the horror film, since the 1970s, aimed at a teen consumption.Only he could take charge of a catastrophic history raised from Vertigo, verismo and rhythm of music video. Copyright terror is what this filmmaker, dignifying the sown field of sequels, handled the technical and hovers more blockbusters to the tops of own label and quality. Over 100 minutes nonetheless amazed studied aerial photography of London, at every level of the immensity of the vacuum, the anxiety warns us. And it is just one example of what you get, without going into parallels with the reality and apocalyptic visions of what awaits us.It was stalwart of 28 days later (released in 2002), and it shows devotion to not massacre its essence, something imposed on the other hand. Is true that already the first part, original, original, reportedly was not. Just take a look at titles in series B already classics like the night of the Comet and the last living man on Earth. From that premise, we can already launch us to praise this unpleasant exercise, excessive, disconcerting, and I stick to the consequences, more than convincing in his thesis.It is true that costs you close history or perhaps not be raised at any time. That being so, there who had not left open in a manner so blatant, but thank you for not take us for fools, not insults our intelligence as spectators, although it is true that as it progresses the footage loses bellows both momentum and just diluted in pursuit of a resolution so poor as correct.Forgive you the oversights in the script for that search for the truth in what appears more a documentary fiction than a fictional story to use. If we wanted to innovate and bring substance to the horror genre, combined with an excellent soundtrack and flat care that enclose choreographies of the wildest, without forget the cutting Chamber, Juan Carlos Fresnadillo thing has managed. how shot this author a story intimate, without special, with all most effects by hand? We us question after seeing the tone which pervades a so deliberately commercial product. What is more, hopefully the next project carried you a record change to confirm if any remaining doubts, we have one of the brightest eyes of European cinema. Copyright, Yes.</body>
</review>
