<review author="Berto" title="Turistas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film about the dangers of tourism, and that, on the basis of the infamous Hostel, it seems (and I say OK, just seems it) pose a social critical minimum to American tourists.</summary>
	<body>Production notes say that tourists is the first American production filmed entirely in Brazil. And I say that seen the result, could have been spared the journey, because even the (scarce) portrayed landscapes offset experience.Alex (Josh Duhamel), his sister Bea (Olivia Wilde) are on vacation in Brazil together to her friend Amy (Beau Garrett). On a trip by bus, they suffer an accident and just knowing the Australian prudent (Melissa George), who travels alone, and Londoners Finn (Desmond Askew) and Liam (Max Brown). While waiting for the next bus, they decide to go to a nearby paradise Cove, where Kiko (Agles Steib) will be host, and after a party night, discover that they have been stolen and are lost without clothes and penniless in a strange country.It is not question of going into much greater depth in the plot, but suffice it to say that just falling in all topics of this kind of films, with the exception that this nobody says that "divide us". That Yes, with all the characters well together nor are may exploit the uncomfortable sense of helplessness of a character isolated in a hostile territory.The worst thing is the slowness with which everything develops: the first hour will teach us bikinis and caipirinhas very mixed. And this wouldn't be bad when used to create a future climax, or making something ask the viewer what awaits to the protagonists, but no, not be fooled, that is not the case. Or there is climax and there is no mystery about the fate of the characters, because between dance and bathroom they are already responsible for gutting everything.The greatest skill of the interpreters is look good the swimwear, that's what the director, John Stockwell, was also responsible for jewelry as lethal immersion and on the edge of the waves.In short, a film about the dangers of tourism, and that, on the basis of the infamous Hostel, it seems (and I say OK, just seems it) pose a social critical minimum to American tourists. But I guess that, among the water, alcohol and other fluids, will be quite dissolved.</body>
</review>
