<review author="Berto" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After all these years of rumours and secrets has the wait been worth? Well not much, actually. And not because the movie is bad, or anything, but because it offers exactly the same as we have been seeing for quite some time.</summary>
	<body>Among the details of the IMDB is one amazing: the screenplay began writing in 2003, and became 158 drafts. This gives a sample of the secrecy surrounding the premiere of the film on the Simpsons, as well as unclear which was the plot of the movie, that is one thing to tell a story in 20 minutes, and quite another fill and a half hours of footage.In the end, what we see on the screen is a new gaffe of Homer that this time can cost you dearly to Springfield, to the point that the Government decides to make them disappear from the map. Literally. In addition, because of its continuing stupidity and selfishness, Marge, Bart and Lisa just abandoning Homer, which will have to save not only Springfield, but the unit family. After all these years of rumours and secrets has been worth the wait? Well not much, actually. And not because the movie is bad, or anything, but because it offers exactly the same as we have been seeing for quite some time, and so is not easy to justify the hopes of hundreds of thousands of fans of the yellow family.Somewhat strange is also that mixture between 2-D and 3-D has been used in the recreation of Springfield. While it is logical to take the leap into the film to offer more showy funds and other types of frames and effects, it does not seem to be indicated film to impress the staff with technology.That Yes, we must first of all recognize that there is funny scenes and good jokes, but also a basis of trying to make a punch line in every line of dialogue. And Yes, some criticism to the system marks the House simpsoniana undoubtedly also falls, although in the meantime gag it is easy that is ignore. What draws attention is the lightweight who have here the side (less Flanders, of course), many times they take the chapter of rigour, which although they must check out practically everyone except the dead, the vast majority do not have or phrase that say, as for Smithers or the director Skinner.Pero those who have been worse treaties are the protagonists. Homer is so stupid and clumsy in all that it undertakes, that does not cause a smile, but stupor and even some anger. Bart is far from the Nice thug that we know to become a traumatized child, and Lisa ceases to be the moral vertex of the family and does not have the lowest moment of glory. In general, and knowing that it sounds strange, have caricatured a few cartoons.Although perhaps is being unfair, and what happens in the background is that we already have as "openwork" to the Simpsons, that it is impossible to get them something different to usual, and when you try to do something surprising, it loses some of the vital essence of the characters. But it is inevitable to recall one of the first jokes, we hear in the mouth of Homer: "I am astonished that we have paid for something we can see free on TV". What bad timing chose Homer to be right.</body>
</review>
