<review author="Berto" title="28 semanas después" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It isn't any bombing, or anything you like, doesn't have no cache high actor, but even so it is not bad film, leave it in that is an acceptable movie and quite entertaining.</summary>
	<body>The film that I am going to criticism today is of Terror and is entitled 28 weeks later. The argument trafficking that a severe virus attacks Britain, the virus in question is transmitted by direct contact and transforms the wearer into a kind of zombie bloodthirsty Cannibal (is not really a zombie because technically not dead, but for me are zombies). As result of this virus, the vast majority of the population is exterminated (transformed into zombies), the few survivors remaining, congregate them in a security zone, in quarantine in some neighborhood of London, protected by tight security around the perimeter, this is possible thanks to the army American that it is responsible for protecting survivors and begin reconstruction in a moment in which the virus seems off.The protagonists of the story are part of a family, and events occur in the following way, the children of the marriage, were traveling, the father manages to escape from the attack of the infected leaving women behind and giving the dead. When the children return from the trip and join life decide to circumvent the security measures and go to their old house in search of a picture of his mother, when they arrive at his house discovers that his mother still alive, later discovers that while he is immune to the virus, it takes him inside, so that what they have done is put a "Trojan horse" in the area of protection, from there you can already imagine, infects the husband and breaks the security. Did I not tell you more of the plot, or what happens because fate? the film has no grace. Rather than London could be called Racoon City because reminded me much Resident EvilLa film isn't any bombing, or anything you like, doesn't have no cache high actor, but still isn't bad film, leave it in that is an acceptable movie and quite entertaining, if you have not seen and not see anything in the film to draw you attention toThis film is a good option.</body>
</review>
