<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film lacks a tad more of political incorrectness. But it is what it is. And fun and entreniene, which, in essence, is the main thing.</summary>
	<body>For a long time, those responsible for the Simpsons, is proposing making a feature film with their characters. What's more: both James l. Brooks and Matt Groening, over a long season, denied guided a possible step to the big screen. They should not know that the "never say never again", the phrase that snapped the wife of Sean Connery to this when, in the early 1980s, the Scottish actor returned to embody James Bond figure. And the Simpsons, as Connery did in his day, have finally invade cinema screens around the world with his film: the movie; uppercase (click on this link, the official website, because it has no waste) is not surprising fear, by producers and scriptwriters of one of the best series of the history of television animation, make the leap to the big screen. In fact, they have since 19 seasons in antenna and, initially, because of the success of hearing, not needed any other type of empowerment for your product. It is undeniable that, during a long decade, episodes of the Simpsons were brilliant in almost its entirety. And now, just when the series begins to lose its initial freshness and part of its corrosive force, appears the claimed film.The Simpsons: The movie suffers, largely, of the defects of the latest television deliveries. Its hurtful sense of humor has become more light, acquiring at the same time, a tone more family and intended for all audiences. Even and thus on the tape, there are details that recover that critical and stabbing side that were characterized, as is the case with the initial question that loose Homer Simpson, and from which it arises as to why the viewer attends the film when, from the couch at home, could also enjoy their presence without having to pay. Shortly thereafter, Burt will write his usual punishment in the slate of school: "do not download this movie from Internet".Despite the softer hue, it is not a bad film; just the opposite. Entertainment and fun in abundance. Perhaps too elongated in their final 20 minutes, but full of excellent and unexpected gags. Surrealism and the hooligan spirit come together to offer the viewer moments of great ingenuity. A sarcastic nod to Disney (with included the forest animals) or the relationship that Homer keeps a pig newly adopted, have already become part - own - from the classic and pure delirium simpsoniano right.His argument is unimportant, but alluring. On this occasion has opted for a policy-fanta-fictional story, in which pollution of the planet and furious the clueless President of U.S. intervention.UU. (the own Schwarzenegger occupying the seat of the Oval Hall), could be wiped off the map of the world to the city of Springfield. A terrible tragedy whose solution only lies in the hands of Homer Simpson. Although they may be greasy due to multiple remains of Donuts and burgers.A horny reference to the media now Al Gore and his incovenient truth, and a lot of passages in which totally dominates an enviable sense of the absurd (the antiidiotas barrier installed to prevent the dumping of waste in the River, or the fleeting appearance of a total physical similarity to the Simpsons family), stand out among all kinds of political and social improprietiesat the time saved more than excessive protagonism of Homer and the little (or almost no) exploitation of this unique Gallery of secondary geeks, in the Fund and with the passing of the years, have become the Simpsons a gigantic series.A curious addition to loyal fans of the series (including myself) Although overall, showing unable to overcome the majority of television episodes that they comprised the first seasons. Everytime I remember that chapter in which Homer maintained a priceless conversation with God, I think that the film lacks a tad more of political incorrectness. But it is what it is. And fun and entreniene, which, in essence, is the main thing.In conclusion, allow me to a Council led directly to the restless spectators; those that rise from the Chair with the first letter of the end credits: not to abandon the room until they finish because during them, there is a pleasant surprise for the Simpson family and its large fauna of adepts.</body>
</review>
