<review author="Antoni Messa" title="La noche de los muertos vivientes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The night of the living dead, revolutionized fantasy films and, in particular, opened guidelines for a subgenre as popular as the zombies.</summary>
	<body>George a. Romero, in his film debut with night of the living dead, revolutionized fantasy films and, in particular, opened guidelines for a subgenre as popular as the zombies. Many have been the debtors of the Opera prima New York filmmaker titles. Currently, Billboard, you can find a good example of this in 28 weeks later. 1968 was the year of the premiere of night of the living dead, but to Spain did quite later. Censorship did not see with good eyes the proposal of Rosemary but finally and disguised with the false label of arthouse, ended up showing in some rooms of our country. Very few were theaters that screened, because the so-called art and essay was considered as a rarity and very minority. So only a few españolitos chosen (most of them bearded, gafapastas and a macutito to the shoulder) enjoyed in his day, the zombie cannibalism who both upset the guards of morality and good national practices.For a long time not it reviewed the work of Romero, until that yesterday (at the request of any of you) I was forced to do so. They have to ensure that, in its first viewing (when I was a brat barely afeitaba), struck me in a brutal way. View now, I must admit that, for me, has lost all power and force that had almost 40 years ago. Continue to ensure that night of the living death is a masterpiece, I think it is an incredible misrepresentation. It is true that this is an original film, whose treatment, in his time, mold-breaking and opened new frontiers for other filmmakers and own Rosemary. Nowadays look carefully - due to his pathetic conduct, his chaotic (full of numerous failures of racord) Assembly and their abysmal performances-more than a masterpiece has become a film of destined lovers worship more garbage. It frightens or distracted. Or, at least, who writes this, reviewing it again, supremely bored. There are titles fatal aging, and this (although many them hard to accept it) is one of them.It is indisputable that their home, in which two brothers visit the grave of his father in a solo cemetery, has its charms. A home that, by the way, and through different visions, has been honored on more than one occasion by other filmmakers. The appearance of the first (and disastrous) zombie is successful, while with the happy over the years, it is now laughable rather than terrifying.The idea of enclosing a few types, in a House besieged by zombies (which more picturesque), and in the midst of a solitary forest - a nice nod to the Rio Grande of Howard Hawks-, is your Coif; and more when this closure is hidden inside a small sample of the different social classes who populated North America in those years, without disregarding the sex and race, and at the same time, becoming the only man of color in a hero of strong convictions and a girl heartfelt in a clear precedent for the Linda Blair of the Exorcist (although cutting version and canibal).The accumulated tension with the situation that has created the film from its outset, falls apart completely due to the dialogues that are beginning to keep the accidental inhabitants of the House. True dialogues for sea bream, repetitive, ridiculous and supported, at all times, by actions that always promise (but never initiate) their poorly shaped characters. The weary stubbornness, one of the protagonists, by hiding in the basement rather than attempting a flight to safer places, or exaggerated portrait of a woman played by a strong psychological shock, they point towards scurfy film.I should never return it to see and stay with the good memories that kept her. Certainly a cause of that aforementioned premature ageing of the tape and aware of, at least, keep your film cult, Romero and the co-screenwriter of the same tag, John a. Russo, now 10 years under the guise of celebrating the thirtieth anniversary of its premiere, decided to get down to work and restore a bit of the work. They honed their image and the such Russo, crediting for the occasion as a director, was pulled out of the manga additional a prologue and an epilogue, in which the figure of a priest takes a special role. A few additions that, by the way, still damage more wear on night of the living dead. This, and a few inserts with new zombies, is everything that meant that rather than unnecessary revisitación who passed through screens with more penalty than glory.A special mention is the it deserves one of the multiple editions in DVD run on the original film (which opposed its useless upgrade). Specifically is that released Suevia Films before editing, themselves, a version for collectors (little well, DVD, expect of these people). The used copy is without remaster that brilliantly!, they used a saccade of a spent and battered VHS, full of shredded and grainy image. Dubbing is virtually inaudible (inclasifcables noises and voices off is your brand), while his band is unfortunate by some subtitles, apart from huge and badly translated, are completely outdated audio original anticipation dialogues in a few seconds; developed enough to let the viewer out of orbit. would I have been too bad with night of the living dead? It must be losing respect for the untouchables and the classics without blush is. Bread, bread, and wine, wine. This innovation and the surprise not spent initial (what already is much!). For getting my mouth taste bad, now I will to reconcile with the genre and review dawn of the dead. There is ná!</body>
</review>
