<review author="Bloody Will" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is perhaps the best version that has become of a horror film in the last five years, no doubt the horror film with a capital of the summer</summary>
	<body>Certainly, when a few years ago Wes Craven directed this film, I doubt very much that would be influenced by getting a hit at the box office. Previously, this type of film, fear and bloody, had a very specific audience. Now tries to open the fork as much as possible, so that an adult, as well as a 16 years old kid going gang to the movies to see. The spark that had the original version is lost and becomes a palomitero product for those who has stomach, clear.Of course this version of "The hills have eyes" is infinítamente superior to the version of "The massacre of Texas", and that joke was "The House of wax", here nobody cut hair, and occasionally touches the brutality (Aaron Stanford covered with blood), but that does not make it an essential film. That Yes, is the horror film with a capital of the summer, no doubt.If you like blood to GLUGs, going to enjoy, because here the liquid runs with an extreme joy. The story is easy: ua family en route through the desert to California just by taking a shortcut that takes them to an area inhabited by humans altered by nuclear radiation who only know how to kill, rape or cut each unhappy which is crossed on his way. Well, father, mother, teen, teenage daughter, eldest daughter, husband of eldest daughter and baby make up this pretty absent-minded family as divertimento for such children of his mother. The cast is full of side recurring, such as Aaron Stanford (Pyro of the "X-Men"), Emilie Ravin (Claire from "Lost"), Kathleen Quinlan ("Apollo 13 &#8243;") or Ted Levine ("memoirs of a Geisha"), and at least the director Uwe Boll. It is a stranger Alexandre Aja, which has sweetened the original.There are two minutes of footage the director cut to be able to be rated R in the USA. I would like to know that they will, but probably the DVD will include them as extras. If they are more beasts than some of the scenes of the final Assembly, I prefer not to see them. This movie is not boring, but if disturbing, sometimes unpleasant, but perhaps it is because to be so acosumbrados to versions light and descafeinadas terror productions, has been a success at the box office in the USA. No wonder it is perhaps the best version that has a horror film made in the last five years. Even so, and as I said before, you can avoid running to see her to the cinema and wait its premiere on DVD to get close to a cushion, or even pause to avoid spontaneous indigestion.</body>
</review>
