<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Finally, for enjoyment of the simpsoneros, who are legion, there are film. And fortunately in film we are given the same who in the television series: fun at the expense of ourselves. The fact that the series is already two decades occur is not a mere coincidence, as you can imagine the reader.</summary>
	<body>Finally, for enjoyment of the simpsoneros, who are legion, there are film. And fortunately in film we are given the same who in the television series: fun at the expense of ourselves. The fact that the series is already two decades occur is not a mere coincidence, as you can imagine the reader. Said the classic you can deceive few for a long time, and many for a short time, but you can not fool many for a long time. "The Simpsons" are certainly the most influential series of the history of television, and his humour acid, corrosive, sarcastic, but at the same time tender, human, emotional, it has become popular in several generations of viewers; because it is a serial that also reaches children, adolescents and adults. Moreover, I am of the opinion (do not always shared?) that adults savored more crazed this lower-middle-class family humor and the landscape and form surrounding her.All of this is in "The Simpsons - the movie": criticism of the established powers (do with this President Schwarzenegger which is descacharrante nothing more than the mere enunciation that could reach such a high judiciary; of course, after seeing George w. Bush to serve in such a position, anything is possible: maybe even Schwarzzie does it better?), messing about citizensboth high cradle and low bed (do heaven, look like Cecilia?), distribution of tow right and left, without anyone to be saved. And all this with the frantic rhythm of any of the great nearly 400 chapters so far manufactured by the calenturientos brains of Matt Groening and company. I said: a joy.</body>
</review>
