<review author="El vengador toxico" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I have to say that Interestingly the film reminds me the evolution of the series. Begins dramatically and has a very bright part, for ir decaying as it approaches the end.</summary>
	<body>Because finally they made the film in the series that revolutionized the world of animation. We already know what often happens with movies series, giving rise to such magnificent movies such as X-files, the Avengers, lost in space? where have the Simpsons been?I've been fan of Simpsons since almost 20 years ago cast the first episode in the 2 to that of eleven and peak of the night. But it is also true that over the years has been declining, and fails to maintain the high level of the first four or five seasons.So I had all my reservations about the film, is at the beginning? It will be in the end? It will be worse?I have to say that Interestingly the film reminds me the evolution of the series. Begins dramatically and has a very bright part, for ir decaying as it approaches the end.The movie begins in a cinema, where the Simpsons come to see the last premiere of "Rasca y Pica" (his favorite drawings) and where Homer says that all those who do not see the pirated movie at home are fooled. At the moment we see the classic start of modified Simpsons, Bart copying on the Blackboard that not pirateará the movie!.In this first part really is distilled a good dose of acidity, which reminds us of those first seasons. The plot focuses on the large contamination of Lake Springfield, and as Homer manages to put his invaluable help to the disaster.I have seen the movie at 6 in the afternoon at a shopping mall surrounded by teenagers who just pillaban any fairly elaborate joke. I think that I was the only one who has laughed in the first scene with the President of the USA. That, in the second part, no longer endured more and were commenting on where would go to the exit. I will not see a taquillazo at meeting of teenagers, I will not see a taquillazo at meeting of teenagers, I will not see a taquillazo in?From the moment, as we approach the denouement, the film loses ingenuity starts, becomes more friendly and directs us towards a happy ending. It is true that the episodes of the Simpsons have just almost always, but in this case quite mordacidaz is lost.Anyway, I think that any fan of the Simpsons, for the film is justified by those first 45-60 minutes.</body>
</review>
