<review author="Plissken" title="Planet Terror" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Rodriguez has a brutal budget (and takes it), and although work on make a bad movie, just leaving a hilarious "qualité" macarrada.</summary>
	<body>Beginning of the film: as a reaction to the foolish trailer for 'Machete', several loud sound from every corner of the room. Ten minutes of projection of 'Planet Terror': some people start to stir in their seats to nibble their glasses of soda or nailing killer looks to her partner, probably responsible for that are seeing that piece of garbage instead of the of the Bourne that. Half an hour of 'Planet Terror' screening: six or seven couples leave room between arcades and looks of disgust to the rest of the attendees.I love when a filmmaker achieves its purpose.Robert Rodriguez honors with 'Planet Terror' his particular casposas movies from zombies, on the one hand, and the action movies of bottom shelf video store, on the other. And it is all a look greenish, crappy, crappy so that it knows to be part of this project called 'Grindhouse' which, unfortunately, has not worked as the Weinstein Bros.. They hoped. But in my opinion, not needed: 'Planet Terror' is a magnificent film casposa luxury, to the chagrin of the absent-minded summer Viewer.The synopsis can be behind any Record Vision cover (thinking they were those who brought 'Reservoir Dogs' Spain) or one of these movies of the Cannon: "A mysterious plague threatens the quiet existence of a small Texan town. '"The Wray', a mysterious trucker, and Cherry Darling, an explosive go-go dancer, are the last hope for the terrified inhabitants. "Draining corpses, action and explosions in abundance in a film that you will not forget!"Thus, Rodríguez manages a great divertimento soaked gore's references to the genre, but with a shade more eighties than setentero: starting with the parade of old glories ("Grass cutter" Jeff Fahey, Michael Biehn "Terminator", Carlos "El Mariachi" Gallardo, Cheech Marin.) and continuing with the badass tone "Delta Force" at its beginning. Later, the zombie gore takes over the narration between funny lapidary phrases, mutilation and explosions without ton haphazardly; and in its final stretch, the delirium of the paramilitary plot and the myth of the flight of the few survivors to paradise lost. All this between buckets and buckets of blood, pus, and other fluids. And Furthermore, a couple really charismatic protagonist (magnetic Rose McGowan and Freddy Rodríguez) and a brilliant Marley Shelton, even on the edge of absurdity. 'Planet Terror' doesn't offer neither more nor less than the same already offered 'The Bronx warriors', 'The day of the dead' or any of those small new posts of late 1970s and early 1980s: action, blood and a free sex scene. What happens is that Rodriguez has a brutal budget (and take advantage of it), and although work on make a bad movie, just coming out a hilarious "qualité" macarrada.</body>
</review>
