<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Ratatouille" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This episode is exemplary and emotional, cinematically splendid, denotes one technical virtuosity of both</summary>
	<body>Good animated film, directed by the Director of the great "The Incredibles".Here I am not sure that will be able to both crítico-comercial success, but what doubt can be achieved one very disftutable tape, full of good gags and successful dialogues, filled with teachings positive universal as the attempt of overcoming of a humano.o rodent, trust between them or to work that one you love, friendship and love, above all, and continuing with the tradition, the love of the family, that despite differences in criteria among its members, is always a sure to be helped in penalties resource.Perhaps is somewhat long, especially for children, as I could see, not enough patience (the smallest) to endure a story that departs from the simplicity and the easy and forgettable gag.It is imaginative, agile, humorous and dramatic elements, but not stop them, fortunately. Because the playful aspect is that prevails throughout the footage with a psychological path of the characters well measured and studied, as well as a virtuoismo in the layout of the drawing, where the funds they acquire their own life.Perhaps, paradoxically, the best happens in its first third, just prior to the protagonist comes to the restaurant. Family life, Amen from attempts to steal food in the House of a snowing are prodigious in his comical. Everything that happens in the restaurant, then is regular in the rhythm, but never bored or ceases to be interested.That is why that "Ratatouille" is, in my opinion, a very estimable tape of animation, that like and does have a very enjoyable time, with a few last minutes, the preparation and delivery to the hard crírtico of cuisine, the plate surprise asked and which will depend on the future of the restaurant. This episode is exemplary and emotional, cinematically splendid. denoting a virtuosity and emotional técnicocomo, which goes directly to the heart.</body>
</review>
