<review author="Torbe" title="300" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>These flat primerisimos of the mouth, this naked torso, these pucheritos and painted eyes say very little of a great Chief and much of a mad marica with wanting to be God on Earth. But in that would be thinking the stylists of the movie?</summary>
	<body>I have been seeing the name 300 movie, they say has devastated in the USA. Based on a comic book by Frank Miller, the movie is much better than the comic, according to my opinion. Many things have drawn me attention, and among the more notable this mariconeria that says goodbye to the movie from beginning to end. This gayer of fashion worldwide, and the caricature of the Persian king Xerxes has been the more Mario-frik, who has been in the film in years.These flat primerisimos of the mouth, this naked torso, these pucheritos and painted eyes say very little of a great Chief and much of a mad marica with wanting to be God on Earth. But in that would be thinking the stylists of the movie?And the parade of guys with bellies as a tablet of Nestle? Will be because little, eat only one block in the movie, because but that tell me how it is possible today to be so fine. With so much ice cream and hamburger cerda neither of coña. How difficult is to be as I am, with this tummy so well looked after and redondita, my years of eating well has cost me, children.ATTENTION joke: I believe that these guys were not of Sparta were Basque, because they spent all day saying: Agur! Agur! Agur!EXPLANATION of the joke for LOS corto:Agur means goodbye in Basque. In other words, is flashed from the Persians, because going them to kill.Or maybe the Basque comes from the Spartan? Not what, but none saw with txapela.(hey that happens, in the comedy club release worst jokes and the barque of insubstantial is rie.) (Be that emborrachan them before?)The movie? I liked it much, is not beating, you becomes in a santiamen, except where the wife of the prota, that only worthwhile when fucks the bad by UNAs magnificus goes, the rest is bla bla bla.It is dramatic, does not give you time to think, and everything seems a larghissimo seasoned video for several TV commercials. The voiceover resembles the voice announcements of cars, and in many times you loose the frasecita and it seems that you are seeing a fucking car advertisement.This is the picture that represents that battle in the thermopiles, and as you can see, the Spartans would in balls all day, thing which does not reflect the movie because but the ladybugs are already mad at all accepted.And videoclipero this very MTV, mola roll at the beginning especially when riding the free-for-all, that you put the batteries with this music that resembles a Prodigy. Sugarcane to the fullest.Anyway, I see that this movie, in addition to abuse the videoclipero roll and TV ads saying what magnificent are the Spartans (when in fact, in the past, the guys were very dull), it copies too Gladiator. There is a map in the end where this the aunt in the wheat field which have even gotten the same music that comes out in Gladiator!What's going on? Not you can do something different?And fights with caretas, the slow motion is very similar to the Kingdom of heaven, another movie by Ridley Scott, as a Gladiator has been copied to the extenuacion."" Photo of the original Xerxes, nothing to do with the mad that appears in the movie releasing this hint of "my subjects can't imagine what I can do with them" general laughter in the cinema.Anyway not I be victimized by these comments, the movie this very well, I recommend it, you can see, no great shit as usually in this kind of movies, and hooked from beginning to end. It is a spectacle for the eyes, there are a thousand details and incredible technique of the image. Today, the two best action movies are this and Apocalypto. Not you the you must lose, hamijos, who are very well.</body>
</review>
