<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Los 4 Fantásticos y Silver Surfer" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The fantastic four and Silver Surfer is the perfect film for the summer. Without another claim that entertain. No other address than the obvious.</summary>
	<body>The narrative solvency of movies Marvel not adheres to century canons nor considered among its virtues fundancionales the please large segments of the audience. Their aesthetic concerns nor require the more ponderous (and perhaps leaden seal) intervention of a film buff gourmet to understand the message, put by case. Here there is no message or grilling cinéfago concerns. The high segment of the audience, already talludito staff, may refrain: won't get lost absolutely nothing. Singer, Raimi and Nolan have set the standard Marvel at high altitude, but there is still a well nourished payroll filmmakers unpretentious (Story) that only comply with the order and billed a spectacular product - is not difficult in the times in which we live – and simple consumption.The fantastic four and Silver Surfer is the perfect film for the summer. It's bringing together a gang of kids and give them a generous helping of superheroes and sidereal call. Looked at this way, the film is exemplary: not lost in ramblings on the loneliness of the hero, not enfanga his amenísimo speech with reflections on the goodness of the human being. The plot is shipped in a plisplás: nothing needless and nothing is lacking, as in a good film of Frank Capra. Honest and direct, therefore.The emotional and psychological contrasts of other Heroes (Spider-man, Batman, X-men) are here omitted deliberately from the libretto. Do not have to bear the statutory introduction: we know who each one and how is spent. So the plot starts more or less quickly and we enjoy (Yes) with a predictable, infantiloide and majestic avalanche of special effects. I don't think that anyone with some fingers in front look in this summer device aimed at something more oblivion. If the intervention of Stela Plateada/Silver Surfer, add you to this benign accumulation of Visual sweets because honey on pancakes, saying my grandmother. If the gentle reader was fan of the stories of Stan Lee and Jack Kirby has insured the entertainment. When you want to take a bath of purity, sure that will know where to go and what spiritual balsams take to comfort his sagging composure.</body>
</review>
