<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good movie, quite hard for most, which meets the expectations and that rises above the rest of remakes and genre films</summary>
	<body>Again comes another remake, although I have to say on this occasion had many eager to see the proposal by Alexandre Aja, the trailer for "the hills have eyes" gave a very positive sense and gave us hopes of seeing a film that we kept in tension and that was not a mere commercial product that seized the pull of the original. Because once vista, I can confirm my sensations, since the proposal of this French director is a great film that will delight fans to this type of product. While it is true that the original Wes Craven I liked a lot, I have to say I don't remember too much, as the years pass, so I will leave the comparisons for when has more fresh. Taking the new version as the only, Aja presents an argument that we may be familiar, as it tells the trip of an American family trying to reach California, across the desert, decided to follow the advice of a villager and take a shortcut. From this moment that attractive Road will become his greatest nightmare, as they will have an accident and instead of aid will come another type of service. Do you sound argument, no? If the family we replaced her with a group of friends, will have the history of "The Texas Chainsaw Massacre", "Km 666", "House of wax" and a long etcetera. This approach comes strengths who plays Aja, among which includes a portrait of the characters, and above all a mise en scene very own, maintain the tension and transmit us unpleasant which is the situation they are experiencing and his impotence. One of the best sequences is the first serious attack on the caravan, in which Aja shows almost all the harshness and brutality of the situation, I do not know if by the uproar that could mount and if it is illegal, came me to mind another apex of evil that could have elevated a degree over the madness of the situation. After this sequence characters have to enter more action and try to resolve the difficulties and challenges that have arisen.Aesthetics, music, effects, locations and others is something that have been able to choose very rightly, that introduces us to this unhealthy, dusty world that was created after the nuclear tests. Not everything is outstanding because there are actions of the characters are somewhat absurd and even ridiculous, rub the cliché, and that do raise the intelligence of the American people (in this case), because they decide to do things that no one will, even when in such situations as atrocious. In short a good movie, quite hard for most, which meets the expectations and that rises above the rest of remakes and genre films that abound both on our boards lately. Finally say that they are already preparing the second part, which will be another new revision that Wes Craven was in 1985.</body>
</review>
