<review author="Bruji" title="La noche de los muertos vivientes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A cult movie and an excellent example of how to create fears without means, while the story continues under the opening credits...</summary>
	<body>Today will see the ingredients that make up, no longer a simple masterpiece, but nothing less than "a cult film", which is different.Firstly, the absence of money (the budget is practically non-existent), is supplied with multi-faceted staff which, moreover, has clever free time, good friends and relatives.In the absence of professional actors, who can not pay, requests please the wife of one of the producers, a school teacher and a burly truck driver. None of them had experience in film, theatre, or student comedies, and none of them returned to make a film. That Yes, the lead role offers a true actor Duane Jones, an unknown absolute, embarked on this project to make debut in the film. Both liked the experience, which would not be gender, reducing his filmography characters related to the world of the living dead and the vampiric creatures of the night.This is also the first feature film for the director. George Romero comes from advertising, and exploits the situation to ask photographer, screenwriter and film editor. For its part, the producers become supporting actors, make-up artists and sound technicians. They receive no salary, but all the members of the technical and artistic team (uncles, cousins, friends), obtained the promise that "you charge if the tape of manners works at the box office". One aspect that does the Distributor, the Continental, which invests a sum of money derisory in to introduce it.Chocolate syrup (the picture is in black and white), organ meats you buy to a butcher and the dollar that is paid to the extras (they are so few, that enough time to become familiar with all of them), do the rest. And that begins with love, shot on weekends and holidays, is revealed as the benchmark of hundreds of filmmakers; history with which many film buffs fall in love of the genre.Is true that the tape contains rabbits that give to write a book. The car without key in the contact that moves along a path to take three curves without any problem, do not block the flyers in these situations?. Do the same car who ends his adventure passing by a tree? that not touches - to declare sinister altogether, or blood that it comes on the back of a zombie that has shot up front, without that appreciation of the impact of the bullet in his chest. Clear that, it is likely that the "blood of the zombies" (good title for another movie) to flow differently.But true is also that it has memorable frames, unforgettable scenes that will be repeated endlessly in the following years horror movies. The fixed level which encompasses a tortuous road that approaching the protagonists, clear premonition that evil awaits them (Jeepers Creepers); the flight of Barbara (the massacre of Texas, Friday, 13); the psychological evolution of the protagonist (Scream); the truck surrounded by "stuff" hungry of viscera (which they bought the butcher); the explosion that is reflected in the faces of the actors (the debutante and producer); the close-up rolling camera in hand, paradigms of the facts unleashed after (impressive which reproduced the recipient of radio, the tombstone, the fuel pump).With a political background of acid criticism of the career of nuclear weapons, an unusual abundance of imagination, intelligent dialogues, and a dash of extraordinary composition that warns of the consequences of interference in alien wars ("the deceased, by dear sean, would funeral, not being more than dead and dangerous meat"), night of the living dead is an excellent example of how to create fears without mediaWhile the story continues under the closing credits.</body>
</review>
