<review author="José A. Peig" title="El caso Bourne" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Simply put: the visualization of Liman isn't at the height of a story that requires a greater psychological penetration. Although handled very well the tempos and the suspense, it is evident that there is a certain imbalance between form and substance, between what the content offered and the representation of the same.</summary>
	<body>The Bourne Identity is the excuse to delve into the mythology of the espionage film, the character played by Matt Damon here represents the paradox of the common man which is doomed to spiral of frames, mysteries, ins and outs of an apparatus of power serving openly and without that nobody can give explanations. Amnesia is an opportunity to break with the past. The Doug Liman film is a trip to the encounter with himself through the exorcism of the demons that lurk in the interior and abroad: the interiority of lost memories and doubt in a crucial moment that determines the last decision, and an exteriority populated by executing men of death as hidden automata in secrecy.The CIA is the omniscient quasi which seems to control it all, a myth deployed with remarkable scenery and characterization: solitary and armed men who expect the time to kill according to plans that only a few know. Ignorance of Bourne, daughter of amnesia, is a phenomenon parallel to the ignorance of the own ringleaders of the conspiracy, one of them, in the end, also become puppet who handled a macabre game.Alleged ambiguous tonality of the story part of a clever premise, but the visual execution and development do not exceed a routine procedure that ultimately results in a thriller of conventional scheme and situations subject to the clichés of the genre. Simply put: the visualization of Liman isn't at the height of a story that requires a greater psychological penetration. Although handled very well the tempos and the suspense, it is evident that there is a certain imbalance between form and substance, between what the content offered and the representation of the same.Some action scenes wield an unnecessary dramatic, sometimes the story becomes too predictable, when not inane because of the inability of the Narrator to offset the iterative scheme narration (set the reader as throughout the film just happens much more than always the same: búsqueda-desencuentro - search-misunderstanding-búsqueda-desencuentro.) with a progressive depth and penetration in the psychological drama.However, we are dealing with a very decent, entertaining film, it has a couple of very well filmed action scenes and, anyway, you can not disappoint fans of the genre, especially for those nostalgic for those setenteras movies about espionage in the cold war. Circumscribed the scope of cinema as art (the only area that interests us here), just a too warm, although correct and entertaining film, and when you encounter the dreaded cliches so abundant in a specific genre like this, do it with some dignity.</body>
</review>
