<review author="JLO" title="Juana la loca" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The anecdote is depleted quickly, telling the comings and goings of the couple continued infidelities of the Prince and the ninfómano of her character, making excessive the 117-minute.</summary>
	<body>Spanish film of time based on the life of the infanta Juana, daughter of the Catholic monarchs and owner of a controversial history not favored by the official story, but the director's compassionate eye makes immediately feeling sympathy for her.It all starts in Laredo, year 1496 and her journey to Flanders for arranged marriage with who would be known later as Philip the handsome. So far strictly historical because the film does not focus on the political side of the story (which is rather complex) but on loving and tumultuous relationship between the two protagonists. And here is failure of the film because the story dries quickly, telling us the comings and goings of the couple continued infidelities of the Prince and the ninfómano of her character, making excessive the 117-minute saved only by actions couples of all the cast, although most of them with figurative characters, rescuing the role of right-hand of Philipstarring Giuliano Gemma.Nos shows a Joan with an anachronistic character women from their surroundings, with an excessive rebellion, a good mother despite being Queen and their occupations (died his mother and older brothers taking charge of the Kingdom of Castile), with a few sickly jealousy towards her husband highlighted Moreover, justified that Yes, that make it touching the mental illness easily gaining the nickname of crazy by all the people.The love triangle (one of many) complements it "preferred" King Philip, an exotic dancer with taste by black magic, that triggers the end of him as the film itself. Interpretative force of Pilar López de Ayala (Juana) would already make from alone one worthy of the film bears see.Mature, somewhat misogynist, guided with ex officio by Vicente Aranda (lovers, El Lute) with more than 20 films under his belt, but that it is too slow, mammoth, sinning of pretentious in some respects. That Yes, a reconstruction of remarkable time to confirm the reason for the nomination by Spain Oscar with this film, knowing the weakness of hollywood towards this type of genre.</body>
</review>
