<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Snake eyes (Ojos de serpiente)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There is no harmony between image and content. It is not a very good movie because it disregards the plot and the emphasis in the marvelous, Yes, elegant and addictive collection of images from the master of Palma.</summary>
	<body>In the unlikely event that someone had the idea of doing a remake of Snake Eyes, am almost predict a resounding thud, a now it more than likely disaster of foreseeable consequences. What happens is that Brian de Palma is an amazing director and knows his craft as sufficiently well enough to compensate for the narrative shortcomings with a prodigious operation of the camera or a hypnotic dance of absolutely disturbing scenes. It does not move us go advance the plot but the muscled choreography montage. Does not absorb us the interpretation of its cast (do Nicolas Cage is last lap, above all in the first twenty or twenty-five minutes and Gary Sinise is reckless, as alien to what? little - that is cooked) or nor the brilliance of the story but the syncopated chained of situations and environments that leave you, in the armchair, violated, given to this massive mess that it is not possible to exit without any wound in self-esteem or consideration alien.That David Koepp (do Jurassic Park, Carlito? s way, the war of the worlds, the next Spider-man or the next Indy) firm fiasco does not exonerate the signatories. The plot is simple, has no hook and is denying itself until you reach a final disastrous, unworthy of what we saw in the fantastic start of the film.The technique to return to recount events already occurred and, therefore, seen, but housed in another point of view (viva Tarantino) advises the trend of De Palma to become pure ego kept in an exercise of personal statement engolosina by its visual proposal - histrionic, effervescent, Baroque - but decaying his films by his (occasionally) disinterest in literary.We are left with priceless images (those first minutes so highly recommended or the vibrant persecution of a girl by the two protagonists from a room of a casino to the adjoining hotel room). Also with a magnificent soundtrack (Sakamoto). After: I tedio, deception, that feeling of bittersweet have had a good meal, but be sure that digestion is going to be complicated. Nevertheless, this chronicler enjoyed with the eloquence of the images, with its plasticity boredom-proof.</body>
</review>
