<review author="José A. Peig" title="El mito de Bourne" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do it is a trick very used by mediocre filmmakers: when there is no visual imagination, nor a history to play with truly original and significant elements, put him cane to the viewer with a music video? televisero? and you'll be foolishly while she devours the cone of popcorn.</summary>
	<body>Paul Greengrass directs this continuation to the history of the amnesiac spy, who in a new cycle of enigmas and persecutions focuses its investigations in order to understand and know his true past and the true reasons for the secret operation of the CIA, marinated with the theme of revenge and reconciliation through the knowledge of the truth. Bourne is an alma en pena has already begun a desperate race to nowhere, prisoner of the manipulation that he himself helped to keep.In film you he cannot forgive the repetition of a previous scheme with the same essential content and, above, reducing the quality of stylistic resources. The film does not really have anything that was not already implicit in its precedent, and limited its objective to develop a bland plot which just moved up from the first to the last level. The confused man who wakes up at his home in the India in primeas them images, is the same man confusing that rambles through the streets of New York, leaving patent vacuous narration and blatant stretching of a product exclusively designed to entertain with spectacular scenes of action and some timely point of effective suspense. The protagonist spends the entire film fleeing, and the rest, they pursue him and conniving depending on a plot that deals with politics and corruption in the oil companies. Worst of all is that the Viewer already knows who is the "bad", in advance, and the other characters, such as hierarchical characterization and flat, just provide a counterpoint or some life to the springs of the predictable script. If outside, we also have the bad direction of Greengass, with excess of close-up, use and abuse of antitheses, zoom and sudden twists of the camera, style sloppy videoclip. I.e., everything in this movie is intended by and for the "theatrical", not for the benefit of a narrative and constructive effectiveness of an emotional state or specific tone in keeping with the theme that aims to address. It is a trick very used by the mediocre filmmakers: when there is no visual imagination, nor a history to play with truly original and significant elements, put him cane to the viewer with a video clip "televisero" and you'll be foolishly while she devours the cone of popcorn (added the role of a repetitive soundtrack you are looking for a well known from psychology effect)() aimed at, literally, "Captivate" the Viewer. Then leave the film and commented that the film is good.Finally, worst things say.</body>
</review>
