<review author="José A. Peig" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will be to understand cinema lovers as an art, for those who are tired of old roads and the dramatic visual treatment as not creative, is a hodgepodge of which better flee as he runs away from a plague.</summary>
	<body>Look at what we have become. The search for Bourne and a trilogy about the origin and identity compressed in a format of action / spy film, ends with this phrase three films to tell almost the same thing three times, with which we have one of the products more blatantly stiffs who have been. When we arrived at the "the end", the joke is so irritating as predictable. In fact, we have one of the worst in the history of film Trilogies.The story itself offers nothing original, and this is particularly striking in the last minutes of a tape that had close the circle with a grade higher or complementary to already exposed in his two preceding, and not return to reiterate the implicit ideas, because what you do is say verbatim what they already knew (what I knew any spectator that has provided a minimum of attention). If the schematic had already mella in the previous installment, here is a ' fundamental problem: all scenes of action - "here you hide and you get here", "you think I'm there but I'm here", etc. - they are exactly the same, the writers always use the same structure to design situations, and the only purpose is the create spectacular scenes depicted with the bombastic pulse of the camera by Paul Greengrasswhich gives rise to a purely dramatic visual impact devoid of authentic sense of narrative; a narrative is set with the pace of new emotional and/or ideological States on the characters, or with the discovery of new data binding to reinterpret the byways or motives underpinning the history. I.e., that each sequence devised establish a progression on the previous.There are many ways to build a narrative, but what we cannot do is confined to a chain of scenes to each one more spectacular and extensive (look at how action sequences, are stretched symptom course that the writers do not know what address the footage), and let the information essential for the last ten minutes. And above, to know what already we knew. Some filmmakers and writers need someone explain to narrate is to synthesize and make progress towards the outcome, not on disperse and outlined.In short, and if what it is looking for a bit of entertainment, the film can satisfy fans of the genre. It will be to understand cinema lovers as an art, for those who are tired of old roads and the dramatic visual treatment as not creative, is a hodgepodge of which better flee as he runs away from a plague.</body>
</review>
