<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Planet Terror" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fun, sparkling, very entertaining and enjoyable horror film, in charge of the overheated imagination of Robert Rodriguez, who get a film very entertaining and above all, very well done here.</summary>
	<body>Its special effects are perfect and combines in his desmadrado but at the same time careful script, action, horror, humor, and much, much gore. Under a very careful rickety aesthetic, where the colors are altered, the screen dancing happily, the stripes appear everywhere and screen appears it will explode at any time. That Yes, the sound is great.The revelry begins before the movie, with this false (I think) trailer for "Machete", alleged upcoming Robert Rodriguez movie, starring one of their conditional "Danny Trejo" who only see the mug one will put the hairs as hooks. A sparkling trailer full of explosive violence.And respect to "Planet terror", then that, that contains everything that a viewer of the so-called of popcorn, which in essence we are almost all, you may like: much movement, rampant action, beautiful and great girls and sex scenes, that in this case we cannot see in its entirety because as we stated at the time: we're sorry but we need this stuff. At the very moment in which the screen (like when we were kids and we often happened in intimate theaters neighborhood that good film buffs were regulars) is burned.But has more positive characteristics, as being little by little to see various friendly performers, heroes of yesteryear series Bs, as Jeff Fahey, Michael Parks.En end, that I I had frankly well, although it is not round, because in my opinion it is somewhat repetitive sometime, for example when, precisely, is it inserted the protagonist the famous machine gun in the stump of his right leg. They are a lot action moments, explosions everywhere and heavy fire, but as say something repetitive. Anyway, all very well done. There are also excellent, although something foul scenes, such as the attempted rape to the protagonist.</body>
</review>
