<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What could have been a product of Hollywood without pretensions and moderately entertaining as the original, turns into one film action.</summary>
	<body>Before fully entering the analysis of the film, let's spend a moment to talk about these small pieces that largely determine the success or failure of a film: the trailers. Most of them are extremely false, and that of the Bourne Ultimatum is no exception. Less usual is seen in them blunders as speaking in the South of Europe, is quoted London and Tangiers, which is not even a European city, and instead omit Madrid, which by the way is the most southern European city of all those listed.Leaving aside this small claim, the Bourne Ultimatum is the final chapter of one of the most profitable action Trilogies in recent years. On this occasion, the Viewer is witness to the investigations and inquiries carried out Jason Bourne by half the world for (at last, and it was time) find their true identity and recover his memory. What could have been a product of Hollywood without pretensions and moderately entertaining as the original, turns into one film more action, the lot. And it is that the Bourne Ultimatum is full of clichés, and most of the plot is easily predictable. The duration of the film is clearly excessive, and Paul Greengrass fails to print enough intensity, doing that whole lost packaging and interest. The action scenes are well saved, although occasionally being shot camera shoulder lift headache. All this leads to a forced, absurd and predictable outcome that will leave outraged fans of Bourne. The highlights of the film is the presence of great actors like David Strathairn, Albert Finney and Glenn.El Scott Bourne Ultimatum is another of so many action films Hollywood, entertaining to the most enthusiastic of the genus, and that puts an end to one of the most popular sagas of these years. Or at least we hope so.</body>
</review>
