<review author="Bloody Will" title="Los 4 Fantásticos y Silver Surfer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The fantastic four and Silver Surfer? It is the definitive adaptation of a comic paper to the screen: easy script, recklessness plot, special effects proper and not suitable for lovers of the deep characters. Do to my I jumped the tears?</summary>
	<body>We have here another big bet of the Marvel after?Spider-Man 3 &#8242;, and another controversial no doubt. Authentic frightens write opinions on this kind of movies because it joins same and film buff tastes, and it matters little whether you like Ford western, the visual impact of Tim Burton or the drama of Aronofski, that if you give superheroes to navigate you stay stunned. Of course, there are superheroes and superheroes but since that Singer and Raimi auparan mutants and newspaper to the heavens the rest is target of fierce criticism.Do I assume my own contradictions: could see?Daredevil? other two hundred times more and vomitaría if I find it again?Ghost Rider? on my way. So I do not do case if you prefer, but as a staunch fan of the comics of?The 4 F? Since that did not exceed the meter of height?The fantastic four and Silver Surfer? It is the definitive adaptation of a comic paper to the screen: easy script, recklessness plot, special effects proper and not suitable for lovers of the deep characters. Do to my I jumped the tears?Do if we went to the archives of the comic, and look at these numbers of? the f 4? pre-John Byrne will see that the scripts weren't anything out of this world, where everything is explained and repeated a hundred times, where Johnny a.k.a. torch was very cool, the thing only delivered firewood and villains fell with astonishing ease after some inventito pulled out at the last minute. The film is a calco and only missing Alba and Gruffrudd leaving the sandwiches of the mouth with the scarce three phrases that pronounced. But that's small change introduced by this sequel to its predecessor, and is that if someone thought that the director intended to something serious to take the film to this family with superpowers, and was a tremendous disappointment, the sequel should be very prepared: this is A movie for children, of n-I - N-O-S!, not an essay about solitude because of stone, or the emotional catharsis involved burn in flames being sad and far less inconvenience to extend your body sometimes.Tim Story has decided not to be influenced by the line followed by many directors to take cinema superheroes always. Does Singer began providing to the?X-Men? of intensity in which combined action of Exchange supergolpes with loneliness and concerns of beings who were discriminated against for being different. Do is opening the door for Joss Whedon ended in shape permanently to the patrol X in the excellent collection?Astonishing X-Men?. Do after this, Singer went to?Superman? and it afforded the same clear and shadows with the unconditional love of Lois between stockings. Not to mention the Raimi of the first two installments of Spider-man, linking popcorn with a special script that showed what was Spidey: a loser whose fate is to be only. And you say Nolan, never saw a Batman so cojón **, pure Lord of the night. Do this to show you what is not?The 4 fantastic 2 &#8242;, no more, no less. The historia-trama - script is simple not being able, specially designed to not confuse you at any time of what it is telling. The wedding of Reed Richards (Ioan Gruffudd) and Sue Storm (Jessica Alba) in sight, a threatening mysterious hangs over the planet, recorriendolo and causing various anomalies that satisfyed the attention of heroes. When they finally encounter the powerful Silver Surfer must join forces with a newly awakened enemy (McMahon) to avoid what is coming: the Devourer of worlds called Galactus.Con some new hue, and an update of our times, will see a version in this sequel of?Do The Coming of Galactus?, history of three numbers (# 48-# 51) beyond published by 1960s featured for the first time in the comics silver stele and Galactus, two characters who have survived to the present day in the adventures of Richards and company. Removing a couple of characters that at this stage do not paint anything and removing some cosmic references, the Fox and Tim Story have reduced everything to a basic scheme: the f 4 meets S.Surfer, S.Surfer batters them, the f 4 discovered as defeat him, and predictable final act. All seasoned with lots of action and much CGI, essential to make this a real blockbuster palomitero and little else.Perhaps I crucifiquéis by what I say, but this sequel surpasses the first part in everything. No longer are the characters, so save us the pain of the initial half-hour. Parade of the mythology of the series characters is exciting: Stela, Dr. death, Frankie Raye a.k.a. Supernova, the fantasticar, a Conatus of super-skrull and Galactus. There is no pretensions of hooked to an adult audience, only innocent fun, and humor, much more humor. Course, the scenes involving silver stele are what I, as a fan of these characters, I have been waiting for all my life: last genuine, and not because its special effects are innovative, but because I've been 20 years seeing it in crumpled paper. Being prepared for what is going to be once you sit in the armchair, everything works. Until raisins ignored the script written by Don Payne, which we already jo in a sticky ** with the libretto of?My super girlfriend?, and it was believed the very unlikable that it writes good. could have been a peliculón?, Yes, and that is the only thing that bothers me. A decent director and less clown this might have had something of a narrative quality, but is that Tim Story isn't Christopher Nolan, and or in his dreams could reach that level. Do so, with a very good basis the director is dedicated to put a stamp of?All the public? and how easy: not much dialogue, unnecessary scenes (the hen of Reed), children's jokes, a subplot of exchange of powers something stupid, and that you will never be forgiven: the appearance of Galactus. Without intent to annoy the only reason why some bring rooms to see this film, I must say attention SPOILER that we see the cabezón purple the end SPOILER giganton but for the rest of the treatment of such immense and promising character, Story can go to the very same ** · @! # **Do I already is what you're going to say of?The fantastic four and Silver Surfer?: is a very careful firecracker. Because, in many respects it is, why neither entered interpretations of Alba, Gruffudd, Evans or Chiklis, who are of school playground. Do do do so have involve this sequel in the list of? movies that everybody hates less I?, because I leave aside my critical sense, which says that the script is lousy and the history requetevista to embrace the kid loves?The 4 fantastic? Stan Lee and Jack Kirby, who has grown up with Mr. fantastic, Invisible girl, thing and torch faced death, Galactus or the skrulls, and sees all of them in action on the big screen. Do accordingly will leave orphan classification of? buena-excelente - bad-very buena-regular?What you want, of course I am going to buy the special DVD collectors of this sequel, but if I pick up a Tim Story I can kill him (figuratively, already I understand)?</body>
</review>
