<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="Solos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fun and exciting reflection on affective relations, of the confusion so many times lead to loneliness and confusion are both difficult and complex. And do not expect more, because the film loses interest to passes the footage.</summary>
	<body>José Glusman, director in the independent Argentina film, try to answer to a "difficult" question in his latest film: is good men are alone?His response has dyes of comedy-drama, one of these as recurring in the latest Argentine cinema, between EL son DE LA NOVIA and NO SOS VOS, SOY YO. Where people and their circumstances are what really matters in the course of the story that we try to tell. ALONE is a film that speaks of love, friendship and loneliness? and portrays, in the final analysis, insight into possible in the way that men love and suffer for love.The film tells the story of two men and their destination. Henry (played by Sergio Boris) is 37 years old. The last 12, living with his wife and two children. Sick with jealousy, just separated once again from his wife. Louis (played by Adrián Navarro), 40 years, has just completed a passionate affair with a very hysterical television journalist, which he was madly in love with, and left him on the other.So one comes from the horror of jealousy and wear, and the other of a passion that swept it, and finally left him alone. Do as Henry has no where to go, Luis invited him to live in his house, provisionally? do not want to know anything about women. And it is at this point where begins the coexistence. Full of obstacles, stages and sensations coexistence. A moment in which one is needed to each other more than ever.ALONE tells one of those stories so common in the last Argentine cinema: it's a therapeutic history. Situations that are going to live the two characters in the film are those that are going to allow clear that "sea of doubts" that have weakened them in their daily lives. The suffering that carries with it a separation they will make stronger? and is that, as said many times, "there is no evil that good does not come". And I forgot, you will discover the power of viagra? but, well, that's another story.ALONE is a fun and exciting reflection on the difficult and complex are affective relations, confusion and confusion that so many times lead to loneliness. And do not expect more, because the film loses interest to passes the footage, in the absence of a development of the characters as well as ambiguities in the script.</body>
</review>
