<review author="Tony Astonish" title="Wolf Creek" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a small and delicate piece that details melt in an only objective: pass genuine fear with the horror live their protagonists.</summary>
	<body>While billboards are dotted all the years of abundant films that promise to fear, increasingly is more difficult to find any that really gives genuine terror. And that is precisely what get Greg Mclean with his film "Wolf Creek".It is difficult to talk about it without disclosing nothing of his argument and, on the other hand, it is better to do so to assist the surprises that we have reserved Mr. Mclean. In essence it's a journey carried out by three young people during their stay in Australia will be interrupted by something unexpected. While many see this film as an imitation to others that were already successful in his time, I think that "Wolf Creek" is very clever and that Mclean goes precisely of those references so that the viewer trust in his armchair thinking that he knows what is going to move to surprise you and terrify you.During the first part of the film, attended a quick but effective presentation of the three young actors starting their adventure through the wonderful and grandiose landscapes of Australia. While all seems calm and controlled, there is something that bothers us: as the actors, something we are disturbed, but we don't know why. To pass the facts, and when everything is quiet, we feel that anytime something bad can happen. And such is the case in a second part very well linked and finished in which all the elements fit perfectly, and where, we shall undoubtedly distressing and terrifying moments.The consistency of the script and the extraordinary interpretation of actors save some common mistakes in movies of this type. Excellent levels of the vast Australian desert and a soundtrack which conforms very well to the film are other details to keep in mind.IMHO, it is a small and delicate piece in which all details melt in an only objective: pass genuine fear with the horror live their protagonists.</body>
</review>
