<review author="Bruji" title="El perfume" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There was only a filmmaker who could uncover the essence of that fragrance that inspired a song by Nirvana.</summary>
	<body>'Perfume' is the film that turns verbs "read" and "see" in antonyms, and surprising novel that many found in our adolescence, in a Plantigrade tale: dull, sticky, tedious, annoying...The names of five directors who know approaching history to convey to the viewer the concern and anxiety that off your pages could mention, at least. Even so, no mistake. There was only a filmmaker who could uncover the essence of that fragrance that inspired a song by Nirvana.Si you want to speak well of the Perfume, we have to confine ourselves to observe the art direction is appropriate; the setting of the 18th century and narrated in the novel, the correct; and the production, the right design. However, if you decide to delve into the essence of the story who was fascinated by half the world in 1985, soon it becomes convinced that the chosen approach could not have been worse. Does fails on three fundamental elements: the measurement of time, the proposal of casting, and in the most unforgivable: the structure of the script, which becomes an evil plagiarism of?Amelie?.With all these ingredients, can you develop a good perfume? The history of cinema flatly replied us no, and it reminds us of the extreme case where a technically perfect film gave the fret with the prevailing system of education in Hollywood, because of an inconsistent hyphen (rebellion aboard, to the 1,962). Long before, John Huston, with his directorial debut, had shown that the primary basis of a good movie is a good script. The Maltese Falcon, in fact, is based on a best seller that other filmmakers had failed.In general, there are too many cases in which renowned Directors did not finish convince address literary projects. Happened to Brian de Palma with the bonfire of the vanities, to Roman Polanski with Oliver Twist, even to Coppola, to include a love story that was never in the mood of Mina Harker or emerged from the pen of Stoker. But there was also a genius who knew how to liberate the words to transform them into images, even if it meant having to invent a new narrative structure in cinema. It happened in Lolita.Esa genius is not in the collaboration formed by Tom Tykwer and Andrew Birkin.Tykwer not has adapted the novel to the screen, but to their own possibilities as director. In this way, it recreates in sniff the first victim to show his virtuosity behind the camera. Now, a close-up showing the technique for drying flowers. Now, a framing retailer of the cross that leads to the neck Laura. Later, she flits through the fields of lavender, and ends crossing at breakneck speed to narrate a nasal Chase, in which copied some scenes of the worst movie of Ang Lee. That in which Hulk goes jumping by the mountains which graceful mariposilla.With this auto-contemplación, has managed, as well as a wasteful footage, simply despise the time of drafting. Do remember that the choice of the twelve fragrances? moments summits in the original story - is reduced to a blow on the head (to eleven, in particular).Say experts that director mission involves not only properly placing cameras, but that he is alone, at all times, have a global vision of the film. Here, Mr. Tykwer overlooked one important fact: the pages of that book emanated aromas.Birkin managed to succeed to adapt the name of the rose, that took the precaution of focus the script on the detective plot and flee from the philosophical conclusions of Umberto Eco. More in the Perfume, it has committed the most serious mistake of going from one extreme to another, without realizing the virtue of moderation. On the one hand, literally adapting the novel and the voiceover plays full paragraphs of history, making the film especially tedious. But, on the other hand, is obviate many descriptions, so you get blur the central characters. It has nothing to do "being great and abominable, comparable to Napoleon, grotesque, deformed and repulsive in the eyes of women" who created Süskind with the physical attractiveness of the British actor who gives life.And it is that the topic is more than clear. This role was always for actor John Hurt, the Narrator, and the film for Stanley Kubrick.Al out of the film, came to several conclusions. The idea that a Europe that shoots together, stays together, find me moving. The hiring of La Fura dels Baus, a great success. The high technical quality of this tape, an aspect of the subject to the popular theories of relativity or, better said, the comparison. And, although I admit that it sounds like glory of the "new German cinema", the assertion that Tom Tykwer has managed to adapt this novel with brilliance, seems me far-fetched.Mental straws in film, there should be the fair and, if possible, that they are well done. Managers who want to experiment, can always do so by telling their own stories, which screened before a small group of intellectuals, those who worship what you do not understand and call "transgression" which is not more than mere stupidity.Fortunately, there is always who note that the emperor was naked.</body>
</review>
