<review author="José A. Peig" title="Re-Animator" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Synthesis and simplicity; It is a film with two faces or dimensions of meaning. The deep horror, and the fun and frantic satire.</summary>
	<body>The so-called "splatter" film inspired by stories that referred to the macabre aspects of human existence, such as blood, viscera, and meat subject to all kinds of violence resulting from the harassment of the human body in its material dimension, which can cause a whirlwind of images that affect the sensations, specifically disgust, exploiting a theme so universal as the fear of death, but from its purely morbid manifestations. Consequently, we can say that the "gore" creates the most primary feeling of horror of all, almost primordial suffering; the prehistoric humán which sees his flesh torn apart by the paw of the beast or contemplates terrified how the jaws of the beast decapitan the body of one of their peers. Stuart Gordon directed this masterful exercise in splatter film based on the intention of talking about fear of death and the desire to overcome, this immutable skull of terror, in this case, expressing itself through a sharp look that it agglutinates shades with skill as satire, cynicism, irony, macabre humor and sadomasochistic sensuality.Despite moving on a ground "underground", the filmmaker and his writers have shown due concern for telling a story, without falling into the trap - as usual in this type of film - subordinate the significance of the tape to a mere and uncontrolled show of hemoglobin and viscera. No. In the Stuart Gordon film the top and bottom overlap to articulate the discourse around a basic storyline depicted in the character which we see in the early sequences tries to revive the body of a dead, followed by the subsequent malaise by the sense of helplessness induced before the echo live with death. In the final sequence, that same character returns to deal with death, new failure, this time reinforced by the loss of his beloved fémina, which motivates the macabre last action, the well-deserved climax to the suggestive orgy of the Dantesque. I think that it has already said, it is worthwhile to repeat it; in the cinematic language, the image - or images - which opens the story and the image that closes play a fundamental role. Re-Animator is pure and perfect structuring and articulation of the story, without beating with unnecessary detours; simplicity and precision.The other great handicap we see embodied in the figure of the scientist crazy, characterized by way of a Dr. Frankenstein coarse and cynical, which has an excellent counterpart in its competitor of Brasil profile and repulsive cartoon expression, and who see holding his own head in some of the passages most delusional of the film (in truth, in this film)(Science and scientists are represented with an eloquent satirical sense and good dose of bad grapes). Miracle whey is which provides the metamorphosis and the step that goes from humanity aware, or already dead, to the of the pure automaton, the gestural mimicry that characterizes the figure of the zombie and induces a feeling of horror nestled in the primordial fear that used to do reference to the beginning of the text: the disgust arising from these automated movements, these gestures of sheer insanity without conscience, the no-muerte but neither is life. To be more concise: the human being in a land unknown, devoid of soul, slave of the chaotic reflections movements of the nervous system, where no longer makes sense.That feature of the zombie is which removes some very deep fears, and the film we are discussing today explodes with wit and overwhelming sense of the grotesque zombie feature that just described, and supported with disturbing elements of great relevance in what psychological impact refers, thus flow sensations of horror while they walk on macabre comedy tonesthrough an intelligent use of dynamic narrative and all the springs that fall within the own cómico-siniestro story possibilities. Synthesis and simplicity; It is a film with two faces or dimensions of meaning. The deep horror, and the fun and frantic satire.Overall, an undisputed masterpiece, perfect example that the kistch and the "underground" are not exempt from being matter from which cinematically represent ideas or stories freighted with wit and a penetrating and provocative look about the same universe kistch in which they move. Robert Rodriguez is well would learn the lesson, if you consider an artist. This is art. His film is remake.</body>
</review>
