<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Cuando ruge la marabunta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Classic mistreated by the passage of the years on a legion of ants that wipe out a plot of South America. Becomes something heavy around the middle of the film, with unlikely situations and dialogues have been very outdated. But no one can remove the vitola of classic.</summary>
	<body>Many times we are very permissive with films that have a certain number of years, with the treacly textures or impossible costumes. If these films were made in our time, the critical abalanzaría on them as hyenas in a television documentary. Even so, they retain this stale charm that has made classics. If not, tell me you, what was to be a classic film of ants that shows at times the same level of ants by attacking, or it spends more than one hour until referred to rush. This is cinema.The film is about a white woman who travels to South America to inform her husband, since he had married by proxy. Her ideal death, arrives to meet with a powerful landowner who has stolen the River hectares of land to cultivate cocoa. But the meeting is not entirely satisfactory, inexplicably, given that rather than kill as they kill cockroaches, they enzarzan in discussions about the honour and not be more. It was already the end of the film, the largest force known by those lands, rush, begins to get closer to their crops.My mother-in-law, that film bonanza. When I said see the ants, I remembered vaguely two things, I spent when the ants build rafts with leaves to cross the river and tension which was in black and white. Nothing else see that it was in Technicolor was afraid that the tension was not the same. And, indeed, nothing to do. The tráfago over the years has given on all sides to this movie turned into classic. To begin with, is not understood as a type in the jungle for years not abalance on his wife and does not leave the room until that ants are nibbling the faucets. I understand that special effects are crappy and I do not go for anything with them. That Yes, to draw eight times the same plane, at various points in the film is a bit of nose.In short, classic mistreated by the passage of the years on a legion of ants that wipe out a plot of South America. Becomes something heavy around the middle of the film, with unlikely situations and dialogues have been very outdated. But no one can remove the vitola of classic.</body>
</review>
