<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fine offal with a screenplay by the introduction, development and ending something absurd but passable. Recommended for lovers of cinema of terror sangruiento and violent.</summary>
	<body>UY, a hill that has eyes, hell to fright. And with all the dust in the desert, we are sure that all pay drops is left to cool them. By the way, say that I am a coward, but I do not understand how in these films the protagonists do not commit suicide. Well, it may be because they are Catholics, but get your in one of 28 days, in which humanity is half extinct and the zombies you dismember but not before kill you scare. Pussy, you stick a shot and so quiet. If you know that you're going to eat and it will be worse. The hero there is loose, really.The film is about an American family, which the parents silver wedding, decide to cross the United States, from end to end in caravan. When it is going through the desert, they encounter a gas station where indicate them that to save a few kilometres can go by a shortcut that very few people know. So they decide to follow him, but a few miles, they have an accident by a blowout, which forces them to spend the night in the middle of nowhere.Well, we have before us a tape of a genus of disgusting terror, thin guts and good scares. The typical American family, as always, is to kill the first round. The bad guys are quite elaborate and, although show them us openly since the first frames, you finish does not get you to them. The development is quite distressing, bearing the climax towards the middle of the recording. And the rest? The rest is already worthless for almost anything. The timorous family guy is trasmusta in an indomitable marine that espachurra ele with great ease and fits the blows as the man of steel if it were. The characters, up to half of the film are all in place and very well, although towards the end they disfigurement too making us lose interest. The story is elaborated, with his revindicativo touch against the nuclear experiments. And the scenarios I have liked, giving the total certainty that what they do is all he could do.In short, offal fine script of introduction, development and ending something absurd but passable. Recommended for lovers of cinema of terror sangruiento and violent.</body>
</review>
