<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The pace of the film is trepdiante, the jokes are still just as sparkling and beasts and Homer is in its sauce, always so rude and careless.</summary>
	<body>When I found out that the Simpsons would move to the big screen I took a huge disappointment. Along with many other fans of the series, I thought the yellow family would be destroyed and converted in 3D and, of course, that the grace and brutality of the series created by Matt Groening would miss. Very fortunately, the film directed by David Silverman is, without doubt, an episode of television led to the cinema and, of course, longer (although not believe that both, then only lasts about 80 minutes). The pace of the film is trepdiante, the jokes are still just as sparkling and beasts and Homer is in its sauce, always so rude and careless.With the Simpsons: The movie I laughed as I have ever seen for the first time on a movie screen drawings than in three dimensions and even I has missed the chord (this video of Marge). It is entretenidísima and no main character has been abused, although I find that the neighbouring Flanders has been softened somewhat on the number. The truth is that this movie which most recalls are numerous gags that confront us, because they are related to the family or the other side (unforgettable moment of the Terminator President). Perhaps this format of film, with a screenplay with development, knot and ending makes you feel different to see the Simpson family, but but to do a movie? And I recognize that part of having a great pace, the script is pretty good, despite having some other too familiar topic.The truth is that there is no much more to say about it, because unless you do not like the yellow family, the rest of the world you see will be, or at least that I think, satisfied. Perhaps the principle is somewhat uncontrolled, because you acrivillan too close to gags, half of which already you know them (malidta promotion!), and scenes that do not come too much beside the point. Yes, I know that Bart kickbike is great, but does not have much sense.So we have a movie very fun and entertaining with memorable gags and others not so much and yellow characters so ordinary, Catholic and hooligan as always. That Yes, some aspects could have been improved, because in some moments gives you the feeling of watching a few Simpsons somewhat manipulated for the more youthful audience. Also emphasize that there are several critical to American politics and gags that make reference to global warming which are not wasted. Yellow fever has landed into theaters with one more than satisfactory result.</body>
</review>
