<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Un buen día lo tiene cualquiera" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nice comedy provided by Santiago Lorenzo, after his groundbreaking "MOM is boba", gets behind the camera for a second time.</summary>
	<body>Nice comedy provided by Santiago Lorenzo, after his groundbreaking "MOM is boba", gets behind the camera for a second time.I do not do comparisons between the two works because I did not see the first, but I guess this is less good than that. And just for some reason, this, "A good day.." is entertaining and part of a very good idea, but will deflate slowly.Anyway you can enjoy and, above all in its first third, you laugh really, and you descojonas even three or four times, especially hearing perogrullas, philosophy mad and other diatribes of the old spídido, as well as the descharrante visit of the protatonista Hacienda. A man who, if he does not take his daily pill seems a vegetable, but once taken, breaks out in a verbiage without end that crazy to the very Holy Job. here is the best of this, in general lines, funny comedy, good do Juan Antonio Quintana as Onofre. Not sure what will come out of his lips, but it is always something original, that part of reality, but adorned with a concoction of disjointed ineas causing hilarity.However, little by little, as the minutes pass, the pace numbs and everything becomes more or less calm, without much imagination, rather flat. Only in its final part, in the moments where the protagonist must opositar, returns to the messing and quality guionística, flourish with, for example, memorable departure of the President of the Court to the opponent when this tells them his age.In short, it is true that are in solfa important issues as loneliness on the human being, the problem of housing and work, the value of friendship and confidence, but it is no less true that, seeing the work as a whole, we can see clearly that this film would have required to be a medium length rather than a long.</body>
</review>
