<review author="Bruji" title="Ratatouille" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With the intention? limpérrima? inherent in these products, intelligent humor that characterizes his writers and the continuous references to the classics of animation, the Pixar returns to win the game.</summary>
	<body>An effective career of Fund of irregular home, care, development and an apotheosis outcome. With the intention to "limpérrima" inherent in these products, intelligent humor that characterizes his writers and the continuous references to the classics of animation, the Pixar returns to win the game. At times, the spectator forgets that, in Paris, are the rats which cooked.At this point in the film, little trusts this servant of the good intentions that accompany the American creators of the new school when they focus their stories away from its borders. A mistrust which, in his day, was widely justified with titles like my great wedding Greek (Joel Zwick, 2,002), Lost in Translation (the daughter of 2003) or under the Sun of Tuscany (Audrey Wells, 2003). And it is that, after a wacky comedy, Miss Coppola and a delicious romantic tale, revealing rebellion did transcend, to shame, the topical and distorted image given by Americans of the various peoples and cultures visited. All this, of course, seasoned with a great sense of humor (humor), that names "fool capirote" to one that does not understand.I am afraid that the custom has come to "Dibujilandia". We know that a desktop, in which the trajectory of the talks is unknown came out extraordinary titles such as bug's life, monsters, Inc. and Finding Nemo; and more than likely, however much it to strive in mislead the Distributor, that arose the history of the rat Cook of a walk through the fields of Mars. Only already are in charge of dressing the dish so that on our next visit to Paris, we refrain to call a master host that lurks its innumerable gardens "rat".RA-ta-tuí, as they require us to pronounce in Spanish, because its clumsy beginnings two fashion film, rescued from the best classics, to be, in recent years, painfully used. He is voice-overs and a lengthy flashback which justifies the story of the protagonist rodent. Also to a dangerous approach to one of the titles of the competition, neighbors invaders of noticeably inferior to the Pixar productions quality, brilliance and depth. Exceeded the unpromising home, missing the annoying voice of French accent in off and forgetting that the story is due to some facts of the past, the narrative structure takes a perfect linearity enabling the deployment of the magic. The studied faces of eyes always human, able to excite those who already lost last dandelion milk, creating fun and intelligent situations, the continuous references to lovers and exemplary lessons, will do the rest; to accommodate an apotheosis end with a declaration of principles of required reading for the criticones. By the way, appreciate a slight variant of Chaplin famously said, "If you institutions on what you leave behind, will not see what you have before". We are witnessing the bizarre flight of a restaurant, that reminds us of the adventure of the crab Sebastian with the Palace Cook. We discovered the "lower depths" of the French capital, after having known from the heights, thanks to the Hunchback of Notre Dame. We understand the danger involved in entering other unbeknownst fascinating worlds, and the importance of the family, inheritance of Ariel. We know a peculiar fairy godmother, who, at all times, trying to do we understand the true meaning of the word "self-esteem". We wonder if "there is a better place to dream that you Paris", while looking at the movie in white and black that replaces the operatically runway with a railway station, in which, possibly, Ilsa and Rick gave a last goodbye. We return to the banks of the Seine, in which all say I Love You to the rhythm of a beautiful soundtrack that an American devoted to Paris. And we got to worship a neat and hackneyed, rat with bland face of Coco of Sesame, giving testimony that "great artists can come from anywhere".All of which, leads us to the conviction that, with or without double intentions and/or spirit of mockery, the "adults screenwriters" have much to learn dibus designers. In the end, "anyone can cook!".</body>
</review>
