<review author="Bruji" title="Los Borgia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cesare Borgia unconvincing... an amalgam of episodes of television series, clumsily United by a deplorable montage.</summary>
	<body>Boasted as the great dream of all film lover lover of the historic gender: a passage from our story told by a filmmaker himself. Perfect atmosphere, excellent actors, technical deployment unprecedented and a prepared script. An attractive proposal, in which the only discordant note ventured at ceceante diction of peculiar Catherina Sforza. But, in the end, a dream... What could have been. It is possible that, on leaving the film, some film buffs remember that funny phrase with which American critics defined the work of the actor John Malkovich in the 1988 dangerous liaisons: "Sus andares, most characteristic of an inhabitant of Brooklyn to a French aristocrat of the 18th century". Bridging the gap? if you can - something similar could write, on this occasion, of one convincing short Cesare Borgia. A painful performance, which owes much of his little brilliance to the strange licenses linguistic, in many moments, allowing the script, and that are closer to the slang of the movida madrileña that language characteristic and own character in the 15th century.Still, isn't this a matter for RIP vestments? still-, if we take into account that this aspect? costume - what is deserving of a prominent mention. For something or for something we are talking about a blockbuster.Within a framework of incomparable beauty to have been filmed in real historical spaces? made cameras have failed to exploit or transmit to the spectator-the history shown remains faithful to the story of the novelist Mario Puzzo. A new vision of the family gandiense, aimed at dismantling the black legend, envisages in its time, the shoulders on it for centuries. Get good characterizations of the characters of Lucrecia and a Juan Borgia discreet, coming from one more than acceptable performance. Do the Lisp (and others), own from a quarry of actors that he has not worked in theatre ("the mother of the Lamb" of the Declamation), it is not obstacle for peace Vega, on this occasion, shine with their own light, as opposed to the new look be thundering about Alexander VI, in which accidents? that follows giving you the novel - is transformed into cartoon folly.In the historic area, the viewer must not fear. Responsible for the footage guarantee the various Italian States continue keeping their names (for example), and the history of its essence. With the "perspective that gives the distance" have been numerous cases in which American filmmakers created Kings and countries non-existent. Remember, El Cid in 1961, in which the advice of D. Ramón Menéndez Pidal could not prevent that Heston Díaz de Vivar take the square of Valencia "on behalf of the King of Spain", in full period of the reconquest. In this sense, Los Borgia that arises as a masterful and typical kind of history. We understand by "typical" that first hour on Monday, in which the tone of voice of the Professor, monotonous and linear, did the imagination, not to the 15th century and Yes to a much more recent past: the last weekend. A mental journey that used to be abruptly interrupted when the tedious and tired voice raised the volume. In the film, the giro that does leave the torpor comes from "informalization", breakdown of the script.There is no doubt that it is unwise to begin to tell a story by almost the end of it, back "twelve years earlier", advance "three years later", return to the starting point and end. An invention that worked you at one of the big one of ours, Don Martin Scorsese, and usually get the attention of the Viewer. Now well, for many blockbuster than and much decomposition to propose, entire film has to have a beginning, a development with its "heat of the moment" corresponding and an outcome. Try to have too many starters with their subsequent analysis, merely give the impression to be attending the screening of an amalgam of episodes of television series, clumsily United by a deplorable montage.In the section of the surprises, what Yes striking thing is knowing that there is not a single epic battle in the film. Various contests insinuate the viewer with the presence of corpses on the battlefield, with Cesare Borgia playing with his sword, or by resorting to the old trick on the map, in which a red line marks the unifying advance. Something similar was suggested in his day to Stanley Kubrick to tell Spartacus. An idea that the director made, because go to this narrative process would never convey the historical significance of an army of slaves who put in check the greatest political power known in the ancient world, of Rome. And that is precisely what is happening in this work, which fails to understand the fame of wise strategists, best warriors, and arrogant insolentes that encourage hatred and envy of those who agreed in their walk, that is not known to where is the greatness of the Borgia.Aunque, perhaps most striking of all the tape halle in the unfortunate scene in which Lucretia shows a letter from his brother Caesar to the Duke of It ferrara, at the top of a tower. A sequence unworthy of a filmmaker who is a little gem in the city without limits and this is the story of Los Borgia, a product intentionally designed to be rentabilizado to unexplored limits still by Spanish films. To the "How was shot", has followed the film, and it will do the television series, with its annual revivals during the next century. The Alcantara family has rival.</body>
</review>
