<review author="Tyler" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the best movies that will be seen in years, not only for herself, if not for what it represents. We know the Simpsons better than our family because we are dealing with the artifact of geniuses.</summary>
	<body>It is true that today the American TV has almost the best writers that exist. Real workers of the script, that curran in series that have nothing to do with each other and still make real masterpieces. They deal with different tones, different characters and not out of his line. That is the more difficult of all, because the TV series are followed by millions of people, more than cinema, and is very difficult to keep us happy as spectators, any episode of our favorite series that we like least is reason for us to criticize him, and it should not be so. The characters of the TV series are better developed there, because those who are the writers have more time to publicize, and them are built on the fly. There are things that you can do, you know for a fact of their lives, characters in film and already, even the biopics develop less characters than the TV series. This is summarized, a HOUSE seguior (I myself for example) knows better to Dr. House that to Howard Hughs although it has seen ten times the AVIATOR.What I mean with this esque possibly all, better know to Homer Simpson that many people in our own family, him know almost everything. What we have seen in countless situations. Know you better than to family, friends or co-workers. And not only to him, if not whole family Simpson.Pobre of those who wait to see something entirely new, because not as hiba to find and true fans to the Simpsons, that we we love deeply, not wanted "something new", we wanted see it as always, but in a context film, not television. Good esque know so well that it should not submit to anyone, we all know who is every one in the city of Springfield, so he goes to the grain. The movie to the series is not comparable, they are part of the same, so no we could have expected something better or worse, it is only the family moved to the film.The movie is absolutely masterful, with all the letters, a script that should participate as a candidate for the Oscars. The story is fucking great, it's almost science fiction, if someone tells you that argument, you have a fantastic idea almost to make a prequel of how started the world post-apocalyptic MAD MAX.The best esque the writers have had time to develop a film history, far removed from the pace which requires a TV series. The movie is more relaxed, more powerful in the movement of images, this more sustained by the image that the dialogues. Spanish dubbing of the series simepre I preferred it to the original, but since that died Carlos Revilla, the original voice of Homer, things changed a little. While Carlos Ysbert does a great job, let us remember that he doubled to Walter in EL GRAN LEBOWSKI, llevabamos years with the voice of Revilla and is very difficult to adapt. Also the great voice of Paul Sempson faded (If Yes, Sempson) folding Mr. Burns. The movie this very well folded, like the series.We can see almost all the characters that have appeared in the series, almost all, the fun will be when the DVD is displayed and we can stop it to go identificandolos and guess in which chapters appeared. (A little freak not?)History has a great film rhythm, a tempo of the host and a classical structure, remember to Wilder and the movies, like no, by James l. Brooks. One of the writers. One of many that there is, all of the series, all have written major chapters and have created a totally film plot. Not imagine this chapter, you can not because it is pure cinema. The Simpsons series is more longeva of the history, I do not remember what lasts longer East Enders, even is if it continues, but East Enders is a soap opera, very good that if, as a good soap opera is limited to tell us every day of a few characters that change from time to time. The Simpsons is a series, and always have the same family, and never bored, for 20 years. And still staying, they remain the series that keeps alive Antena3 along with the news. Homer is posiblemnte, the best character written in audiovisual history. better than any of Welles me atreveria to say. regardless of critical or not critical to American society. Homer is a character built on echos that we have seen all over the past 20 years, and as I have already said, we know it better than our family.The movie is not as strong as the series in some things, I mean that in some episodes of the series had contained more adult and in others not, but in the movie have dcidido for the second, more public, normal. You can see this movie as an animation because it is, but it isn't the same, this is for adults but it always has been. A movie for adults that can go children, RATATOILLE is a movie for children that adults can go. Of course, a movie of the characteristics of RATATOILLLE has organized success, because they want to see the children, and if they go because his parents also have to go, you're not going to go alone them very mamoncetes.SIMPSON, one of the best movies that will be seen in years, not only for herself, if not for what it represents.THANK YOU MATT GROENING</body>
</review>
