<review author="Robgordon" title="Brokeback mountain" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film more overvalued given the film in recent years</summary>
	<body>Finally I could see "Brokeback Mountain", the laureada and lauded film from Ang Lee. The film that everyone expected after triumph at the Venice Festival, in a great number of awards American criticism, Golden Globe and almost surely in the Oscars, if no one remedy or anything. "Brokeback Mountain" seems to me from now, the film more overvalued given the film in recent years. And more that me what it will look like if it achieves the maximum statuette.The viewing of this film of landscapes and pastors, I was disappointed. And I record that I have tried here vedado way more objectively as possible, without stick to the large amount of awards granted to date and without stopping to think what is in my view the career of filmmaker Ang director Lee.El Taiwanese has to date an unequalled filmography, as disparate as unpredictablecapable of making "Sense and sensibility" and "The ice storm" and at the same time that martial outburst was "Tiger and Dragon" or a tape of superheroes for the Hollywood as "Hulk" System.And is that Ang Lee demonstrates not having that power that has Clint Eastwood to sensitive stories, with extreme slowness and that you look wonderful. And that here he tries, but get this love story between the two Cowboys to be insufferable, long and tedious. "Brokeback Mountain" tells a story of misunderstood love, of impossible love. That I've already seen many times before, and with a greater passion and interest in a large number of films. I will cite an example, in which I not Alexios of rural, of the time and setting the pace; "The bridges of Madison County" by Clint Eastwood, which I think is key, as a comparison judging definitively as major Lee's tape work. Only some glances between Meryl Streep and Clint Eastwood in the film already contain higher doses of passion than the two hours and quarter of the Cowboys of the mountain.And it is that regardless of "Brokeback Mountain" is a homosexual, heterosexual history or whatever, is first and foremost a love story that does not transmit a light feeling to the Viewer.The history of "Brokeback Mountain" never reaches fonde because never get pass that character of relationship which, in part, fails to be consummated by issues or social prejudices. The few strokes giving Ang Lee, on the fear that may exist in the characters on the relationship, are slim to convince us.In addition the protagonists are extremely loose in his performances. Ledger and Gyllenhall are expressionless. You never know that they are thinking, what are their intentions, and not simply put face of angry or angry. Extremely loose in their roles. Only salvaria the submissive wife, Michelle Williams, which has the best level of the film, when he discovers her husband kissing with Jake Smith.Como equally weak is your script, very flat, which outlines just a few notes of all this footage long lag between sheep, mountains and esporadicos meetings, without developing any of the sub-plots, while none of them captures the attention. The work is therefore totally of the direction, that puts in her practice this little theory offered their script, lengthening the meetings of its protagonists, which are repeated over and over again for the viewer boredom as much as possible.And is that when the landscapes you seem more beautiful and interesting than the story of love that is this, is that something is not working. Fails the passion, emotion fails, fails as poignant. "And that is extremely important in a film which is giving the title of masterpiece with great ease.""Brokeback Mountain" I has known little even to wasted film. Is true that Ang Lee is not intended to make a plea for homosexuality, just tell a romantic story, but if some small brushstrokes of no social acceptance which never comes to finish pointing. It seems that at times has wanted to give longer life to the film, introducing new and possibly interesting passages (such as the of the father-in-law of Jake Smith), but it ends up being prisoner of the script, the story and little claw of the relationship that is based solely and exclusively this film. It is not that the Taiwanese who lived in Hollywood film has nothing in his favor, only the intention of telling a romantic history with a classic cut already gives some point in its favour, in these days they run. "Another thing is that her it was able to take advantage of or shape with enough intensity on the screen, which is not the case.""Brokeback" is that films where his music you seems wonderful or charisma, his photography and precious or pretentious places, its sublime history or empty, void or great performances, his script perfect or bulb. For me, these land forbidden, are today more overvalued than yesterday, but less than tomorrow.</body>
</review>
