<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The impeccable direction of Paul Greengrass is one of the aspects most highlight of this overwhelming and intense film. And do not forget that the final scene already belongs to the list of the best end of year. Unforgettable, unique.</summary>
	<body>The problem that there are today in the triologías of films is one of the three always ends up being bad, or even very bad. And you may wonder: why everyone admires to the Jason Bourne? Very simple: any of the three films is bad, what is more, they are all great. The first was good, but the second exceeded. And to top it off, the third and final delivery exceeds the first and the second. I that call you to be ready. La palma, undoubtedly her is Paul Greengrass, director of the myth of Bourne and the Bourne Ultimatum, the last two. It is not that Doug Liman did a bad job with the Bourne identity. It was an entretenidísima film and I think that without it nothing would have ended as it has done. Thanks to the opening of the history we enter the world of the amnesiac spy in a vicious manner, because the pace and exciting action sequences deserved applause several. That's why ending in the last film all in an impeccable way, all cables come together and finally, Jason Bourne remembers everything. Although this is not the final end?Not only is the Bourne Ultimatum, an action movie absolutely trepdiante. The political content also introduces to the history, corruption and the dirt of the secret agencies. I confess that I hardly moved throughout the film. And is that we can already be considered to Greegrass as a synonym for hectic: camera in hand so realistic persecutions, the constant plot turns, traps and intrigue (introduced masterfully). Not only that, but that Jason Bourne is one spy any. That no one will compare with 007 or other equally or more surreal. Perhaps not remember his identity, but we, the public, does remember it him as one of the best spies in recent times, portrayed in a manner very realistic, staff and, above all human. As Damon said: can you imagine James Bond asking for forgiveness to the daughter of one of their victims? And I do not come with the excuse that is now fashionable humanize the heroes. Not only because Jason Bourne is not a hero, but also because humanize a character it is a good thing and that increases the credibility of the work. Returning to the film, say the amnesiac spy stars in several of the most impressive action sequences that we have seen over the past ten years. Both of the first journalist in the Airport (one can not lift their eyes from the screen) as the Tangier (the persecution on a motorcycle, across the rooftops, the fight in the lababo?), and for not forgetting us of the last persecution automobilística in New York. And not only the film features scenes of action and really witty dialogues, but that much footage also belongs to the intrigues within the Department seeking to Bourne and company. Say that some particular scenes remind me to the control centre of the magistral also United 93. as well, the real master of the Bourne Ultimatum is, as I said before, its director Paul Greengrass. His style, his way of narrating, communicate, catch us, get nerves, make us skip any than another smile, another tear some. His impeccable and gross at the same time address makes us believe that where we are more than watching a spy film live live and direct. If the myth of Bourne the strong point of the movie was the novelty of the hectic, here the thing is already far more advanced, and not only admires the total presence of the Greengrass style during the footage, but that, as we already know, can witness that this is not a current spy film. We are not to the good Shepherd, a complex plot and slow play, but first and foremost the opposite. And both movies are magnificent. Yes, the plot of this ultimatum is nothing out of this world, but the way that is told is what really matters, then but had come out too easy film. That Yes, is not foreseeable. I followed from beginning to end all the plots, sub-plots and traps entangling by in the Middle, but that yes I knew is not what was going to happen in the next minute. And in this, I call cinema in its purest form. The end is a clear example of this intrigue. The truth is one predicted more or less what will happen from the beginning (by "guilt" of the flash-backs), but the Viewer cannot know what the changing of sides between officials and heads and the sudden final destination of our beloved protagonist.As the only weak point find that any plot or character could have used a little more, but it is true that in a film so everything can not get to be absolutely perfect, because what happens is, somehow, imaginary. And perhaps also highlight that some of the falls, trompazos or the enigmatic protagonist breaks had cost him, in real life, a certain death. And I say that because the scenes that surround these "acrobatics" are shot with a tone very, very realistic. But we must also assimilate this is a spy film and that he is Jason Bourne. What I also fails, and it is not the fault of anyone involved in the film, is the large amount of unnecessary advertising (especially the telivisivos spots) put before release the film. I, unfortunately, knew (not at all) what was going to happen, approximately, in one of the final scenes of "surprise" (because there is more than one). And is that in the Bourne Ultimatum everything just having sense, - almost - everything ends up resolved and many of the characters evolve more in part II. Needless to say that the dialogues that keeps Bourne, especially with Pamela Landy and Nicky, are not only revealing, also inteligentísimos. And that is partly thanks to the wonderful screenplay by Tony Gilroy and company, able to keep you intrigued and tension for almost two hours.And finally, speaking of the extensive and excellent cast. Start, no doubt, by Matt Damon, the absolute protagonist of the film, and that increasingly is becoming best actor. Here suffers, but not put face of agonies. First and foremost, Bourne is a spy hard and strong, but nobody takes his terrible amnesia and its continuous clashes with frightful characters, that you want to or not, just running out (to a spy portrayed realistically, of course). Its interpretation is even better than in the two previous deliveries. In the first we discovered, it was just right in the second and the third we realize saba to do more things that stick smacks, also known as any person. A key scene in the film is when Bourne enters House of the brother of his now dead girlfriend (great Daniel Brühl), where (as it also did in the end of the second) can be witnessed that Jason Bourne has human feelings, which can apologize to someone who has hurt. Highlight above all side David Strathairn and Joan Allen, two veteran actors show that they are the very best of contemporary American cinema. Their looks, their dialogues, their nervous attacks, their clashes. He plays Noah Vosen, a peaceful outside but very manipulative inside character. And she, which we saw in the myth of Bourne, a woman who goes after all and wants, above all, discover the truth either. Also say that Julia Stiles is not so sosa in the second and showing here a more courageous, more humane facet. A good scene where you can witness this change is when she appears for the first time, in a flat in Madrid, scared before the emergence of Bourne, and then, when speaking with him the cafeteria. And not forgetting two veterans not appearing here too: Albert Finney and Scott Glenn (this especially). Performances are great, but that was no doubt. The only actor that is truly untapped is Edgar Ramirez, the character of which could have been a lot more juice. Thus, the distribution of this film is great, with a protagonist that is better than ever and a side of authentic luxury. Greengrass can not complain.The Bourne Ultimatum is a masterful spy film, with a frenetic tone unforgettable and one of the best action sequences for the last years (always accompanied by the sensational score by John Powell). And it is that, first and foremost, the impeccable direction of Paul Greengrass is one of the aspects most highlight of this overwhelming and intense film. And do not forget that the final scene already belongs to the list of the best end of year. Unforgettable, unique. Let us give thanks to Mr. Greengrass for making us suffer during this hour and 51 minutes full of pure film.</body>
</review>
