<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Los 4 Fantásticos y Silver Surfer" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I have no choice but to not rent, buy or get the first part of the fantastic four. Lucky that this second is minimally entertaining and has some good moments (the rest are truly shameful).</summary>
	<body>Horrified was when began the film, with such tremendously bad gags and that impossible production design. I must admit that as it progresses the film I've entertained, but also recognize that, in reality, is a real crappy. And therefore what I summarize in 4 points, which are few. And that I have not seen the first, who say that it is peor.1. The characters, however much that Mr. Story we want to try to show, there is not a shred of personality, and sometimes release each phrase which is to burn them, choke them, leave them stone or wish they become invisible. Or the beautiful Jessica Alba, which here seems more a Barbie cute Nancy Callahan in Sin City, get me to decant for one of these fantastic four. And therefore chosen as the best character to Silver Surfer (despite offer us some truly pathetic scenes - not because of him, also must say-), either because it is new or because so many stupid things like everyone else does. And also let it run to the Victor (of Nip Tuck). 2. The script is one of the worst ever written. It has no sense, neither maintains nor grace. Dialogs are simply pathetic, with some of them you get even feel embarrassed. And what is that Chinese wedding? They will be tacky! This story is really of the simplest I have seen in my life, and look that director is named as it is called. 3. The film itself is more flat than a sheet of carpaccio. At times try belong to this type of movies that are interested in the visual and leave to part the content and the moral, and then walks with bullshit like some I can not mention and claiming to be "deep" or dramatic. Decepcionante.4. and finally, I not want to leave it so, so bad, because there is something that it caught my attention: Visual effects. The truth is that nowadays all these sci-fi blockbusters have an incredible technical section, and I guess that thanks to him many of them are saved from being authentic shit (an obvious example would be the film in question).So I have no choice but to not rent, buy or get the first part of the fantastic four. Lucky that this second is minimally entertaining and has some good moments (this is truly shameful), as London or the forest. And wouldn't let me others four points, this time all positive: the first, Doug Jones as Silver Surfer (in reality this surfboard is a tacky, and I apologize to the fans of the character); the second, special effects; the third, the music of John Ottman; and the fourth, which is relatively short.</body>
</review>
