<review author="Dragon negro" title="TMNT: Las tortugas ninja" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Director Kevin Munroe and the newly created Studio Imagi start with right foot, which makes their upcoming projects, command G or Astro Boy, is wait more eager even.</summary>
	<body>Returning back to the big screen, and after a few notable sequels, Ninja turtles, and this time come fully digitized. Input is appreciated that we never again have the birth of the turtles and as they got their powers and it seems that the previous films have been taken into account to get in position. The story begins one year after that Shredder has been expired, with a few turtles away from their tasks of superheroes and surviving as you can. Leonardo, leader of the band, had just returned after spending a year isolated in a jungle in South America where he was sent to complete his training, Rafael has continued the steps as hero and is dedicated to monitor the streets at night and face hidden crime, which makes that clash with Leonardo by their different points of viewDonatello deals with technical troubleshooting and Miguelangelo masquerading as turtle and performs at children's parties. Each goes to his roll, until a new threat will be that they should again return to fight together.Turtles have grown and are no longer crazy teenagers who were now have real problems of survival and coexistence, and Leonardo will have to try if you can be the leader of the band and not to disappoint his mentor, which brings us a new vision of the characters, more serious and real, turtles do not stop being beings with problems and questions, and each one of them with its own cargo. But not everything is seriously in the film, dumb jokes, action and spectacle. Everything is distributed, a film that will like children who come for the first time to a movie theater to see the characters, both the veterans and nostalgic that we come to see our characters of childhood again.Technical invoice is really successful and it is spectacular at times, and with some very detailed plans and some action scenes that are seen and understood perfectly, while the camera is nothing mareante, although that fails in the same aspect to many productions of this kind, humans are still too reliable.Turtles have a worthy adaptation in this film and also leave you wanting the thing continued in a new film. Director Kevin Munroe and the newly created Studio Imagi start with right foot, which makes their upcoming projects, command G or Astro Boy, is wait more eager even.</body>
</review>
