<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Los 4 Fantásticos y Silver Surfer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To the defined better what search the public a tape of this kind? relax awhile?, production has followed more in this proposal an as lawful as single purpose: entertain without great pretensions.</summary>
	<body>Given the proliferation of adaptations of cartoons heroes, no longer seems so simple that guaranteed success which seemed to bless each film inspiration comiquera when these were exceptions to the rule in the action genre. That is why I surprised this sequel to fantastic four, whose initial chapter I am far in his reception of a thunderous box office success and the welcome of the followers of the creation of the tandem Lee-Kirby.Es more, many of the most devout of this Quartet of Heroes found that introductory chapter of more mediocre. In my case, I've always been more a confessed follower of Spider-man, the tape left me rather cold. The combination of action with digital effects seemed poor and jokes at the expense of squabbles between the human torch and the thing of the weakest.Starting a Ribbon at very low altitude, the improvement was not a titanic mission. And certainly can be considered this second installment an improved version, in all aspects of its predecessor. But because of its adherence to the script set in the first film, the predictable result reduces this to a distracted pastime. I doubt very much that contente to staunch the paper version, but yes I believe that it will provide expected to those who attend the aware of the characteristics of a tape of this type film.Arguably, the film is the richest to focus on one of the most legendary comic in the fantastic four series: the arrival of Star Silver (Silver Surfer) to our planet with the mission to destroy it and the stubborn defence that Reed Richards and his will he face so powerful rival. Also reappears, although in a secondary place, the traditional enemy of the protagonists heroes: Doctor Muerte.El longer footage dedicated to action, at the expense of weak jokes or tramas seudodramáticas as the tension prior to the wedding of Richards (Ioan Gruffudd) and Sue Storm (Jessica Alba), make more bearable and enjoyable viewing of the film. Perhaps here lie the improved result of this the fantastic four and Silver Surfer. To the defined better what search the public a tape of this kind? relax awhile?, production has followed more in this proposal an as lawful as single purpose: entertain without great pretensions.</body>
</review>
