<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Locos por el surf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not, at all, masterpiece that some are saying there, but it is good, excellent in some moments, sparkling in much of the footage, and enjoyable throughout.</summary>
	<body>Funny comedy cartoons, with the world of the surf as the main theme.In it, in this amazing and competitive world, all kinds of characters, is: the Super champion, here stuffing of vanity, the young man who dreams of emulating his late Idol, the inseparable friend, a sparkling Brazilian chicken, the girl fell in love with. All pretty convencional.al least in story to the profile of the characters.That makes it very different from the rest of movies with dibus, is the technique employed to narrate the story. A technique which combines wisely the camera in hand, the flash-back, file images, filming type "Survivors on the island", and the wonderful shots in the water with these superb pranks made by surfers in its grandiose and powerful waves.The film is at all times very entertaining, if somewhat uneven in its pace.The beginning is very good and serves to masterfully portraying various characters, using a wonderful music to emphasize her. Later, and until the character of Geek appears in action, interest is growing and enjoys really.However, with the emergence of Geek, the tape becomes nostalgic and with a point of sentimentality that does not bother, but yes lastra vivid pace hitherto prevailed. Even the humor becomes somewhat and becomes a child (the peculiar tribe of cannibals), undoubtedly to meet (seems to me nda bad) to younger viewers. However, there are great moments, as when Geek attempts to teach Rocky a good surf board manufacturing process, how should be sanded wood. "A moment of rare intensity, carried out with great tenderness, passion and love for the job well done by oneself.""Crazy for the surf" is not, at all, the masterpiece that some are saying out there, but really it is good, excellent in some moments, sparkling in much of the footage, and enjoyable throughout.An animated film advisable for entertainment for the entire family.</body>
</review>
