<review author="José A. Peig" title="Tren de sombras" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the most beautiful films has given the history of the universal film. No we have been able to explain it better; its qualities exceed the capabilities of any analyst.</summary>
	<body>They send us a copy of the film by José Luis Guerin (European production in 1997) accompanied by a warning, because the sender knows that long ago that we are going in search of great findings. Really, now, after the viewing, the palpitation and emotion directs each letter that, to harsh penalties, will try to put in writing what can only be and understood in the eyes of a God that has endorsed the significance of the image, or essence of the film.Of course, we said, not only cinema is technical, art. But art is more than aesthetics, especially when facing certain realizations to grow from an imaginative flight originated in a search so beautiful and placid as driver of the uneasiness that sinks. What we hope to go, without falling into excessive bombast; the seventh art is a mystery, and life is the portion of experienced image which may be seized, or at least we try desperately to apprehend and comprehend.The more I understand, more love, because all covered is good. The more I look look (not see) more love, because every image is hiding something from being. A being in time. A being in space. A being in the memory.Train of shadows is a look at the existence, naked, primordial, but at the same time dig in depth with the light of a watch is aging to find the past, and rejuvenate so that past and present hatch on an x-ray of a world subject to the rules of time and flows of the physical forces in the most recondite spaces of a homewhere nothing and silence are the best place to locate the prospect of a narrator. It is not a "nothing", in reality, it is an aspiration of a creator of images without words (in truth, what need does the world of words, when the film is the gaze of God?), sequences of rhythm and mounting that carry the look on the Tatty tapping on celluloid, to pause mode in which cinema is reborn to shed its light on the days of the life, and you'll see the Sunrise, you'll see in black and white the happiness of a family, you'll see the eyes of a girl who looks the sky, you will see people run through the field, look at the camera as if they knew that behind the camera there is a viewer that the look and makes questions about nostalgia and a sense of the passage of time for decades.The structure of the film is the structure of the lyrical and the "physical" time; from the past in a home full of laughter and silhouettes they do things that only a human can do, so far, the vacuum of the home, the tic tac of a clock that emphasizes the temporal impulse in each room, in each photograph, a curtain moved by the wind and the shadows moving while the sun goes falling on the horizon. Corners of the self. The universe would not be what is if there is a conscious entity that should dealt with its empty. As a poet who asomase his stunned gaze to the rooms, to the living and dining room, or on every shelf or picture: there is nothing, and yet there's something, the mystery, ultimately.The common thread is the same image that focuses the world with consciousness and intentionality, and establishes two fundamental accomplishments: the passage of time has a sensitive complexion, the Viewer may feel the same materiality of the time, of how the abstract can be humongous in an almost empirical feeling induced by the play of images. On the other hand, we have an essentially lyrical film, that uses its structures in order to delve into the metaphysical concept of time, i.e. in the mystery. Construct of time, and time it takes a concrete representation in each sequence. There are more, and it has stressed its intention to restore the purity of the film, but it is also a look at the life and the "depths" of the world. This is something intuitive and no explanation which we tried to give here could clarify the concept: something as simple as showing a floorplan of a street which leads to the river of a life that changes with the evolution of phenomena, or a moviola of images you are looking for - with almost desperate momentum - catch the essence of a face, the face of time, the illusion of retaining a footprint that never dies and the film wants to apprehend to dignify it, to go beyond. To understand life.If it has not been clear, one of the most beautiful films has given the history of the universal film. No we have been able to explain it better; its qualities exceed the capabilities of any analyst.</body>
</review>
