<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="White Noise 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A sequel to whose only virtue is the do that, by comparison, its predecessor seem a masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>Two years ago we had the opportunity to see White Noise (2005), a supernatural thriller with Michael Keaton at the head of the cast that sought to exploit the phenomenon of psicofonías as a basis for a horror story. The film was quite poor in cuanti results, dedicated bad than good to destroy a plot with an enormous potential. As well, two years after that failed attempt becomes White Noise 2: the light (2007), a sequel to whose only virtue is the do that, by comparison, its predecessor seem a masterpiece. I fixed that by the end of this year, this title will appear in several lists made out there with the worst thing that us has fallen through the screens.The title of "sequel" is only nominal, because in principle has nothing to do this film with the first part. Even though mention is made of the exorcism which consisted of argument based on its predecessor, White Noise 2 is a completely different story, this time taking as a starting point other paranormal phenomenon quite controversial and "documented", of near-death experiences. The difference is that, unlike the first part, in this film there is no claim of delve into the supposed reality of this quasi-mystical event, only serving as an excuse for the Assembly of a history that mixture (fairly chaotically) psychic perceptions, Satanic influences and even a Superhero Tale: the protagonist is a man whoAfter being rescued by doctors just before palmarla, begins to perceive a luminous aura that identifies people who will die. Motivated by this new faculty, and believing to have found his true vocation, it is launched to save the doomed poor is day to day, not knowing that alter the plan of death is not something which go unpunished.It is clear that this film makers have mixed a hodgepodge of topics and situations that already had been touched on tapes much better, from flatliners (1990) to final destination (2000), as well as this masterpiece of M. Night Shyamalan which is protected (2000). The problem is that, even more than its predecessor, White Noise 2 has no idea of what kind of movie it is, and shows it shamefully veering from a genus to another without any criterion and generating a terribly confusing and misleading research plot, in which the character almost by chance discovers a terrible curse that surrounds those gifted as him and which has its origins in ultraterrenales areas. Without the slightest decency, the story goes through increasingly ridiculous situations and (this really is unforgivable) is improvising the rules all the time. To make matters worse, the film uses, even from the opening credits (!) to typical cheap scares, those that make you jump from the Chair but after which immediately you parts of laughter. Laughter is also the end, simply incredible by the tacky. Or speak in addition to the vergonozoso resource of inserted "dark" images in a completely free and incoherent way, intended not to the characters, but the Viewer, that Yes, leaving it well obvious that until the most palurdo of the audience so caught. A mockery in any rule.It is impossible to catch this film anywhere, unthinkable to find therein any virtue than that of projecting a light positive on his mediocre first part. In fact, the only positive reviews which has to date received White Noise 2 seem to come unconditional fans of Nathan Fillion, charismatic actor who has earned a legion of fans thanks to his participation in the sadly defunct series Firefly. But even these can not overlook the fact that we have one of the lowest of the year, a direct-to-video that sneaks in the cinemas by mistake (at least, is this the only explanation I have for its premiere).I forgot to mention that the director of this nonsense is Patrick Lussier, sponsored Wes Craven and director of "curious" products as Dracula 2000 (2000). It seems that the bar was not very high after all.</body>
</review>
