<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Turistas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bad very bad, to get bored, no wonder that they have taken centuries (rather leave for the summer it) in release.</summary>
	<body>Welcome to the refried summer!!! There was no originality among many of us goods was by all known, and is that, for a time this part, what it does not copy the Japanese film, is it plagiarism of other films, but sequels, superheroes or the mother who bore them, then to say that it is a tribute (issue fixed).This film is intended to be, without success, that already got "Hostel" (and its sequel) Eli Roth. That is, group of young people with claims of having are deceived and converted into guinea pigs (never better said).John Stockwell is beginning to see "the Duster" with this type of film, and in their hands (and shoulders) are tapes as the insufferable "on the edge of the waves", or the summer "immersion lethal" is this a worthy successor of Uwe Bowl with this crappy summer Court cinema?Josh Duhamel, regular series "Las Vegas" and lately more famous thanks to "Transformers" film and Melissa George (to which I remember as one of the villainous series "Alias" and wife of Ryan Reynolds in "Horror in Amityville" (remake of the film of the 1970s), led by a cast of those in which one expects from the first minute of footage that make how much more "matarile" better and if possible of the) It is cruel and bloody, better than best.I am however good the pretext of the sale of organs, as in vogue in these times in which we are and more in Brazil and Latin America in general (with their dark urban legends), but the impunity of the surgeon is the same rich product of Tarantino would-be killers (and that unlike "Hostel" is not produces). Offices of tourism of Brazil and Slovakia will be contentísimas with the tapes, soon to my was I happened to go to Brazil, but when they begin to kill people me I take the first flight to Barajas.Mala very bad, even bored, no wonder that they have taken centuries (rather leave for the summer it) in release.</body>
</review>
