<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Teresa, el cuerpo de Cristo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I can not say that the tape I has delighted, that he was expecting something stronger, more controversial and voracious from Loriga, and I found something that tries to give wax, without getting to do so at any time.</summary>
	<body>Since that I knew of her conception was expecting something of this film that Ray Loriga (another epileptic as the Holy and a server) has been responsible for bringing to the screen, generating some that another controversy with the Church, which, I imagine that you seeing Paz Vega in the poster imagined the Saint appeared in minor cloth; Unfortunately, and for fans of "the divine" peace come only appears briefly nude. but on his back.I can not say that the tape I has delighted, that he was expecting something stronger, more controversial and voracious from Loriga, and I found something that tries to give wax, without getting to do so at any time, with a strange montage (both Fade in, Fade out, bored to the painted) and where perhaps Paz Vega and Leonor Watling saved from burning (the rest of the cast is simple)(, and seem to be more concerned with the cold of Avila that by being faithful to their roles), that Yes, amazed and open-mouthed has left me the excellent costumes, Eastern Court, created by the winner of an Oscar in 1993 for "The cell", the Eastern Ishioka.Cierto Eiko is that I know little of the life of the Saint, go, what known anyone with a bit of general culture, and that his life and his "ecstasy" (for my epileptic simple attacks) isn't that never have struck me too, although if it is true Monica Bellucci got sit Chair with his Mary Magdalene in Mel Gibson's "the passion", expected that Paz Vega did likewise with the santa de Ávila (sincerely)(fails).Ultimately, a tape that it could have been much more if, and that unfortunately remains in an I want to and I can not do perhaps tape compulsory in schools when they touch the life of the Holy? (or much to tight the LOGSE).</body>
</review>
