<review author="Caty" title="Amanecer de los Muertos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The great triumph of?Dawn of the dead? they are the characters, archetypes with which everyone can feel identified... all are human, quite solid and credible characters if we take into account the genre of the film and what it wants to convey.</summary>
	<body>Creativity and innovation are not exactly words that are happened to me over the head when I knew that it would make a "remake" of the historical "Dawn of The Dead" (1979) by George a. Romero, which is why I asked me one thing: does makes sense do a review of a film of mythical lovers of terror unless you want to take advantage of the pull of the title and thus most capitalize?. And when I finally saw this movie, my question was very pleasantly answered.The great triumph of "Dawn of the dead" are the characters archetypes with which everyone can feel identified, the more cowardly to the bravest of the creeping to the more noble. all characters human, quite solid and credible if we take into account the genre of the film and what it wants to convey. Is also a merit director would not resort to a face of fashion which now populate by Hollywood without anything more than offer than his last romance or her dress at the Oscars gala, but used actors of truth, who really believed her roles as Sarah Polley (the adventures of Baron Münchausen), Ving Rhames (Pulp Fiction)Jake Weber (Pelican), Mekhi Phifer (8 miles), Ty Burell (Black Hawk down) or Michael Kelley (protected), which is stuck in the world of the cinema and people who have made dozens of films, leathers dishes based on hard work. It must also pay attention to the effects of make-up, made by Tom Savini, George a. Romero confidant in the original film.It captures the essence of the first film, with humanity full of zombies, of which nobody knows anything, nor as they left, nor why. a group of people given account are the only survivors of an infested humanity and whose only output is or die or flee to Earth somewhere where everything is still normal, how it took refuge in an abandoned Mall (here the director has portrayed the spirit of the original with a critique of the American hiperconsumista society)(, hence that develops in a typical Yankee Mall) and enjoy capitalism more pure and hard, where have all the amenities that the modern world can give them: clothes, food, dresses, weapons, tools, cars, cash. in the early days do what it seems, but always with the terror of having a much higher outside enemy, anything they serve all these advantages when mankind is destroyed.A couple of details I have bothered a bit and are the only ones. One of them is a fairly common "problem" in the current horror films: the excess of visual "cleansing". It's all very aesthetic, and with that goes the sense of realism that characterizes to the mythical horror films, but I guess that this feature goes with the evolution of the times. Another moment that I did not like is the only detail of "moralina" typical American in the film, a license that does not appear on the original tape: when all the characters decide to flee the mall to try to reach the port and set out to somewhere not infected, one of the protagonists risks his life to save a dog endangering the entire group. in the context of the argument does not fit at all, for me it is the blackest point of the film.</body>
</review>
