<review author="José A. Peig" title="El final del espíritu" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A proper narrative deals with themes of humanitarian, but boarding stays in an idea? wildcard?, well-intentioned but without ability to reformulation or dissection of the fundamental problems.</summary>
	<body>With films like this, so designed in order to give moral, humanitarian or ethical lessons, we must not lose sight of the discursive nature of a not focused narrative to its effectiveness and full realization, but it is subordinate to the same speech. Put another way, the representation splits into two layers; the visual layer and the word. With which we have that the representation is more spoken than imagined (image) representation, and this produces a bias in the final result. A film with which we perceive that its content and development could be equally understood image with or without it, can never be a great movie, because it is more oral discourse that expression of the image (never to be away from the essence of cinema).The voiceover says more than the image itself, and this is also a consequence of the limited visual capacity of filmmaker Jim Hanon, although it is true (and at this point we are faced with the major handicap of the film) that at some key moments looks a great precision: the scene of the deaths at the hands of a few Indians at home did not seem hostile, but resulting in a brutal violence, or the image whose function is the intersection or center of dramatic meaning: one in which we see Mincayani contemplating the photograph of the son of man which was just death, whose crumbling silhouette we see at the bottom of the plane. The same photograph will play a key role in the future, key moment of reconciliation and forgiveness.The truth is that all the elements are well organized in the face to tell one history as they send the canons, at the structural level not can be reproached nothing, the problem is the story unpleasant and typical of the Mannerist narration throughout time wants to control the thoughts of Viewer, and that is something that must never be done when it is a story of a reflexive nature, while their intentions are good.A film about the violence and bitterness, and how is the return to the origin (a wound that started the spiral of violence), and the recognition of violations mutually inflicted, leads us to forgiveness and empathy. What happens is that the speech and thematic background is a topic in itself. Rather, the film itself is flat as a folio, discursive and giving (including religious moralina), too often gets carried away by the precocious and corny, tone in the recreation of the beautiful Amazonian landscape as in the drawing of the loving relationship between father and son (how many times we have already seen the farewell hipermegatópica between a character to be aboard a vehicle - a plane?)(do, in this case - and another character that runs at the time that shouts "I love you", "back" or things like?).Finally, a proper narrative deals with themes of humanitarian, but boarding stays a "wildcard" idea, well-intentioned but capacity of reformulation or dissection of the fundamental problems.</body>
</review>
