<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Action, which be charisma thriller. Although it is fast-paced and packed with good action, it is not less true that it hardly nothing more than that.</summary>
	<body>Third and, for now, last installment of the adventures and misadventures of Jason Bourne, the agent of the CIA suffered from amnesia, it desperately to discover who is in reality.It is for my taste, I do not know if the best looking strict quality film, but the more alive, more agile, the more adrenalítica, with many sequences that remove the hiccups, intense and vertiginous. Perhaps they are too many, this could be his only, but important downside.And it is that, at the end and out, although it is fast-paced and is filled with good action, it is no less true that it hardly nothing more than that. And as we know that, for many blows, shots, explosions, and above all tremendous milks that will stick and they hit you while driving being chased by the "shooter" on duty, who suffers Bourne, can never with him, ending being little more or less than an immortal being.That, in my view, take away credibility or at least likelihood. And stripping emotion and suspense because you know that it will go away with (although go leaving honest corpses on the road, as well as multitude of criminals) and that, although he hit shots and numerous beatings of karate in the body (superb the fight with the "shooter" of Tangier), although magullado, will go away and as much a bit lame and disheveled. This, in the cinema is idem, very spectacular, but has that you can not see from a merely realistic point.Moreover, because exactly like the second installment, also directed by Greengrass. And is, his films, if they provide with perspective, showing that they are identical in the form. Same level, same way of filming, with those affected levels of St. Vitus dance. Come on, not to say that you betray himself in their do different? work.But, anyway, which leaves a good taste in mouth the movie if you like full tapes action rampant (and not very reflective) and we will be waiting (seems to be that for quite some time) for the fourth installment. I do not I care to wait long because honestly I am now a little empachado of the such Bourne, shooters, traitors and his friends.</body>
</review>
