<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El fuego de la venganza" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apocalyptic vision of the guilt and redemption in the costume of a tape of irreproachable, but charisma action altogether.</summary>
	<body>We have seen dozens of movies where the hero is his redemption in the limbo of bourbon. This physical punishment blunting the brain and delete the exercise of memory which, in this case, in the Tony Scott film, is a predictable decline to the hells of war and the latrines of morality of their stretch marks. The narrative pulse of the tape is fragmented into two antagonistic, necessary blocks: one an ex-marine flawed by the excesses and taken refuge in the Bible and the alcohol takes its time in protecting a rich girl bands of kidnappings plaguing Mexico D.F; on the other, what we see is an overwhelming display of blood and revenge, a climax already seen pure film adrenalítico, mounted with the dash and the claw that Scott signed his films (love at point-blank range, put for example). The existence of the second part is an inevitable consequence of the first and it is understood that, to greater degree of tenderness and humanism in the strokes of a thunderous and unbound will be those who pincelan the course of another. The surly, airtight and unsympathetic bodyguard full Charter, seeking to atone for their sins in the lines of Scripture, is a girl seeking her still honest part, the hidden man in the shell. Defense mechanisms, once defeated, offer a beautiful film of characters added formidably described (the writer of L.A. Confidential or Mystic River, Brian Hengeland work), but then the fireworks of revenge illuminates a sky less artistic and more in line with the fireworks of the film as a window to other world. This is manly and sparsely metaphorical: Peckinpah style. Scott plans to his films as a long video clip (two and a half hours, in this case) and has access to the universe of advertising, where they came to favor the visual impact on the narrative sanity, denying the essence of the story and his purely literary discourse to fall into the trap of subjecting the entire weight of the plot in the technical architecture of your, in any case, dubious professional efficiency. Worse it would have been if Michael Bay had taken the reins of this matter, which appears that it was about to be tristísima reality. Anyway, so we will never know.The appalling spiral of violence unleashed by the kidnapping of Pita Ramos, an incredible Dakota Fanning, raises many ethical dilemmas in the viewer interested in be carried away by the socio-political implications of a direct film that not censorship more explicit barbarism and where you can attend warmed-over dialogues on the interference of God in human affairs. Rusty photography by Paul Cameron, the abusive use of slow motion, the fracture of visual continuity with incessant levels unrelated to natural events spinning or the Baroque palette of grossly subjective levels confirms that Tony Scott is a very personal, recognizable, equipped with an undeniable talent to capture the viewer's attention, but nothing of this recitation benefits granted to be an author close to excellence. I had the painful sensation of that, although I was liking the film, was eager to of that ended: perhaps was sobrevitaminado of fire, the dark network of crime investigation Mexican or simply exhausted by this hectic thesis on pain and guilt, on the ethics of violence, ultimately. Tarantino tends to check a similar product, but not enfanga in mixing mystical revelations, centuries past and this aesthetic to the mtv ending fatigando too much. Campechano fascistoid tone here encouraged does not deserve further reflections: we have come to see a vigorous extravaganza, which it is, and to see to what extent the American film, who both love you, passes funds from catalog and continues offering the same story. Because the fire of vengeance, despite the melodramatic novelty and the pastelón of its first half tone, is a greasy exercise of violence, pleasant to the curious eye, but not overly worthy for the measured sieve of memory. Ah, the soundtrack (Gregson-Williams) exudes an eclecticism that is so outstanding that it ends up being deficit. The passages of great orchestral masses, drum n' bass buffered or folk guitar and local lamentation incursions despitan staff to the point that McLean viewing.</body>
</review>
