<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Cars" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Create an imaginary able to challenge this desire of glory the sense has more value than it seems.</summary>
	<body>Despite funny are the stories of Pixar, its protagonists always pose serious problems that can be stated as something like "what place I take I in the world?". "Toy Story 2" posed if Buddy wanted to be a toy or object of exhibition, the "Bugs" comicos had to decide if they were going to be clowns or heroes in "Buscando a Nemo" Nemo has to choose between a tank and an ocean, in "The Incredibles", Mr Parr has to decide between being an insurance agent or a superhero. Lightning McQueen, the protagonist of Cars, has to choose between the selfish life of triumph, and friendship.Lightning McQueen seems above all to the Buddy of "Toy Story 2". In a world like ours so mindlessly obsessed with fast television fame is an act of courage to defend the anonymous life of townspeople. To Mr incredible asked his wife why she wanted to do things by him. What sense does the lone hero? In a Pixar film the hero is always the friendship.McQueen is poised to Los Angeles to win the piston Cup that will make you famous when he/she loses at the legendary Route 66 and then forgotten radiator Springs Village. Forced by the Court to perform social tasks by an infringement, McQueen will meet a group of neighbors that has nothing to do with his own world. Sally Carrera, the girl, Luigi and Guido, two Italian cars who admire only the Ferrari, Mate, the horny of the place, which has fun scaring, tractors, and the mysterious Doc Hudson. Each character has something that makes them endearing and something that ties it to the lost people. McQueen will be descubriendolo little by little. Does radiator Spring something for him? Is there anything more important than fame? Many criticise American cinema his obsession for the triumph. Therefore, create an imaginary able to challenge this desire of glory the sense of a film has more value than it seems.The new invention of Pixar is valid by all the human background and dazzling for all the expressive vehicle which has been used to transmit it: nostalgia for the 1950s, double readings, coche-persona, tractor-vaca, marks, progress, the objectification of the competitions, the recreation of a world made for cars.</body>
</review>
