<review author="Dragon negro" title="White Noise 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The idea of the film is not entirely wrong and could have given more than not to be by a painful direction of Patrick Lussier, responsible for this mess, get, come to some extent, boredom and tiredness.</summary>
	<body>To begin, saying that it has little to do this film with its predecessor, the film starring Michael Keaton that was already of if something loose, whereupon, there were not many expectations from this sequel.A man looks at a restaurant and no apparent reason appears a stranger who kills with a pistol to his wife and his son and then commits suicide. To overcome it, you'll end up committing suicide, but they will save at last moment in the hospital. After this ECM (near death experience), he starts to notice and see strange things, and discovers that he is able to predict the death of a person through the aura that sees in them. It will soon begin to save lives on the brink of death, which will make you feel much better, but that ignores is that each life-saving brings terrible consequences.The idea of the film is not entirely bad, and might have given for something more than not be by a painful cheap TV address full of cheap and surplus embellishment, incapable of creating tension and interest during the footage. Patrick Lussier, is responsible for this mess, abuse scare easy and predictable at the same time, with the appearance of ghosts and bloody faces when he want, getting, come to some extent, boredom and tiredness.A shame as a harmful direction for a script which if it had found better director had been able to become somewhat correct, but does not pass of mediocre. I guess that the participation in the project of two actors on the rise as Nathan Fillion, the unforgettable captain of the Serenity, and Katee Scackhoff, the intrepid pilot of Galactica, has done that this sequel end premiered in theaters, rather than direct to DVD, which is where corresponded.</body>
</review>
