<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Effective film of persecution rather than well orchestrated for enjoyment of every lover of the genre.</summary>
	<body>Postmodern cinema we were accustomed to giving up the possibility even suggest the absurd idea that every hero has, like the rest of mortals, a past life and? less - that that life influence decisively in its future actions (save the world from bad very bad, knowing men and dazzling, traveling to exotic places with all expenses paid)(, and one handful of benefits that have that be postmodern hero).The case of the saga Bond exemplified with justice. Never mind the past life of James (name cliché of the elegant, cultured type and with resources that crazy woman is crossing). What interests the Viewer is see how Bond, James Bond, and again displays their stereotypes effectively, and without disheveled, tainting the suit or aging. Because? that is the truism - the postmodern hero never dies or is subject to natural laws that we unfortunately endure mortals of a foot. If it were not so it would lose its fascination.Those Greeks who listened to their elders the Homeric deeds of Ulysses, Hector, Achilles and the entire family of Greek heroes of insurance were also fascinated by the strength, perseverance and perfection of these demigods. If any of us had even tried to emulate one of their smallest deeds, not would have left well stopped them at the first start. The postmodern hero is a hero because it concentrated all those qualities that mortals would like to possess. But the Greek hero was not hero just for being different (or better) than mortals; his heroism was only proven and immortalized if he assumed his destiny, a destiny which in most cases ended in death. Even the Christian hero par excellence just after the Greek model of hero and just crucified. The life of the classic hero is not therefore a bed of roses. You must first reflect on himself, finding inside the necessary knowledge about its nature, and so act accordingly. The Greek heroes are some patterns, but are also honest and intelligent. And without this attribute would not be a mere Rambo.El current film begins to opt for more traditional models of hero, in which occurs a process of internal search to become what later will demonstrate that they have never ceased to be. The hero is forged, does not arise on our screens from scratch, as suggested by the postmodern film. See if no cases like the Nolan Batman, Bond Campbell or this Bourne that closes the trilogy of the absent-minded hero slowly regaining its past (i.e., their identity, their humanity). Do even Spiderman Raini? a hero naif of advertisement - explores in his memory to mend his hero role.Bourne, unlike Bond, is a less focused hero to do its work of secret agent with a license to kill, and more inclined to know how and why became who is. Bourne needs to know it. But Bond is and will always be Bond. And nobody seemed to mind him from where comes this gentleman until Campbell came up digging in his past, offering us a job deconstructive on the old postmodern hero who begins to need a facelift image.Bourne, like the Nolan Batman, builds his heroism on the basis of the acceptance of his tragedy or their fears. They are both heroes that have a shadow that haunts them and which in turn makes them react and do what they do, beyond the rest of mortals, delivered to an eternal present without remission. Now, Bourne closes with this third installment its ability to exist as a hero, that after knowing and renege on their status of killer, you no longer need more trips in search of its identity. The classic hero must always die.Not without narrative intentions one of the promotional posters located in Bourne on his back, offering the viewer a clear metaphor for the memory of the hero.Out of this short reflection on the nature of the hero, it must be said that the Bourne Ultimatum is an effective film of persecution rather than well orchestrated for enjoyment of every lover of the genre. They are those persecutions which make more tragables the scenes in which an anything emotional (as always) Damon seeks answers to a question that viewers already have resolved or would ignore with great pleasure. And is the third installment of the raids of this killer for the greater glory of the State that does not want to be more than he himself only gave for this: a good action movie, with a mise en scène that keeps us attached to the seat. What else can request? why the two murderers who persecute Bourne are Arabs? Why not be let see a bit more of Madrid? Why Damon only performs decently when you child that seems good but not?</body>
</review>
