<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El Club de los Suicidas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The suicide Club is loosely zafia, vulgar and lacks any grace. In short, is a perfect example of the State of Spanish blockbusters.</summary>
	<body>We live in a world of fools, in which we are all with the nerves to the skin surface, and when the Queen the order of political correctness, she is not going to be that someone is offended by a simple comment. Where these effects are most noticeable is in the comedy, where the authors themselves are tied hands so as not to disturb to certain groups. But, what or who decides what is really offensive or simply an ironic or satirical joke without malice?Anyone who knew the path of Roberto Santiago, would expect to find in the Club of the suicide a pretty crazy and wacky comedy. Instead, you'll see a film quite correct politically, what about the issue of suicide gingerly by not trivialize with a serious theme. It should be reminded Roberto Santiago the last work of maestro Billy Wilder, here a friend, hilarious dialogue on suicide it held Woody Allen all say I Love You, or attempts to a Bill Murray trapped in time. This is perhaps the worst flaw in the Club of the suicide, but unfortunately it is not the only one. By his ambivalence between drama and comedy, the tape not never ends boot, and at no time attracts the interest of the viewer with enough intensity. The script does not help for anything with a few characters that happen to be mere empty cartoons, and a few own the mindless adolescent film dialogues. All the care that had not offend anyone with suicide lost it as soon as they deal with other topics, much more given to the easy and rude joke. But we know that nothing wrong with offend certain groups of our society there is. As for the actors, little can expect of them with similar characters and dialogue. Only saved from burning Luis Callejo, that brings the few really funny moments that has the film.The suicide Club is loosely zafia, vulgar and lacks any grace. In short, is a perfect example of the State of Spanish blockbusters. Perhaps, if Roberto Santiago would have left aside the easy joke and had opted more for the wacky comedy, the result would have been better.</body>
</review>
