<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="White Noise 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Painful sequel to a painful tape which becomes doubly painful experience. And there will be third punishment. Will we be masochists?</summary>
	<body>Into slaughter, conjurado to make something positive of this hodgepodge of acústico-imbécil inspiration - is the first time that marriage those two adjectives, perhaps not the last-, White noise 2: the light escapes from the trash of terrifying intent covering the expectations of many teenagers aborregados and eager for strong emotions which release them its insipid leisure of last generation consoles. There is no barbies of generous chest fleeing a spasmodic psycho-killer.There is no incipient acne heroes pivoting between the love to the presumed victim and the censorship of their venereal impulses. Why this summer film we install a higher stage: on the sparsely demanding adult who feels comfortable in the role of compulsive consumer of anything supernatural vocation. Gives equal come ghosts of middling, esoteric conspiracies or Merovingian secrets hidden in a basement for at least a thousand years. Literature amply supplied these frivolous exercise of historical foolish. I said literature and perhaps should have used another word less noble. Something similar happens with the film. I have no doubt that this film is film, of course, but is so brazenly invoiced for their consumption and so far from artistic parameters that would need to go looking for another word that accommodate her. Film, understood as something intelligent and beautiful, there is no or perhaps I had not taken the day more appropriate to appreciate it and, indeed, true cinema located by one of their frames and to me, what going you to do, I caught yawning, slightly closing the eyes, thinking in something else, friends I don't see long or the time that makes that not floor a Museumfor example.This history of premonitions and more or less achieved hearing scares has no heart or soul. Brain not to engage in an honest conversation. Everything gets carried away by this hobby already niponizar hartible terror and give height fantasmagoria packaging, when what they achieved is to surrender an infamous hodgepodge of mediocrity sold as Excellencies, pathetic scares and characters debilísimos, barely sustained by an invisible fabric that stretches to get bored and wish end of the footage and one can go into the blessed Street and breathe the urban realitythat is more prosaic than the string of lies told to us, but which excites infinitely more. The supernatural genre, that they are trounced by regardless, is likely to become telefilm desktop balance, although (ay) notes of production I've read after seeing the tape insist in the novelty of the special effects and the exquisite love professed by the entire team by this kind of argument. They have therefore blunder, and have a little more enfangado the summer Billboard, which shines neither in excess. But that already knew.</body>
</review>
