<review author="José A. Peig" title="Criaturas celestiales" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Extraordinary storytelling, prosaic and poetic at the same time, where fantasy and reality form a whole depending on which explains why a tragedy without justifications or superfluous moralizing.</summary>
	<body>When the film is loosely based on real events it is common that the product should take a simplistic and schematic turn which makes that the representation be limited to a narrative that emphasizes the sensibleros or morbid aspects at the expense of the penetration and reflection on a few facts of extraordinary brutality, which would be the highest goal for the creation of artistic aims - or at leastIt should do so - to shed light on the incomprehensible aspects of human behavior. "Heavenly creatures", Peter Jackson gives all a lesson of film and effort in what is undoubtedly his best creation.The torments and the innocence of the adolescent impulse are presented through two women's souls equipped with a characterization between the plausible and idyllic, between tenderness and sinister, in a descriptive account of a relationship and a progressive obsession love between two souls to hatch because of its peculiarities and its desire for freedomwhich collide against the Puritan moral of the New Zealand society of the 1950s. The remarkable pace visual, like a sober and quite devoid of exaggerated tricks expressiveness, result in a narrative that cohesiona fluidity tones and themes with enormous versatility: the mystery of love and sex, generational conflicts, the imagination as a way to sublimate or subjugate the stark reality, the sarcastic with that tone often represents adults with a nude look at adolescence and their vulnerability, the magic of fantasy with the sinister desire to kill to achieve freedom of actions and thoughts. Life as literature and literature as a method to idealize life itself. History heartbreaking about two souls great and hypersensitive to degenerate toward an act criminal and macabre precisely so the magic never, end the fire of eternal friendship and love, or rather, that fantasy and pre-adolescent hope that dreams of a higher life despite the threat of the adult world.Peter Jackson does not yield and ends his story without Manichaeism or pretensions clear of facile of any kind, without using other words of the own image of two souls who suffer from the fear of loss and separation, symbolized with a farewell obliged after committing an act that will condemn them forever. We are surprised when we hear news about children who kill their parents, and tend to simplify using explanations such as evil or insanity. The film, in this case, expresses the contradictory dimension of the human condition, the complexity that arises when the feelings clash against reason and ideologies against the ideas or dreams of immature minds; how the magic and fantasy, and love and friendship (the luminous dimensions of life) can lead us to more sinister corner of existence. We are angels and demons, "Heavenly creatures", so vulnerable, that end up shaping their own hell for wanting to win the sky.Extraordinary storytelling, prosaic and poetic at the same time, where fantasy and reality form a whole depending on which explains why a tragedy without justifications or superfluous moralizing.</body>
</review>
