<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Caótica Ana" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Caótica Ana is a film that does honor to its title, a chaotic and frenetic journey that confuses the spectator, and in which Julio Medem is not recognized anywhere.</summary>
	<body>The day that were confirmed preparations for the filming of Caótica Ana was a great day for the Spanish film. We recuperábamos to one of our largest creators, Julio Medem, plunged into a deep depression, among other reasons, by savage persecution which underwent by certain sectors of the political and public life by his documentary the Basque ball: the skin against the Piedra.El film by Julio Medem is difficult to describe, since that symbolic, poetic elements and even magicalthey have always been very present in his films. But Caótica Ana is situated one step beyond. The story tells of the life of Ana (Manuela Vellés), a young artist who arrived in Madrid to make their dreams reality. However, Ana saves power, a hidden danger in your subconscious in his peaceful life in Ibiza could suppress, but which is now coming out afloat. Julio Medem is one of the most personal authors of Spanish cinema, and to understand his works and appreciate them, have to be carried away by its history and its characters. With Caótica Ana does not pass the same, even though the Viewer do your part, is impossible to connect with the characters or less with the journey of protagonist, Ana and its chaos. As it is advancing the film, the trip becomes a frantic free fall that drags the audience to unexpected places, in which nothing makes sense. The tape is full of symbols and metaphors, but on this occasion rizan curl in such a way that nobody is able to accept them or let alone understand them. The entire film is narrated through a countdown, which makes the public feel as if it was the protagonist of a bad dream that wants to wake up as soon as possible. Never recognizes the style by Julio Medem, a dark and suffocating, atmosphere with some really unpleasant and unbecoming of the San Sebastian film sequences. What do abound are the nod to earlier, like sex and Lucia, or directors as John Ford. For its part, Manuela Vellés performs a very natural work, although he cannot hide his clear lack of interpretative skills.Caótica Ana is a film that does honor to its title, a chaotic and frenetic journey that confuses the spectator, and in which Julio Medem is not recognized anywhere. It's a very intimate and personal travel for the director, certainly very necessary, and which we hope exit strengthened to cope with their upcoming projects.</body>
</review>
