<review author="José A. Peig" title="Caótica Ana" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Medem does not intend to go to another port that which finally arrives, which is already an achievement, and his film, in short, is an exercise in style of content and an essay rather than a conventional work.</summary>
	<body>In tribute to his sister, Julio Medem tells this story about a young Bohemian artist who suffers an experiential process, in the narrative level, while it is true that admittedly the allegorical intention which is the true raison d ' être of the product. The final significance is closer to the capricious construction of an archetype of femininity, related to the myth of the female soul that rises from the ashes produced by human violence. There is no shortage nor the totemic elements, in this case birds, in an account of a marked turn indigenist.The art, the philosophical pretensions, sex, the intellectual and vital undefined post-modern generations as well as the feeling of lacking a point of reference from which identify the purpose of a life, or the nonsense of their own, the varied elements configured keys of a film that moves between the purpose of being an x-ray of a female soul, and in its more abstract manifestation, the progressive birth of Anne's totemic and heroic. What is curious, in any case, are the ingredients chosen by Medem to characterize his girl, which are the least interesting thing about the film that they are part of the ideology of the author (or honored sister) and reveals certain Mannerist tics which deplete fairly discourse, as we shall see.Above all, it is clear that Medem builds a proper structure to represent a progression from the girl who lives in a cave with his father, passing by their emancipation in Bohemian circles of Madrid, knowledge of frustrated love, travel by boat to New York, and its final ripening for a whole process of chaotic existence. The transformation of Ana is given by a confluence of factors that rallan towards popular beliefs of the thought "new age", such as reincarnation, hypnosis and the return of the Mother goddess. The search for female purity contrasts with a passage from representation performance in which the protagonist loose a rant about women as element that perverted the creation and the ascent to God.Through hypnosis, Ana reveals the experiences of different women at different times, all of them belonging to the indigenous area, as well as the nexus between her and her lover Sahrawi. All these elements are those of the counterculture jipi and other anti-establishment movements, and that Medem subordinate the speech with a fairly irregular, effective result in some passages due to coherence and development of the above reasons, but sometimes drift in an inevitable simplifications.See the peak of the narrative, when the rebel diosa-heroína-is faced with a very hateful, American Tycoon he because it supports the conflagration in Iraq (do?!), a Lord of war painted with a "buenista" speech that causes blushed for a typical simplifications of the politically correct: "even the bad guys have something good in your interior". We then see the own protagonist deposit feces on the face of the Lord of war, a kind of revenge and ridicule of the rival through the delirium in the most violent and Resolutive passage. Finally, the misfortunes of the world are not arranged in this way, but according to Medem, that was the most beautiful of paying tribute to his sister. You will see.Final images, in which we see Anne walking the streets of New York after his feat of integration and its totemic power maximum expression as fémina which brings together the pain of other women in other times and places, with that smile of mischievous satisfaction, expresses the idea of an innocence lost time back at sea in Ibiza and in the cave of the abandoned father with sobrietyto become cynical and rebellious goddess. It is a product of society, or what society deserves it.Overall, is a very personal and interesting proposal with a very careful staging and a display which emphasizes the dreamy, sensual sensations in perfect coherence with a speech that calls for things like the dream, delirium, parapsychology, elements that sometimes seem stuck with a shoehorn but functionally valid if we look at the final result, its coherence. Medem does not intend to go to another port that which finally arrives, which is already an achievement, and his film, in short, is an exercise in style of content and an essay rather than a conventional work. You may like more or less (who writes this recognizes that the film has been boring at times), but regardless of tastes, the correctness and clarity of ideas is evident in its resolution overlapped with the beginning.</body>
</review>
