<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La buena estrella" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ricardo Franco carefully nurtured country these three distressing characters always bordering the pathos, the undeniable harshness of a life in solitude and the negation of all joy, abismada victims of the tyranny of the heart.</summary>
	<body>A wounded man writes better about the nature of his injury. Something like this should think Ricardo Franco when Pedro Costa proposed it burn the good star. Almost blind, sick, vulnerable, Ricardo Franco filmed La buena estrella, the misadventure of the manso, the one and the pretty face with intimate satisfaction be narrating a complete work, literary adhesions and incontrovertible hardness. As life itself. It is not possible that isn't hard life when you aspire to find happiness and only find disenchantment, desolation, hardship and moral misery. All this should think of Rafael, the butcher, (Resines), a good person, a man without qualities to what Musil which zarandea his routine life of neighborhood with the arrival of Marina, a pregnant prostitute (Verdú), which he hosts, mima and considers the fundamental step to build a family. What otherwise, he wondered. Daniel (Molla) is the offender boyfriend, the hanged man, the necessary evil for the goodness of the history avails itself to the traditional mechanisms of the melodrama, which here are nobly amplified, written with grief, played with heart and served in a filmic device impeccable, oblivious to the passage of time, soaked sentiments as few films. This very crude x-ray of pain is also the Testament formidable (black tears not was completed entirely) of a man devoted to the film and to the diffusion of culture as something great. Let me not explain otherwise. Ricardo Franco carefully nurtured country these three distressing characters always bordering the pathos, the undeniable harshness of a life in solitude and the negation of all joy, abismada victims of the tyranny of the heart and patients Guinea Pigs their sad litany.And still I do not know anyone who has seen the movie without a lump in the throat. And today, not being this enthusiastic chronicler of his eyes in the patriotic film, I have not seen more poignant movie. You can make a movie with these twigs, but not a more lyrical.</body>
</review>
