<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="La casa del lago" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I cried as if I had dead boyfriend, but the story does not have nor ton or they are and raises a number of inconsistencies that make it a great nonsense</summary>
	<body>I have just returned from the announced movie La Casa del Lago (2006) which marked the reunion of one of the most popular movie couples: Sandra Bullock and Keanu Reeves and this editor can not more than say the following: PLOP! (Condorito style, I demand an explanation!)In the last post, a comment left by one of our editors, Oli, indicated that the film was hiperromántica and in fact, I have to agree. Even I must admit that I cried as if I had dead boyfriend or they hit my favorite pet. Peroooo. The story does not have nor ton or they are and raises a number of inconsistencies that basically makes a great nonsense. That Yes, a great romantic Super nonsense.To me I bought with the reference of impossible love that makes the book persuasion of my favorite now and always, author Jane Austen (author of the fabulous pride and prejudice which was adapted for the big screen last year).Kate (Bullock), a lonely doctor and Alex (Reeves), a romantic architect, are perfect for the other. Both love the Lake House and are owners of the same dog (Jack). But the great but with this story is that Alex lives in 2004 and Kate in 2006 in the period are known via correspondence through the "magic" box of the Lake House. Since the approach without further explanation can notice the Rocky ** may be the story. Why, yes they will see, go with the intention of seeing a fantasy and not try to understand this illogical plot.His love that starts in 2004 will have to stand the test of time and wait until 2008 to materialize. Why not in 2006 which is when Kate falls for Alex? Because by pure whim of the writer. See her and realize of because I say this. In fact it is more dramatic and romantic that the protagonist has waited for her four years. Well, that to me made me moquear like crazy. It is certainly an effect well Austen, which seems to be having much success today.Drew me attention to the director, the Argentine Alejandro Agresti, who seems to have happened to the ranks of Hollywood with great support. For more references, he was the director of A night with Sabrina Love.Otra thing that has left me: OHHH, is the fact that Sandra Bullock and Keanu Reeves have not aged anything since that made Speed in 2004, more than one decade ago. Pact with the devil? Another point in favor of the film is the beautiful photography and architectural beauties which shows the great city of Chicago.Una actress in a supporting role in the story is Shohreh Aghdashloo who already saw action notably in the House of sand and fog. The casting of the Lake House was going well until that they chose for the lousy actor, Ebon Moss-Bachrach as the dreamy brother of Alex. Also little exploited is the history of love-hate of brothers with their father, but well, this is perhaps a problem of Edition, which have cut more scenes which had to meet a defined length. This is my speculation is in mystery disappearance of Alex age, prior to 2004. Data: The film is based on another Korean film Il Mare or Siworae. I would like to see this original version, there is a little more consistent.</body>
</review>
