<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The pace of almost constant urgency not leaves no room for boredom, but so much speed going to the detriment of a more substantive account.</summary>
	<body>There are few findings that the amnesiac spy Jason Bourne (Matt Damon) makes in this third film about their identity prior to entering the military program Treadstone. The Bourne Ultimatum, directed by Paul Greengrass with nerve, verismo and rigor that are themselves, maintains intact the structure of the spy flight constantly harassed by a large rotten fabric of the CIA. Bourne is still not know much, but begins to tying up while in the dome of the American spy agency there is nervousness before a possible and compromising uprising of carpets. In sum, and without wishing to be simplistic, you could say that the game of mouse and cat offered in two previous deliveries remains the leit-motiv of the last sequel of the character created by novelist Robert Ludlum.Montaje agile, nervous movements of camera and exemplary score by John Powell for seasoning the joint are the main guarantees of these tapes of action shot style Greengrass. A style consistent with the first film directed by Doug Liman (now executive producer of the two continuations) but improved by the sober varnish of British director. In addition, the prospect of a European filmmaker seems key in a realistic and identifiable recreation of the locations used in the follow-up of the itinerant Bourne. If to all this we add a Pleiad of magnificent actors, led by the talented Matt Damon and supported by side luxury as Albert Finney, Joan Allen, Scott Glenn, Brian Cox or the last to join the list, a master David Strathairn, the result is a function of spies of high quality film and located one step above the average in its genre.Despite all its virtues technical and interpretative, tape weakens in its history. The structure of persecution and flight ends to make the story into a loop where only change the landscapes of Fund (different European train stations and two buildings of the CIA in Langley) and the enemies of Bourne by the pursuing party. Is true that the pace of almost constant urgency not leaves no room for boredom, but so much speed going to the detriment of a more substantial story. Discover small details of the biography of the main character prior to its transformation into Jason Bourne, they will suggest us that the use of this as a murderer on behalf was much more chilling inferred in the previous chapters, but not much more progress this story whose epilogue leaves the door open for possible future sequels. Not in vain, Robert Ludlum, who died in 2001, endorsed author Eric Van Lustbader to continue writing about this character that has already published two novels after the death of the latter: The Bourne Legacy (2004) and The Bourne Betrayal (2007). I suspect that, given its good reception on the big screen, film will be followed by interested tell more things about this enigmatic spy joined already, by its own right, the collective imagination with renowned colleagues as the legendary 007.</body>
</review>
