<review author="Silvia Giner" title="La última legión" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film has absolutely nothing worthwhile, to go to see it, do not recommend, as well is that do not waste your time or your money.</summary>
	<body>The film is absolutely predictable, is boring until the absurd and battles are pure garbage. Yes, I admit, the topic of as the great Scalibur reached the rock and as Pendragon had Arthur and everything else is original, it is, but it could have been a great movie that the script is not overly stinky but good movie of popcorn at the end and a niño-actor that puts the same face for everything, everything interprets equalgo shit casting, with good children there.Director Doug Lefler, does not have much shooting in the body, his career focuses on directing a chapter of Xena, Hercules (among others) and that Yes, long Story Board, the kid the Story that has eaten in all the years of profession, notice you.The film has absolutely nothing worthwhile, to go to see it, do not recommend, as well is that do not waste your time or your money.But all this crappy surrounding "The last Legion" (whose trailer is misleading) is due to that the movie has wanted to do quickly and to get out of the way and kill 4 birds with one stone. This film meant an investment in some studies and Hollywood producers seeking to consolidate and launch new products in the film market.And so that you may know that I speak, I come with my section despelleje: what do do in Hollywood when want to launch new talent to the market? Answer: Make a crappy type "The last Legion" where the actores-productos to be launched suck close-up sometimes even absurd and misplaced.And you will wonder is it really profitable the Gringos to do a bad movie only to promote actors?Answer: Obviously yes because each of those actores-producto be one devoted through several peliículas is already filming or signed and that will bring them millions of dollars to the producers who work with them and must also take into account that "The last Legion" won't be a taquillazo but bear the investment has meant, whicheveryone wins. At the end and after all this is a negocio.¿Y who are the actors-product that we are talking about? 1 - Colin FirthQue has given nothing more and nothing less than 7 movies for sale of which 2 of them are foresee as taquillazos, what end conviertiendolo definitely in a new Clive Owen, with what will be the end disassociate from the genus televisimo to which he has devoted most of his atística career. It is the largest investment of this film.2 - Aishwarya RaiUna women's most spectacularly beautiful of all time. Of the few comparable with the great divas of the classic film. Imported from Bollywood where is a consecrated star, his leap and consolidation in Hollywood her become a new Angelina Jolie. It is also an excellent actress of action which will mean that it unseat the pusilámines to win roles of heroin and super women. Aishwarya is full of talent and is a polished diamond ready for display. Its participation in upcoming productions will be rewarded with millions of dollars. You have 2 pending release, including American films "the Panther pink 2".3 - Rupert FriendDestinado to become the new Orlando Bloom (that is you has posted fame to the head and walk asking a priceless cache). This young man who has become confused on many occasions with Orlando it is also noviete of Keira Knightley and the paparazzi as conundía with Orly. The first levels that get you in "The Legion últims" come on, look good, are estudiadísimos to make the most of its beauty as their destination will be the sexual icon of all adolescents in the next 5 years. His career is composed of 6 films made between 204 and 2007 and has for sale other 6 all made in 2007 and 2008 (just after "the last Legion", what a coincidence).You do not quejaréis of the doctoral thesis in despelleje that I have made in this critique in addition if you are sensible I shall give the reason.</body>
</review>
