<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Caótica Ana" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting but not fully convincing work by Julio Medem.</summary>
	<body>Curious and interesting work by Julio Medem, which continues with their particular world where unites past, present and future, reality, dreamy scenes, dreams, fantasies, painful realities and loves catalysts, this full of symbols and metaphors. To begin my comment I have to say that I liked and entertained, mention of excited in a couple of scenes. Only a couple, it is true. And if you start saying this is because I then also say that not me has convencido.del all.This, without doubt, is for the particular way of telling by Medem, that if well in "Red squirrel" and "Sex and Lucia" it was so prodigious, in "Caótica Ana", sometimes, tends to the mental dispersion and to flourish too much, the free narrative will.Thus, mingle excellent scenes, such as the various deaths of Ana in their past lives and the reunion and dance with her father, with others that must accept because Yes, as the appearance of Ana in the boat of the father of her best friend. A moment shown magical way, but without greater logical sense. As I say, you must accept, but there is no doubt that it is very strange and why, perhaps unacceptable for the more conventional Viewer.Maybe the tape is without doubt, the printed strength in images, with a masterful prologue, a magnificent use of music and a superb work of mounting. In its negative side, in addition to the already above, some facts that do not contribute too much to the plot.However I her advocate because I believe that dramatic intensity as well as the pace is of less to more. For this reason, and seeing the epilogue of the story, I think that the taste is more than acceptable when not good (in my case). However, this film is the clear example of tape which, if not you enter from the outset in the history and accept the narrative of its author, disconnect and let you either indifferent or worse still, very disappointed.So, I think honestly the final grade her must place more than ever, the own Viewer.To my have worked me effectively holds Medem best job, but I think it is a very estimable movie I guess will be revalued over time.What I absolutely disagree is in the comments pointing to that this film does not acknowledge just nothing of the previous Medem. Man, I think Yes! The items listed are common in all of his works. What might change (think that not too) is the way to expose them.</body>
</review>
