<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Next" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Worst of all is that the seemingly interesting end is nothing more than an absurd theory that I doubt very much that Dick had told it that way.</summary>
	<body>Having a notable premise, Lee Tamahori Next, director of the justita die another day, fails to engage the public in any of his apparently attractive moments, which are sequences of action. Note, perhaps what me more motivated this tape are the moments where Chris (a sosísimo Nicolas Cage) sees what will happen in a while (either 2 minutes, 2 hours or so that Tamahori happens at that time). First and foremost, Next is a film without sense, consistency and just pace. And then, friends, think: who is the dreaded writer? Well now I do not remember, or feel me like looking at it, but what I do know is that it is based on a novel of the legendary Philip k. Dick, author of novels that have been adapted to film with absolute mastery such as Minority Report or Blade Runner. And worst of all is that the seemingly interesting end is nothing more than an absurd theory that I doubt very much that Dick had told it that way.Ridiculous to say enough is enough, without just a decent Julianne Moore (his role is more cold, distant and unfriendly and not even has a reason to be so) and a Jessica Biel, the only thing that is as to show off body (and to provide two hours of time to the protagonist, I do not even remember!). It is that which has made the mount is an authentic ACE of bad movies, because you don't have a single scene linked with the following elegant way. Even the opening credits are sopopíferos! And it is a pity, because the trailer not promised so little and had a trio of stars of good quality (well, Moore is one greater thing and Cage when he gets succeeds). But I do not know what damn trick did Tamahori to make such crappy no feet or head with a very bad staging (except when are locating the bomb at the end) and with a few action scenes too little credible.Do not recommend to anyone, nor to action cinema fans. Go and enjoy with Bourne, that that are big words.</body>
</review>
