<review author="José A. Peig" title="Naturaleza muerta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very honest and precise, work which each level is intended to evoke the idea of the central theme, although unable to transcend the obviousness of his own speech and reiterated in excess the same idea.</summary>
	<body>A film can find its raison d ' être in alternative to the narrative fields, you can have a purpose purely expository, lyrical or metaphorically build a State of being. In some of these areas - and depending on the treatment - the laws of narrative were outside to emphasize a more concrete aspect than the of telling a story; Eastern cinema has a clear tendency towards the contemplative glances and the connection between spiritual state and scenery is a single resource for a wealthy, but not necessarily whimsical visual presentation.Nature dead, directed by the Chinese author Jia Zhang Ke, is a film of processes and divergences, looks and subtle thoughts, not of facts that are developed on the basis of the scheme that subordinates us the script as often. To be contemplative film, the author used and abused the flat long, slow, flat sequence that run profiles with the simplicity and naturalness of the typical story of manners, or fix a landscape of Fund that serves as a reference for the visual significance. It is logical that the film is boring, and is not recommended for those who want to go to the movies to entertain, and perhaps gives the impression that Chinese filmmaker gets carried away by arbitrariness and the comfort of limited shooting situations repeatedly.But the truth is that, broadly, the visual composition and the use of the Assembly are designed based on a concept, and an expressive idea that encompasses humanity with the landscape under a bleak tone. A too simple idea, and although this represented a devoid of redundant devices accurately, the result and expressed no longer too obvious, so best to assess this film is opting for a midpoint between the intellectual honesty of the author, and the obviousness of his proposal.The film exposes the process of two lives, a miner in search of her ex - woman and a girl looking for her sentimental partner. Separation and informalization is the central theme in all relations, both romantic relationships at the landscape level - human being. Social psychology has defined how the destruction of the landscape affects negatively the spiritual and mental state of its inhabitants, and almost the whole corpus of images that form the film is intended to express the disorder in the human-landscape relationship. It is true that the representation does not have explicit dramatic tension, but we are dealing with an atonal gaze, filmmaker exposes a few situations in a given context, without manipulating the emotions of the Viewer. This does not imply a cold look - at all-, and on the contrary, the atonal rawness is its best asset as film expression.All visual resources are in function of expressing such dissociation: the landscape background of the Lake and the mountains that characterize the enclave are the frame of reference for introducing two characters who bear the weight of the speech, and configure a visual parallel which is to be the most common stylistic resource: a man or a woman, and a landscape in the background. The ruins, house demolitions, the mists that hinder the view of nature, work and hobbies in a place in which it seems that there is not much to do or nothing interesting to say, these elements correlate with the separation and the difficulty of understanding with others or with the beloved, the search for something that never comesa society so apathetic and dam of becoming imposed by the changes, such as the permanent mists and buildings that collapse without that nobody can do nothing to prevent it.In short, a very honest and precise, work which each level is intended to evoke the idea of the central theme, although unable to transcend the obviousness of his own speech and reiterated in excess the same idea. It is a film that may be sleeping for a large part of the audience, but would not be fair to ignore a very conscientious and work meticulously designed for the purpose of a concept clearly expressed.</body>
</review>
