<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="The invasion" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a pity. Perhaps he hoped that with the reference in the 1956 and the excellent Filmography of Hirschbiegel The invasion was a product higher than the found.</summary>
	<body>Until the 19th century Western culture attached to the emotions a paper negative and dangerous when setting up the nature of the adult male. And I say man because it was attributed only and exclusively to the male gender the noble endeavour to humanity through their rational capacity towards progress and moral perfection. For its part, the woman was a paradigm of moral weakness and intellectual disabilities; for this reason would be naturally the exclusion of female gender in public life, which was assigned to him - with almost paternal benevolence - the roles of loving mother and caring wife, more tailored to their nature unstable, superficial and unhealthy.A longing of the origins of mankind (Greek culture), and thereby will be already under the ashes of the illustration which will emerge from the hand of the Romantic movement also a reaffirmation of the human passions as necessary substrate for life. It is not the reason which makes better human beings, but natural and noble feelings arising from its interior. It is more, the exaltation of reason, so characteristic of the modern world, so it has only vilify and away to human beings of their nature, altering its ability to act with wisdom and goodness.Oliver Hirschbiegel has never throughout its short filmography so far from this romantic thesis about the causes of human violence. In fact, the excellent experiment and the sinking are perfect examples of the interest of this German from Hamburg to make us reflect on the levers that drive human beings to be caught by the captivating inertia of power. The experiment will be a woman (Maren Eggert) who serve as a counterpoint to the perverse universe recreated in this experimental prison moved under the carcelero-preso binomial (or if the Hegelian slave), and only responsible for return to the character played by the always wonderful Moritz Bleibtreu (elementary particles) to reality. Also in the sinking is a woman who tells? and serves thus awareness - the facts which she herself lived in the bunker of the Führer, hours before ending his life.In The invasion (pending release in Spain back in October) the psychiatrist Carol (his profession makes knowing human emotions) with no little histrionics starring Nicole Kidman will be in charge of struggle to keep your child awake against the male sueño de la Razón. Not in vain the character's relationship with her ex-husband should be as flat before it infected against emotions, thus underlining the rejection of the patriarchal model representing the infected. That is why Carol will only accept doctor Ben (Daniel Craig), which feels something that suppresses even if you want to, if it recognized therein the basic emotions of affection and respect that yearns for after their marriage failure.The sexual roles that Western culture delimitara old with tight determinism reappear in The invasion of form peregrina and superficial, not reaching the intensity and depth that gives us the experiment. Ben is medical, scientific, rational, protective of Carol; Carol, psychiatrist, expert in reading emotions, mother wolf that protects to his offspring. Even the end becomes a postmodern game with this movie buff nod of the final sentence pronounced doctor Ben to read the press. And of course, American science relieves the heavy Viewer unholy suspecting that virus ends up becoming human beings an improved spice dispenser of tobacco. How not, the happy end just by curtailing polyhedral capacity that Yes possessed the proposal of Siegel generate infinite readings. The invasion is light, only shoots with adaptor, without desosegarnos bullets.The socio-political metaphor for its mythical history and reference, Invasion of the Body Snatchers (Don Diegel, 1956), which is applicable with decency even to the remake made by Kaufman in 1978, opts since the beginning to not contribute more than a stifling story (not to be confused with disturbing) of the desperation of a mother to find his son, worthy of a telefilm of three and a half (as the series Rex)(, a different police officer who ran Hirschbiegel in Germany when it was not yet known internationally). Not even found in The invasion an anthropological reading aiming as high as did the previous work of Hirschbiegel. And if what you want is one of fear, without intellectual pretensions and double readings, nor The invasion brings much to the panorama of films scares and persecution. Its potential, focused on the family tragedy of the loss of the child at the hands of an inadvisable husband, is bland and without grip, while the action scenes try to conceal defects of Fund. Recall that a similar story in the hands of Kubrick (the shining) provided us a visually powerful and disturbing work.It is a pity. Perhaps he hoped that with the reference in the 1956 and the excellent Filmography of Hirschbiegel The invasion was a product higher than the found. Hopefully at least one decent fundraising help its director to find new and more evocative stories to tell us. Hopefully.</body>
</review>
