<review author="Luis Zueco" title="Caótica Ana" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is worth going to see it because it is an air of freshness that film, and not only Spanish, urgently needed. It also proposes a story interesting and original, with a beautiful soundtrack and the special ambience that give the tables.</summary>
	<body>Chaotic Ana is without doubt the best Spanish film of the year, and Julio Medem one of the best Spanish directors. Does this post should be entitled "in defense of Caótica Ana", because the number of attacks, is incomprehensible criticism destructive, insults,? that is treated in this film.From the point of view strictly film, anyone who says that this film is not special, different, ambitious and courageous, it is not much understanding of cinema. It is a complicated film, welcome to the cinema of truth, which is done from the heart, from what one feels and wants to express. It is chaotic, please read the title. That the end is not the most successful, agree, is that if he had also succeeded in adequately finish the film, we would be talking about a masterpiece. I think that you can forgive you the end for the hour and a half of freshness, feelings, emotions, desire to live, etc that offers us the tape. I have come to read critical that most highlights of the film is that the protagonist, that makes a simply incredible interpretation is passed throughout the film naked. The first thing is that it is a lie, and the second thing is that if it still surprises us, and furthermore does not bother to see a nude in the film, it is that we have made very little progress in the last 60 years. I also read that it is the worst tribute could do to his sister (the film is named after she died when heading to make a presentation), who believed the people what to say as it should honor a brother to his sister, who would know her better than him and who cares. Finally I also read that the protagonist is simply a bleary-eyed hippie, until it was a spice of Heidi who lives in a cave with his grandfather. What happens is that there are people that bothers them that currently there are people with principles, with different ways of looking at life, people who want a different world.The film is worth going to see it because it is an air of freshness that film, and not only Spanish, urgently needed. It also proposes a story interesting and original, with a beautiful soundtrack and the special ambience that give the tables. But you cannot finish it properly, which can forgive.</body>
</review>
