<review author="José A. Peig" title="Los puentes de Madison" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Here yes there are humanity and complex decisions, dynamism and a suggestive in several directions narrative, provided that what we circunscribamos in the field of the human being in its debate between vulnerability and the value of being something more than what the inertia of society imposes on us.</summary>
	<body>This could be the reverse of the previous film commentary. If that was intended to be a complex black film focused on impulsiveness and the irrational, here we have a history of spiritual love with claims of creating complex human actions that lead to a positive message about happiness and life. Let's say there are two ways to evaluate this film. First, and in response to his unmistakable tone of sentimental romance, would be a repletito tale of topics around the relationships that cause an embolism of the irritation you between one see so much escenita romanticona, so many lagrimitas and other hosts in vinegar: Meryl Streep and Eastwood to the beat launching miraditas, with dialogue full of clichés about unsatisfied women and free solitaire that dare not love what by nobility spirit can never be yours. And there throw the couple throughout the film taking beers, preparing the lunch and dinner, walking through the field, cut flowers, brushing the legs and caressing your shoulders. I love you, do not want you to, I either, I also, but do not dare because I have family waiting for me. bla bla bla bla. At the end - tachaaaaaaan - true love it fixes everything, family is the best thing in the world and must strengthen the ties of fraternity grounded in a pure honesty that seeks the happiness of the beloved beings. Been global: a telefilm corny, conservative, Mannerist, false, prescindible.puajj, puajjj, puajjj.No, no, no, baby, here is showing the difference between the "cabezacuadrada" that goes from smartass and objective look of what us is representing. As bit would be a brilliant melodrama that would demonstrate the ideological prejudices of a large sector of public and critics: i.e. those who before any film in which the family or the lofty patriotic values appear with a certain relevance, react off of immature, conservative, giving, Mannerist and other crap. Recently we have seen this with World Trade Center; moms, dads, sons and hermanos.y crucecitas. Anyway, do not confuse the intentional pamphlets, with depictions that show social and human reality as much as appear crosses, military with crosses, lovers that give crosses to remember, families who are reconciled before made pickpockets. Because in such cases - and in the case - what we have is the emotional, spiritual and symbolic reality of a society. Punto y aparte. With "The bridges of madison county" one can feel the infinite mystery of distances in a love affair which, with humility and heartbreaking honesty, breaks (or renewed, reborn, reconciles) a scheme of beliefs and routines: will not mention what schema is broken (or renewing) in the case of Francesca as too obvious, but yes stop the eyes of my spirit in this Bohemian photographer who travels the roads with pulse free and uprootedTherefore the immensity of this character forged most of the mystery and he is the true soul of history. Who originally wanted - to half unconsciousness - presenting himself as a loner invulnerable not needing a home and a family to escape from fear, will finally recognize his own trap, her fear, her inadvertent falsehood that suppresses the desire to possess, to recognize the true love that is deserved. That love with detachment, that confidence from loneliness and bonhomie. What is born and dies where they end and begin the dirt roads that lead to the bridge of the encounter eternal, of love that will always be a new chance, even in the distance that separates a dreamer locked up in his role as housewife and the prisoner of their uprooting hermit. It is throbbing infinity of possibilities afforded by the love that fills all the space between each of the Poles, gives a flavour of importance to life. Here yes there are humanity and complex decisions, dynamism and a suggestive in several directions narrative, provided that what we circunscribamos in the field of the human being in his debate between vulnerability and the value more than what the inertia of society marks and imposes on us.Sensitive and honest love story in a flawless film in its first part: the development of the nascent spiritual link that cometh between the two protagonists is anthology. Then pass more topical, although understandable passages, and the narration loses something of bellows, but the last of all narrated consequences have a stunning resolution in the last section, waste of humanity and feelings and the image that best expresses the core of the conflict and the love: that Clint Eastwood in the rain, lanky, vulnerable and strong, which offers his last look and his last smile of understanding and hope, and the cross hanging from the rear-view mirror that drew the last chance Francesca, whose tears seem to want to compete with rain. That's sensitivity and lyricism without vain pretensions that choke the honest course of history.Here there are also dads, moms, sons, brothers and patriotic values. In the end, the family is reinforced and cohesive, but under a bath of spirituality, hard at the crossroads between alternatives of enjoyment for life, by nearby humans and that in the distance give us the true life. That - in this case - it is not conservative nor simplistic pamphleteering, is a real humanity and a beautiful film craft.</body>
</review>
