<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Superman returns" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>They will enjoy as children with this new Superman seemed hexed for movies and that Singer and screenwriters Michael Dougherty and Dan Harris have given life again.</summary>
	<body>I was fortunate to be able to attend the press pass for one of the films most awaited by all lovers of cinema that we still maintain an adventurous spirit: "Superman Returns" by Bryan Singer.En she tell us how, after a mysterious absence of several years, the man of steel (Brandon Routh) returns to a planet Earth who has used to survive without him. Upon arrival discovers that the woman he loves, Lois Lane (Kate Bosworth), is living with another (James Marsden) and had a son (Tristan Lake Leabu). To make matters worse misfortune Lex Luthor (Kevin Spacey), his great enemy, has come out of jail and has a plan.The nostalgia factor plays an important role, and I am not ashamed to say that a smuggler of moonfleet as hard as I was about to drop a lagrimita, during the initial credit titles, to listen to the mythical theme composed by John Williams. Theme, by the way, brilliantly honored and used with restraint and intelligence by a John Ottman which is to rise to the occasion.Bryan Singer had a really difficult challenge before it and showing that it is a courageous director took several risky decisions. The first one is to continue more or less history where he was after "Superman II", thus maintaining a certain narrative and style with the previous films continuity. In fact this return saved much of the spirit of the "Superman" by Richard Donner, to the point that could even be considered a disguised remake. Point that may make happy to those we saw in theaters for 28 years but could remain indifferent to the younger and more distant from the original public.Another risky decision of Singer is to print the film a leisurely pace. The film focuses more on the problems of Superman to find again its place in the world, in the pure and simple action. Action which, putting us demanding and despite being brilliantly filmed, we must recognize that it lacks that pure emotion that did "Batman Begins". Here the emotion not the find both in action, that something also in the intimate moments. I cannot deny that see Superman fly again in arms carried Lois Lane came to the heart.To loop the loop of the risk, Singer decided to dispense with the final climax that is assumed to a tape of these features. This decision, together with the above-mentioned leisurely pace, can upset much of the public potential, possibly eager to see Fireworks at any price, but is entirely consistent with what you want to count. We are not to a character with the innocence of the 1970s. The Singer Superman is a mature character, who suffers, who is overwhelmed by a world that would require too many like him to succeed. Perhaps this Superman pretends to be younger (even though Brandon Routh is one year older than Reeve when he played it for the first time) but life has become very expensive bills and that enriches the character.Much of the eyes of critics and fans will be directed to the actors. Are Routh and Bosworth and Spacey at the height of Reeve, Kidder and Hackman? In general, I think Yes. Especially striking found it me the actor protagonist because if it is totally credible as Kent (his performance is really cloned the Reeve), since then convinces altogether as the Acero.Evidentemente man could one complain that the plan of Luthor is a little weird and little concrete (even a smart way to connect even more this film with the above)that has very few and clumsy helpers or that it is impossible that so savvy journalists are not able to see that Clark Kent and Superman are the same person. But accept all these premises is necessary condition to enter to see the movie. If one does not accept that it is better to stay out of the film.But all those willing to accept the rules of the game, will enjoy as children with this new Superman seemed hexed for movies and that Singer and screenwriters Michael Dougherty and Dan Harris have given life again, adapting it to 21st century. Superman Returns to stay and that is certainly a good news.</body>
</review>
