<review author="Tyler" title="El ultim치tum de Bourne" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie that closes the trilogy of Bourne tells us what we needed to know about Jason Bourne, resolves the incognitas on which was kept the trilogy. A required summer movie in times in which action lapses.</summary>
	<body>The Bourne trilogy arose thanks to the success of the first. There were other books on which to base more movies, but the idea was to make the first and point. The success of the movie of Doug Liman(Sr._y_Sra._Smith) was enormous and it opened the way for a trilogy, typical of Holywood. It was decided to slightly change the tone and they hired another Director, Paul Greengrass, who had garnered much success with this wonder who was give SUNDAY. Successful change has to be said, while the first worthy nothing to the trilogy. The case Bourne had the worst screenplay of all, and it did not sell so well. The phrase of promotion of the movie was "with a pursuit of emotion similar to the French Connection", which is not true, nor joke going to compare. Even so it was a success of the chalice. Well, the first part was the most similar to the book which was based, something that the other two seem rather short. This it is because I've read, not because there are read books, therefore not can be very reliable in that regard. But gives equal, when it apadta a book send a tomar por culo many things, necessarily because the literature is not very film, with the exception of Elmore Leonard and Raymond Chandler would say I, but my opinion matters rather little.THE BOURNE ULTIMATUM is a very good movie, with a rhythm reminiscent of the movies of the 1970s, type PELHAM 1,2,3 or the movies of Don Siegel, but with a touch more modern, long computer and technological paraphernalia. It has a tone very much in the line of the previous, even more nervous, Greengrass has molado him la Movida Madrile침a in Flight 93, a true pelicul칩n, and repeated the formula, more camera on his shoulder, until almost abusing it. But he forgives her, because history not it decays. The Bourne trilogy is risky, because the three parties are of the same, this note want to know quies is, because this and that and which. and that is painful, because the writer has to count that there are people who have not seen the previous two, and build a script that works by itself, but that you also put in that situation, and fast, because if you throw long explaining becomes boring, especially for those who have seen the other two. I saw the movie with my girlfriend that I had not seen the other two, and he understood everything to the perfeci칩n, it took to get into the story, but he saw that something typical and explanatory, originally was necessary because if not, you have not understood anything, she did not have specific information about the character that I if because he had seen the other two movies. Then it got in the movie and enjoyed her until the end. Matt Damon is the ideal actor for this character, without being the best actor of his generation, if it is one very fit, with great ability to adapt and that, increasingly, you do better, always improves, alcontrario that some hold that being good, he always improves. The end is very good, did not expect me this at all, it is a well built and very well prepared, because without being the typical surprise ending to the beast, surprised a lot only by well prepared that is. This tells us that there is no need an overwhelming, if not a well constructed story end and a well prepared final.</body>
</review>
