<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Fracture" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Notable legal thriller with truly good moments and a masterful interpretation of Anthony Hopkins. Perhaps Fracture we will be in the memory for a long time, but I do not think that Hoblit intends. This is a movie to watch and comment out of the film. Point.</summary>
	<body>It looked like the typical legal thriller without the slightest grace and originality directed without hardly any personality. The case is that it is nothing out of this world, but nor is it a bad film, nor much less. This air to the thrillers of the 90s with great interpretive duels and intrigue of the good is certainly appreciated. What most stands out here is, without a doubt, great performance by Anthony Hopkins who, as always, catches the viewer with his ferocious looks and phrases of English humor really disconcerting. It is not cast, Ryan Gosling, teammate cheapen being named, but is that Mr. Hannibal eats it alive just appearing half of footage that the protagonist of Half Nelson. Perhaps one of the key scenes of the film is that conversation both remain in prison, where Hopkins psychologically caught that Gosling talking everything what he knows about his life and what he sees as weakness. As you can see, Fracture has its moments, some brilliant, other correct and others left over. It never becomes boring, what is more, this is a very entertaining film, just without action. It is not that too many there are sudden changes of argument, although there are several unexpected turns. The end, very characteristic also of intense films of the 90s, reminds us that we are seeing a hundred percent legal film and its message more clear and critic is that there are many ways to get to the truth through justice, whether they are good or bad.The script is what, in my opinion, most falters in this interesting film. It has a truly intriguing start, but there are several aspects of the knot which cannot convince me come. I am not going to appoint them now, but for example, the character of Rosamund Pike does not look too, moreover, is as the female complement which, undoubtedly was to appear in the film. Gosling plays a winning type, which has had the working life and now cares more about his salary that to resolve cases as a lawyer that is (quoting one of the phrases that the great David Strathairn named in the film). And everything changes when she meets the Hopkins manipulator, which makes it radically change to the point of obsession with the fact if there is really the perfect crime. Reminds me the first feature film by Hoblit, two sides of the truth, a correct movie of trials with an interpretative duel between Richard Gere and Edward Norton really amazing. And is that you for what deny it: the majority weight of Fracture lies in the doomed Hopkins, and of another film in the also condemned Norton (received a nomination Oscar for her performance). It is not that "prosecutors" have misinterpretations, but there is no denying that the bad guys end up being better than the "good guys". Perhaps in the new film is not as in depth the theme of human psychology as it clearly noted on both sides of the truth, but they do have several points in common that are, at the same time, somewhat suspicious. Comparisons aside, and focus on Fracture, say that without being a wonder, get beat most thrillers which have been released over the past years (except for teachers like Fincher or Greengrass), obtaining a remarkable outcome, very conviencente and nothing Manipulator. After all, I was going with the intention of seeing an entertaining film and that is what I found. Perhaps his main mistake is that they can spare you a few minutes. Two hours was too much for telling a story like this, but the truth is that it is not heavy. And not to forget the great side of which highlighted the already named Stratharin and Pike, and the always magnificent Fiona Shaw in the role of judge.A notable legal thriller, with really good moments and a masterful interpretation of Anthony Hopkins. Perhaps Fracture we will be in the memory for a long time, but I do not think that Hoblit intends. Finally, this is a movie to watch and comment out of the film. Point.</body>
</review>
