<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="Salvador" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With Salvador settled outstanding accounts in the Spanish cinema. It was not enough to metaphors and exercise of copyright. Better late than never. A necessary movie. Catharsis.</summary>
	<body>Some time ago I had the opportunity to chat by phone, in a radio program, with Manuel Huerga, director of SALVADOR (PUIG ANTIC). One of the first things I told him was that he considered his last film as "necessary". Huerga do not believe so, they called it "movie therapy". An adjective in the mouth of one the top architects of SALVADOR, without forgetting the most important (as producer and initiator of the project) work of Jaume Roures (Mediapro).I decided, on the basis of the comments of the director, define cine-terapia: a treatment of film? a new way of treating depression? We could talk about the film as audiovisual therapy. Therapy does not cure, but can help to address real dramas. In this case, the film is the vehicle by which comes the message that helps us to move forward. The movie as medicine to our woes.In the case of SALVADOR is not that we better leave when we left the cinema. In fact, the feeling is completely reverse. Hence, the first definition I proposed him to Huerga: it is a "necessary" film. This allows us to know (especially if we refer to the new generations) about horrible events. Therapeutic of the viewing of the film through, possibly, "that which cannot again be repeated". In short, learn to grow, to move forward. This type of movies allow us may trouble us, suffering, llorar.y, at the same time, discuss, relive what happened. Impotence it produces us but also gives us the possibility to download it. And injustice (the so-called "social depression") against injury which is difficult to close ever is reflected in us, as spectators.In the end credits of the film by Huerga, appear a whole series of actual images of the latest massacres that have happened in our world: since 9-11 to 11-m. Speaks of this new fascism, of fear, of the victims inocentes.todo what we have not overcome. The message is our failure.Thus, in the absence of justice a "movie therapy". The case of Salvador Puig Antic is best known by almost everyone. March 2, 1974, this young militant of the Movimiento Ibérico de Liberation (MIL), became the last political prisoner executed in Spain by "garrote vil". The film tells its story and desperate of his family, colleagues and lawyers to avoid his execution attempts.The international paradigm of cine-terapia is, without a doubt, in Argentina. In the Argentine cinema of the past twenty years we find key pieces. I will appoint four essential titles: the official history (Luis Puenzo, 1985), the night DE LOS LAPICES (Héctor Olivera, 1986), GARAGE OLIMPO (Marco Bechis, 1999) and Chronicle of an escape (Adrián Caetano, 2006).With this type of film is settled outstanding accounts with torturers, murderers and savages. Do express such denunciation passes for focus, without hesitation, on the victim, above all, person. Describes, in a thorough way, humiliating and inhuman situations which suffered, with greater or lesser success in its outcome. A memory rescued as the best antidote to oblivion. And in the most direct way, describing facts and not judgements, unless explicit. Again I stress the idea of cinema as medicine to our miseries. where lies the difference between the last Argentine cinema and ours? Just in one: the elapsed time. Three decades after the end of Franco's dictatorship is the first, and genuinely, film therapy. In Argentina, two years after the fall of the dictatorship military (1983) with Puenzo film, starring Norma Aleandro and Héctor SALVADOR Alterio.Con settled accounts receivable Spanish film. It was not enough to metaphors and exercise of copyright. Better late than never. A necessary movie. Catharsis.</body>
</review>
