<review author="Kiko de España" title="Hostel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>90 minutes to forget a little tristísimo world that surrounds us, full of hardships, injustices and disappointments, seeing what the Yankees of Slovakia laugh. And the rest of the world.</summary>
	<body>Eli Roth conducted in 2002 "Cabin fever", one of the surprises of the last intelligent horror film.On that occasion a large number of young people suffer unspeakable to death in a horrible way in a cottage in the middle of nowhere.Seen the success of mouth ear had, and turned into a cult movie, now comes with a little more money and sponsored by the infallible Quentin Tarantino with "Hostel", that I saw, that it was one of the most anticipated titles of the season, and in which a number (not so) Youth suffers unspeakable to do die? in a horrible way in the middle of nowhere. And the movie doesn't disappoint. Or if?The case is that it is not so violent as they paint ("Passion" still has the top in sadism, gore and torture is concerned in the cinema of terror? 21st century) but it is fun as it was the earlier work.Notice to Mariners: is the movie with more good aunts and tits and ass with Thong (and without it) there is on the Bulletin Board. The argument is the least (not so I will gut, but in the background is another one of "those", already as you will see) and the first act could pass through the imaginary "American Pie: study trip", which does not exist, but that if there would be something like.There is a cameo appearance by Takashi Miike, the most gross of the moment, and will that think young people who, with summer just around the corner, believe in the interrail, or as balls type.The makeup effects are the work of the great Greg Nicotero, which better than get any movie in which there is currao, almost 100, the mirais in IMDB and flipais.The music of Franco-Giacomo Carbone is not bad (and at times, especially in the end credits), reminds of "psychosis".The director not innova nor is inventing flat "never ever made", fashionable in film today, but thank you that he does not walk with rodeos (although again, is not so wild as it should, to see if there is a director´s cut chachi) and that show us about subnormal characters with brain of penis that really matters to us a damn what happens to them.With a third act a little absurd, since during the two others look forward to seeing the torture chambers and then, when it arrives, it is running (or this will be a success that you cagas?), you can enjoy 100% and is missing one a couple of laughs, something that is appreciated, as well as the end, where the Viewer, an accomplice of the matter and infected by the dominant dementia, becomes another "of those" already what you will see.In summary, 90 minutes to forget a little tristísimo world that surrounds us, full of hardships, injustices and disappointments, seeing what the Yankees of Slovakia laugh. And the rest of the world. Do not you miss to the Slovak enfants.</body>
</review>
