<review author="Kiko de España" title="Hostel 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Roth approves let go wrong girls and because it has potential to be a large, although its great movie (and I thought it would be this) has not yet come. Not desesperéis.</summary>
	<body>My impression of the first Hostel was quite good, despite the fact that many people did not end catch the trick and see it as what it was: a comedy. Eli Roth is an uncomfortable director in all aspects. Cabin Fever, your letter of presentation, was an excellent treatise on the horror of the 1990s with special aftertaste to the first Raimi Mirada excited the way as mercía.Then came Hostel, a gift from Quentin Tarantino, which has allowed it to enter the clan, participate in Grindhouse both actor and director and produce a very funny, 2001 cult-movie Maniacs. Today is Eli Roth preparing the filming of Cell, adapting to Stephen King.Pero let's talk about Hostel II, is not as fun as the original and presents a number of details that make us go back a couple of decades in the film genre, specifically in the section "aftermath ochenteras" the continuations of the two key of the genre made slasher films in USA (Halloween and Viernes13) wereas well as it was in Porky's, the "next day" and that is present in the movie of Roth, with a clavadita scene which opened the continuation of the adventures of the children of Crystal Lake. Furthermore, before we have on screen to Luc Merenda, seen in Torso, and the great Ruggero Deodato, the Holocaust dire Cannibal, making mischief in one of the best scenes of the movie.The main difference of Hostel II with its predecessor is point of view. If the first part were mindless three newly despedazados by laborers, this are three girls who are also lured to finish in the torture room and the details of the auction of businessmen, impressive, almost as much as torture. And it is the new point of view on these men. In Hostel we suffered by the victim and Hostel 2, we are suffering from the executioner. And by the victim, clear.The surprise factor goes away, but the movie has an atmosphere that did not have the original, although it is true that, as I said after the first, there are more gore in any film Mel Gibson that on all the Hostels in the world.Roth approves let go wrong girls and because it has potential to be a large, although its great movie (and I thought it would be this) has not yet come. Not desesperéis.</body>
</review>
