<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="El Club de los Suicidas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To the black humor must have very good hand: master Rafael Azcona knows a lot of that. But Roberto Santiago does not.</summary>
	<body>Roberto Santiago the previous effort in the direction, "The longest penalty in the world", resulted in a reasonable commercial impact (more than five million euros: who catch them today in the Spanish film, think more than one!), but with one more than discreet acceptance from critics. With that success, at least in the aspect of the Peel, Santiago has launched his second feature film, but does not seem to have made much progress. For the occasion suited again (because the film has already done so on several occasions) a novel by Robert l. Stevenson, "The suicide club", which is certainly not one of his most exciting works; prefer, of course, its legendary "The treasure island" and "Dr. Jekyll &amp; Mr. Hyde". Santiago raises the possibility of giving a group of depressed for several reasons, gathered around a group led by a psychologist therapy with serious problems of self-esteem, founding, in the manner of the novel stevensoniana one of them brings a club in which weekly touch you one die and kill him. The idea seems to work, until our protagonist eyebrow in his efforts to kill, find a new illusion. To the black humor must have very good hand: master Rafael Azcona knows a lot of that. But Roberto Santiago not: a story like this requires a touch of sinister humor that make us smile with complicity; It must necessarily be intelligent humour, and there on the screenplay of Santiago, and less on its rather pedestrian realization, glimpses of this. Some sequences to Martian fuer have his grace (cf. the ambulance at the burger bar scene, or the erotic event between Laurel and psychologist), but in general the Viewer, it will delivered, costs work stretching up the corners of the lips. Mention apart for the interpretive cast: Fernando Tejero confirms what we temíasmos: always plays the same role, whatever its character, and when it does not, as is the case with the gay "Film days" deployed boom, even worse; Lucía Jiménez is also confirming that it enjoys an inexplicable predicament between criticism, far superior to his diminished talent; Luis Callejo, anonymous face usually doomed to hard characters or outside the law, as a result of their baleful mug, gives her character a very personal tone; but all them eaten them with potatoes (and see that it is well advised, with these mollas?) Juanma Cifuentes, a new face, at least for which subscribes, but with an interpretative capacity only comparable to the many pounds over his bones that supports. All a discovery this Juanma, excellent comic vis, and with a rare ability to tell more merluzos dialogues with an astonishing naturalness. Do so, although East "club of suicide" has been a chestnut, at least we found one of those wonderful supporting actors (do because el bueno de Cifuentes it not imagined as the protagonist, given the limitations of its physical?) given by Spanish film worthy of a better than our cinematography frequently?</body>
</review>
