<review author="Kiko de Espa침a" title="Viscosidad (The incredible Melting Man)" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie directed by William Sachs is a gap which plays in the same League that I drink your blood or Supersonic Man, the League classic series Z.</summary>
	<body>How to begin to talk about a film like this?I will tell you that is three sentences: an astronaut to be Saturn becomes viscous and radioactive and is devoted to kill pe침a to regenerate, to go missing eyes and ears on the way, the very ga침치n. how many phrases were those?Well, the fact is that the movie directed by William Sachs is a gap which plays in the same League that I drink your blood or Supersonic Man, the League classic series z. Special effects by Rick Baker are, without a doubt, the worst of his career. It is a film, (although it seems a telefilm) that goes straight to the point and five minutes already have seen as the monster is loaded to a slightly idiotic nurse, because it passes through a glass door rather than open it, in one of the most stupid scenes I remember.Then there are the dialogues, which are level E.G.B: do contaminate?, I have found to Frankenstein! or words forgotten as tontaina and beanpole fit in this spectacular film of shit that has the virtue of being only to create a new fantasy genre: the regore.I will try to explain the term: in one scene, the incredible derretible man attacking a fisherman, start you the head and the Strip to the River. The scene shifts and appears a muchachada about ten years smoking a few pitis and thinking if playing hide and seek or doctors. Then the scene changes and we see the head down the River until you reach a waterfall. The head falls to the rocks and breaks into pieces. Sustained Gore. Regore.Y talking about sustained, the levels have a disproportionately ridiculous duration, they are extremely long. And speaking of ridiculous, only I can tell you that there is one impressive scene, attention: A marriage viejuno will drive along a road in the middle of the night. On the sides of the road, as says the Lady of the car, there is "trees that give lemons".Derretible man walks around the area, therefore, the only option that old the palmen is that they stop in the middle of nowhere, early in the morning to collect lemons. And do it. Go laughter.For little more I can tell you. There is some point Z.A.Z. (the old on the stage of the corpse of the fisherman), that there are times in which absolutely nothing happens. Highly recommended for night cannabis.PS: The doctor well of the movie goes in search of "viscosity" with a meter giger, but what need you if the monster leave obvious traces, either in the form of bodies or in the form of viscous mass?PD2: Leaves Jonathan Demme. She plays Matt. It is a game of fun trying to find him. I think that I got.PD3: just edit on dvd.</body>
</review>
