<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Carta Esférica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The spherical letter is a film of intrigue that aims to provide lot of tension and excitement and at the end does not comply with what was promised.</summary>
	<body>There are genres which the public seems only associated to a particular cinematography, commonly the American. Genres such as musicals, war movies, film adventures or the surpluses of time seems that in the eyes of the spectators can only be in Hollywood. Why not American films of this type almost never connected with the respectable by very well made they are.Same thing happens to the intrigue and mystery film although ironies of fate, this has been a genre rather cultivated in Spanish film, which still gives excellent fruits such as La Caja 507 or X. Now comes the letter spherical, adaptation of the novel by Arturo Pérez-Reverte, one of the authors whose works more often have been reflected on the big screen. The film tells a story in which a sailor banished from the sea will be forced to help a mysterious woman in his search of a sunken ship that holds many secrets. The spherical letter means return to the film by Imanol Uribe, one of the most valued filmmakers of the last decades. The film has a good boot, which seduces and captivates the Viewer, but little by little the plot loses tension and intensity. After his good start, the tape is unable to maintain the interest of the public, and gradually becomes monotonous and predictable. The characters become flat, without any kind of development, in particular the interpreted by Aitana Sánchez-Gijón, that pretends to be a woman fatal but the attempt loses credibility as the minutes elapse. Own work of the actress does not help to give strength to the character, which ends up sinking hopelessly. For its part, Carmelo Gomez ends nor give her character of the necessary force, although broadly complies with its work. Elements to emphasize there are few, but above all it stands out Javier Aguirresarobe.La letter spherical photography is a film of intrigue that aims to provide lot of tension and excitement at the end does not comply with what was promised. The end result is not bad but is not what could have given of it in other hands.</body>
</review>
