<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Death Proof" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Death Proof is the new film that emerged from the imagination of one of the most delusional of contemporary cinema minds, and is a real pity that his vision and Robert Rodriguez have been distorted in order to get more revenue.</summary>
	<body>Less than a month ago he came to our Planet Terror, the first screens of the two films that made up the Grindhouse project. Project that in Europe we have seen eaten into by the poor results of box office in United States. If the intention was to duplicate the benefits, shooting went them backfired, as in Spain Planet Terror has achieved a fairly discreet result.If the Robert Rodriguez film was a visual orgy of blood and entrails seasoned by a very black sense of humor, Death Proof is a film more contained. Well, contained if it is that this word can apply to a work of Quentin Tarantino. On this occasion, the story is also about less, a piscópata that uses his car as a weapon of destruction against a group of attractive girls. Death Proof has an atypical beginning to what is usual in Tarantino, is featuring the character gradually and leaves uncertainty grows in the Viewer. Master but hilarious dialogues of the filmmaker, being protagonist himself from several of them are present from the first minute. Since the entry into the Kurt Russell character scene tape is gaining in intensity and tension, for finally erupt into an explosion of really frenzied violence. Only a genius is capable of performing an auto-homenaje brazen as the character of Rosario Dawson mobile and that encime is well. The last half hour of the film is simply stunning, with the best car chase seen on film in many years.Death Proof is the new film that emerged from the imagination of one of the most delusional of contemporary cinema minds, and is a real pity that his vision and Robert Rodriguez have been distorted in order to get more revenue.</body>
</review>
