<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La última legión" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Epic of adventures on the last stop of Rome, which begins in search of a sword motivated by the Goths. It is not a great film, but fulfills a purpose clear, it has entertained me, and long.</summary>
	<body>These pseudohistóricas movies give me a tad of rabies, given that not is if I'm learning history or a comic book I am learning. Then so paint me hair, I've lived thinking that the Congo were some negritos docile than July Cesar could not dominate all Gaul, or in Spain had a called the TIA Intelligence Agency. It should be as drugs, with prospect "the historians Association warns that the viewing of this film will make picha a mess" or things.The film is about a Roman emperor who is appointed when he is only a child. Shortly after the nomination, has a Gothic problem (begins the festival of humor) for what send you to the island of Capri, that it is not yet of great luxury, if not a prison. Accompanying him his mentor is, a type of aspect of Druid of the Gauls, and her rescue runs a few selected men and the Chief of the guard. Can they rescue the presumed last Cesar? That more jittery nerves.Hard is the profession of film critic. Luckily I am computer, so I can say with all the pride of world this movie poop I liked very much. I direis that the script is a ful of Istanbul, the ending is predictable, the action is predicible, the amorio is a pain in the ass and things as well. But hey, that I loved the film. The action scenes are certainly not great things, the inclusion of a woman has truffled tape nonsense (some very funny) but has very good things. Develops rapidly throughout the tape, has very good points of humor is nice all the time and the final epilogue has seemed very big.In short, epic adventures on the last stop of Rome, which begins in search of a sword motivated by the Goths. It is not a great film, but fulfills a purpose clear, it has entertained me, and long.And if the harangue had been minimally motivating, her hull 5, ale.Besitos.P.D: In addition, it has weird stuff. A Goth with dreadlocks and rubio died three times in the same fight sequence. The rapper that accompanies the Chief of the guard reminds me of the brother of the girl who liked to Stive Urkel.P.D.2: two things I have not been clear. On the one hand, it is big-budget or something more modest? And the other is seriously or is laughable?</body>
</review>
