<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="28 semanas después" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apocalyptic film about how a virus rock humanity for don't know what reason. Great tomato sauce that I would say my mother-in-law, some scares, and a script to the height of a resecuela. I do not like.</summary>
	<body>Madrugda, Madrid, August late Monday. The deserted city. Smart few drivers who dare to tread the streets do so cautiously. They know that a virús is loose. Rumours, have heard by radio, television, nothing for sure. I pushed the Tome of concrete and glass. At the door, a metallic voice asking for the key. "I have come to make a guard, cagonmismuertos". The chancel is opened. Everything in the dark, a little light in the background with a seated figure. Asked me for accreditation, and I feel, when I go, as a smile. The night will be long, since then. And of course that I do not understand as the seguratas they shit not fear in these night guards. It canguele.The film is about a man that, faced with the diatribe that eat the stumps a few zombies or save his wife, decided to leave it to their fate. Time passed, Great Britain is recovering normality after a lethal virus that returns to the thirsty people in blood (it is not football, but more or less). Really only have assured a small parcel, with snipers on all sides to avoid entering the zombies. In these, the sons of the Lord before decide to escape plot, go to his former home, meet his mother and back accompanied by the "fortress". what want tell you? For me, there are two types of terror. On the one hand, of the scares and the other on the blood. This is the second, and I do not like. The script seems to me that it is flagging by the edges. Ahead, with security that seems the pussy of the Bernarda. And behind, the tontez end to tell us as you have box office, we quarter. It has as a positive thing that not only give us fear by dark, if not that the zombies come to full light of day to eat brains. This is positive. That Yes, what the hell want the zombies? Dan a bocao one and go for another. This is a marraneo. If see you my grandmother gives them a Campion that fuses them by marranos.In short, apocalyptic film about how a virus rock humanity for don't know what reason. Great tomato sauce that I would say my mother-in-law, some scares, and a script to the height of a resecuela. I do not like.Besitos.P.D: I will admit it. I spent all night without sleep shit scary. I had to go to sleep with my baby that I protected the zombie. I cannot see neither one of these!Pd2: Come, there are two helicopter scenes that I quite liked. Especially the first, flying over the city, very good (though not original).P.D.3: The time of handkerchief and laying mucus spare you to a movie, right?</body>
</review>
