<review author="Tyler" title="Noviembre" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie boring and irritating spirit. After an entertaining movie 'The ball', we got this stupidity of inaguantables Brats.</summary>
	<body>John Ford has already said in this list of 10 rules to follow a strictly when making a movie. And it goes to mass. On that list was repeated the same sentence 10 times "not boring". As well, in this film Achero Mañas fails it, because it is a fairly large suckling pig. The movie is based on a funny idea, a sort of pseudo mockumentary, which mixes alleged statements by the theatre group which speaks in constructed history as fiction, with this part, the same fiction itself. We can see as members of the group theatre had their experiences to camera and then see the normal history.To begin with, in terms of content, the movie is quite irritating, put on display to a collection of stupid Brats ranging from artists with a neo roll completely unbearable hipiesco. This type of alternative urban tribe that exists now that ranging from Liberals and compare themselves with the youth of May 1968, without having any fucking idea that balls are talking. All very "cool", all in the cespecito of a park sharing a PORRET with a guitar, talking about that art is something that should be completely free. Please. more child impossible. Easy is to brand someone tell what I say of facha, but nothing from reality, the last thing I am is a facade, but I do not like anything false which are this type of young people. All go Communist rojetes with their t-shirts of Che and his red stars, without knowing that red star is the one that wore Mao, a genocidal as big or bigger than Hitler himself. It is an esbastica.The movie is more irritating for your content that by their structure or rhythm, which is quite slow because the director just do not know at what point to statements and at what point to the part of fiction; and that makes the movie Miss much pace, and do not know clearly where is the approach, where development and where the conclusion.The message of the movie esque art should be totally free, that anything can be and that you can not set limits. Art needs limits, need them, to technical and structural level but not at the level of content. I mean that a movie, for example, cannot have the structure as one you want. There are rules that must be met, and this is the case. Oscar Jaenada seems as bad as overrated actor, all equal, what makes the same expressions with the same face. A character that no one believes that you fall badly cn his roll "cool alternative". Anarchist youth go without having any idea of who is Bakunin.Si you want to see a film with a message really strong and anarquico, have to see this wonder elevated to the cube that is EL CLUB DE LA LUCHA, a movie telling the truth about humans and our nature.The tiny group of this cool, not to make representations on the street, all painted and making the parguela; except for a representation in which he faked an ETA attack, the rest doesn't interest one. The representation of the murder of ETA is the only interesting because the only provica is a real reaction of the environment, others just create anything important reactions, which do not create plot. A distorted murder creates an interesting reaction which Mañas wasted because not queire develop and again the same thing of all. freedom of creation and bla bla blaUna movie I do not recommend by that bore more than anything, and because you get nervous these characters so irritating.This neo-hipis generaciño do not know what was May 1968, can compare with them not wanting to be like them. These people was as well at the moment, today in da there is no Viet Nam, you can't have hipis. hipis is not therefore the hipis or have died or are old. And this wonderful movement made is unique, they not imitabn anyone, they just reacted. Nowadays it is easy to be so, in the comfort of the modern world. We cannot be as them, and the people that mimics are false, and those who compare worse. In addition. This ´poca us haregalado the best music in history.Habalndo film and after this pollez which I have released and sounds the host of pretentious, say that it is a film has no pace, and that does not seem to have conclusion, only a lot of scenes together without any narrative sense.</body>
</review>
