<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Las edades de Lulú" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Erotic movie, jewel of the Spanish film about the sex life of a girl, from adolescence to maturity. Heavy sexual scenes tell us a story of submission and love does if not become essential in the library of any movie buff follower of Onan.</summary>
	<body>The ages of Lulu is based on a novel by Almudena Grandes. The actress who was to embody the main character at first refused after learning the explicitness of the sex scenes. Since then the scenes are not without reaching film pornographic, nor much less monjiles. We would rather say that they are equipped with an important sexual load, overflowing sensuality. More best, that makes me the picha to break coconuts. As you wish.The film is about the life of Lulu, its evolution through sexual intercourse is. Tells a story of submission to Paul, a friend of the family, which takes you by the hand through the world of sex. Since his teens, up crazy maturity of a woman who has lost the North, Bigas Luna directed the writing of Almudena.Recuerdo the first times I saw this film, which had recorded glorious early Telecinco. I was able to completely scratch tape, the times that I gave to the "palante" and the "Patras". With the passing of the years, I learned that between tit and ass had some dialogues that perhaps deserve the penalty be heard. And later, I realized the story who wanted us to have. Certainly if it becomes one of arthouse not had given so many opportunities.In short, erotic film, jewel of the Spanish film about the sex life of a girl, from adolescence to maturity. Heavy sexual scenes tell us a story of submission and love does if not become essential in the library of any movie buff follower of Onan. Spanish erotic film classic A.Besitos.P.D: The actress has a morbid which must be mortal sin.Pd2: Both sex, sex so much and I forget serving Bardem, making gay amateur to weird stuff. The scene in which put you what has been the fist behind the boy gives up afraid to see him. Good, and acts her mother, Mrs María Barranco, and more that I don't remember. The truth is that Francesca Neri and her sensuality overshadows them.</body>
</review>
