<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los managers" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nice comedy to see without more pretensions than the spend a good time with great scenes and tremendous nonsense</summary>
	<body>Wow, that fear of film. Nothing more and nothing less that Fran Perea, teenage singer-songwriter ja, ja, ja (just kidding) and Paco León, supported by two side classic Spanish cinema, Enrique Villén and Fran Tallafé. Not be as I'm daring to see Spanish film. And the fact is that then we see beads of having a good time as the Calentito, but in others we collide with the sides of the bed and its child melon and have to run. That uncertainty over bad. Anyway, luckily here Sancho Gracia and María Jiménez, that sure loose some bastez.The film is about Maca and Rena, two cuarentones without profession or benefit that seeking to make the pitch that we all dream in life. By a twist of fate, they try to access the programme of Lauren Postigo, which does not leave them enter, but where they discover that the good in this life is to be the manager of the artist. So they are with two kids (roll tow) that have good paint. These are Pipo and David, Paco León and Fran Perea respectively. So join in a strange Quartet, dragging on summer terraces and bingos, until that they encounter "La Rota" (María Jiménez) who sees something special in them.Well, it's with the Spanish films should grab with smoking paper. Let's see, the film is the easy divertimento we like around here. Drugs, sympathetic types, easy tune, sex (more real insunuado), strange scripts, etc. And this has it all. The beginning is very promising, given that there are good actors. The problem is that, throughout Spanish film who boasts, have a moment of Supreme stupidity all give us telling it's patriotic film. And the truth that tired. Damn, have to Sancho Gracia, María Jiménez, two major luxury, much material to put them in the rubbish of the American military base. That should not be, man. Incidentally, since I liked, given that it is of facilitator them, that you sit and you see with a giggle in the mouth. Up even sticks a canutito to be in line with the theme.In short, nice comedy to see without more pretensions than the spend a good time with great scenes and tremendous nonsense.</body>
</review>
