<review author="José A. Peig" title="El capitan blood" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A delicious narrative around the adventure understood as an evolution within a vital process.</summary>
	<body>Say that the pirates film has in this movie its best exponent, the ideal model that has inspired and may inspire forever when it comes to shape and build a héroe-antihéroe. That is the point that most strikes me of "El Captain Blood", a delicious narrative around the adventure understood as an evolution within a vital process.The great qualities of this film are all those which will be a good adventure movie: sharp and witty dialogues, built and antagonistic characters with fair efficiency and complexity, rate fluid, fast and at the service of the intensity of the different phases. With a good script, achieving the optimum result is the sea of easy; hero, heroine, bad, friends of the hero, enemies, the powerful good-natured, etc. A large number of characters, built with simplicity and unpretentious empty ending by spoiling the whole something very typical of most modern productions, trying to manufacture complex characters and what comes out is a pale, insubstantial and deadpan, churro as in "Alatriste".No, here appear here many characters and many pieces (Patriotic and political elements including) that play a role in history, structured in such a way that the viewer acknowledges to everyone in its role, forming a whole very well developed. To make a great movie you need the elements that will be part of the same are the fair and necessary, not on not missing anything: all, during and at the end of the story have been configuring the destiny and fate of the central character around which the narrative is organized.Above all, the story of a man more than "cinema of pirates", "adventure", "action", etc, the film by Michael Curtiz is a not insignificant history of intimacies, contradictions and secrets. The rebel personified by Errol Flyn - ideal romantic archetype as freedom, the stateless person feeling, service to those who have been excluded by a particular political order-, to have lived a past of military adventures, which denies, is involved in an Odyssey to save the oppressed that will lead to the creation of the way of pirate life, seeking freedom and community coexistence, but in the end it is discovered as an act of spite and revenge against the suffering and injustice generated by the established order. But the hero is aware and knows of the lives that it has cost your company awareness fueled by the female character, here is something more than a cliché which complies with the timely significance: the reproach to the immoral and life uprooted from the hero, contributing to the redemption of the same. All adventure film must have a core of humanity, a process in which the hero WINS is wrong, and returns to the origin. And in this story all the characters that surround the protagonist must play a role to obtain that all significant, playful, but also metaphorical, so that the héroe-antihéroe is a reflection of our lives, our lives are or cease to be. And thus, "The captain Blood" is a remarkable adventure film and a model to imitate.</body>
</review>
