<review author="José A. Peig" title="Dracula" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Coppola Yes knew offer something personal and genuine in a film that is gradually winning admirers as he will pass the time. However, the irregularity of the set and the same excesses just playing against him.</summary>
	<body>In 1992, Francis Ford Coppola offered us this revisitación to the myth of Dracula, and on that occasion we could say that, while you may like more or less, the experiment contributed quite to an icon already very overused and revisited in the past. This "does Bram Stoker? s Dracula" is not exactly a vulgar creation, although in the early 1990s it was Yes think recycle Count Dracula was a little novel occurrence.From the formal point of view, this film is a dazzling discovery of successive images that recreate environments and own icons of the genre classic horror, a frame Assembly organized in a way that comes to be an overwhelming visual Symphony full barroquismos, icons and symbologies belonging to various areas such as religion, medicine, sex, aristocratic lifethe same film and, more specifically, the horror film primeval, with clear echoes of Nosferatu, the werewolf, the Mummy, the Exorcist, etc. The music of the images is accompanied by a penetrating and breathtaking soundtrack composed by Woiciech Kilar, which fits perfectly to each visual compass each gesture or dramatic turn, and at the end, rather than a conventional narrative film, appears a video that pays a worthy tribute to the corpus of icons and creatures of legend. The plot framework relies on some basic issues that define almost all visual and narrative structure: sex, madness, the blood and the rebellion against fate and gods for a love lost and sought through "oceans of time". Love is the impulse that survives and manages to defeat death and dignifies even to the most despicable creatures, prisoner of his resentment and the obscurities that surround him, turned into nasty beast of the night, bat, Wolf, wrinkled and decrepit monster in the solitude of a castle that moves in the shadows, in the memories of a unreal, dream-like space: the eternal nightmare of the "no-muerte", the price to pay for rebelling against the creator. Here Count Dracula is depicted us as a deeply sad and powerful, being a God of the animality of everything that moves away from humanity. On the other side of the line, Mina, embodying the most beautiful innocence, the only thing that can redeem the beast. This is the fundamental axis: the ultraterrestrial and eschatological obsessively human, visceral love story, a metaphysics of love and sex which gives the film a strange romantic beauty. The essence of the visual poem by Coppola is a romantic idea of evil, death and love, and the most sordid and dark corners of the existence.Thus, Coppola Yes knew offer something personal and genuine in a film that is gradually winning admirers as he will pass the time. However, the irregularity of the set and the same excesses just playing against him. Say that some of the elements of the design and the caricaturisation of Count Dracula and the other characters ends up being abusive: Van Helsing is more a cliché than a functionally valid character and the character that plays Keanu Reeves (who is presumed a main role) is on the sidelines and delocalised work, another pointless cliché, and the same applies to the rest of characters; they are not integrated in the great drama of romantic and sinister that aims only characters really articulated in the great visual Symphony to Mina and Dracula. You can be said as a result, the film loses interest when Mina and the count will disappear from the scene, by the paleness of the remaining set, which, in addition, little help mediocre performances from a cast that leaves much to be desired. In such a case, only the splendid picture and rich visual imagery manage to maintain interest.</body>
</review>
