<review author="Kiko de España" title="Crash" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>So cool isn't. Haggis wheel well (she is 50 years old and works with Eastwood), but is not any genius: is the creator of the series "Walker Texas Ranger".</summary>
	<body>For a time this part come producing in Hollywood stories that seem to want to laugh of people. Robert Altman directed 1993 "Vidas cruzadas" (Short cuts) and the choral film fever began to invade us.The Altman film lasted three horazas as the putative daughter which came six years after the hand of Paul Thomas Anderson, "Magnolia". They were two great films. In 2003, Alejandro González Iñárritu conned us them all with "21 grams", a kind of "hagoloquequieroconmipelo" film version."I personally believe that"21 grams"is made with descartes of" loves dogs ", seems a bad sequel, those that do not know well if they are second parts, remakes, autohomenajes or who is I.""21 grams" was the plot of a movie of desktop, and script editing was horrible and the picture came to load. The hate you almost as much as "Strange coincidences" movie of last year which offended me but that very much.On this occasion, Paul Haggis, writer of "Million Dollar Baby", he debuted with grace at first, before time to stumble and fall in a succession of clichés that comes to despair at the end.The plot involves a series of characters (a couple of cops, a locksmith and his daughter, a family of Apus, a marriage rico da equal, because everyone has a thousand and one moves later or sooner face each other) in the now routine movie in media res.I am getting sick that the choral tapes have to have an accident as a link (Iñárritu takes 2 of 2 and I think that the new is also on there.) and having to endure stupid situations (that the Bullock on the stair slip) to stay afloat of difficult to give during resolution premises.It has interesting moments, such as boot, with a flat interesting sequence, and the criminal act of the couple of buddy renegríos. What happens is that it is anticlimática and does not surprise you at any time. Not never know what happens to many characters and the "21 grams" rubs ridicule in extreme situations (is really so difficult not to ridicule the supposed death that chains all?.)Not thrilled, and worst of all is that at the end, when you bromeas with the "ahorá fall frogs in the sky" it is about to pass. Finally, say that not so cool is. Haggis wheel well (she is 50 years old and works with Eastwood), but is not any genius: is the creator of the series "Walker Texas Ranger".And it ends with a theme of Stereophonics that paste not or glue.Best regards.</body>
</review>
