<review author="Natalia Eseverri" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Go see the Bourne últimatum, if it is that you like to enjoy a movie of action with constant tension, a good script and phrases of these sentenciadoras that leave you stone.</summary>
	<body>Lately I do more than complain about my boss. I did not know this facet jefera which is must always criticizing the employee for the minimum fault committed, more than anything to emphasize the degree of superiority which are before us. If that makes them happy, beyond them.The fact is that this aspect is hindering you enjoy my great radio moment and see that my dream slowly (even though my patience not hold it) will meet. Once I heard that careful what you wish, and do not so agree. In reality, it is more careful with what you dream because then when you look, what you want does not have the result that one expects.Am not going to let this woman do to go with bad side in the morning and not only by me, but by the people that every morning even if it is a little plug radio so I encourage them their cleaning, their work or that it simply entertains him and make them forget their problems a little while.I love to enjoy each step I do nothing else enter the study, when I go to organize my tiny desk with all the roles I have to announce (lost cats, blood donations, exhibition of reptiles urghh), then I'm thinking that songs are appropriate to start each block and that I want to hear, between means I have to put some obligation because people have to listen to everything and not only what to my I like.And so, one day and another, and the thing is that each time I costs less I get to go to work, I replaced by I wake up to have some fun with my radio.And please, go see the Bourne últimatum, if it is that you like to enjoy a movie of action with constant tension, a good script and phrases of these sentenciadoras that leave you stone. And I hope that many directors will account which not many punch Gets a better result for an action film. Mr Damon, this has been one of the best roles for refianzar his career, believe me.Now, women should look at your partner and seek that Bourne every man has inside, when you find it, enjoy it and make it appear more often.</body>
</review>
