<review author="Jose Contreras" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We can not feel seduced by an individual who confronts an unscrupulous Agency, a Ministry valued a life as a decimal, a Department of men wearing a tie and notebooks last generation who decide on the lives of others as if were choosing your dish on a menu.</summary>
	<body>There is a scene of "The Bourne Ultimatum" that takes place precisely in Madrid in which Jason Bourne a trap to the agents of the CIA with a fan. The viewer expects you to use it with violence, but in reality, the fan serves so officials think that there is someone in the room. It's a ploy by disinformation. "The Bourne Ultimatum" is a genuine film of our troubled century, does not win the strongest, wins the one who has more information.While the saga of 007 exhausted all the possibilities of a countdown of Miss Bond at the last second, never in the penultimate, the Bourne saga deck the possibilities of information in real time. The two duel protagonists are Bourne who knows the tricks of the CIA, and a head of the Agency facing him from his Office in New York, moving threads, handling huge sources of information, mobile, GPS, Internet, video cameras and databases. Bourne travels through cities around the world illustrating the variety of their roofs, its meters, and their police uniforms. Each geography stuffed a piece of the puzzle, each dead serves to supplement the information that should lead you to discover who he is. Bourne ignores things essential, as its name, while the Agency knows everything, as a fierce big brother. Bourne has some annoying insect in the Immaculate network that has woven the power. It is the splinter that makes flying through the air a protective and paternal system at first glance. Although we are not sure of the trail of deaths left justified, cannot fail to feel seduced by an individual who confronts an unscrupulous Agency, a Ministry valued a life as a decimal, a Department of men wearing a tie and notebooks last generation who decide on the lives of others as if were choosing your dish on a menu.</body>
</review>
