<review author="Jose Contreras" title="El Club de los Suicidas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"The club of suicide" part of a good story, so lovers of Tejero will have double the pleasure of seeing you do Uncle enrollao and suffer with its history.</summary>
	<body>The press speaks and speaks of Spanish cinema with the hope of playing any chord at the expense of my compassion for the poor figures or my patriotism. I've always ignored why the Spanish adjective added to a title of a film has to cause me some emotion that will not boot, of Yes, the show I'm consuming. And to question my patriotism, which is quite doubtful, I have to say that I was disturbed both the decline of the Spanish film and the resurgence of the Nepali poetry. To me give me good titles, like this of "club of suicide", and me not bother much with the flags.A good part of the films that want to saddle me with the excuse of the patriotic adjective not amount of the classification of sainetes. Producers are not put to work when they have a good history, are put to work when they have a couple of friendly names whose tics have conquered the public. Aware of this, many actors learn to sustain entire functions at the expense of his own comic vis. The Actor's Studio in Madrid is a histriones factory. The viewer will see films of Fernando Tejero because you like, and no need to know the name of the directors. "Even less of the writers.""The club of suicide" part of a good story, so lovers of Tejero will have double the pleasure of seeing you do Uncle enrollao and suffer with its history. Lucía Jiménez helps less, not because it does well the role of suicide ciclotímica that it is, but because it is not able to do anything else.The film rediscovers the best of our cinema of the 1950s, Jardiel Poncela, Edgar Neville, with a story of the absurd full of tenderness. A therapy group decides to put an end to their problems with a Covenant. They will meet every Tuesday to decide who will have the pleasure of dying and who is going to be the executor in a card game, following the example of the novel of r. l. Stevenson.El fine humor comes from the irony of the approach, the paradox of situations, because it is fortunate if they just evil and a frustration if they survive. But the main inspiration is the contrast of the characters. Gordito, perhaps the most successful, is a fudge to kill, and that makes it endearing. There is a memorable scene in which Fernando Tejero wants to support him and goes to his burger bar with ambulance work. Each character in the scene is understanding a different story, to which more crazy, the spectator, who understands them all, don't know where mess. It is a sequence worthy to be included in the short list of examples of high comedy.</body>
</review>
