<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="La Caja Kovak" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the Kovak box the pace is in great danger, because even in the seemingly interesting end lacking in entertainment and it ends up being, nothing more and nothing less that a simple and blatant "homage" (copying, plagiarism...) to more classic thrillers.</summary>
	<body>The main mistake of the film by Daniel Monzón is feel good, or is believed good. Already in the beginning is this tremendous capacity to begin to count events (strange or fictional?)and then leave them in the air. And that is where the second and very serious problem arises: these events are not well explained or end up being resolved so coerente. And this, in a film of intrigue, it is essential to be well carried out. In the Kovak box the pace runs another serious danger, because even in the seemingly interesting end lacking such entertainment and it ends up being, nothing more and nothing less that a simple and blatant "homage" (copying, plagiarism.) to the more classic thrillers. Moreover, this bland outcome is contradicting to its apparent aspect too bombastic. So ridiculous little, final suspense and, of course, awful script. I would only highlight an able to entertain the Viewer without being shameful Timothy Hutton and with pretty good scenes such as the hospital or House of that partner. His companion, a soda and agonies Lucía Jiménez, fails to give the height in her first foray into English-speaking film. His performance is tired, but I think that this is due to the monsoon, which has directed painfully. It is one of those characters that end up getting tired to the Viewer. The rest of the cast stays in the line of Hutton, as they are not too annoying. They only complement. And it is that already media film you realize that this is a mixture of movies (badly mixed) and that not only he has no feet or head, but that it also lacks personality. And only have to see several of the sequences where initially has to witness that touch Monzón (sorry if it is too ridiculous), that, unfortunately, only is presence in a scene (if that is his personal touch): the terrace of the bar and the fall of the protagonist. And I say the way is shot, a plane sequence "false" remarkable quality. The rest, disappointing. A bad film capable of surprising us by disappointing that comes to be, more than anything because I at least, I was expecting something much better. And it is that I had never seen an ending so inconsistent and failed like this! I hope that the next time this such monsoon Daniel knows what makes and you roll the scenes with a bit of common sense and, above all, personality.</body>
</review>
