<review author="José A. Peig" title="El quinto elemento" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are many moviegoers winks in a recapitulation that resembles a parody of the genre at the same time seems to want to apply a renewal on it.</summary>
	<body>We served the request from one of our readers that we talk about the fifth element with certain slackness by the references that we had until then the Luc Besson film was a "deceptive" and quite overused product in its approach. Other fields emphasizes in its thematic richness, but they are the least, and now, after the screening, we conclude that it has been one of the most profitable requests, and we must do justice to one of the misunderstood films by antonomasia in recent times.Starting from the assumption that we are before a film halfway between science fiction and pure and simple action, the so-called thematic richness would perhaps best defined if we speak of many lectures that converge in a structure of tones articulated perfectly. (The thematic richness refers to the isolated concepts, the structure of tones more affects the polyhedral character of its global texture). One method (among others possible) whether we are dealing with a good movie, mediocre or bad for artistic purposes, is to check the diversity of readings produced in the mind of each spectator, provided different interpretations are at its base a verifiable film content in the eyes of the spectators. To greater diversity, higher quality, unless there is some kind of inconsistency in this internal structure, and this inconsistency not depend on whether the themes are compatible or incompatible, but if are valid with regard to the purpose pursued.It speaks the fifth element as object of entertainment, film shots, harassment, call and gossip at the service of Bruce Willis, actor here this in its sauce more than ever. Refers to the playful look that envelops the story from beginning to end and also refers to a transcendent message about the current state of civilization. All these readings are as certain as the visual and plot fluidity of the film material this prepared and organized according to the above-mentioned thematic characteristics, and importantly is that Besson achieved effectiveness at all levels proposed. The most obvious result is a happy combination of science fiction, mythology, and humor from the earliest moments in which we see a group of archaeologists in a temple and the spacecraft descended, with the subsequent parade of aliens walk with debauchery. Often criticized that plumbous and humorous tone that dominates the narrative pulse, but since the first scenes the work reveals his intention to be a delusional and sardonic look to a genre and its clichés. It is not a defect of the film, but an attribute set out with such effectiveness that becomes the true spirit of the work, its differential feature of other similar products and which gives the uniqueness. From a global perspective, the film is a representation of a universe with identity and own uniqueness which brings together elements of universes moviegoers as the original star trilogy with irony wars, Blade Runner, Star Trek or other products whose enclave this closer to the comic book or the so-called "series z", why warn in many passages tics scurfy film which serve as a springboard to introduce characters who rallan - with consistency and sense of set - in the grotesque, as, for example, played by Gary Oldman or histrionic and irritating color shemale participation. There are many moviegoers winks in a recapitulation that resembles a parody of the genre at the same time seems to want to apply a renewal on it.Thus, as action movie - humor, a playful object not lacking wit whose sarcasm is the main attraction that configures a script dotted with sharp dialogues, sometimes, inclusive, bitter irony. The visual section, highlights the designs of Moebius and an exotic and exuberant Futurism of colours and shapes, a stage in perfect concordance with shades of history: myth, irony, acid humor and parody unhealthy. Therefore the integration of the scenario with the history is another of its virtues, of how plastics resources and dramatic content form a whole for an irreverent and dynamic genres crossing. Merit of narrating fluently and great pace a very simple story (attention also to the use of mounting, superb) on a Savior of the world and an anonymous salvador that they discover, fight and end up falling in love with, should be added the wisdom of using the tone humorous to offer a critical on human society look, banality facing us and the chaos that US rules when the machinery of the universe plays against us. What it says is a ridicule of the human system and their myths not devoid of some bitterness, as we see in the scene of the female protagonist looking at photographs of war and death, and the expression of pain on his face, we come to the end and discovered that the smile and the sardonic despiporre hide a tear in the future.</body>
</review>
