<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Death Proof" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Death proof is not the best film of Tarantino, but is perhaps one of the best examples of why he got himself into this filmmaking.</summary>
	<body>Gus Van Sant (psychosis) and Soderbergh (the good German) tried to with your favorite classics, but his cinephiles proved too Orthodox. More than honor, copied the original or emularon scenes in order to play to see how it is or simply as a craftsman. And so it was. Tarantino for its part, as it already did through his filmography, not copy, does not want to look like to?; its cinephiles is selective, episodic, spreads, giving rise to an original Frankenstein, or that makes us believe (especially to viewers that we have not tracked the video libraries of the Z series, populated beings nothing classic, but it is archetypal of the underworld that surprised and touched the teenager Tarantino). The tribute is not the classics of cinema or literature. Moreover, Tarantino would help later filmmakers to not be afraid when choosing their narrative and Visual affinities of the rake of what the Academy termed film offal. And is that she times of a new cinema, less scrupulous to resort to other means and techniques of production (digital) and other forms of storytelling (comics, video games, music videos), away from the literature or the picture.On the other hand, Tarantino is a cinematic tradition both European (Italian neorealism, Nouvelle Vague) and American (Arthur Penn, Martin Scorsese, f. f. Coppola) that seeks to portray the lives of characters terminals, extreme, pathetic, esperpénticos, born to his proletarian imagination, relating that another American, camouflaged by political correctness. Only that Tarantino does not exist another intent (if any) that have fun and have fun, play this great Carnival that is the cinema.Death proof (A proof of death) demands the viewer's complicity which partly originates both acceptance of its universe (and the laws that govern) the familiarity with which the viewer faces their personal archetypes (tuned cars, Warrior girls, violent males, road, local music clubs), taken from a full product non-transferable cinephiles serie B that they ran back in 1970s and spoke of cars, girls, weapons and very male males (in fact, Grindhouse mention continuous sessions of Z series and gore films in the 1970s, usually damaged or incomplete), or the slashers of the sixties, with the murderer of adolescents (so fashionable in the thriller today). In Jackie Brown is seen on television ads with girls Warrior selling arms, archetype in the Z series of the 1970s.Even obliges us to recreate his previous films (and if not stay tuned to the car of the second group of girls, or the ringtone from one of them). Its cinephiles is such that even the garito Guero? s is lined with posters of Latino films such as the limits of love (Rafael Moreno-Marchent, 1976), starring Juan Luis Galiardo and Charo López, or the Mexican the three Elenas (Gómez Muriel Emnilio, 1954). The girls discuss the movie point limit: zero (1971), another road movie, but with script - attention! - Guillermo Cabrera Infante. When the girls come down from the car, they are squatting to speak, this scene is one tribute to another of the flight (1972). Stundman Mike rubber duck appears in the film Convoy (1978). The black car with the skull is equal to the brake broken, crazy cars (1980). Persecutions sounds music impact (1981). The circular camera movement while they speak is equal to Reservoir Dogs (1992), when they are in the cafeteria and discuss tips, or in the final scene pointing each other. The same Kurt Russell is a substitute (reduced) of his character in 1997: rescue in New York normal that the sensations after viewing of Death proof are as extreme as the proposal itself of its director. However, somewhat skirting the issue of taste, Death proof is a quality product, of careful and visually powerful, colorful, aesthetic with a soundtrack as good as fun. If anything can blame you excessive recreation in the dialogues in the car and in bars, which dilate the narrative time and perhaps despisten or bored. But they are these final twenty minutes to remedy that. Tarantino always liked to hear their characters everyday issues, laughing, cursing, Miss life between shots and drives. And in a breath rip the narration with extreme actions that will surprise the Viewer. Thus, Bridget Fonda will die in the hands of a De Niro pissed by not shut up. Or Travolta, who will die after shit. In Tarantino not should never confuse the border of their beings and lives with its aesthetic character.No need to be fond of the chile, the nachos or the bizarre violence to recognize that there are many scenes that hide not outstanding Visual expressiveness and richness. In fact, the Tarantino film is all image striking our retinas. His scenes are the scenes that the Director will have an impact, or as a ghost were kept briefly in his retina when he saw them in other films.Death proof is not the best film of Tarantino, but is perhaps one of the best examples of why he got himself into this filmmaking. In its day the Nouvelle Vague it distanced itself from the themes that concern to the preceding generation, seeking new ways of seeing the world. Tarantino is perhaps a good example of the fascination of the film (and with it the society) contemporary by engulf fast images per the only pleasure of enjoying them without respite or reflection. The greater contempt for his film is the apathy or boredom.</body>
</review>
