<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los 4 Fantásticos y Silver Surfer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about fantastic four which have to rid the world of a threat that it wants to destroy. Something better that the first delivery, but remains very directed to a too child audience to appeal to adults.</summary>
	<body>Whenever I see the poster of the fantastic these, I think would be my preferred superpower. The stone seems to me that not it cool me. Very handles but does not cool. The elastic is good to catch the beers from the fridge without having to move the sofa. Mola. The firearms cow poop, if my santa is angry if he sees a chinazo on the couch I can not imagine if you see that I have burned the whole couch at a fart. I'll be invisible, which in addition that I go in balls all day, I can fulfill all dreams of mind teen body of man with mustache.The film deals with a threat to destroy the Earth. He is not a missile or an asteroid, or Martian with horns, if not one thing that eats planets I as the cacahueses of the aperitif. To go preparing them, peeled them and removing the seeds to the planets, send first to Silver Surfer, surfer silver balls. So the fantastic 4, aided by one who should be the villain in the first and the army of fools, must save humanity. We deserve such aid or we must succumb?The pastelosa if a little Ribbon, with a wedding between superheroes as we want to show that they have feelings. The moments of action are quite nice, but you still with dialogue and lacking call. Thank God they have set aside certain jokes that were more than horrible, pathetic. And not to mention the army, which are to be given of kicks in the very cataplines from here until Saturno. Hey, poor Saturn, which is eaten the bug eats planets. A minute of silence for the ringed planet.In short, film about fantastic four which have to rid the world of a threat that it wants to destroy. Something better that the first delivery, but remains very directed to a public too infant for like the adultos.2 mine and one of my girl.Besitos.P.D: at the end of the film spotted the criticism with clarity and saw how anymore you 2 stars as my name is Chinchán. But came my medium Zucchini and I said has been very well, a Yes? Putting me in my role of man says, if honey, if. So we are going to put 3.</body>
</review>
