<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Frantic guignol of all the vices of Tarantino, amplified, converted into delicacy for greedy and, of course, garbage for his film enémigos.</summary>
	<body>Perhaps the verbal incontigencia of the protagonists of Death proof despiste on true cinematic mechanisms of the tape: its predatory revivalism of the exploitation of the 1970s and the double programos scurfy and greasy film little presentable and, above all, autoparódico and a few upstanding wanting to taunt his own seriousness, but Tarantino, the former enfant terrible of filmmanages budgets baggy and the presence of the capitalist duo Weinstein so this trash-movie is not a fiasco, and Amen to feed the ego of its author and its nombradía, click box, which is a noble exercise than Hollywood never despise. There is no Death proof tufo to serie B, while all his dinamitado footage transpire serie B by all their dinamitados pores. Tarantino attends what better do: the linguistic, lúbrico, desvergonzado and paroxysm machine-gunned by a chorus of Greek heroes (heroines in this case) drunk on tequila, bourbon, fast sex, cars impossible horsepower and pleasure hedonistic of violence as a lure for intellectuals open-minded and simple parishioners eager to impact scenes and legs mutilated half of the asphalt. And Orchestra it with talent who has enjoyed a lot with film to the indisimulado pays tribute, this carousel of curved malicious and road bars illuminated by the addictive neon of the beer brands of renown and very grounded soundtrack of the jukebox of the era, capturing the spirit of the entire batch of classics from the Motown or Stax label. At that rate, sweaty and procaz Arlene/Butterfly (Vanessa Ferlito) marks a bold lap dancing that can not be missed without a bow.The narrative merchandise of Tarantino rummages in the predatory ability of a spectator nonconformist, fetish and annulled by the mediocrity of mass culture, which sells consumer universal sampling artifacts, films to have smoothed them the edges so that they can be embedded in all cultures in all countries where it is supposed that it is going to make money. The insolence of Tarantino is to pursue this goal without it note in excess. Ageing of color, the terrible sound quality, roll breaks, gray tones, the burnt frames and even the black-and-white false which then becomes the second tranche of the Ribbon color are winks accomplices to a film already dead, discredited by the very abundantly infumable quality of his proposal, but that has fueled the cinephiles of many of the directors that are now considered essential and that, over time, if they do not enfangan in divismos and unnecessary ombliguismos, will be considered classic. Death proof was justified by that falsified variant of the cinephiles of their creator, but reformulates action cinema, conveniently nostalgic and crowded of film quotes - from Russ Meyer and its Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill! the fundamental point limit: zero Sarafian, passing through the cannonballs of Gone in 60 seconds by Halicki or the masterpiece of persecutions by car which is Kirby, the tape of Steve McQueen that put Peter Yates in the Gazetteer of Directors of worship of the seventy. Having seen Planet Terror does not prevent this review complete a tour total on Grindhouse, Opera double Rodriguez and Tarantino that should have been Preparatoria in one session, but the machinery of European distribution has preferred to start with, fracture, doubling revenue and generate one greater expectation. The erotic component amplified in the first part of the tape dwindles in the second, but the tape is swept by this dirty look of worship voyeur. Own character of Stuntman Mike (A formidable Kurt Russell that leads the way that once enjoyed Travolta in his role as Vincent Vega) is a genius of the controlled perversion of the author: a psychopath who had made the delights of Cronemberg, a murderer who destroys women with his car as a ruthless weapon. The populated list of females shadowed memorable moments of other tapes of Tarantino. There are occasions in which we believe we see a scene in Reservoir dogs or those sparkling dialogues, lighted from a morbid fascination with the black series, which make Pulp fiction an absolute masterpiece. Stuntman Mike hunting parts, materials on the asphalt, charged in the second part of the tape new life with a thug trio of female warriors, drawn directly from the bestiary of the inevitable Meyer, not allowing cough them or that a nutty rajada face damaged them their games. But we do not destripemos the end of the Symphony.The viewer outside what Tarantino describes, who does not comulgue with that juicy cinematic B or Z series reference list or blaxpoitation or giallo or everything this Capito man has seen in his earlier days an accomplice, nothing remilgado when it comes to getting bogged down in low-budget products, outs pathetic scenes and provocateurs like few others to translate sex will not enjoy the same as the Viewerviolence and fast cars. This is the perfect recipient of this whim of author, excellent in his daring, maybe swollen minutes to establish itself as a single piece and can be exploited outside the four Unidos.Anoche States scheduled a double session classical tarantiniana (Pulp Fiction and Jackie Brown). Opportunism, business vision, Audacity, but opportunity that new public attend, in the front row at home arrebujado the favourite armchair, the delirious imagination of this master.</body>
</review>
