<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Death Proof" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good film genre, more serious that what it seems and with good ideas, both Visual and verbal, showing once again that Tarantino is a large, much to those who consider him a chupóctero that takes advantage of the strengths of other colleagues.</summary>
	<body>Estimable work of Tarantino films previously, that, as always in his film, baby playing different genres, popular in the 1970s. To begin we must say, although this already knows almost everyone, is "Death Proof" is the second film which made up the "Grindhouse" created by the own Tarantino and his friend Robert Rodriguez, of which we have already seen the first "Planet Terror" Grindhouse.In United States he was in session only, but given the uneven results (rightly) considered that in Europe (and I guess the rest of the world, although this do not know with certainty) should do so separately.On this occasion, Tarantino manages to work very entertaining, full of spectacular, intrigue, well measured tension, humor humorous and a little terror. To achieve this he has directed beautifully to a group of, above all, excellent young actresses, some of them with experience only previously as a specialist. In this sense, Zöe Bell which, for example, had been the double for Uma Thurman in "Kill Bill" is a discovery. However, to my cost me enter a little into the heart of the matter, as they say, to seem me their first twenty minutes, somewhat insubstantial. I refer to the tirades, conversations and discussions between the first four girls. The truth is that everything, everything they spoke I was alien. Me the refinflaba.This made desenganchara me it a poquillo. But, with the appearance on the scene of the character of Kurt Russell, the interest returned until no longer disappear until the end of the tape. A tape which, in its second part, acquires dyes majestic, full of interesting and humorous approach to the life of the four friends that have been addressed to Tennessee to try a wonderful car to get all the juice. They are full of fun, laughter in a few scenes that manages and which draws a smile at all times. Here they are magnificent, spectacular, desperate shooting moments, and that put the willies to the Viewer. Feminism to power, or fight against the sexist bastard who tries to break free, beautiful women and a future to conquer. A good genre film, more serious that what it seems and with good ideas, both Visual and verbal, showing once again that Tarantino is a large, much to those who consider him a chupóctero that takes advantage of the strengths of other colleagues.</body>
</review>
