<review author="Tyler" title="Death Proof" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cinema can die calm after this movie, a true classic film. The movies are made to make things as well. Anyone who wants to see that is it for the film, see Death Proof. cinema is pure.</summary>
	<body>The film is a collective experience. Or at least that is thought despite the appearance of videos and DVD's. You get in a room with a lot of people that no0 know and share, want it or not, same experience. Because that is the film. And what you see, unlike books, happening at the same time. The screen is a window to the same time in which you live, there are flasbacks and sketches of that kind or not. Lately happens much managers come in the film something more than it is. The film is defined from long ago, and there is no way to override it, it is what it is, and segurá so until his death. Tarantino is, possibly, along with Clint Eastwood and Silvester Stallone the last really classic cinema filmmaker. The film is something that should produce a physical rather than emotional reaction in the Viewer. The film is more a way of conveying feelings emotions. The film is not an internal experience, it is external to the contrary to the literature. The film is a less pure artificial experience to rather than, for example, the theatre, but not so.It is not time to redefine the cinema, it is time to glorify it, do with it what to do with him.Quentin Tarantino is the person that has possibly been more movies in history. Someone who loves film more than all of us together, someone who understands it better than anyone else alive.DEATH PROOF is pure cinema of truth. Is film that must be made and does not, it is an experience physical for the senses that gets you in a career of kinetic movement on board car movies that some may have forgotten but that Tarantino handles that I know what they are and that movies come.From the outset breathe film, film drunk. All levels are film, the entire movement and history. Because not just any story is film, and this is. The movie tricks you, something also for which the film is made. Cinema should not be sincere, the film is just the opposite. Cinema should take the hair but do not think that you are stupid. DEATH PROOF makes you believe one thing to then show you another. Makes you believe that someone is the main character (or characters) to then change the tables and tell you that not. All within a logical narrative perfectly built and taken.Tarantino looks to cinema to rediscover us film that truly is. It may be, as I said it in my review on PLANET TERROR, the only movie "tribute" of Tarantino. Here in addition to steal and recycle, it pays homage to cars. All the players cars, are also; they come from some classic: from BULLIT point-to-point límite:cero and his driver Kowalsky. Stuntman Mike's car has the duck Kris Kristoferson in CONVOY (Sam Peckimpah), one of the best movies that exist and the least valued.Stuntman Mike is facing its objectives, chosen randomly among the girls you see in any of his travels of two acts. It shows it as someone that does this from time to time. We see the bastard that can be, and have not gotten to then put it in a situation in which him, begins to be desired. They are two acts, such as the movies by Kubrick, prfectamente balanced so that it is not arritmico, so will again become film and his movie not to smell like stupid experiment, because Tarantino is filmmaker.The cast is the host. We return to retrieve Kurt Russell that we we, rescue in New York and blow in little China. An actor that can give much more of what they allow and here shows that it can be as good as Michael Parks and Michael Parks can be as good as Al Pacino or Robert de Niro.Michael Parks, actor educated at American 70 especially TV, is an interpreted subvaloradísimo and has demonstrated much so not to call more. It is terrific, and returns to Earl McGraw, as already it was open until the dawn, KILL BILL or PLANET TERROR. And it seems that it has interpreted at the same time, because it is exactly the same as when it did open up the dawn, more than 10 years ago. It clashes nothing.The girls are perfect, and each fits into its role as Madonna conceded in his suit of leather of FOUR ROOMS, perfectly. Girls normal roles of normal girls. Talking about like normal girls and normal subjects. Nothing of artificialismos in a part of the movie that asks it, girls normal ansolutamente.Tarantino plays Warren, the bartender, a role which seems an updated versiçon of the roles of barman did Karl Malden. Cameos for his colleague Eli Roth and the sobris of Rodriguez. DEATH PROOF is a fully cinematic experience that goes at full speed, and that you want to see it more than three times. This is pure cinema, of truth, of that which invented it in the film. You enter and upload to a film that you can not resist you as a viewer, a film that makes you think that all the movies should be like this, with this unpretentious spirit, only the give to the public a film.Cinema has forgotten that cinema should thus be cinematographic experiences supported by principles that are running in the history of cinema for years, and many film rejects saying that the film should be more original and reinvent on symbolism and ideas more committed (see: Medem, Lars Von Trier and other peña no idea of which is to make movies) DEATH PROOF is a movie that reminds us that it is cinemaa movie with which we enjoy as I enjoyed the film before, when is towards truth. The film may die quiet if you want after a film with its quality. Absolutely perfect. Maybe that Tarantino is one of the best filmmakers in the history, which is why we are fortunate to be alive when he is. Within much we will talk of him as a genius, and we as the fortunate ones to have enjoyed living.Again and again there is that see is movie and realize that the film is this. Enjoy authentic which want to pay to see.</body>
</review>
