<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Disturbia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Disturbia was born to be flavored with popcorn and Yankee syrup. Intrigued, no, we will not find nothing more than scares of telefilm. Even the sex scenes promise a climax exceeding an advertisement.</summary>
	<body>Much of cinema universalizable consumption found lately by the charts continues the icon of the avant-garde artistic dictum pop-art, Andy Warhol, whereby the essence of art is not the originality of the work, but in its reproductive potential, both in the popular psyche and in the process of production and dissemination. The art, therefore it is not creation, but eternal return of the same, always fleeting, and in their contingency is where its wealth. Thus, a portrait of Marilyn can adopt various colors, even knowing the obvious repetition of its forms and still coming its figure of popular iconography drawn from the common media, leisure or consumption.This philosophy of art entails a decrease in the slow process of creation (in this case playback) classic, and a cheap and universalizable dissemination. But in turn he evades responsibility that Yes existed in classical art to be creator of a genuine work, product of the brilliant idea of his maker. On the contrary, the postmodern artist is heir of art as a form of popular dissemination of icons that one day were called works of art or teachers, but today only reactualizan from the movie fan nostalgia, or as it is here, from its reproduction warholian for fast and cost effective consumption for a large mass of spectators.Disturbia is, like so many others, a recent example of this trend in which supported with more than demonstrated success crematístico the apparatus of Hollywood production. In fact, Hollywood invented film as this machinery full of fetishes (geniuses that it looks as if we talk of painting) represented through their actors, actresses, directors and movies. The idea, the concept, the theme, the intentions of the author (screenwriter or director) are diluted by the dazzling glamour of this props that both love to the fan-áticos of its pageantry. See if not photogenic glamour that sold emblematic as Cannes or Venice festivals, guarantors on their day of a film blessed as classic today.Disturbia is adaptive reproduction of the classic which supports, there in it will nor less deconstructive passion still seeking to pay homage to the Hitchcock and his rear window (1954). Everything is cold and calculated. More talluditos characters come to adolescents, who is with whom mainstream (which polls say fill the seats of theaters in the developed world) will identify most likely. We are thus presented with elements whose contextualization (modernization?) does not comply with an artistic or narrative function, but a mere adaptation to the public that will bring the expected final benefits. This is the case of the use that is made in the film of new technologies (mobile phones with camera, laptops, digital cameras high definition and small size), whose archetypal shall exemplify the typical Eastern clever (but histrionic), faithful friend of the protagonist American shamelessly. To allow the director (do not know if suggested by his lucid producer) the idea of including in the protagonist knowledge of Spanish in clear complicity with the most influential Hispanics in the United States.UU. Up the aspirants to the White House know that they should be bound to venial winks to the potential voter Hispanic if they want to scratch votes. That Yes, the Hispanic police will not have a very decisive role in the resolution of the facts that Disturbia suggests. Everything must be like the America welfare would like: white men seeking white women in residential area of single-family luxury.Disturbia was born to be flavored with popcorn and Yankee syrup (more profits leaving the exhibition halls). Not disappoint to who is swayed by his futile but natural need to bask in this September that promises much backward heat. Intrigued, no, we will not find nothing more than scares of telefilm. Even the sex scenes promise a climax exceeding of an advertisement with girl mona palmito strolling the neighborhood.Warhol not deceived its delivered Viewer. Everyone knew that the empty banality of several colored Marilyn lies in that, in his electrifying transience of fair media.</body>
</review>
