<review author="Txapulin" title="Caótica Ana" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I have mixed feelings. On the one hand the film has things that fascinate me, but I think that to Medem history you are Manus.</summary>
	<body>I have highly conflicting feelings about this movie. Who I have read enough here or know something my film tastes knows that I think Julio Médem best current Spanish film director. I am fascinated by their first two films, cows and the red squirrel, surrendered fell to Earth and I think it is one of my favorite movies. Lovers of the Arctic circle and Lucia and sex are two separate exercises of style and mastery, and even his documental-entrevista pelota seems a brave and sincere tremendamiente film, which although he failed in intention at the time, is one of the best portraits of the fucking Spanish tension in recent years and a torn cry of request for dialogue at a time when nobody was concerned about the dialogue, and why were loaded. Yes, were it they uploaded. The stale Spanish right crucified him as radical, and I imagine that from the abertzale left nor do they do very well regarded. The documentary had to be a preface for his fiction film Aitor, which was never done and I imagine was in the library of the never completed films. To make matters worse, his sister Anne died in traffic accident. After six years without a film of fiction of Medem and as a result of all these events comes Caótica Ana, an escape route on the subject of the Basque conflict and an emotional shock following the death of his sister. Or so play it I, which for something the movies of Medem are subjective and intepretables, and therefore better or worse depending on mood.I said that I have mixed feelings. On the one hand the film has things that fascinate me: images, music, camera movements, the Division of the movie into a countdown?, all the narrative magic of Medem is there. Do do then I love some characters, the same Anne, as we have at the beginning of the movie (do then changes and?, I do not know, then I will try to investigate this), Linda, the character of baby Klaus, German father of Ana?, then landscapes, the sea of Ibiza and the streets of Madrid, the use of art (the paintings of Ana, painted by the sister of director Ana Médem) as one narrative element?But I think that to Medem history, the argument itself, you are Manus. There is news that the director works his films at various narrative levels; This causes a smart complicity with the viewer who participates in his game. But here I something went wrong, the pieces do not fit. Or as Yes they fit, but a part of the resulting picture is ugly, I do not like, and that saddens me because of my favorite director wonders I hope, but you can not always have everything. I try to explain.I like the film as a tribute to the dead sister, as the portrait of a woman through the art expressing their inner chaos and his fear to die. I also like the portrait of the character of Anne through the excellent work of casting that has resulted in the choice of actress Manuela Vellés to interpret it. It is the casting of a look of multiple green, of an expressive smile of a voice, a laugh which is linked to the Angela of Earth or the Bethlehem of Lucia and sex, and by the way, of a beautiful body. I like both the character at the beginning of the movie that gives me lot of anger, how will degrade as it progresses the footage, especially at the end, finally being a ghost of what is at the beginning. I really like how the issue of death in some dialogues and I like the history of the women of the alleged "previous lives", but I do not like everything is explained from hypnosis and reincarnation. I like the treatment of sex and relationships male-female, and even the theory that that are all about whores and we are all a few rapists, but I do not like anything that serves as a political metaphor about the Empires and countries without State, and much less with this absurd ending that spoils the movie, because it gives importance to the least interesting topic that we have seen throughout the film so far.Overall, I felt that I was watching a very dispersed film, who does not know very well to where you want to go, and that when he arrives says me nothing interesting. That Yes, meanwhile, narrativamente is so poetic, magic and with scenes as emotive as only Médem knows to make his films.</body>
</review>
