<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Caótica Ana" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Medem cinema is,? per is?, poetic character. But oh!, the line that separates the verse of the gravel is so mild?</summary>
	<body>Visitors to this site know that I'm an admirer of "Lovers of the Arctic Circle", the masterpiece of Julio Médem, although I'm not a fervent follower of this Basque director film, in which magnificent works such as the aforementioned coexist with other interesting but less interest, such as "Sex and Lucia", or decidedly unsuccessful, as "Land". With this "Caótica Ana" seems that you tap the sand: Medem cinema is, "per are", poetic character. But oh!, the line that separates the verse of the gravel is so mild? The new film by July is very far from approaching, or remotely, to what purpose, a poem about reincarnation, a literal Ibizan girl and topically "ad lib", rescued for art and society by a patron franchute, in love with a Berber tormented by his past, and finally literally emptied of their many (and tragic) past lives through hypnosis. Medem background allow the viewer granted a credit which the donostiarra squandering soon, as soon as we see that history is Martian, what should be poetical is just corny, and there is little a scene with the mark of the House, to remember the powerful visual creativity of the vaunted "Lovers of the Polar circle", and yes a considerable mental empanada. Does chaotic, as its title, soon shows that Medem does not know what tells us in this film, unless we are all not one but thousand, great discovery, entirely as the penicillin? The characters are unfortunate, since the Ibizan catetita who could shout, as in the Bible, that "my name is Legion" (although without demons inside; or it?), that goes from spineless for life, to his patron, a Charlotte Rampling entirely outside the role without a profile, without edges, a species of matriarch (do something interested: 60%, specifically?); the hypnotist, who goes a bit Seraphic Angel, "glam", is true; the empollón Berber with its ethnographic Bleus and its stormy past; the father of the catetita, as soon as they removed from the cave where he lives dying? the only character with any consistency, and better served by her actress, is baby, the friend of the protagonist, a video artist with a peculiar vision of relations between men and women and great desparpajo. Special mention in the negative, in the awful end, in which which Medem, pobretico, come from the makers of the war of Iraq (making use, therefore a kind of doublet of Donald Rumsfeld, "hawk" do Secretary of Defense, supposedly mastermind of that warlike nonsense that is giving so many headaches, and what you rondaré, brunette?), becoming our protagonist give a giftthat we not destriparemos, but that sounds like a boy child tantrum when not enough to give him the kick to the great who abuses him. Finally, each one is very owner of revenge as he sees fit, but not at the cost of bastardear a film with a pegote which not is beside the point. Or perhaps Yes, perhaps the estrambote suits this absurdity inevitably doomed to the costalazo at the box office.</body>
</review>
