<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="La Carta Esférica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The fact that the fascinating history of the?Does Gloria Dei?, the Brig of the 18th century that blanket so precious treasure, left blur and hardly count runs not precisely in favour of the outcome of the film.</summary>
	<body>Imanol Uribe is not exactly the height of subtlety. Said it in the wake of his "Journey of Carol" and must be repeated now, in the light of this adaptation of the novel by Arturo Pérez-Reverte. It goes without saying that "The spherical letter" is not a bad film, although perhaps not the good movie that could have been extracted from the interesting work of the Cartagena academic. The book is powerful: Describes characters of some archetypal form, but with specific weight. The translation to the big screen by the Basque filmmaker isn't at that same height. The story is attractive: marino unemployed meets devastating female (in the best tradition of the vampires in the film, but updated) hooked you for a company perhaps impossible, with several moscardones, which more dangerous, lurking, although the main danger of the couple is so close: inside, specifically. But the praying mantis which should be the female character of Tangier far women perfidious, embaucadora, treacherous, calculator, Pérez-Reverte imagined. It has to do, of course, the own Aitana Sánchez-Gijón, that villain roles not you will mostly, but it is also the fault of the own Uribe, which never was a paragon of perfection in directing actors. Carmelo Gomez has got three quarters of the same: his Coy does not have the entity, the background, the sediment of his "alter ego" literary. Enrico Lo Verso is an unconvincing Palermo: not seen never the bad viciously kill or a fly, not the adventurer tanning in a thousand battles and with more bad grapes that the stepmother of snow white that describes the book. So things, "The spherical letter", in its film adaptation, it is be a neat product supported professionalism but without spark any personality, confirming that day that they talked about creativity at school, Uribe had Miss, perhaps with mumps? Does not this be a critical devastating, because there are products that deserve much more: there is here a correct design of production, a story not bored ever (is impossible in the stories of Pérez-Reverte, where to spend much, and almost always stimulants, or at least striking), a cute couple (although Gomez is starting to put fondón, and the poor Aitana Basque director makes fornicate as if instead of making love I was hitting with) (her lover) ridiculous resulting rather than erotic, beautiful coastal and underwater landscapes, the search for a hidden treasure, bad (something bogus), good (something carajotes) and mediopensionistas (it, hell and paradise in one body). However, the fact that the suggestive history of "Gloria Dei", the Brig of the 18th century that he blanket so precious treasure, make it blur and hardly count does not run precisely in favour of the outcome of the film. Incidentally that the journey of the Jesuit ship that he tried to avoid the expulsion of the company, at the hands of Carlos III, well deserves a film for herself. That itself, if possible, her head not Imanol Uribe?</body>
</review>
