<review author="El vengador toxico" title="Ratatouille" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He is not a film of laughter as it could have been Shrek, but of a kind comedy with funny moments. A chapeau to Pixar by this wonder.</summary>
	<body>Pixar returns to the attack after the small fiasco that turned out to be Cars (in comparison with the previous wonders of the House). As in this type of movies one tends to compare them with previous ones, I will say that in my place the masterpiece from Pixar is finding Nemo. And in this case I must say that they have managed to return to the level of that film.In every Pixar movie you expect the best of animation by computer (remains ahead of others) and it could not be less. Although I have the impression that not give everything they can about as realism to continue looking like a cartoon. Because the scenes that stand out as the eddies in the sewer or rain on the cobblestones of Paris, seem so real? that in the end have been a stamp indicating that real images have not been used or "capture of movement". It is impressive in the three years that have passed since Nemo as the realism of the water has increased so much.But let the technical aspects, which have continued to be bright in the Incredibles and Cars on the side. Always gives me bad spine when an animated film is announced through the stars appearing as actors/dubbers, as if they are not delivering anything (is not always so, eye). And as usual, Pixar has not done, despite having big players in English, such as Ian Holm, or Peter or?Toole (okay, are not stars).The script is a very clever piece that, like Nemo (since I know I repeat myself) animals interacting with humans, but do not speak, but that humans treat them as it would be usual, until the protagonist Gets a communication.Remy is a rat of field that has a delicate sense of taste and smell. This makes that the garbage sifted his father and other family (the clan) is very unsatisfactory. Therefore it is sometimes slips into the kitchen of the farm where can give free rein to your desires, and there met the greatest chef of France, the great Gusteau recipes. Do all goes well until one day?.I love how it handles the communication between humans and rats. Humans see them as disgusting vermin that are, pursue them, seek to kill them? only Remy (that so it have drawn blue) will succeed in entering the world of haute cuisine.He is not a film of laughter as it could have been Shrek, but of a kind comedy with funny moments (umpteenth reference to Nemo), which are the typical characters Jesters, embittered bad (the chef Skinner and the critic Ego), and other conventions of the genre. But do not believe in any case adults do they heavy or they think that "this already I've seen". A chapeau to Pixar by this wonder.</body>
</review>
