<review author="José A. Peig" title="Death Proof" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tarantino laughs at himself as well as viewers seeking to take the film seriously. But always on the basis of a concept ideation macabre and funny at the same time, regains their ingenuity when it comes to ridicule certain aspects of American society and the film as a product of entertainment.</summary>
	<body>Piece of Robert Rodriguez set your images to evoke pure nostalgia from the image and the clichés of the genre, aesthetic retro, pure sensationalism and free morbid sensations and taking advantage of the expectations with which the viewer digest the visual Porterhouse. I.e. evoke exclusively from the form, which limits the product to a mere hyperbolic statement of actions and ICTs themselves from the scope which intends to pay homage. I.e., in last instance, emptiness and game jamaipanese lacking a personal stamp. Quentin Tarantino wants to become involved as a film lover and as a filmmaker contributing their drives to the set, and manages to reduce the imbalance between form and substance, so evident in Planet Terror. The history of the conductive psychopath of cars of death that pursued and harassed girls good see is ideal plot support for Mr Tarantino develop their neuro and remain exposed through a film treatment which appeals to sarcasm and parody.Tarantino laughs at himself as well as viewers seeking to take the film seriously. But always on the basis of a concept ideation macabre and funny at the same time, regains their ingenuity when it comes to ridicule certain aspects of American society and the film as a product of entertainment. The representation of the psychopath and the muchachitas responds to an intention to talk about repressed machismo and the consequent remorse. I.e. Tarantino exceeds the model to emulate, to bring it to a binge of sickly tones, brutal satire and sharp characters. Lo de Rodriguez went from being a Mimetic exercise. Death Proof mimics from rabies and the comical, creates a concept through images. Therefore, beat the theatrical and manages the film validity.Perhaps the main virtue is balance and thematic consistency between the action and the dialogues that precede. The construction of characters and tones emerge directly from a few dialogs that may seem, at first glance, tasteless, but analyzed carefully see the playful plot that hide the puns, the winks, and the emergence of reasons that "explode" in the subsequent action scenes. I.e., is not a narrative mess at the service of the spectacular action and the morbid (as in the case of Planet Terror), but possessing a deliberate narrative structure according to the satirical content. One possible interpretation of the film material would be that we we have a sardonic Elegy about the struggle between sexes in its most primitive strata; pure testosterone, wish to intimidate, influence, not be less than the others. In short, pathetic and natural aspects of the gregario-borreguil instinct premium in a spree of weekend in this america profound Tarantino both loves and hates both.In any case, like it or not, his toy is expressive. The filming of the persecutions by car transmitted the entire load of insanity and neurosis inherent in the story (often recalls the mastery displayed by Spielberg, for similar purposes, in "Duel"), perfect example of that to create frenzy and climax is not necessary to move the camera in excess - case by Paul Greengrass - and how you can create a psychological climate that covers the whole range of profiles in a specific situation: great example is the scene in the bar, in which the second group of girls has a long conversation (conversation which sets out the two issues resolution in the subsequent duel of cars that nobody be fooled in this film all this tied up and well tied) camera describes a travelling in a circle, until at one point we see Kurt Russell in the backgroundsitting at the bar than moments later he leaves.That scene summarizes, for dialogues that there are condensed and so it is visually expressed in a significance (precisely, a good filmmaker uses his camera to create meanings, not for the theatrical, resource of less artistic value) the macabre and at the same time satírico-cómico nature of the work, which, despite its weaknesses and abusing elitists elementsIt does not lose sight the possibilities of exploration of a genre and the style of the author.</body>
</review>
