<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Factotum" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Function words, concepts and the idea, but naufragan the images, are not able to transmit the feeling of loneliness, emptiness and existential anguish counted by Bukowski</summary>
	<body>Is there anyone out there who still has not read Bukowski? Big mistake. Because Charles Bukowski is one of the great writers of the last century, one of these geniuses who, with his stark prose and loaded with sex stories, fights, gambling and alcohol, rose to the top that realism more dirty merely dirty, so loved went to many American writers of the 1980s.And, however, if you see the adaptation of some of their stories that shows "Factotum", you will be somewhat disappointed the film. Starring a Mat Dillon that is aging with enormous dignity, as we had occasion to see in "Crash", in this case only work really well the words written by Bukowski, placed in the mouth of his alter ego, the savage and unclassifiable Chinaski.Funcionan words, concepts and the idea, but naufragan the images, are not able to transmit the feeling of lonelinessempty and existential anguish counted by the author of books as excellent (and explicit) as the own "Factotum", "Fuck machine" or "erections, ejaculations, exhibitions". The picture is too perfect, the atmosphere is too light, there is too much light. How does not miss the fascinating, cloudy and dark "Barfly", starring some emotionally agonizing Mickey Rourke and Faye Dunaway?The case is that the film is well, has brilliant moments and conceptual, very suggestive images as when each of the two protagonists riot to vomit in the toilet, while the other is espatarrado in bed. There are dialogues and kafkianas situations appear dirty and cruel humor abduction and, in general, not you get bored. But Bukowski deserved much more than a simple "not boring".Best of "Factotum" is that voice which talks about life, literature, creative radicality and, at the same time, laperseverancia commitment and effort. with the important things in life: writing, fucking, drinking and gambling. A movie that, beyond their frames, makes it very desirable to return to re-read the intense pages written by the author and are invited to revisit that glorious "Barfly" of Barbet Schroeder.</body>
</review>
