<review author="Kiko de España" title="Cabeza de muerte" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With a bit of Asian horror (shadows walking frame to frame, glups!) and a lot of cool modernism tries to look like so many things that it ends up being a complete mess. The mushrooms and the tension does not combine well...</summary>
	<body>Alexandre Ajá, Rob Zombie, Adam Green (Hatchet) or Zach Snyder are directors with talent. Paddy Breathnach is a director without too much talent who has shot a movie that kids are scared to the brutal volume of "scares".Do with a bit of Asian horror (shadows walking frame to frame, glups!) and a lot of cool modernism tries to look like to so many things that it ends up being a complete mess: two pairs of Yankees and a girl alone that he has his churri in Ireland travel there for? eat mushrooms. It might accuse such an argument be a supine stupidity, but Eli Roth used it in Hostel and worked, because that if I think. Who wants not to go to Holland with colleagues to quit a bit of good grifa? I know people that gets to the a by mushrooms, have never caught a plane to such bullshit.Well, the fact is the grandson of John Huston explains them that there are a few mushrooms debutis, a cursed orphanage, ghosts and mushrooms that should not never eat: cause death almost fixed. If you survive the mushrooms side effects are "spectacular": ability to communicate with the dead (does?), aggressive and uncontrollable force, the power to change shape (do?) and finally, but not least, the ability to see the future.Some more there, but we are sure that it destripa a movie that lacks interest by very cool whatever the dossier that we have given in the pass. So does not help that the genus is respected, because Jason had already been a sack in the chola before putting the mask, oafish native those we recently saw in Calvary and the rest? well, you could say that it is a movie about how a blonde girl gets dirty in the forest. There more plagiarism, but become spoiler tell you that ends up as? quiet, kidding.</body>
</review>
