<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Cabeza de muerte" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The argument, or the actors, scares or the soundtrack, reaches hooked in no time (more laughter than screams were heard in the audience), and if one is annoyed at some point is not horror, but by the increases in sound, until my grandmother with her sonotone to minimize had scared.</summary>
	<body>Best of a morning press pass is not always the film, it was as I was a footballer was with more interest to the cañeo after that with the hope of making a good match, here Mr.Trujillo sent me to see this film (at his own request) urging me to meet several of the characters that populate (flora and fauna) in muchocine.net forum (if you like the film)(, you know), and so I got myself, after fighting me first with the people from Deaplaneta what else give them how many people will watch the movie if then are 4 monkeys that inhabit the room? there I stood with my phone waiting to know these characters, it was they who, at the entrance to the room I knew to my.After the intro of excitement and joy, we go with the film; I have to say that the horror genre not I am passionate about and that while all my friends went to the movies with the bride to be she who is "achuchara" to him during the slide, to my I was always always otherwise, that was I who had just scared shitless catch of his arm.Starting from that side I can be scary things so mixed from Frog Gustavo until the man in the sack, but this film, which is sponsored by the DEA, the project man and the Foundation for help against drug addiction, scary, laugh or anything, it is true that must be envy at least that other films left in limbo (trillion), and that however, although with its stupid and laughable approach has become a reality does Cuantas with best argument will live the dream of the righteous?Neither the argument, or actors, or scares, the soundtrack nor history reaches hooked in no time (in the audience were heard more laughter than screams of terror), and if one is annoyed at some point is not terror that run through his body, but by the (unjustified) increases in sound, even my grandmother with her sonotone to minimize had scaredIt is not joke.In the poster exhibition of newspapers that have given us just upon arrival to the room (and that a critic has thrown with rabies to the ground half of the footage.) embody the opinion of its director, who boasts of mixing the most narrative film, the mystery and Eastern cinema where? To me that she made a film and have been distributed to another.In short, someone pay 6? by see such crappy? (I do not, of course).</body>
</review>
