<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="Superman returns" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This new version of Superman leaves airy</summary>
	<body>More than two decades have passed since the release of the classic Superman movies starring Christopher Reeve remembered (they were four, the first premiered in 1978 and the last in 1987). With regard to the current release of Superman Returns, the A &amp; E channel has been passing these old movies, to which I could give them a miradita and appreciate better as time and technology has improved the story of Superman barbarically. It is others say that it was a dangerous bet, as Reeve lives in the heart of million viewers as the true Superman.Y however, I believe that this new version of Superman Returns get airy. To begin with, now yes it seems that Superman flies through the air and that is not an actor hung in front of a screen. JL already talked about other good space film effects, so I no stretch in them. Just say that they are made in an impeccable way.History does not vary much of what everyone already know about Superman. The man of steel has returned to Earth after five years of absence, which was to see with their own eyes the destruction of his home planet Krypton. He has now returned to continue saving the human world and try to win back his love of life, Louise Lane. A parallel between the story of Superman and the story of Christ could be, but in this respect you may draw your own conclusions when they see. It is quite obvious.The work of casting special recognition. The protagonist is very well chosen, looks like enough to Reeve for not missing him, and in any case is an improved version of the same. Brandon Routh is super, but super cute. Where was this? Because until now has been a guest on several known series of TV, but insurance we will be listening more than him in other films. In my view it is wood.Male audiences will also be very happy with the choice of the new Louise Lane, reckless reporter of The Daily Planet and Clark Kent work companion, this time performed by the young Kate Bosworth, a beautiful actress who is also becoming fashionable (gossip: is the current partner of Orlando Bloom).I also liked the inclusion of James Marsden as Richard, the new husband of Louise Lane, a good kind people, who took the panic of the disappearance of Superman by five years to take over the heart of Luisa. He also works in the newspaper. And I liked to see it because recently we saw in X-Men 3 as Scott-Cíclope, so you already have experience with these steps of the comic into a film. OK, OK, is also handsome.Another which is extremely charismatic is the lovely child of Jason, the son of Louise and Richard, which is called in real life Tristan Lake Leabu and has an air well Macaulay Culkin in his best seasons. This is his first feature film and well managed could have a good future in the world of cinema. But the best cast is without doubt, Kevin Spacey as the evil Lex Luthor with a flawless and Machiavellian actions.SuperwomanAhora, to what is the title of the post? It seems perfect Superman do incredible things and neither uncombed, surprisingly, is a super hero. What if I do not think is Luisita remove chochoca countless times and not come out with any scratch. For example, notice the scene where bounces tip to tip on a plane about to crash. Or worse, when on a boat fall you on the head a steel door, which Faints, but five minutes it is already well awake and without even a mild headache. Is that Superman caught him some super powers?Data interesanteNo know if noted in the credits that contained the late Marlon Brando in the same role to take films of two decades ago: Jor - El, the true father of Superman. How they did this? Simply with archive images.The músicaEs classical music but remastered, original creation of the always great John Williams, my real super hero, who is putting the musical sound to all my favorite movies since that I have consciousness.AtenciónPara 2009 is expected the sequel to Superman Returns by the same director Bryan Singer, who has in its curriculum the interesting X-Men 1 and 2. Singer wanted Christhopher Reeve appeared in this film making a cameo appearance, but he died before. Finally, the film is a tribute to Christopher and Dana Reeve, who is dedicated to (see credits).</body>
</review>
