<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Most ironic of this matter is that probably we would have failed if the producer of the Weinstein brothers had not decided to separate the two films, forcing each of them to measure solo against the public to appreciate the unique character of this segment of Grindhouse.</summary>
	<body>As second part of Grindhouse, Death Proof (2007) is when less disconcerting; While Planet Terror (2007) Robert Rodriguez starts as an evasive entertainment of a nostalgic nature com, becomes very soon something else entirely, freeing its referential function as well as the supposed formal precepts of the dual experiment which served as the initial reason for its existence. Most ironic of this matter is that probably we would have failed to appreciate its unique character the producer of the Weinstein brothers had not decided to separate the two films, forcing each of them to measure solo against the public. As well as the whole of Grindhouse, Tarantino divides its segment into two distinct interconnected parts: in the first, Stuntman Mike (all praise to Kurt Russell) appears from the shadows as an assassin in series in the classical manner, a psychopath of road that kills young damsels using as a weapon not an axe or a dagger, but his car "death proof"which allows him crashing his victims while he leaves unharmed. This first half is fairly typical, and even is framed within the original aesthetic proposal: intentional scratches in the tape, abrupt cuts and typical grainy image of the 1970s. In the second half, however, the director turns the omelette of the slasher genre and becomes his film the other side of the coin "sexplotativa": that of feminism understood as greater male fetish, that sub-genre popularized by Russ Meyer and in which solid aunts shared his just punishment to men without for that reason cease to be beautiful. And punishment is precisely what he comes up to Stuntman Mike, who finally found her shoe in its not as incautas three victims horna. By this time, Tarantino has already forgotten altogether of the formal corset of his particular experiment: cinematography is now perfect, without alterations or intentional fault, and has place among best persecutions by car we have seen in recent times, the duel between Stuntman Mike and his new victims, three tough girls among genuine specialists of cinema (all praise to Zoe Bell). And beyond the references to this film that is no longer, find here a Tarantino film fledged: contrasting somewhat with the blatant action of Planet Terror, this segment follows the typical general verbiage of its director. Approximately one hour from the little more than an hour and a half of footage is going in the dialogues of the protagonists, which (admit) found me a little disproportionate. Luckily, however, that Tarantino has managed to offset this incontinence verbal with two of the scenes spectacular and intense he has shot so far, both marking the climax of the respective mini-segmentos in which has divided his film: terrible "accident" that sega the lives of the first victims of "Stuntman Mike" (and that in a brimming with detail of morbid reproduces six times before our noses) and the aforementioned persecution in which the monster Kurt Russell gives hunting new heroines. Also, both halves are so different and reach very different conclusions, that we realize soon that Death Proof is itself a formal proposal so ambitious (or more) than all of Grindhouse. It may not be so enjoyable at a basic level as Planet Terror, but the superiority of Director Tarantino has managed to create a film that goes beyond in their eagerness to take the Viewer to the site where he simply has given the win for him, even at the expense of throwing overboard all the estético-nostálgico precept of which started. The only downside that I put to Death Proof is nothing short of paradoxical: does makes sense to use forms of the Grindhouse project only to finally get rid of them and revert them? Not it would have better to launch a proposal so solo instead of attacking the concept of this tribute (while his predecessor segment) been much? It is not in itself an action which, although great, may be somewhat self-centered? It is clear that I do not have the answer yet, but a very radical Act can only leave the mind of a privileged filmmaker or a tocapelotas. And now that I think, why not it can become two things?</body>
</review>
