<review author="Robgordon" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A fabulous closure for this carousel of damaged reels, veneration of extinct genera, cachondeo, winks and intentional failure of continuity, comprising "Grindhouse" with "Planet Terror"</summary>
	<body>There are several films in "Death Proof", a film that Tarantino appears to have felt like a fish in water, giving rein to their more sickly fixations, its high level of fetish and the constants of his film.On the one hand we find in "Death Proof" film of the Tarantino of always, which we all know. The rescuer Tarantino of myths of Hollywood that years ago were all, the man with an enviable ability to recover forgotten that music heard now, they sound wonderful, the enfant terrible of Hollywood who enjoys writing lengthy dialogues on unexpected topics.That Tarantino exists, and much, in this part of "Grindhouse". Girls are the protagonists of these dilated talks born from the mind of Quentin, and this is precisely how it starts the film with the endless figure of Sydney Tamiia Portier, Jordan Ladd (daughters of Sydney and Cheryl Ladd, respectively) and Vanessa Ferlito and similarly will begin the second block (with change of actors included) that, "Death Proof" is clearly divided.If the Viewer is capable of entering the game of those long dialogues on women and guns, sex, the movies of the 1970s or the cars, their enjoyment of "Death Proof" is garantizadísimo and shall be complete. Certainly, by moments, the extreme length of the verbiage tarantiniana around a table, can go to tire, but quiet, it will soon take action that will prevent with one blow, any mood of yawn.The overwhelming presence of Kurt Russell and his character, the "specialist" Mike, is another of the great successes of Tarantino, expert in casting and already recovered Travolta or Pam Grier on previous occasions. Let us not forget that the was the Carpenter Pliskeen of "1997"; "Rescue in New York", MacReady in Jack Burton "Blow to the Chinese small" or "Thing". All a myth of the 80, which now receives a role for its fair measure and for his gallery of glorious heroes and antiheros.In this work, full of easily recognizable elements for the follower of the director of "Pulp Fiction" and which is not, and following the line marked by the spirit of grindhouse, Tarantino is allowed the luxury of skillfully, mix between all its obsessions, a slasher and a very clear and declared homage to the cinema of the 1970sfull of car chases and doubles and film specialists, that made it possible. As two films in one, marked by the QuentinEn stretch of the slasher, Tarantino universe introduces the character of the "specialist Mike", recreates (recurring in his filmography) female feet, delights us with the careful selection of music, ranging from Jack Nitzsche to T-Rex, passing by The Coasters, (or perhaps not you has bitten the curiosity by the Group Dave Dee?)(Do, Dozy, Beaky, Mick &amp; Tich, following the story of Pete Townsend tells Poitier?) and with another dance, the "Butterfly" for framing within his filmography. An atypical film with serial killer where the deadly weapon is a car and that closes with a comic dialogue between Michael Parks and James Parks, the two policemen Texans that already appeared in "Kill Bill" or "Open until dawn".In its next stretch, Tarantino passes to other paths. With its particular tribute to "point zero limit" and other setenteras genus tapes that Tarantino reverence. Here, pointed on the specialists of cinema and its current decline and its rise as a result of special effects, takes body, via Zoe Bell, actress specialist (and double for Uma Thurman in "Kill Bill") in that scene, the most colossal and the best ride of the film, in which women are placed at the height of "Stunt Mike". Rosario Dawson, Mary Elizabeth Winstead and Tracie Thorns accompany revenge, in which there is a long time (perhaps too much) dialogue around a table and for the sexual thoughts of the protagonists (very for "nenas"), but that will give way to a remarkable Chase.A fabulous closure for this carousel of damaged reels, veneration of extinct genera, cachondeo, winks and intentional failure of continuity, comprising "Grindhouse" with "Planet Terror". Two works (though conceived as a single) tremendously entertaining and few claims where reign the casqueria and the messing and offer an exercise in style, although it is not, at all, novel, are grateful for being rare these days.</body>
</review>
