<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Locos por el surf" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A different film that stands out precisely why: for being different and daring, even, to replace the final moralina and bet instead on ridicule to a society that, like ours, is based on more aggressive competitiveness.</summary>
	<body>Compete in Billboard with another product of animation Ratatouille characteristics must be difficult. And more when the main protagonist is a surfer Penguin. Among the recent cinematic abuse of penguins (the Emperor's trip or Happy Feet, are clear examples of this) and how bad that generally work on surf in Spain films, is clear that mad about surfing has it tricky. If also add you that, despite being of a genre usually directed at children, this is a product treated in a way too adult that some of his jokes can be caught by children.Mad about surfing is a joke stark reality shows and docu, that satirizes ingeniously. The falsehood and the cynicism of the majority of this type of reports are fully reflected in the film. In it, a camera of a film crew, after which hides an anonymous reporter, will see Cody Maverick wherever it goes and, interested in his character, will also close the microphone to more friends. In this way, his mother, his brother, friends and work colleagues, verterán (or, rather, spit) all kinds of opinions and anecdotes about him. And it is that Cody is not more than a teenage Penguin whose highest aspiration in life is to become a famous surfer. Nobody understands the unhealthy obsession of the youngster palmiped to be at the top of the pedestal. and less when it comes to a ducks much care.The camera will follow our seabird along the route that separates his native land, Antarctica, of Pen Gu, a small tropical island in which will celebrate a championship of surfing at the global level, the Penguin World Surfing Championship. Once there, devoted most of his attention to analysing the born relationship between the rookie Cody and the once popular Big Z, an old and famous surfer who all were dead, and that the cazallosa voice of Jeff Bridges, in its original version, gives a very special character.Because it is an animated film, breaks moulds with respect to other similar and therefore starts by shying away from the appearance of those winks moviegoers so common (and sometimes unnecessary) in this type of film. And, even so, the treatment of student Cody with the elderly risen master, is almost impossible to stop thinking Karate Kid.Su humor is subtle, too complicated at times for the child audience, because even certain references to drug use (though somewhat covert) make an appearance during the footage. A chicken fond of surfing is placed thrusting the head just above one of the blowholes a whale, getting some hallucinogenic and anesthetic effect everytime the cetacean expels a strong stream of water; at the same time, the depressed and finish Big Z is a penguin, addicted to the oysters: without them there can be sguir forward. In order to carry out this proposal, the Sony contacted Ash Brannon and Chris Buck, two directors with extensive experience as animators in the service of the Disney and Pixar (before the Union of the two houses). Looking for new shades in the image processing succeeded, thus distancing itself visually the style from the most direct rival, the cited and wonderful Ratatouille and, unlike this one, at certain moments, showing dramatically real, as is the case with images that embody what surfers known as "the tube"; pass or just in the middle of the gap of water that forms a giant wave. A feeling so well described and filmed, although in the case of animation, transmitting to the viewer the same sentiments that surely run through the minds of those who practice this sport. A different film that stands out precisely why: for being different and daring, even, to replace the final moralina and bet instead on ridicule to a society that, like ours, is based on more aggressive competitiveness. He is not a round title to 100 percent, but your (laudable) efforts to distance itself from the avalanche of animatronics that is invading screens, (sympathetic) narrative as a mockumentary treatment and its tone (aplaudible) critical, make this a somewhat endearing work. And it is that good intentions always should take them into account.</body>
</review>
