<review author="Silvia" title="Tiempo de Valientes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It entertains, amuses and ensures a frequent smile more than constant laughter, because despite dye tragic situations which live actors, the film offers an optimistic message.</summary>
	<body>These are "times of brave" for the Argentine cinema. It is to be courageous to dare to face on the Bulletin Board with the Hollywood blockbusters and succeed in the attempt. After the success of directors like Juan José Campanella with his beloved son of the bride and Adolfo Arinstarain (common places), arrived in May to our screens Damián Szifron with a funny police comedy. What begins as a typical action film becomes a tragicomedy in which you do not know whether to laugh or mourn, pity that cause you some situations who live the protagonists couple. Thus, after a well-constructed start, this alleged police comedy us into the genre of the buddy movies, in which appear couples opposite, so common in the Yankee action cinema. In the case of this film, one is polícia and joins their police tasks as an escape route after discovering his wife deceives him. The other is a psychologist who will accompany her on its police routine in the investigation of a case by way of therapy. Psychologists, seems to have answer for all types of behaviour (or at least try to look it up) and therefore Mariano Silverstein (Diego Peretti, known for the film No sos vos am I) can find a logical explanation for the actions and feelings of inspector Alfredo Díaz (Luis Luque), investigating in his traumatic past. They are two diametrically opposed characters (the security of the psychologist from the emotional trauma of the polícia) but come to approach and understand better than anyone else.However, after the shocking and violent opening scene of the murder carried out by the cynical gangster, the script suffers ups and downs so the film loses interest until the half-hour it reaches its tipping point and the attention of the viewer recovers. The film gives a plot twist from the moment in which the apparent world of security and firm psychologist belief collapses after discovering his wife's infidelity. Psychologists you always have what we need to deal with a problem. say you it all so relaxed and convinced of what you have to do... But what happens when the problem has the patient has that take care of you? Things are not as they seem, but quite the opposite and thus appears insecure becomes safe and vice versa. The personality of the players exchanged so that the psychologist who boasted of being self-confident becomes the horned depressed. The emotional stability of the psychologist is broken and the police becomes the best psychologists. It seems that it is now the police which has all the answers. The problem most joins the two and turns them into accomplices to the desubrir a fact of corruption to try to uncover it. From this time the protagonists are involved in a full of hilarious moments research.But in addition to be comedy, the film has its own social and political criticism of corruption in Argentina, but not wallow in it. As in other films that were filmed after the dictatorship, the Federal Police and the Argentine army remain in evidence for her performances outside the law. But that is not its main argument. The important thing is that he entertains, amuses and ensures a frequent smile more than constant laughter. Because despite dye tragic situations which live actors, the film offers an optimistic message. Everyone can be a hero or because everyone can evolve, because it is time of brave.</body>
</review>
