<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El señor de la guerra" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Social impact of amazing technical invoice document, but orphan of emotions and slightly interesting as film and film divertimento.</summary>
	<body>The Lord of war must have been conceived as a documentary host to this new genre of cinema of complaint that favors the message about the narrative discourse and sacrificed the classical forms by a concatenated demolition on the injustices of the world or on the aberrant arms escalation that will despanzurrando this world of ours once so blue. Gray is the color of this tape of New Zealander Andrew Niccol Gattaca (Nicole): a sterile grey, a grey not makes us boil blood before the dark plot of interests and conspiracies to which witness because the tone of the tape is shy, sparsely risky, even if you have enough arguments to get abreast of the mafia of the arms trade and the hypocritical justification of the democratic Statesso aware of the excesses that they themselves cause. Perhaps the prodigious boot had enough: the life of a bullet since that is billed until that staying in front of an African child. It's raw. Those minutes, added formidably assembled in the credits, it encapsulates the spirit of the film, a subjective, symbolic, journey of what is to come. The rest is extra. Or, at least, does not add information: Niccol is limited to illustrate with images, technically impeccable, the biography of an arms dealer. He left the option to delve into the psychology and supplies an irreproachable plastic ammunition that moves the Viewer to consider very seriously the ametrallado flood of moral considerations about the war and its damage and collateral benefits.Fiction hosted on the label of "real facts" confirms that this is an exercise in complaint naïve: succeeds to make explicit the barbarism that portrays, but remains pitifully short in that, in the light of the means deployed, would have not cost much greater effort: make an entertaining film and not a documentary so impostado like this.The story of Yuri Orlov (a satisfactory Nicolas Cage, Hallelujah) is the story of the last stretch of 20th century had: cynicism and hypocrisy to full hands. So the film can be for encyclopedias, as a devastating document on a thorny issue, but not the round film that could have been. Lacking verve, dreary, orphan of emotion budgeted as necessary to cope with the flow of sensitive information, the Lord of the descarria war its noble purpose and joins in that social, pretentious film that does not last in the memory and just arrumbado on the store shelves of failed projects.</body>
</review>
