<review author="Bruji" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After the direct reference to films as point limit zero, La Indecente Mary or Larry the madman, movie fan memory drags us into cult titles such as Christine or the devil on wheels.</summary>
	<body>Excessive passion to lead shown by the Director of Tennessee, its proven movie fan militancy and its vast film culture, ranging from the series up the Z transform a slasher of the seventies in the attractive argument to fascinara to filmmakers such as Carpenter or Spielberg. Death Proof is the contribution of Quentin Tarantino to the Grindhouse project and a tribute to his own filmography.I guess that one of the direct consequences of having released two films comprising Grindhouse separately, and marketed them as "standard products", has been the flood of protests voiced by viewers on the "poor quality" of Planet Terror; that, surely, has led to the emergence of a funny "note of company" in some cinemas, according to which "the flaws showing Death Proof are intentional". Easier would have been explained from the beginning, that both are part of a tribute to low-budget films which, in the 1970s, swarm by American screening rooms. Once made the warning, it is important to know that multiple technical shortcomings that accompany these productions, (Death Proof and Planet Terror), not undermine quality to the final outcome of the same. The loss of sound, the striped frames, intervals that are offered in black and white and the disastrous Assembly, are only a mere fact anecdotal, and another of the many genius that characterize two stories, in many respects, perfect.To look seriously at Death Proof, must take into account that deal with the films of Quentin Tarantino is not an easy task. Entering it, involves twinning, inevitably, the difficulty with the utmost of respect. Above its readiness for the B series, his tribute to cheap films karatekas, of his tendency to the creation of situations, in appearance, absurd, and its obstinacy for drawing characters, in not few occasions, unrealistic; a unique film wisdom, which covers all genres, is and culminates in a style unmistakable, impossible to find in contemporary cinema. His original way of directing, the inclusion of unstructured scripts, Scorsese inheritance; the recreation of impeccable usual scene implementations of Kurosawa, and the obsession with details, make a filmmaker of risk, with courage to the limit, only comparable to that always demonstrated the Welles himself. There is no doubt that Tarantino is one of the few great remaining.The trouble with "the big" is that, sometimes, licensed a joke to lovers and give them with one of those stories that can only look with benevolence knowing the prior work of its directors are allowed. Remember that even Huston took advantage of a holiday by the Mediterranean to the seventh art an unspeakable parody of the Maltese Falcon entitled the mockery of the devil; and this, just prior to publicize the bastards without glory, seemed the right time to not shoot seriously. Fortunately, that is not the case with Death Proof and, once again, Tarantino returns to show their worth, to surprise, to revolutionize the tedious film scene.What starts as a typical bloody crimes, a 1970s slasher film, soon becomes attractive argument to fascinara to directors such as Carpenter or Spielberg. After the direct reference to films as point limit zero, La Indecente Mary or Larry the madman, movie fan memory drags us into cult titles such as Christine or the devil on wheels. If this applies the "Tarantino touch", the success is assured. The master definition of characters, some of them, drawn with only two strokes; endless dialogues, that only in the best classical stories manage to capture the viewer's attention; the profusion of details, which are its irreplaceable place in the resolution of the outcome; the continuous winks to lovers of cinema, and Spanish viewers (remember the posters of movies starring Charo López); explicit references taken from Pulp Fiction, Jackie Brown and Kill Bill, made in Death Proof one of the best films of the year.To remember, the bet of the filmmaker for the massage on the feet, the delight that produce you mobile phones, incitement to the reading, the bright yellow, weapons women taking and playback. For the glory of the film, the shooting of one of the best cars in its history persecutions. To his followers, the tireless search for volume two.</body>
</review>
