<review author="Jose Contreras" title="La casa del lago" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film full of inconsistencies, but also full of successes and spells that get moved to the coldest</summary>
	<body>The doctor Kate Forster, who plays Sandra Bullock, listen to a girl, his patient, talk about his MOM. His mother tells that no matter leave a man, because there's always one just around the corner. The physician listens and corrects her: "can one also are old waiting for to appear that man." It was not an innocent conversation, they are talking about the same principe azul which talk about the film. They talk about if we are left with the man that serves to muddle through or if we play everything for a dream.Alejandro Agresti is based on a Korean film ("Siworae") which in turn is based on a novel by Jiro Asada. However, Agresti has sought a benchmark West in a novel by Jane Austen, "Persuasion", to speak of the love and time. In "Persuasion", the lovers decide to give a time before joining, but when they become to see already is too late for them. "The Lake House", the doctor is close to a House that is in the middle of a lake and there begins a correspondence with the former tenant who lived two years earlier. We do not have any explanation to tell us why emails from a man who lived in 2004 appear in 2006 and which she sends in 2006 appear in 2004. The paradox serves to speak of the distance, because any event decide, he will have to wait two years, and in those two years many things can happen. One of those things is that it may change your mind within their own future, for example in 2007, whereupon, he would not appear in the quote from the 2006 because he would feel abandoned in 2005. The appeal of the two years serves to play. If a letter can travel through time, there are many other wonders that can occur. It is a premise full of suggestions that enriches the very Jane Austen. "Austen had a Victorian world to seduce her lovers, Agresti has the world of temporary jumps that have become everyday for the viewer of today thanks to films such as journey to the future, Terminator, the butterfly effect, Paycheck.""The Lake House" is a film full of inconsistencies. Very strong bet with the theme of the temporal paradox, so "our friends the logical", as he called them Hitchcock, do very easy. But it is full of successes and spells that get moved to the cooler. She approaches him from the future ahead of its bad moments, he cares since last leaving traces.</body>
</review>
