<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The jungle 4.0 is one of the best action films of recent years, which remains faithful to the spirit of the series to which it belongs</summary>
	<body>Major studios think that they are coming to the conclusion, better late than never, of remakes fat cows time is coming to an end. And how not, they have already started the search for a new source of income safely and quickly. But one not overly original, because as said, eh?, this is Hollywood! They have become or will soon do so mythical characters of the film's action and adventures such as Rocky, Rambo, John McClane or Indiana Jones. Without forgetting those who never have ido, as James Bond.En the framework of the digital age, where it is virtually unthinkable to see an action movie that do not contain large number of plans and sequences generated by computer, again John McClane. Most irreverent New York Police Department detective is once again in the wrong place and at least suitable time. As if it were a dinosaur, McClane must face a cyber terrorist evil plans. The jungle 4.0 is first and foremost a honest film that doesn't fool your audience, because it offers what it promises, something worthy of praise in the current action cinema. The almost two hours they spend flying, and at that time the Viewer is witness to a frantic and spectacular, action that stands out for its realism versus artificial of the computer-generated. The only that I can put the tape is the short patriotic speech that loose Bruce Willis in the middle of the second Act. Bruce Willis is in its sauce, and fans of the Crystal jungle will be abundantly satisfied with the end result. And the rest of viewers who are looking for authentic entertainment film, also.The jungle 4.0 is one of the best action films of recent years, which remains faithful to the spirit of the series to which it belongs. The fights, chases and explosions are seasoned with the particular sense of humour of John McClane, real raison d ' être of the film.</body>
</review>
