<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Tocar el Cielo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Touch the sky is a film that will delight lovers of melodrama, but which the rest of the public will cause you a rise in glucose due to the stodgy cake must digest.</summary>
	<body>Argentine cinema has lived a golden years of great splendour, but has gradually been going into decline, and therefore the vast majority of titles arriving in our country are co-productions with Spain. In some countries, the contribution of Spanish producers is minimal, but more and more are mostly Spanish productions.A clear example of this is to touch the sky, the new film by Marcos Carnevale after the great success reaped with Elsa and Fred. The film narrates in a tone of comedy-drama the relations between a group of friends who live in Madrid and Buenos Aires that share a common tradition, launching on December 31 at the same time their wishes for the new year tied to a balloon. The term comedy-drama is quite disconcerting, and the truth is that it is meant to cover a small vacuum emerged following a new type of films that move halfway between comedy and drama. The truth is that touch the sky is seen with a half smile from beginning to end, and on numerous occasions the tape will touch the Viewer. But it is also true that the film needless you edulcoramiento and sugar that make a real sentimentaloide cake not suitable for diabetics. Some of the stories of the script are little credible, and sometimes feels as if Marcos Carnevale was more concerned of psychoanalyze characters than plot development itself. The weak script only stays in place thanks to the excellent work of interpretation, notably Facundo Arana and Montse Germán, and an immeasurable Chete Lera, claiming once again as one of the big players in this country.Touch the sky is a film that will delight lovers of melodrama, but which the rest of the public will cause you a rise in glucose due to the stodgy cake must digest. The sacrifice is only worth to see the work of Chete Lera.</body>
</review>
