<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Mr Brooks" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Much Jekyll and Hyde little. Only transgressing the complacent correction in which sits the genre we had perhaps been able to enjoy one history more than usual. Again will be.</summary>
	<body>In an attempt to be disturbing, the archetypal actor of honesty American - as it was in its day James Stewart or Gary Cooper - Mr. Costner, is pulled to the mud and strives seem credible representing without great force (with the expressive restraint that characterizes him) the thousandfold emulated the unfolded or more literary murderer, Dr. Jekyll character. And making the dark replica of Mr. Hyde we have the always prodigious William Hurt, which absorbs the attempts of good Costner by seem very bad in every scene. At the end we soon see how nesesariamente this actor works best lover, father or husband as tanning officer of murder.The same head, Bruce A signed script. Evans, a rookie filmmaker, trained as a writer of texts of mediocre movies such as account with me or Starman. However, we can say that Mr. Brooks is his best screenplay to date. This helps a sunset in austere scene (thankless debt of good make the Coens in easy blood or Fargo) and a leisurely pace that work effectively for all genre of killers fan might expect without asking an elm tree pears.However, despite their goodwill, Mr. Brooks was soon opts for standardize dualism disturbing character into resabidos territories of the genre, where the family stays pristine despite the murky basement that sits. The proposal would even have been refreshing if this personal universe of the murderer would have drawn by transverse lines of elusive definition, and not that clear resolution even with that final innocent just saving the set.In fact, at the end of the projection the viewer has that feeling of déjà vu as widespread in these years in products of the thriller genre with intelligent murderer. Only transgressing the complacent correction in which sits the genre we had perhaps been able to enjoy one history more than usual. Again will be.</body>
</review>
