<review author="Naty Buqué" title="¿Qué he hecho yo para merecer esto?" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excellent film by Pedro Almodóvar, with characters in-cre-í-bles, live, wonderful performances, a setting that falls from kistch and a series of adventures suitable for burst of laughter.</summary>
	<body>Excellent film by Pedro Almodóvar, with characters in-cre-í-bles, live, wonderful performances, a setting that falls from kistch and a series of adventures suitable for burst of laughter.But also the movie, starring a Carmen Maura 10, explores, as always, or almost always, certain traits of the female Constitution which, if in other films it is very psychoanalyst and macho somewhere, as defines almost categorically what being a woman, and the woman is almost a clown (always with good intentions, of course, but that is no excuse)in this film the inquiry is rather sociological order and there is a search of what being a woman but did it (ergo the patriarchal order, ergo the man) society.The answer, in a final falling of perfect. Her husband he killed him - albeit accidentally-, to his younger son sold it to a child molester dentist to buy an iron hair, the pet lizard was killed by a police officer and his eldest son just go with her grandmother (her mother) to the hometown of the latter. The House is single. Finally, she is not wife, or mother or homemaker. It will throw off the balcony.But then comes his younger son (who realizes that is very young to sit head with the dentist.) Note: the nene is as 11 years old) and she is saved. Maura already falls by the balcony because you who hold. He returned to being a mother.Women is defined, in what I have done?, by negativity. Being a woman is to be mother, daughter-in-law (not even daughter, that is something too own), housewife, Maid in outside houses, wife (if we look at the other characters add: or bitch or bad parent).Almodóvar exposes the impossibility of women constitute as such: is a pure external determination.</body>
</review>
