<review author="Dragon negro" title="Wolf Creek" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is solved quite intelligently and jumping topics in current horror cinema, is in my opinion one of the best horror films so far this year.</summary>
	<body>They have had to pass two years before the premiere of Wolf Creek to reach our billboards, an Australian horror film that came backed with positive reviews and viewing has proved to be very interesting so far this year.Three young people, two girls and a boy they embark on a journey that will take them through Wolf Creek crater, formed by a meteorite thousands of years ago. What at first was going to be a peaceful journey, eventually becoming the biggest nightmares. Until here everything indicates that this is a more youthful terror tape which Hollywood industry we have come to, and indeed in many criticisms it has come to compare with the recent Hostel and tourists. But nothing further, and is that Wolf Creek happens hand down the face to the two films together and batters them with such ease that one comes to ask if is so difficult to make an horror film worthwhile see and not mediocre by-products that do not contribute anything new.Shot almost to the Dogma style to give more realism to images, the film is much closer to the classic the massacre of Texas than to the above. The director, screenwriter and producer Greg Mclean chooses to move away from the free offal and offer us a vision much more realistic and accurate of what could actually happen if it Skaði us a Homicidal Maniac, in fact the film is loosely based on real events. In addition the film is solved quite intelligently and skipping topics in current horror cinema, which is another success.The film unfolds with calm and unhurried, and may be somewhat slow to who wait a little more action, that there is, but takes its time to present the characters and the situation, although perhaps have too you a slightly long prologue.Wolf Creek is in my opinion one of the best horror films in which carry year, that really has been very weak and should not lose sight to its director from which we can expect great things in the future.</body>
</review>
