<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Wolf Creek" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nothing that we have not seen before hundreds of times, and although the originality doesn't have to be the strong throughout film main, at this stage already becomes somewhat cansón and repetitive.</summary>
	<body>The appalling delay that Wolf Creek (2005) has reached the Spanish billboard has served, inter alia, to grow the expectations around what initially was defined as one of the most outstanding horror films of recent years, a jewel coming of Australia that promised to be of the pieces more wild the survival horror, with scenes allegedly as "strong" which was forbidden by law to show in your advertising materials. All that apparently has gone to hell, because the truth is that this first feature of the Australian Greg Mclean is finally among more typical and seen us has fallen. The good Office with which many of their sequences are shot makes that stands out a bit of the lot, but not enough to justify all the praise that have fallen you over even before its release.Belonging to the increasingly defined sub-genre of "dead tourists", Wolf Creek keeps track of three young backpackers lost in the endless meadows of Australia and dams of the follies of a psychopath who has decided to use them as part of House, nothing that we have not seen before hundreds of times, and although the originality does not have to be the strong throughout film mainby now already is somewhat cansón and repetitive. Which in any case Yes differentiates this tape of Mclean is having a prologue of almost forty minutes in which literally nothing happens, and we only see the three youngsters behave as authentic garrulos and gloat in his bland love triangle. The creation of an environment wouldn't by itself alone no problem if at least this was dedicated to build tension, but almost none of this first half has something to do with what we see then. In fact, when the killer finally appears marked a total break with the rest of the tape and almost makes us believe that we are seeing another film instead of the indie road movie before soporifera. From here see as (once again) a young director tries to emulate the massacre of Texas (1974) for ultimately did not succeed as (incidentally that comparisons with Tobe Hooper film are not any whim; are more than obvious).It is during this "second part" when Wolf Creek gets its most interesting moments. Having only three protagonists, history is obliged by balls to give some relevance to each of them, so at least appreciated the absence of cheap resources whereby several of the cast members are only there as meat gutting. The plot goes jumping of one character to another and although it seems that at times he opts for a character in particular as the action hero, handles very soon change point of view to not make this so clear. Another point to keep in mind is the presence of veteran actor on Australian TV John Jarratt (who has returned to work with Mclean on his new tape), undoubtedly the film acting engine and is here that it overflows in its role as the most overused and endearing Australian cliché of all time, with some touches of humour, capable of booting a smile even in times of increased tension.These two details, however, are the only ones that have captivated me from the movie, everything else is the same old story told in the same way as always, and for nothing justify the disproportionate praise she has received. Perhaps if it had been released about 10 years ago he had a valuation best, but in these times in which every horror film aspires to be more beast than the previous and types as Alexandre Aja, Rob Zombie, Eli Roth or Neil Marshall are the names that most sound in this genre, a movie like that we have today is little more than redundant, and largely only by does not come from the Hollywood circuit. Even so, its almost unbearable prologue, the blatant exploitation of the demagogic and hackneyed phrase of "based on a true story" and that foolishly falls in the same clichés of the slasher already parodied nauseam (when the victim will ensure that the killer is really dead? when?) you there are still many integers. And is that a change of emphasis on the actors and the joke about Crocodile Dundee insufficient to Enthrone this when much medium effort called Wolf Creek.</body>
</review>
