<review author="Robgordon" title="Caótica Ana" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Caótica Ana is a very embarrassing mistake for patriotic cinema and a point negrisimo in the career of the Basque conductor, which will have to improve much on his next tape to regain the favor of your audience.</summary>
	<body>Julio Medem, one of the most important film directors Spanish, one of the most renowned authors and creator, among others, of; "Earth", "Lucia and sex" or this beautiful film that is "lovers of the polar circle", achieved with his latest film, "Caótica Ana", exasperate the viewer with an entirely self-indulgent and compromising tape, because that will expose this film already his figure more fierce criticism of the place.The Basque author has shot a film extremely inherent to his person and his environment. Almost a private craving. The history of Ana, Ibizan girl who moves to Madrid to share his paintings and learn the art and begin to suffer shocks that will take you to remember their past lives from session of hypnosis.Throughout this history, Medem has uploaded his filmic universe to the maximum. He has led his obsession with the symbolism and metaphor to the greatest extent possible, and everything to tell a story that is discovering empty and incoherent every minute that is moving footage.It begins "Caótica Ana" as an exaltation of the hippie and modern world. As an ode to the creative commune, young free and untamed and "buenrollismo". However everything sounds artificial, little credibility. Dialogs keep Anna and Linda (Manuela Vellés and baby) are impossible. Two of three conversations, are metaphorical or with pretensions of importance, something that may look good on paper, but that it is unthinkable that they have left the protagonists. And that Manuela Vellés strives to recite them. Vellés, to be her first film, is commendable. Delivery to the character of Ana is commendable. It appears in 99% of the scenes and lidia with guarantees the different interpretative nuances that are being demanded a role and a character that is not, at all, easy. The Antipodes of the interpretive effort find baby, fatal and easygoing in his role as friend and Adviser of Ana.Es precisely that air of importance, self-aggrandizement, the pretentiousness that lastra "Caótica Ana". Every movement, every moment is overloaded, each scene with a transcendence that prevents the naturalness, which avoids any hint of emotion. There is a scene in which Ana says not find depth in his paintings, but bet on simplicity. Just the opposite what Medem has wanted to do with "Caótica Ana".But where made leads "Caótica Ana"? Required this story such a degree of abstraction? The case is "Caótica Ana" proving finally empty. Little point in us act to join the pieces of that puzzle regressive, full of fades in black and landscapes striking of hypnosis and reincarnation, of parents, women, conceptual art and sex and naked free, "Caótica Ana" is just the story of a misguided, impulsive, dreamy and rebellious girl. The simple story of a hippie aimlessly to which Medem has elevated to the category of goddess that summed up his vision of the feminine power. "Too much artifice for so little.""Chaotic Ana" is the worst work of Medem to date. Addressed erronemente to an immature audience. A continuum of irrational moments of sequences forced and crammed with shoehorn (the history of Lluis Homar, the shabby cameo of Antonio Vega, in the purest style Caetano Veloso in "Talk to her"), which only highlights the beautiful photography and locations, the mystical music of Jocelyn Pook (composer of "Eyes Wide Shut") and the debut of Manuela Vellés. the final sequence of "Caótica Ana" is the image of the Spanish film industry; politicized and lacking in good taste. A shameful and embarrassing sequence. Ugly. Capricious and unnecessary. Even its presence within the plot has a minimal justification.That Medem, one of the banner of the national film scene directors, has filmed a sequence like that, is something truly disturbing and demonstrates the serious health condition of our film, which is very difficult to defend. "An end of film so vulgar and inappropriate to punish the Spanish film on his knees, facing the wall, for 12 hours.""Chaotic Ana" is a very embarrassing mistake for patriotic cinema and a point negrisimo in the career of the Basque conductor, which will have to improve much on his next tape to regain the favor of your audience.</body>
</review>
