<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los ojos del mal" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film horror and gore with a not inconsiderable argument. The atmosphere created is OK, and is not for those that do not understand what happens, if that doesn't quite logic. Not bad, was not.</summary>
	<body>Do not look to the devil, not, draw you the eyes and puts it in a jar of brine for worse times. To ascazo, of course. And that most ugly guy in the poster, with that nose of Boxer and the look lost. Link not ligaría much, no. And less if you all sides with that hook, although as method of ligoteo is not bad, her you hooked a leg and ale, to enjoy life.The film is a programme of reintegration of prisoners that, grab a group of women and other men and leads them to an old hotel to restore it. The group is composed in addition to by the prisoners, a proprietary elder of the hotel that caught fire 30 years earlier, a woman and a policeman four years ago lost a member in a very strange case. Everything goes well, until they begin to happen strange facts relating to the case of the police which was never resolved. And then comes the Lord that ugly of the poster with the hook rolling one you shit on the down.Look I saw the movie with great skepticism and a bit of laziness, insofar as these do not usually like me. And the thing starts pretty bad, since joining prisoners already seems a very silly thing. And that is only to handle them a police cripple and a lady that not be what it is, nor goes nowhere. Then scenes of violence are very exaggerated, even a little stopping the image so you can see it well as it enters the meat hook. But as the subject progresses, and you forget these two buts, going metiendote in the intrigue and the thing is not bad. Especially at the end, there is a surprise that had not seen coming and I liked a lot. The atmosphere created is OK, and is not for those that do not understand what happens, if that doesn't quite logic. Not bad, was not.In short, film horror and gore with a not inconsiderable argument.Too bad the excessive recreamiento in the gore scenes.Besitos.P.D: And then with the collection of eyes, which made? Would it change the eye with other collectors? Let me some Brown, that he had ate them the cat. Things.Pd2: Truth that the obsession for showing the most possible gore do not understand. It is good that they ensarten one in a hook, but not to slow, which removes rhythm for the film.P.D.3: I am going to culturizar a mijica. This Lord of the hook, who was born in Madrid and is called Kane, is or was a wrestler of the American wrestling, that posed by Marrrrr Hector, picket of eyes, the squat is giving the dance of St. Vitus. Memories. Oh, and the director is porn, perhaps why the fixation with the penetration of meat hook, it could be.</body>
</review>
