<review author="Jesus Lens" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The case is the jungle, in its zero point version, an exemplary film that baby television and globalized modernity that go hand in hand then hero and heroes now.</summary>
	<body>We showed suspicion, so long ago days, to the latest installment of the saga of the Crystal jungle, one of those film series that we like and taking part in our sentimental education. Sentimental education not strictly film incidentally step.We all know that John McClane was a cynical and half finished, type carrier this aesthetic of the loser that we love so much. Poorly spoken, violent, politically incorrect and, moreover, smoker. A pity of man, are going. His first on-screen appearance dates from 1988, nothing less. Of the things that have happened in the world since then! Of the fall of the iron curtain the planetary globalisation, twenty years is a lifetime. Playing with this change in geopolitical scenario, cultural and cybernetic, producers of the saga of the jungle crystalline, after giving rest to its protagonist for thirteen years, so rescue the ostracism and, thus, before his film Renaissance, it is reasonable to show concern. What will become of McLane in these years? Because the promotional images shows it quite whole piece and compact, solid and a piece. Is there hamburguesado? Will become politically correct? Will have it left the tobacco?The answer, in "The jungle 4.0", a title that it is already quite illustrative and that, from the outset, put their cards face up. Let's start with the bad. You are these bad very bad but, at the same time normalísimos. Nothing of disfigured mutant or crazy eccentrics. No. The bad are a compact group of Jasper, very handsome and ready them. And its purpose: total chaos, of course. A terrorist attack of cybernetic character which, in addition to making them rich, subvertirán the world order as we understand it.Perhaps a boot like this may sound them. More than teléfilos lovers. Does it not a true aroma of this series which, supposedly, happening in real time? Quickly we turn to the hero, who has trouble with a daughter who denies him, without solution of continuity, present us with a kid and anonymous, vulgar and current, but with a special talent, in this case for computers and that from the beginning is in the crosshairs of the bad guys.And the story is already mounted. What we are in a recognizable scenario? Pay attention to what they said Willis in an interview: "so many characters have been based on McClane is normal." For example Jack Bauer. "Kiefer Sutherland is doing a great job by drawing upon the jungle."Given what was like before, if the chicken or the egg. The case is the jungle, in its zero point version, an exemplary film that baby television and globalized modernity that go hand in hand then hero and heroes now. Because the prominence of the film is two-fold. In the best tradition of the Buddy-movies, McClane helps and is helped by a spontaneous fellow, a hacker for whom the character played by Willis is a dinosaur who, in turn, looks at the genius of computers as if it were a Martian.And this dialectic between the digital and the analog hero moves throughout the film, halfway between the spoof and the chaotic. In that regard, the sorcerer, character played by one of the gurus of modernity, Kevin Smith, is paradigmatic: its operations center is the most modern in the world, but there is a radio transmitter of the of all life, which will be the only thing that works when everything is going to hell because of the cíberterorrismo.And it is the action, in spades. And violence, less explicit than other times. And humor, more acidic and corrosive. And the beatings which fall you to McClane. As always. And, therefore, we have a great movie. Modern and classic at the same time, in the best sense of both expressions. A little long, perhaps. And hyperbolic and excessive, of course. But it is that, even in its zero point version, we are still in "The jungle of glass".</body>
</review>
