<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Death Proof" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Yes, note the involvement with Planet Terror by imitating the B series or as call (the production design and Assembly are excellent), but think that this guy has gone too, towards its own way, and that seems phenomenal.</summary>
	<body>There are essences, there are customs and talents which one you can catch or rather not. With these two masterpieces titled Reservoir Dogs and Pulp Fiction, Quentin Tarantino left marked a seal that vanished over the following years. However, there were personal habits that not them forgot, although that pure essence of his first two works already not was palpable both. Lost their initial identity in a rational manner. Now, thanks to a buddy Grindhouse, has had the opportunity (or intelligence) back to its beginnings, creating an own history, a brutality sealed in each one of their frames by the unmistakable identity of the director himself. And is that to me, as announced in the first sentence, this guy amazes me, I caught, and therefore Death Proof seems a brilliant film tarantiniano bestieza. If the two Kill Bill were a mere exercise (which not bad) on the martial arts and step on the easternmost revenge, his new job is a realistic portrait of two groups of girls and pass a vision less human, but most masculine, a man obsessed with them. Is that his film is a film dialogue, apparently empty, with depth quasi non-existent, but always with the metaphorical question next hidden behind of are cars, attractive women or guns: in what world we are living? At first sight this question I ask may seem somewhat simple, inclusio too global. But focusing and analyzing this moral background, we can see that in Death Proof life these eight girls quotidiana is treated with sensitivity (not ordinary but realistic) which is later trastocada by the current world of the sick, of the obsessive maniacs that much abound in this not so healthy planet in which we live. The metaphor, therefore it is in these two conflicting worlds (who come to play únicmanete by be outdated), of the female group, crazy and that carpe diem to all time, and that killer male, gross and direct, without just heart and too much intelligence cold. And it is more likely is that you think that this is bullshit, an exaggeration to all gas (never better said). But guys, if you see a film, wherever one as Quentin, of course, can not go with the intention, by seemingly very simple and silly that seems, that this is a simple and funny bullshit. There to see, standing and reasoning. And if you still thinking that what I say is useless, this entertainment is much more than a mere entertainment, we do not like the movies of Quentin Tarantino. Why only think that Death Proof is a simple tribute to those movies B where cars and girls abounded in abundance? Why not stop and think that maybe is something else? Certainly I, and perhaps only I would describe this film as a labour-intensive and very, very worked, made exclusively for the director and some few fans (I do not know, but necessarily myself in them) who see his film as something more than a simple blunder made to laugh (cry of laughter), have fun and leave the film saying "How cool!". And is that in this deep and bloody fun about friendship, you can find numerous winks to the film tarantiniano (their own Manias, say), whether it is the tone of the recommandations of Rosario Dawnson making reference to the already mythical whistles of Kill Bill, the close-ups of plants of female feet, the short sequence converted to black and white (that Yes)(, has no sense whatever his intention) or already very common talks of groups of friends in a bar (still remember this impeccable first sequence of Reservoir Dogs, with a simply perfect extensive dialogue). Here the script was also written by Tarantino, and may be noted that, despite his initial plan very simple view (psycho chases a group of impressive young girls), inside it can extract much, much juice. And this is where play dialogues, covering almost half of the film. In the first story, darker (hence putting it at night), talks among the Group of girls (and some that another boy) are incredibly realistic, quotidianas, though sometimes a bit false and disproportionate, note that point seriously, and so dark, that fear that something happens that (he) keeps them us more strained (and therefore to the public) of that something happens, that the evil Stuntman Mike destroze to pieces sooner or later that the beautiful blonde that comes in the bar (memorable dialogue with it, by the way). Also begins to witness that comic air (perhaps with a more ironic, not as black humor) that little by little you will maintain more tension. At the Summit of the first chapter, is when Tarantino turn on the engine and leaves us all paralyzed, with a head-on collision (I say this literally!) absolutely brutal, with a sequence impeccably mounted and repeated four times from different angles. Then takes to fill that gap between the two stories with a no less sparkling conversation between two policemen of Texas (father and son) that stands out most is where the plane sequence than the absurdity of the content (although you laugh also). Then comes the second (or third, if you want) part of Death Proof, showing that radical change with respect to the characters. Here, already more clear the matter, our protagonist returns to the adventures and you intend to pursue another group of striking funny girls. Is then when, very cleverly, director us approaching the life of these four very different girls but that we fall so well (and what mad are!). Here they are, the obsesas and him, initially with spirits but then defeated, is the victim. Personally, attracts me most this second story, because that with this top in black and white, the supermarket scene, consequent dialogue at the bar (absolutely delicious), the appearance of the talented and excellent Zöe Bell, the purchase of the car and the dazzling and perfect pursuit (with final taconazo included), one can not be left only with words. If the first part was a brutal and no doubt also excellent and striking operands, the second you choose to increase this madness (on both sides, sexually speaking) and make us believe that what we are seeing is a film, pure and simple, of Quentin Tarantino. Recognize that also are the Palm eight which are certainly in a State of grace and a hilarious Kurt Russell and less crazy unrelated phrases as splendid as that drops in the first bar. And not to forget not all musical themes, highlighting the already unforgettable Down in Mexico of The Coasters.Creo that Death Proof, is more than a tribute and the final episode of this Grindhouse, the audacity of Tarantino for coming back to do what he likes, expel this so personal essence and already step make a brief appearance no less memorable. Yes, note the involvement with Planet Terror by imitating the B series or as are called (certainly, the production design and Assembly are excellent, with these changes of tone and the shredded on the screen made on purpose), but I think (or at least I can see) that this guy has gone too, towards their own path, and that seems phenomenal. It is that no one must forget that we we have a Quentin Tarantino film, and that can be seen even with your eyes closed. It is not his best film, but yes it is truly personal, and that is what really matters.</body>
</review>
