<review author="Berto" title="Sigo como Dios" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film is quite poor (and I am not referring to budget), if compared with the first, but it is not that it is particularly boring.</summary>
	<body>Another film, and in this case it's up to "Still as God" which is the sequel to, if you can call sequel, "Like God". He ran the year 2003 when I arrive "like God" screens, that funny comedy actors had Jennifer Aniston, Jim Carrey and Morgan Freeman, all got a smash hit. Well, of the three the only one that remains as God is Morgan Freeman (because interprets God) which shares prominence in this movie with a second from the first part, Steve Carell (in the role of Baxter), Carrey should see the script and would lay to run? mania have studies to sequels where not can be drawn.On this occasion, the argument is that God is presented to Baxter, and tells him to build an Ark to the more pure style Noe (I learned something? look in the Bible Genesis 6.14) and this gets her ride with the help of his family (in which all existing topics for American families are met) and also collaborate the animals that come into the Ark?The question is why rides God that mess? Why not punishing the bad guy directly?, ah! the villain is John Goodman (the flintstones Lord) and is bad for wanting to remove a proposed law to build in the boundaries of national parks, we are that it is a corrupt and wants to make money with the construction. No must dios know marbella? because but already would have 5 or 6 built coffers. Humor, is soft and easy, nothing to do with the humor that had in the first movie thanks to the good of Jim Carrey, this new player has a humor? It has an air of Steve Martin (and is a humor that I do not like). That if the film has a couple of scenes quite entertaining and what I most liked was see navigate to the Ark? and Morgan Freeman's performance in the role of God, with their reflections makes throughout the film and the message that gives to care for the planet. In conclusion, this film is quite poor (and I am not referring to budget), if compared with the first, but it is not that it is particularly boring.</body>
</review>
