<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entertaining ration of action cinema to desastacar the mind of pesarosas wanderings. Viva McClane.</summary>
	<body>The jungle 4.0 is a feast of so inconsequential as pleasant adrenaline which appeals to the primary instincts of a spectator inevitably conquered by the mesmerizing pyrotechnics of jumps, gunfire and explosions. Guaranteed amusement not deallocates the certainty that the model of action hero to the McClane is already burnt, although the first version of the franchise implied an ozonated exercise of quality action movie. What has happened with the wanderings of the urban police who saves the world from scratches and blasphemy is that they we not longer astonish. Everything that happens has already seen and everything that we have seen too many times is possible to us not engolosine. The jungle 4.0 brings nothing new to the genre: his subtle progression of scenarios is foreshadow as a clumsy witticism to baste the crossfire of an army of assassins insípidamente handled by a villain is not commensurate with the circumstances. John McClane, Bruce Willis comfortable in a role that belongs to benefit of encyclopedias of film, continues antagonizing the wicked with his homicidal language and its irreducible ability to overcome, despite the thrashing of sticks it receives, the pitfalls, the fights, falls and the damage that he violates the imaginations of the writers, always so eager to please the well apoltronado public.The original Nakatomi, the claustrophobic scenario and true protagonist of the jungle of glass, first and best version, went to an airport and then to a city is now a broadband connection. So are the times. A certain excess of cables, usb ports and screens flickering with cryptic retahílas of codes and algorithms that officiate the eminently apocalyptic nature of the plot: a kind of Total chaos, the demolition of the system, the desquiciamiento of the digital society. But hete here that the rough analog poli, the calibrating McClane, well-armed bad milk and expertise to emerge unscathed from any infringement, skews the greed of the enemy and sends him to hell with a yipi ka yei, son of a bitch, which is what we wanted to hear since that we install in the armchair in the room to receive doses of americanada to use, but we like.</body>
</review>
