<review author="Marta" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tarantino takes a hilarious argument and adds dialogue covers and original, a few precious levels, a wonderful "retro" image, a fascinating protagonist, a great soundtrack and some women who fall in love, not to mention countless references to the delight of the fans.</summary>
	<body>I went with "Kill Bill" and me has returned to spend with "Death Proof". I went to see the latest movies of Tarantino convinced that, in reality, me they wouldn't like too and in the end I have loved. The vengeful girlfriend did not expect more than fights and more fights and proved to be much more. Or not, but at least it was very well made. Now, with the killer driver, was ready to meet with. Good, because that, with a killer driver. But no, that is only a fraction of what this half of the Grindhouse project offers. We will go through high now all say "Grindhouse" as if it were a term that we had been using for a lifetime - Yes, as when we learned to say "place" with "Farmacia de guardia". At this point we know that Quentin Tarantino and Robert Rodriguez were launched to shoot two works in homage to the B-movies that they saw in double session in United States and here in Spain we them have separate, and I don't have much more to add to this. The fact is that, without knowing anything of the genus – like most of those who write these days about it, no mistake - "Death Proof" has seemed great. I have not seen "Planet Terror" and am quite certain that will be very down. While Tarantino is a great director that hoeing them to pick up anything and get something bright, Robert Rodriguez appears, simply a guy with good luck. Anyway, I guess that sometime I will see and I will see if I am right. For the moment, I prefer the friend Quentin. The uncle takes a hilarious argument and adds a few dialogues original and covers, a few precious plans, a wonderful "retro" image, a fascinating protagonist, a great soundtrack and some women who fall in love, not to mention the countless references to the delight of fans, sure that I not got even half, and that I noticed a few. All this in two very distinct parts - something key to make the footage not eternal-, in a very fun and worrying, I suppose, to maintain fidelity to the genre. The truth is that this last is what I liked least. I would have been able to dispense perfectly blood, but the truth is that it is not even a fraction of what you'd expect after trailers and promotion, and I understand that it is a fundamental element. Not they thrilled me especially false failures of image and sound, that were too obvious in a cinema "latest model", but not at all so excessive as I had read in some sites. And, finally, it upset me a couple of stories were completely disrupted and behind, what I gather to be another nod to this kind of movies, because it is somewhat exaggerated. Was no one else eager to return to see the cheerleader or know where to lead the suspicions of the sheriff? Both characters as the actors - in reality, the actresses - that they interpret deserve special mention. If Kurt Russell (specialist Mike) outboard to a seductive psychopath, each of the girls becomes a heroine with a personality and a unique beauty, of those who can really drive crazy anyone. Rosario Dawson, in particular, I will put it on an altar. It has never been so beautiful as here.It was convinced that no one would be able to get something decent like history of persecution and good aunts. I even thought that someone could keep a simple approach during the time that lasts a film. What error. Tarantino does so, and wonder. It is clear that the fame has not come by chance.</body>
</review>
