<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Los ojos del mal" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Empty, decorated artificial characters, bloody and "imaginative" deaths and an almost endless series of clichés that occur without pause, showing aspiring filmmakers that Yes is possible to build a film-based topicazos.</summary>
	<body>Before you say anything, it should be remembered that the eyes of evil (2006) was the first film of WWE Films, a production company created by the Federation which sponsors this show of acrobatics homoerotic is American wrestling at the time. The producer, in fact, was created with the sole purpose of launching a series of commercial films that opened step to the stars of this show in the world of cinema. After this first horror film, the WWE Films has released other two tapes, The Marine (2006) and The Condemned (2007), covering the genres of action and futuristic thriller, respectively. Worth noting, however, that the employment of wrestlers in movies is nothing new, because there always has been a never-ending parade of luminaries who took their first steps between the twelve strings, such as Hulk Hogan, Roddy Piper, Jesse Ventura or the latest The Rock. The use of these stars at the top of the cast is a resource treacherous, as wisely as a friend of mine once said, every are alive (1988) there are ten Suburban Commando (1991).At the beginning of this story see how a COP is defeated and mutilated to try to catch the serial killer Jacob Goodnight (played by the well-noted Kane and whose name could well be of a wrestler of truth), famous for his obsession with eyes, which starts its victims to then retain them in the brine. Several years later, the same agent of the Act now prison guard, was hired to monitor a group of youngsters convicts that should work restore an old and shabby hotel old if they want to reduce his prison sentence. As if the fact that a group of convicted juveniles Sevill in a huge building with only a disabled guard to monitor them were not already a monument to the unlikely, here attend a surprise twist: the ruins of the hotel are precisely the refuge of Jacob Goodnight, who is more than happy for fresh victims to add to his collection of eyeballs. It is clear that this initial, ridiculous situation until over not being able to, not you can keep for a long time, so the film quickly embraces the typecasting and clichés of the genre to convert the characters in a gang of youngsters hiper-hormonados that transforms that work like at a party worthy of the most crappy Friday the 13th sequels (1980). If something must be acknowledged him to Gregory Dark (pseudonym for a man who led a huge number of porn movies and a video of Britney Spears) is that he has managed to mix all the ingredients of what is a horror of these film are produced today by the hundreds: empty, decorated artificial characters, bloody and "imaginative" deaths and an almost endless series of clichés that occur without pauseshowing aspiring filmmakers that Yes is possible to build a film based on topicazos. From the unbearable victims cartoon (conveniently exploited in their sexual appeal) to the inescapable references to the traumatic past of the murderer and even a turn final surprise showing come leagues. The fact that history somehow reverse what one could expect from the characters and their final destination (basically who survives and who does not) is not enough to recommend this waste of time. We are talking about a genuinely bad film that repeats and repeats most hackneyed commonplaces of the slasher, but without irony.This leads inevitably to the saddest of all: the own Kane, an architect that happens throughout the film breaking walls, making stews and putting a laughable bad face which makes it seem as if she were constantly smelling shit, a puppet with absolutely nothing of the charisma of other murderers of the past, an albino gorilla that gives more laughter than anything else. It is true that a film like this do not expect much, but I can imagine that having seen so many horror movies inevitably end up demanding more of the things. Ignore this waste called the eyes of evil is obligatory for any viewer fourteen years of age or older. I, personally, could pass this thing.</body>
</review>
