<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Ratatouille" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>At this point all you have already seen the film but if not so id running to see it because it is, without doubt, one of the great films of the year.</summary>
	<body>After much disillusionment film summer, most of the moviegoers had entrusted to us to Santa Pixar hoping that she we draw from the tedium.For this reason, the same day as the premiere and despite not find me in the best of the biases, I set out to the nearest cinema to enjoy a good time to film allowing me to escape I foul real world."It was a success.""Ratatouille" is a project that came to be on the brink of disaster when the original director, Jan Pinkava, was quietly dismissed and replaced by one of the safest in the company and, possibly, the most renowned animation film director: Brad Bird.No know what would have been the film without him, but with him at the helm of the direction taken hardly could be better.With the arrival of Bird changed many of the elements that make now great movie. The two most obvious examples and acquaintances (imagine that in the kitchen of the project there will be many secrets that we shall not know never) are the script finally written by himself, and the design of (at least) some of the key characters (including the protagonist's).It is difficult to say everything that I like about the film without making a long critique. The above script is a real wonder and works as a mechanism of watchmaking. A script in which everything happens at the right time and in the appropriate way. The dramatic progression is perfect and worth as an example how to go creating excitement around the character of Anton Ego and the great way of resolving it with one of the most emotive flashbacks in modern cinema.Curious is that in a genus as the comedy which I think perhaps the worst the present Treaty and where do brand new authentic clunkers badly written and worse directed Pixar don't forget to release a good film after another although few of the quality of this "Ratatouille" which has already among the very best of the company.Of course the pace is frenetic, situations strung with each other seamlessly and only him could be attributed a dish bajoncillo pace halfway through function.As I say, everything I like about the film. Why not I fail to mention the wonderful soundtrack of Michael Giacchino returns to dazzle us after his brilliant work in "The Incredibles" (another jewel directed by Bird).Anyway, at this point all have already seen the film but if not so id running to see it because it is, without doubt, one of the great films of the year.</body>
</review>
