<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Domino" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In film terms, this production is clumsy, treacherous and fullera, with a hodgepodge which call Assembly</summary>
	<body>Live fast and die faster still. If we look at the caption we just invent, this film can be criticized quickly: futile, irregular and scrap of worship. But does not create that felt us entirely misguided because that he is loyal to its principles and complies with everything what is proposed, from the first commandment: provocarás to all those who spend their money on movie tickets. Now, this is not art but a product that comes from time to time nor bad. Never mind that or concert, with dozens of flash-backs is filmed without a warrant and pulling of advertising resources and light video clips; chaos reigns in Domino and Tony Scott (he/she brother of Ridley) takes him for flag, seasoned with a bath of humor and bravado, memories of Beverly Hills 90210 including. In movie terms, this production is clumsy, treacherous and fullera, with a hodgepodge which call Assembly that denotes how wrong (or not, and this is the funny thing) which is responsible for titles such as Top gun, Spy game, red tide and fan. But as any film style (ex officio assassins, true romance, Pulp Fiction), Domino will have detractors and supporters in equal parts. I have to acknowledge the history of this posh girl restored by the bad — and more interesting — way hooked me from the first moment, in part by his spoof tone? visible in the realization of the television programme on busca-malhechores-Squadron and its dish approach to social, evident in the lesson of racial dialectic, with chinegros and other pseudorazas. The surprise of the unpredictable is the only reason why one can digest the changes of pace, the disinterest of the second part, impossible levels, the pedal that leave us without breath and the slowdowns and moments frozen in contrast. It is not easy dish, so arrived in this line, rises the number of maldicientes, sure. Do in the world of fiction, the rotulito of? based on real events? gives the story told some vehemence status, although it is not guarantee of good doing that, for unusual, the life of the real Domino Harvey, who died before they see the results. She gave her consent that they have his frantic step worldwide but, as in all fiction that aims to attract spectators, there is more action than answers to all the questions that we are on this woman's arms take. Scott is limited to offer us a couple of pictures so we keep quiet, without becoming the preguntones that his long iconoclast 24–6. No style that grab, only interpretations, so maybe the tape? leaning again towards the most critical - is without doubt the choir and its protagonist: Beautiful Damsel stuck to mercenary that hard to recognize in his role of macarrilla studies, hunting rewards looks with disdain the past years who lived rise in heels. An excellent work of Keira Knightley, a curious tape, Domino, that it will go unnoticed, a perception that one has to write about this film made from scraps, some better fabrics than others.</body>
</review>
