<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A real visual and auditory show that should be considered, in General, as a good or at least very effective genre movie. Ask more would be unfair.</summary>
	<body>Quite entertaining fourth part of the "Die hard" franchise, which as good dividends has given and continues to give to the producers of the same. Here, McLane agent remains in the same plan, saving the world from a sinister and murderous organization able to put upside down the world order, at least of the city of Washintgon and some more. Very well done from the formal point of view, with an energetic and explosive mounting, and with shocking scenes as the persecution of the helicopter to the two protagonists, the film, despite its slightly more than two hours, follows without any problem, perhaps because there is no downtime.Everything is action adrenalítica, no time to breathe, nor the characters of the film viewers. However, he attributed that in the end everything is too much. Too much movement, too many shots, too many persecutions, excessive, go. Your first time is all very well, and with the long scene of the helicopter we marvel and we are for good use of the money invested in the entry, not in vain, this scene, as well as many others, it shows that they have cost a pastón. So we can warn that it is a very expensive film, where the money has been used well. However, had could have eliminated some minutes, some little things here and there, so it would be lighter and it would cease to be the vertiginous billet in the end is.A billet, repeat, very enjoyable overall, but something deslavazado sometime and, of course, with several absolutely implausible scenes (many fantasmadas are House brand and therefore unavoidable), as when launched from the control box car.For its part, some "deliveries" are just that, births, i.e. very bad jokes, ears a thousand times and already have little grace. Anyway, that "The jungle 4.0" is a true visual spectacle and auditory (excellent editing and sound effects), very currado, that should be considered, in General, as a good or at least very effective genre movie. Ask more would be unfair.</body>
</review>
