<review author="José A. Peig" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>McClane wanders through a dark and apocalyptic universe in which the loss of values and collective disorientation motivate their participation in this new adventure. Action movie, rather modest, outstanding, although others sometimes lacks credibility.</summary>
	<body>The computer as a weapon of attack and manipulation in the world post-11-S, a State of civilization whose traits derived from diverse social expressions, attitudes, jargon, beliefs and methods from the legitimate power or from the underground society and the same industry on which maintains the system. Anarchy, in the final analysis, is the common factor, West dragging a guilt complex which leads us to consider methods of self-destruction, take advantage of the global network to destabilize what this same network aims to stabilize and unify. The "geek" unconscious and scary played by Justin Long dreams of ruin the entire system with just a keystroke. In fact, the idea seemed so sinister as attractive, and this character largely reflects a latent in our social gear delirium, although never stated clearly: destroy the system because of the idea of guilt. John McClane, living myth of the cinema of the 1980s, appears in this context as an element of sanity and social sensitivity and replica that he is not the system, but people who suffer. McClane is as a hero who travels from his past deeds, which saved the lives of many people, and that never had the deserved recognition, until our present governed by corruption and a nebulous sense of social, effective counterpoint to the chaos and the inconsistency of Matt Farrell. In this way, the story provides a significant chemistry between two characters who bear the weight of a very simple speech, but effectively synthesizes the secondary elements which allude to various nuances of the global delusion in which we live. Therefore, the jungle 4.0 is not so much a film about John McClane in his twilight as on the present state of the society, from a prism of delirium, sponsored by disinformation and the incompetence of the State authorities. The question is whether the role played by a character as McClane fits in the different strata of the film: on the one hand, the preponderance of information technology, computers as "leit-motiv" visual. On the other hand, the representation of global chaos. McClane from die hard (movie of which we will talk about in the coming days), passing by the sequels that followed, was an involuntary and anonymous hero that "was always at the place and time less timely". That, together with its form of expression (Campeche as well as direct and bluntly, with use and abuse of tacos) is the essence of the character, a profile designed to develop in small places in which happen events of maximum tension. Introduce McClane in the current context to be the hero who will save the system (the system, not a particular group of people in a particular space) is create a bias with respect to characterology and texture. I.e., we notice the capricious way to recover the character to be used as propaganda and element related to the "post-11-S syndrome" at the expense of greater consistency and coherence thematic and narrative. First and foremost, it remains a very decent movie, despite the bias to which we have referred, this portrait of John McClane aged, embittered in a life in which not received rewards for their heroic and a dysfunctional family, mistrust regarding her daughter's suitors, the Grouch and impertinent, father agrees, broadly, with the outbreak of total chaos, which involves informalization and distrust with the neighbor.Chaos, emphasized Visual through the dark and ochre tones that predominate in the picture, is not confined to the spectacular artifacts and the vision of the crazed masses, that emphasizes the atomisation of society, in particular, aspects and excessive specialization in the various areas of our - alleged - "knowledge society": see how a computer expert or even know what is morphine. Or the character known as "El brujo", detained in his "throne" computer and enjoying the exclusive control of the electricity grid, example not devoid of cynicism social unconsciousness. In short, McClane wanders through a dark and apocalyptic universe in which the loss of values and collective disorientation motivate their participation in this new adventure. Outstanding film of action, rather modest, at times, while in others there is no likelihood (see the "duel" between McClane and all a sophisticated combat aircraft.) (McClane is an anonymous hero and a human being, not a superhero). But the transcendent tone of discourse, which refers to a global tragedy involving institutional and spiritual degeneration surpasses and exceeds the role of the character.In the last scenes, before he died, Thomas Gabriel (lunatic which represents the destruction of the system under the auspices of a creator of the same system), speaks to McClane and mentions the refrain of "wrong place and less timely", a forced attempt to return the character to its original scope. The phrase does not fit with the story or the situation of the moment. It is then when we notice more bias and when we discovered that this film, McClane with or without him, would be another product again, among the many that lie ahead, on the current state of things.</body>
</review>
