<review author="Bruji" title="Ana Karenina" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bad language that there was not a single day of filming in which the requirements (including feed properly your New cat) and continuing complaints from the Scarlet Ms. crisparan not the nerves of the technical team.</summary>
	<body>Chapter one-All happy families resemble. Every unhappy family, it is in their own way.Five November 1.913 was born in La India Vivian Mary Hartley. Do with Irish blood in the veins, the movie buff world her known as Scarlett O?Hara, the charm of the Red Earth of Tara in "what the wind"; "one of the most charismatic and fascinating of the history of the Cine.Ocho characters years later of the mythical film, Vivien Leigh abided the orders of the director and French writer Julien Duvivier in a new film adaptation of Anna Karenina."Neither a Word nor a gesture you never forget. "How it he could?"The classic of world literature, work Summit of l? amour fou, shows the hypocrisy of a (non-exclusive of the 19th century) reactionary society, which fills with contempt and solitude to those who do not follow their obsolete regulations. Between delusion and reality, the protagonist, desperate, not only begins to doubt the feelings of the man whom she loves, but also his own chances as a human being. An untenable situation that forces to escape from itself.Bad language that there was not a single day of filming in which the requirements (including feed properly your New cat) and continuing complaints from the Scarlet Ms. crisparan not the nerves of the technical team and, above all, the director. So much so, that the producer Alexander Korda (great friend of the actress) has to intervene on numerous occasions, hastily traveling from California to calm down.Finally, the film premièred January 22, 1948 in the British capital and later in New York. Shot in Russia and in London, with an impressive artistic direction of Andrej Andrejew, excellent photography and exquisite costumes designed in Paris, it fails miserably in the recruitment of the main actor (a newcomer that never more was learned) and, what is worse, fails in the narrative structure. Maybe the error is found in a nothing brilliant script which showed the disagreements that have arisen between the director and the producer, who opt for different writers. The result is one product bothered to show the Tsarist Russia pompous, interpretative Ralph Richardson (important actor of the English stage) skills and the extraordinary beauty of the protagonist (his face always appears illuminated when everything remains in half-light), than in telling precisely the dramatic history. The novel of Tolstoy has been carried the film nineteen times, which joined four television films and three television series. Actresses of all time and many nationalities have given life to the enigmatic Lady, but the criticism is unanimous in pointing out to the divine Swedish as Anna Karenina par excellence. Greta Garbo would interpret this role on two occasions: in 1927 and 1935, in a production of David o. SelznickLa plot lead to passion for the impossible love attached to railway stations. "Brief encounter" of David Lean, "fall in love" performed by Robert de Niro and Meryl Streep and the recent "unchecked" starring the attractive Clive Owen, are just some examples of approach of Karenina-mania. Two oscar-winning, undeniable talent and false smile, actress protagonist of unforgettable films. You can to Vivien lost the reins of his life for the benefit of an inappropriate love (which isn't it?). Maybe he destroyed his own happiness with both hands, as did the characters that exceeded. That not cared or that there was no exit may. Or you can simply, to always think that "really, tomorrow is another day".</body>
</review>
