<review author="Bruji" title="La sombra de la sospecha" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The shadow of suspicion, however, does not have the capacity to surprise, factor essential and inherent to all good thriller.</summary>
	<body>The new production of Michael Douglas can be summed up in just five words: nothing new under the Sun. Extremely attractive in its initial, careful with the technical details and remarkable approach to interpretive level, the shadow of suspicion, however, does not have the ability to surprise, factor essential and inherent to all good thriller. On the contrary, Petievich novel seems to be aimed, on many occasions, to underestimate the Viewer. Kiefer Sutherland, brilliant. Who saw the bodyguards (the old things, to me I loved) will recall that Kevin Costner was the best in his role because had worked to protect the life of the President of the United States. When his seductive partner lets you fall "to the presi they beat him a shot", he responds, without flinching, "that it was not in their turn". Does the magic of cinema has wanted that, years later, we discover that who was on duty that day was none other than the very same Michael Douglas.El veteran actor? and also producer of this movie - will introduce us to the world of elite bodyguards, grouped around the secret service, with the Special Mission to ensure the life of the American leader and the first lady. A very interesting approach, among other reasons, the amount of work these professionals must have current date; but, quickly lose its appeal to the step to an intended plot, in many moments, to underestimate the Viewer. It is not too credible, for example, that an experienced agent of the security forces, with more than 25 years at the service of "Her Majesty", devoted to spread to the four winds a hit of information that has come from a foolproof confidant who provides from more than ten, and would endanger the life of the President. Aspect so unlikely to know that the highest levels of the secret services, to know that there is "a mole" among them, taken as a single measure of security polygraph, to detect who is the traitor. And no more credible point to Barranquilla traffickers or former agents of intelligence services Soviets as possible interested in the death of a timely American President. True it is that enemies not lacking to this country, but sounds like a joke in year 2.006 channelled these paths the script. Screenwriter Nolfi, based on the novel by Gerald Petievich, (which was bought by 20Th Century Fox, before being published in order to this film) stated in an interview on the occasion of the premiere of the film in the USA, "who had tried to make the absolutely true story". It must be so, that did not happen nothing better than writing a culminating sentence to be pronounced by one of the characters in the story: "In 141 years, is the first time that there is a mole in the American secret services". Phrase is not at all uncertain, if we take into account that according to research of true and famous Attorney of New Orleans, which picked up Oliver Stone in one of his movies, there would have been a mole but a herd in the 1960s and with regard to the assassination of JFK. A phrase that, knowing the controversial history of the above-mentioned filmmaker, is ridiculous. As ridiculous as they are mobile which has "bad" this bad thriller, personal squabbles that arise between the two protagonists because of a woman named Silvia, ultimately resulting is called Cindy (thing that bothers the "pijoteros" who realize everything), or the love affair between Douglas and Basinger. The latter, two monsters of the big screen, myths of cinema of the 1980s, which complemented Kiefer Sutherland, who already made their first steps by the same decade with what "Today is a good day to die", the cast line mortal; and with Eva Longoria, an important revelation, camera, last minute. Really, I don't know what kind of public will provide for the shadow of suspicion. Certainly not to the followers of the "political thriller"--and it has been--who not take more than ten minutes to find out the plot. Only the great writers and filmmakers in the history of Hollywood have been able to deceive the most clever Viewer. Some of them, because they were brilliant really. Others, because they were based on accounts of the Queen of crime, Doña agate. In any case, the novel, the screenplay and the film that today we are dealing with, are light years from all of them. Nothing new under the Sun.</body>
</review>
