<review author="Bruji" title="El señor de la guerra" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Talk about a great deal (really, it is) we accept sugar as a sweetener without calories, and include Cage in praise.</summary>
	<body>It is often the case that good intentions do not always translate into satisfactory results. On this occasion, to speak of good intentions, I am referring to the brave gamble of the director and the producers of Lord of war, want to address directly the international traffic of arms. A project that forced them to seek foreign investors for his film, not finding capital American because it is a controversial argument. However, usually happens also in film, that the grace of the matter isn't what it has, but the way in which has, on many occasions, and in this story he has blatantly failed "how" to do it. A clear example in which an exciting premise is ruined by an unfortunate script, an inappropriate approach and a little focused direction, which leave a lot to be desired. There is no point have been based on real facts,-such as the existence of military helicopters that were sold as material of rescue, the change of names and flag of ships of traffickers on the high seas, the strange departure from the prison of one of America's most powerful weapons mobsters or the looting of the arsenals of Soviet, after the demise of U.R.S.S.-If not they have been able to take any advantage. The history of Andrew Niccol begins with a close-up of Nicolas Cage (absolute protagonist) giving explanations, that no one has asked, about a life, that it is not yet known, to not know who; and it has two distinct parts. The first of these, especially tedious and clumsily told, is characterized by the appearance of a nagging voice that serves as a common thread, and far from being a critique of anything, becomes manual "the dealer perfect", with an explosion of technical data on the M60 (Rambo I favorite utensil) and the AK-47 (true weapon of mass destruction) that are only of interest who run an Armory. The first part of which all seduces is the idea of leaving the room.Deficiencies in the script (patents at all times) can be seen, for example, in the incredible thing is that a young Ukrainian immigrant who lives in a slum American, without previously knowing the business without contacts and mentors, you not only get entering the illegal traffic of weapons market, but that also can move freely without problems. It must be because in the Cage character figures of five different arms dealers have been condensed, and perhaps, that is also the reason which Don Nicolas ages nor lose professional faculties throughout history. In addition to the absolutely unreal protagonist, screenwriter will make every effort, from the outset, in issue supposedly witty phrases and they constitute definite statements. A goal which is not achieved. I do not know what may think the American Spectator about them, it is possible that even they mean something in that country, but to me little or nothing tell me statements as reflected in this story: "In the world there is a weapon for every twelve people, how are the other eleven assembled?", "the first time you sell a gun is like the first time you make love"": you don't know what you're doing, but it's exciting", "bad fall you in love with the woman of your dreams is that it is real", and other similar features. The woman that falls in love with, by the way, will be one of these trophy wives who are unaware of her husband's criminal activities, but that do not care them to live better than the Pope. And I wonder, is this another real character?. Since then, if so, this you should be called blind trust or excess of hypocrisy. When the naive wife find out the truth, a burst of dignity will prevent you from "fail as a human being", but... and until then?. In any case, a very different approach to adopt another breakthrough, that of Traffic which, for my taste, had a much more normal reaction. The second part of the film, much more promising than the previous one, arises from the fall of the Soviet Union, and in which the voiceover (which remains unbearable) is gradually disappearing. Let's say that we are entering a much more conventional narrative and what is becoming history.It features interpretive duels between Nicolas Cage and Ethan Hawke, between Nicolas Cage and Jared Leto; a great proposal for casting returns to spoil the director, doing work so splendid trio only 10% of their potential. Talk about a great deal (really, it is) we accept sugar as a sweetener without calories, and include Cage in praise. An actor hated by many film buffs, who hasn't done anything decent since Leaving Las Vegas; theory that is ratified with his latest works still not released in Spain, the phantom rider (that must be the version of Pirates of the Caribbean two-wheel drive) and the role of super hero who plays in the last patriotic outburst of Oliver Stone on the twin towers. Something good has also this second part, and is that him director already you will be catching the tranquillo be writer, and get what you had intended from the outset: write a strong sentence in that Cage, prestigiosísimo international dealer, instructs Ethan Hawke, faithful official of Interpol that "his head is the largest arms dealer in the world". Of course, to talk about his boss he is referring to the Antichrist, or what is the same, the President of the U.S.A. clear which. at this point in the footage, already is very difficult to reconcile both sides of the film? should remember that in the first, he urged to leave the cinema - and we think that the legend of the end "major supplier of weapons of the world are also the countries that are in the permanent UN Security Council" should have appeared just at the beginningbecause this not would have subtracted you originality to the story, and Yes would have provided you wisdom. In any case, this is the sad story of an impressive argument which had the misfortune to encounter a director and screenwriter who was suspend the subject of "How are things". A shame!.</body>
</review>
