<review author="Antoni Messa" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although not establishing anything of what can happen to this type, hardly go one to aburrise. And this is a good guarantee within the coordinates of an action thriller.</summary>
	<body>John McLane is a hard COP; a type of expeditious and easy trigger and, at the same time, a gafe of volume and spine that his own daughter can not see nor in painting. As he quotes one of the bad guys of the jungle 4.0, "again returns to be in the wrong place and at the improper time". With the passing of the years, McLane has become a caricature of himself. Anchored in the past, in his car even listening to blaring Fortunate Son of the Creedence. Hates his job, but doing it with unparalleled professionalism: adrenaline, bad milk and the abruptly are the best allies of a solitary cowboy like him, by far, after each of its turbulent and unexpected missions, ending spending a good part of his salary in gel, shower, dry and shredded. There are things that will never change.That is, a brief outline, Bruce Willis, who gives life to the police detective in New York that, the hand of Jim McTiernan and in 1988, his debut in the big screen with Crystal jungle. Almost 20 years have passed and the man still endures almost as fresh and lozano as the first day, despite his constant references to the inevitable physical weight caused by two decades of seeing their best t-shirts made pieces. The spirit remains the same; even their intentions, because pues entretener entertain is the only goal that has always sought the film series.It is undeniable that the jungle 4.0 distracts and faithful to its constants and the age of the character, commitment to a more classical realization and with fewer digital effects than other more current titles in action. All right here, because Len Wiseman, director, has been able to put aside the technology used for their two Underworlds-without giving up 100% to it - entering in a much more formal and less visually computer style. Computer science, in this case, becomes part of the core plot of the film that, through it, a group of terrorists, captained by a resentful hacker, is prepared to lead, with its network of computers, unsurpassed chaos worldwide. Such is the love of McLane in prehistory, in one particular scene, arriving to ask what noses means the word hacker; a scene from which and taking advantage of the curious presence of Kevin Smith, it pays homage to Clerks and default Star Wars.El big problem of this fourth installment is located in the story that raises, is excessively unlikely in too many aspects. Everything seems very by hairs and some of their most hair-raising passages (as the car desmadre inside a tunnel or walk McLane), due to its excess, caught by the wing of an aircraft offer a zero credibility. Anyway, and following the formal tone of the series, this widespread desmelene just becoming one of its most attractive constants (in the background). The jungle 4.0 has lost claw and force on script refers. This is almost non-existent, while their dialogues and, above all, the comments of McLane everytime he is in danger, sounding forced; almost as forced as the construction makes his apayasado character Justin Long who, collecting the testimony of Samuel l. Jackson in the penultimate jungle, brings to life the accidental partner of Willis. In fact, this chapter is a clear example of how to hold a formula film with minimum effort and, however, to work correctly as a mere hobby and not seek three toes the cat. Jungle there is only one, the first, the genuine and unsurpassed jungle of glass: a model film and the birth of a scoundrel and horny, modeling, hero almost exclusively for the showcasing of Bruce Willis who, fortunately, and throughout his career, has shown that it can do more and better roles outside of his celebrated heroes in action. Later, the series was lengthening is degenerating, but without ever falling into error offer a boring product to leave your audience wanting to distance himself from his more humorous poli and brutote. Precisely and despite its errors, the jungle 4.0 is a compendium of what they have been (and can be) the adventures of the detective as a Christmas Eve lost her shoes and stayed locked in the interior of an ultramodern skyscrapers. Although not establishing anything of what can happen to this type, hardly go one to aburrise. And this is a good guarantee within the coordinates of an action thriller.</body>
</review>
