<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Silent Hill" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You cannot have enough packaging to entertain us for just one hour. The plot is bland and predictable.</summary>
	<body>A long and confusing history based on a classic console games sneaks into the Billboard. Only the youngest may avoid that it sinks into the depths of oblivion, having done real merit to this. To forgive me video game experts to compare Silent Hill with Alone in the dark, although on the record that I am only referring to the film adaptations. As a basic point only be mention that the film starring Christian Slater and Stephen Dorff is rated as one of the 50 worst films of the history. Already in his day we cebamos quite with it, so we highlight some niceties of Silent Hill. Part of the synopsis of the original product but the director (of Crying Freeman and the Pact of the wolves) stretches the situations causing the boredom. In different releases of the game, characters of diverse origin just in the heart of a damn comarca. The screenplay, written by one of those responsible for Pulp Fiction, drink from the same argument until just reconducido by the reiteration of a bland and predictable storyline from minute 40 approximately. It is hard to imagine the huge budget invested in the tape, necessary to recreate an abandoned city and combine sequences real with all kinds of special effects and computer designs. It is perhaps a disbursement to recover in the long term for those responsible not ruled out the idea of starting a series with this title failed. Despite reminiscent of based on legends, including burning of witches, horror film Silent Hill fails to have sufficient packaging to entertain us for just one hour. The problem is that there is more envelope in the form of disturbing atmosphere that content, something that is not allowed in an action film which lasted 127 minutes. Video games and film form a so well avenido marriage as the comic book and the big screen, although the second couple less disappointed. Of the sons of the first, that there have been many (Tomb Raider, Doom, House of dead, Resident evil), I prefer the more gifted: Final Fantasy with the Dr. Aki Ross who gave life an excellent actress Cybernetics.</body>
</review>
