<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Los ojos del mal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mediocre version of already seen too many times: pointless and forgettable, with great moments (the home) and aesthetic of disturbed expensive videoclip.</summary>
	<body>The eyes of evil is not sordid. Nor it establishes strong references to the classic film of the genre and is limited to exploit with Audacity and bombastic advertising apparatus sobada history of body count, i.e. the casual group which is on the site made a mistake at the wrong time and the extraordinarily gifted psychopath to collect corpses. Don't look for the gentle reader characters of depth, compelling reasons to justify the bad milk of the murderer or a secondary story that raises the idea that the writer is sufficiently aware of the noble material moulding. Horror has given glory to the history of cinema, but these times of intellectual distress, public engolosinado with the morbid, sparsely tanning depart mental laziness and demand, what beautiful verb, quality in what you pay and what voluntarily - we assume - assists, which abounds is the fast food film, to which we have already referred once. Fast food burdened by the uncomfortable feeling that the organizers of the roost take the Viewer as a perfect asshole. Does not reach all the blood River in frames of this monstrosity salvageable at times, although inevitably destined to oblivion. The height of the matter is that Dan Madigan, writer of the almost-crappy before us, is officiating and master of ceremonies of the American WWF wrestling, and up is produced by a subsidiary company of a chain in the industry. Then we cannot ask much. The man has been left to carry and has written a blowout Libretto by topics. There is the choral group doomed to extermination, the clueless architect whose mother castradora and disturbed Christianity desconfiguró you the hard drive when it was an infant it is delicate and prometedoramente civic and human. We also find the arsenal predictable scenes gore dazzle more since that the Saw franchise opened again the veda closed by Michael Myers or the series Italian balance of video store Z.The aftertaste teenager has made with the until now little relieved resource to go to some prisoners that rehabilitated an abandoned hotel: slasher with an abundance of twisted scenes sonrojarían Hannibal Lecter in fasting and non-technical effectively whooping the Decalogue of the genre. The choice of the mammoth Kane, born in Madrid, by the way, guarantees the physical tension, but the director, Gregory Dark, formerly fajado in porn films, makes it decay into the half of the tape stretch, losing what is, in my opinion, a major boot. Nothing: a broken illusion. The rest of the footage is boring, seasoned by Agile movements of camera and correct setting - missing over a given managed budgets - and some that another gracieta that disarms the sick in the stomach and painted us a light smile on the cable-stayed face.</body>
</review>
