<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Amor y otros desastres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To my I was afraid to think that the film collapsed by this incredibly bland ability to tell the facts, that totally impersonal photography or many gags (some funny, yes) which is worthless or the penalty laugh for them.</summary>
	<body>Since that the great Notting Hill film was released, the English romantic comedies that have appeared over the years not cease to be (some good, other mediocre) copies of the classic film by Roger Mitchell. The hilarious and very good Love premiered four years ago actually, a choral romantic film which, however, little resembled the already named film. But it is true that this was an exception, as many others, among which is this semi-desastre, love and other disasters, are quite simple. Focusing on the film's Keshishian, say, very briefly, that this film lacks personality, several times of coherence and a cold, distant, rare atmosphere. Since starting, shows a lack of respect to the public, not just show the characters and doesn't have a minimum of respect. And that already it tells us everything. Vale which has some other good time (the end, in the cinema), or some successful notes, but this is certainly a film together failed. And as said before, the topics that come from Notting Hill, whether the streets of London, love trouble, the final race in a small car with the typical English friends, they are all already too usual in this type of film. It is not, nor much less, a Bridget Jones or Curtis film already commented. There are exceptions to every rule in the English romantic comedy. To my I was afraid to think that the film collapsed by this incredibly bland ability to tell the facts, that totally impersonal photography or many gags (some funny, yes) which is worthless or the penalty laugh for them. And what I say of the embarrassing end (never better said)? A bad film, forgotten at the beginning of the opening credits end and with a cast of more bland (Brithany Murphy is still decent). We can say has some fun time and it just not resulting heavy, but that get quite entertaining. But it already is. Hopefully upcoming English comedy show they have something further to tell us and that they not already drink Mitchell film (written, by the way, by Richard Curtis).</body>
</review>
