<review author="Matías Cobo" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not surprisingly, almost nothing, but not bored with his chute of breakneck action.</summary>
	<body>The impact of the first film starring Bruce Willis as John McClane was such in Spain that the replacement of the original English title, Die Hard (hard kill) of the jungle, Crystal has kept in the later sequels. The terms 'jungle' or 'Crystal' had some lace that tape whose action was set in the Nakatomi skyscrapers, while their presence in the titles of the sequels is only due to a mere association with the successful tape of John McTiernan. In any case, the perpetuation of the Spanish title of the first film exemplifies the indelible mark left by one.Since its inception, McClane had many ingredients to make a hole between the most illustrious heroes of action cinema. His ill-fated gift of ubiquity, its rudez and strength to get rid of the villains or its 'sobrao' phrases and chop constitute you as an atypical Hero easily to empathize with the public. Satisfied succeeded the sequels, the leading role of McClane grew at the expense of the arguments of the films, clearly at the service of the reissue of the actions and traits typical of the New York police.In the jungle 4.0 does not change this drift. McClane is presented again as a good COP with a privacy shattered. Divorced and with a daughter declared in absentia, our protagonist does not seem to have much served his heroic service record. Nothing new on previous chapters. But the public already knows his veteran poli instinct tanning in a thousand battles take while to resurface. And does it so in the same way as in previous adventures, catching him suddenly the most inappropriate circumstances.Returns to deal with terrorists, political demands on the sidelines, only pursuing fill pockets hand full. This does not change with respect to previous deliveries. Logically, what Yes change methods of the villains are now facing McClaine. The Spanish title already tells us that envelope something computers and bytes will be this new proposal for action. But there is no better remedy that usual medicine of McClaine against the dominant 'hackers' in cyberspace: the call out left and right. The pistol of this hard poly hastened the sophistication of the terrorist Fronte on some computer screens with that, however, is able to sow greater disasters.Anyway, this fourth installment starring a tricky technique as Len Wiseman not surprised almost nothing, but not bored with his chute of breakneck action. It is the best and the worst that can be said of the fourth installment of this franchise of action led by Bruce Willis.</body>
</review>
