<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cannot conceal my admiration for the film of this man who, with just five films written and directed by him, I believe that it has reached a quick status of author with a film that, although it is not tasteful dish for many, offers always a movie fan passion that breathed by every one of its frames.</summary>
	<body>Death Proof is the underside of the same currency that the Tarantino/Rodriguez tandem has coined as tribute to a film of terror and action that wasted originality and transgression in even conservative film times. With limited budgets and chapucero-artesanales technical solutions, those filmmakers pioneers made the need for virtue and only sought to unleash their gruesome imaginations. Sam Raimi, Wes Craven, Cronenberg, Carpenter or Peter Jackson, among others, were some of the directors that were forged in the school of viscera and blood. Today they all have recognized careers as filmmakers, but its blanks left those misunderstood and marginal tape for its majority contemporary public.If Rodriguez dealt in Planet Terror by referencing the terror 'gore', one of the aspects that the Mexican has shown more lair in initiatory tapes theirs as open until dawn, Tarantino has decided to address his tribute to wild racing movies. Regarding point limit zero or 60 seconds, quoted verbatim in dialogues that Tarantino has been on the lips of his characters, are the basis of cinephiles envelope which supports Death Proof.Pero stays there. Because in Death Proof again appear the arsenal of clichés of his filmography: as long dialogues between colleagues on the most absurd trivia, filming scenes with eagerness to posterity accompanied by excellent songs (the revision to the soundtracks of his films reveal Tarantino as a great 'gourmet' classic American musicals and as a lover of morriconianas scores) and the creation of extreme characters able to move from a State of relaxation another of brutal violence without just worry. And praise without dissimulation I film preferences or to vituperar mercilessly cinema that detests, Tarantino not it hurt in clothing becoming several impudent autohomenajes with nod to tape his own recent as Kill Bill. For example, great is the reappearance of two already mythical characters as ranger Earl McGraw (with the moroseness and impavidez of the great Michael Parks) and his son number 1 (own son of Parks, James Parks). The slow and crude analyses that make the brutal crimes that often face are the best sample of kid humor distilled by the Director of Tennessee.Y Finally, for unconditional Tarantino as who writes this, in Death Proof again to enjoy with interpretaciones-trasunto of the glorious past of big players such as Kurt Russell (who Tarantino loves his early works with Carpenter)(, as Escape from New York or the thing). In addition, and following the traits typical of women in his films, Tarantino returned to create a showcase of various female characters: sexy, strong, chulescos and determined. You could say the replica of Tarantino to the profile of the chica-Almodóvar is of a woman beautiful, with strong appeal sexual, intelligent, and hard and sensitive at a time. The cast of girls-Tarantino in Death Proof, from Rosario Dawson to Vanessa Ferlito, are excellent in their respective roles.In short, I cannot conceal my admiration for the film of this man who, with just five films written and directed by him, I think that it has reached a quick status of author with a film that, although it is not tasteful dish for many, offers always a movie fan passion breathed by every one of its frames.</body>
</review>
