<review author="Berto" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A more than worthy continuation of the adventures of John McLane, who manages to entertain from start to finish, showing us a Bruce Willis that it seems that the years have passed you just Bill widely.</summary>
	<body>John McLane again, and returns to big. This last Friday premiere at last in Spain the fourth installment of the saga Crystal jungle, after being released in the U.S. in late June. For me one of the best sagas as action is concerned, especially its first part an authentic benchmark in action cinema and framework the bases for all the films that came behind. Will it be this quarter at the height of the above? Because if and not, let me explain: first of all it is very difficult to maintain in comparison with the original film, authentic masterpiece and that it has not yet been exceeded since its premiere there by the year 1988. But well, is not so serious, because although the two following sequels are pretty well, being the second to my the more loose in the series, nor reach the quality of the original, although they remain a continuation more than worthy.Analyzing the films in this way, I believe that La jungle 4.0 if that manages to become a worthy continuation of previous deliveries, keeping the level of the third installment, which coincides in various situations, either because this returns to be the scene of the action of the film, an entire city and surpassing slightly the second part, which although entertaining doesn't have the hook that may have these other two. It is true that in this fourth installment the action becomes so spectacular that directly pass to science fiction to defy any law of known physics, although thinking coldly, I do not know any film of the genre of action that is realistic, although if attach less exaggerated than this if there are quite a few. Anyway, follows the general lines of the protagonist in the previous installments, already, jump from a skyscraper hooked to a fire hose, go on the wing of an airplane in full take-off and explode it in full flight or the flow of water rather than drag you you boosting upwards just for the single output are things that already has accomplished in previous installments and nobody says anything about that.What if I drew so much attention is the dubbing in Spain. Do I this film already had seen when his premiere in the US, at the end of June, and because of the rating of minors of 13 that put him in the us the truth that the language of McLane lost integers, since I remember, just drop some shit from time to time and little more?. But the situation in Spain to an adaptation of the script in which McLane becomes radically changed, giving us more witty and poorly spoken in all the previous films together, what is appreciated, as much of the personality lost in the original version is due to his finesse when speaking during the footage.History not be you can highlight much, in this case Bruce Willis has to face a group of software pirates, but that if instead of Hackers would have been a Taliban army, or a Satanic sect had not cared, have would have loaded them all just after leaving a trail of blood throughout the film. That Yes, the action sequences are fairly well spun throughout the film, getting that since the film begins action soars and does not end until the closing credits of the final, something essential and House brand.Actors, the role takes him, of course, Bruce Willis, who returns to show us to a John McLane in full form, and with the physical form which shows throughout the film I think that we have McLane for awhile.You can not say that the wrong function, Timothy Oliphant, very discretito in this film, playing without a doubt worse evil that he has faced in all Bruce Willis saga, and is he dedicates himself to wander among computer screens and put faces to mentally cube roots, which does not help anything to your of if limited character. Justin long, it cannot be said much, really annoying in the development of the film nor hinders it, putting the touch more weak to the film, as opposed to that real Action Man is Bruce Willis.De the side highlight Maggie Q, that this beautiful up pasting is kicked with Willis, and Mary Elizabeth Winstead, with a clavadito character of his film father. The director, Len Wiseman, although do not perform a task too remarkable, being normal in a production of these features, which can get you some successes, especially in terms of what the action scenes refers, showing us always the camera from the best position possible to appreciate in all its magnitude and fixed what is happeningquite appreciated seeing the latest fashion videoclipera record a match to 200 frames per second using 7 cameras at the same time.In short, a more than worthy continuation of the adventures of John McLane, who manages to entertain from start to finish, showing us a Bruce Willis that it seems that the years have passed you just Bill widely and that under the success worldwide with this fourth part, already is this talking about filming the fifth, that if, while maintaining at least this film, please.</body>
</review>
