<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Death Proof" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The segment tarantiniano is confusing, disjointed, repetitive. Because one thing is to do a tribute to the Z series of the 1970s film, and another ruedes as if you didn't no pajolera idea of what the Office of the Director.</summary>
	<body>The second segment of the "Grindhouse" project that comes after "Planet terror" confirms that we we have a nostalgic "revival" in the refocilamiento of their authors, but no, certainly the spectator. East "Death proof" that Quentin Tarantino has filmed with obvious pleasure for its part, but we fear that it has not had the same effect on the public. Man, you can understand that there is a number of people affected by the 70s syndrome USA, that, apart from encanijar the meninges, makes one view with elephant leg pants, look a head of curls impossible, eat burritos petty and drinking tequila as that baby a fanta. One to laugh with prefabricated cuts of the film, the way in which those tapes of prehistory, exhibited "ad nauseam" by infima cinemas were constantly spliced by the projectionist on duty can. Does Quentin, son, but at least give us a fairly decent history? Because it tells us the already not so "enfant terrible" (at least by age, which is already talludito) Yankee film continues to be a memez probably conceived on a trip I do not know if lysergic o after viewing one of Ed Wood, nonsense that tells the unlikely story of a former specialist who like crashing into deslenguadas girls and pulling to profanity, not by the fact to correct them (are we in 2007, to see who dares to correct someone?), but for the good pleasure of moving certain amount of his blood from one part to another of his body, physiological topped issue with certain deliquescent emissions (Yes, I know, is a circumlocution literally hell, but do not ask me to be more clear)(do, that this page also her read children?). But when to the idiot to fuer of sadistic the toebox of the shoe is displayed in the curved forms of three females of weapons take, the hard maybe already is not both? "Death proof", it is true, it is funny in his hubris and folly, as it was "Planet terror", while this being totally Martian had some unlikely rationale that amnesty. However, the segment tarantiniano is confusing, disjointed (and not by the courts of montage "ad hoc", which at times seems a homage to Godard's "To bout de souffle"), iterative, with so much persecution by car which terminates the dizzy Viewer, and is even desmañadamente shot. Because one thing is to do a tribute to the Z series of the 1970s film, and another ruedes as if you didn't no pajolera idea of what the Office of the Director. On the artistic cast, Kurt Russell strives to compose a character in hard for which does not need much: just you the coriaceous face that his many years have given him, aided by some retouching makeup Department. Among them I'll stick with the always wonderful Rosario Dawson, the rising star of Black actresses, which well suits this Mannerist update of the phenomenon "blaixplotation"; but which is eaten with potatoes to the rest of the cast is a new girl (not in the Office, but during the filming), the New Zealand Zoe Bell, from the hard ground of specialists, which is splendid, not only as an actress, but also as double itself; It is good having that be used to break the Randhir instead of others: when you get to do it to you, does not lack anyone you replace?</body>
</review>
