<review author="Rafa Marin" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Len Wiseman (from Underworld and its sequel), self-confessed fan of the series, delivers a quarter, as it stands today the world of action cinema, it almost seems a masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>Live a revival of old and tired heroes, perhaps because Hollywood, meanwhile teenager, so blast and both argument without rhyme or reason has not been able to find characters (or actors) that give the baton to men of action of fifteen or twenty years ago (has said I do not know what top model that same thing happens in your area)Perhaps because Hollywood is beginning to see the Wolf ears and is a good way to attract the cinemas spectators who already comb canas or, as the case of Bruce Willis, a.k.a. John McLane, already not comb them. A lot of years have passed since John McTiernan gave a new interpretation to the hero of the shirt and the blood pouring (in many respects McLane is the baroque of the Renaissance which marked Indy), and it shows not only how the film has evolved or regressed in its grammar, eaten more and more the ground by the strongest arguments and more malleable television characters, but in everything what has fallen as then to human beings. The shadow of 11-S, that is today commemorated by the way, has greatly affected the means of mass communication, and yes I admit that it is not over with the power of the superhero in the world of the comic, as I came to believe six years ago, has that covered a patina inability and even alienation between Nintendo and painful any approach to the theme of the terrorist attacksorganizations in the shade and hardened heroes who win battles themselves when we see that there are battles that cannot win nor the most powerful army in the world. It is the shadow of the 11-S which causes Bond to become more "realistic" and less fanciful, nothing else. We have seen McLane in Los Angeles between airports, and on the streets of New York. Now, recovering some video game heritage, City happens in city as Super Mario could move from screen on screen, greatests are all means of transport that can survive and bleeding. They say that in original version its vocabulary contains enough, but in the dub of Ramón Langa (and recognize that without him for us Bruce Willis is not Bruce Willis) not a hair cut. Director Len Wiseman (from Underworld and its sequel), self-confessed fan of the series, delivers a quarter, as it stands today the world of action cinema, it almost seems a masterpiece. Presents a tired but combative, McLane aged, without family (his ex-wife is in San Francisco, his son does not know anything, and his daughter studies in New York and wants nothing of it; it is not strange to assume that Lucy, that inherits many features of his father, has also had an encontroanazo with MOM Gennero - by what "Jenaro" in Spanish? - and has decided to become independent studying at the other end of the country). Expelled from a desectructurada family, McLane barely has a line of dialogue to acknowledge that his heroic are very distant past, and from their 15 seconds of glory he has returned to his work as normal police not found with cases as glamorous as those who they know. The movie entertains, the computer not annoying sidekick (no, isn't Wesley Crusher, thank God), the piece of paper of Kevin Smith doing the only thing it does not at odds, the bad has the packaging which unfortunately lacks the bad (a Timothy Oliphant (which is much more disturbing to doing "good" in Deadwood than here of bad and also lasts from McLane time not finish say yipikahei). Computer trouble are explained enough that us we create them as well with the condescending sonrisita, and although Mclane not de jure and perjure in Aramaic Yes are some politically incorrect moment (punching Mai Lihn, fix you, settled with a tuft of hairs that boot you to the beast). Interestingly, the perception of authority has changed in this new film. Ill still belong to various European countries, a somewhat xenophobic feature of the previous films that arrived even to emphasize his entrance onstage with the Ode to joy, lest we forget, it is also the anthem of the EU. But this time the terrorist is home, and more House, the very core of the club of the guards. Interestingly, for the terrorists who faces Mclane there never the ideology, but the economic motivation. Also, for the first time, bureaucrats and bosses of the FBI are not presented as a useless calzonazos. There are ups and downs of pace every time that they stop to take a breath (and McLane, at this stage, and it is good that it is, you have to stop to take a breath much) and change of vehicle and give explanations. But it is that a graph and so prodigious as the original movie script is now impossible. The virtuous of the clashes of McLane has been replaced by motorized spectacular. There are a couple of very good times: the fight in the elevator, the persecution watered abandoned cars Highway, and the auction against a F-35.</body>
</review>
