<review author="José A. Peig" title="La jungla de cristal" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A millimeter dash harmonized to perfection in which needless to him nor lacks nothing. A fun action toy that goes beyond genre to tell us a story full of tenderness, irony, good dose of bad milk, homages and cinematic events, and reformulation of clichés.</summary>
	<body>A plane lands, a solo passenger who listens with sorna Council of the traveler that accompanies it from the adjacent seat. Under the jacket hide a revolver. It is a police officer. At the airport he hoped a driver with his name written on a poster. We know that his name is John McClane, has traveled to Los Angeles, and California is his first irony. It is a common man, and seems to guess that it has not come to the right place. Twilight reigns over the city of Los Angeles while the driver does not stop with your questions. McClane is taciturn with strangers, &#8220; confined to lead &#8221;. But the driver insists, and so we know it has wife and children, and that it has come to be reunited with his family on this Christmas night. In previous sequences, we see Holly Gennaro inside a huge building, talking on the phone with her daughter, it asks about dad but Holly doesn't know if they will be able see it tonight. Camera describes a short flat sequence until one of the photographs. There are Holly and her husband, the newly arrived by plane. Out in the great Hall, Mr Takagui encourages its guests a holiday for all high on the eve of Christmas. By the Windows enter the reddish light of dusk. Holly pushes the picture with rage and resentment appears in the story. McClane drops the car, a contrapicado expresses the grandeur of the Nakatomi Plaza building, and its latent threat. Threat in the form of family discussion, or a vehicle approaching with stealth from any part of the city. Regardless of the characteristics of action cinema, a plot twist that occurs in the approach to the narrative (not necessarily in the knot or the outcome) is a laudable dose of dramatic force. Die Hard starts as a family drama starring a citizen foot &#8220; lost &#8221; in a place outside their interests (he prefers New York, but his wife is in Los Angeles), which will have to face old marital squabbles. Suddenly, became embroiled in a desperate struggle against a group of armed men who assail the building and take his wife - and the rest of those present at the party - as a hostage. Films such as &#8220; Rambo &#8221;, &#8220; Rambo &#8221; and similar, so frequent in the Decade of the eighties, products already start demonstrating the preponderance in the story of the violent action, personified in the cliché &#8220; musculitos &#8221; shift, either Sylvester Stallone or Arnold Schwarzenegger. Jungle of glass, on the other hand, proposes to develop the violent action on the basis of an ordinary human being and a framed (marital crisis, voluntary migration) situation in other film genres, namely the melodrama. The violent action is the lever that restores the hero on their marital problems and his role as a police officer. In short, allows you to use the action genre to tell a meaningful and solid story in their dramatic budgets while it reformulates the idea of the &#8220; tough guy &#8221;, and elevates it to the rank of art. John McTiernan directed with effectiveness and passion on the basis of a written script detail and a seamless Assembly work, in which each dialogue, every scene and chaining of scripts, each new element introduced in the development of the adventure will serve as a cornerstone to a conclusion in which all roles converge. Let us not forget that Crystal jungle baby cinema of catastrophes, and narrates a collective drama in which human as a whole is divided into two blocks; those who live the experience from the inside of the building (McClane, terrorist), and those who live it from the outside (police, citizens, press). In this way, the story offers two perspectives, outstanding contribution to narrative dynamic and to the creation of antagonistic, which also gives rise to an ironic game between these two human groups. Note the bias on information from police officers on the reality of the lived circumstances by McClane and the hostages, which contributes to raise the turn of claustrophobic drama: the dissociation between the outside world and what happened in the interior of the Nakatomi building emphasizes the solitude of the hero, and becomes the terrorists the real puppeteers (for example)McClane scene on the roof firing into the air to save the hostages. The us on board the helicopter think that it is killing the hostages. Or that of &#8220; maybe was a depressed broker &#8220;). This reaches the extremes when appear the two FBI agents with the anti-terrorist manual in hand. Each of his actions is a step forward for the intruders; Hans Grubber statement: &#8220; you asked a miracle and I give you the FBI &#8221;. Reading that is outside of what happened in the interior of the building, serves, from purely plot, to justify development of Grubber operation and theirs. For purposes of cinematic texture, creates an ironic tone, a ridicule of the security forces which autoarrogan the role of protectors of the citizen. The schema and structure are designed with the aim of extolling the figure of the unsung hero, a simple police found by chance in the epicenter of the action, the existence of which some even deny. The writers, in his excellent work of writing, not forgot to introduce a link to unite the two separated worlds, and features the character portrayed by Reginald Veljohnson (agent Powell). Within the global catastrophe, the film features a subhistoria in this description of the friendship that emerges between Powell and McClane via auditory communication. A description and development not devoid of sensitivity, since it establishes a spiritual connection and empathy between the two characters: Powell admits the tragedy of his past, and McClane confesses his weakness in its role as spouse and as a human being found in a situation that surpasses. Thus opposition to solitary confinement, the cynicism and the inhumanity prevailing between the two worlds represented in the remaining set Agent Powell and McClane are a cry of hope and fraternity in the midst of chaos. And in the final scene, we see the success of circumscribing the relationship of friendship - hitherto - auditory communication. The look of appreciation and complicity between the two in their first face to face meeting puts the final flourish, and any viewer who has apprehended the sensitive significance of the relationship described earlier, cannot prevent the lump in my throat, especially when Powell releases past trauma to kill Karl (Alexander Godunov) to save the life of McClane and his wife. Attention to underline that the soundtrack of Michael Kamen at the time of the action, and the expression on the face of Veljohnson. THIS IS FILM, GENTLEMEN. The CANON for a good action film requires the presence of a wrong with charisma, and there we have the unforgettable Hans Grubber. If drawing (characterization) of the character is already in itself attractive (cynicism, lack of scruples, sense of humor, engolado language and references to the classics) the charisma of a so prodigious as Alan Rickman actor does the rest. Its antithesis, John McClane, a vulnerable human being facing the tragedy with irony and sense of humor, expressions testosterónicas that relax the tension of the story to draw a smile at any time (&#8220; hear, not fuck me miss, do you think that I am entrusting a pizza? &#8221;, or better still, &#8220; nine million terrorists in the world and I think kill one foot of woman &#8221;). The large handicap of McClane, as a fictional character, is its ability to provoke empathy and connect with the spectator, because of its intrinsic characteristics. The spectator living and suffering from the adventure from the point of view of McClane, hence the absorbent quality of the story. The architecture of the Nakatomi building induces the feeling of claustrophobia from the visual-físico stratum, complementary to the claustrophobic nature, from a purely psychological layer provided by the above-mentioned dissociation between interior and exterior of the building. Tunnels, rooms, corridors, ventilation ducts and elevators, constitute the appropriate setting for the virtuous of a violent action that always moves in the field human and credible. In some moments, the fire and fumes that wrap to McClane evokes the aesthetics of Ridley Scott, Alien or Aliens Cameron testosterónica action. Who doubts that part of the plot and thematic idea of the film is inspired in &#8220; Rambo &#8220;, &#8220; shark &#8221; and &#8220; Alien &#8220;. The death of Grubber deserves special mention, the gesture of McClane after the Resolutive shot - blowing to the mouth of its revolver-evocation of John Wayne (to which the same Grubber had alluded), moment in which the hero acquires almost supernatural stroke, sublimation of its anonymous to move to the area of the film myth, but from his human basenot from the cliché pre-established. The fall of Grubber, the simple thief who is posing as terrorist, induces the last bias. Someone, back down, he said: &#8220; hope it's not a hostage. &#8221; Already with McClane outside the building, and rain a poetic of banknotes that evokes the prolongation of the farce, profiles representatives from each of the unlinked worlds converge to settle scores. In the end, only McClane account, the new hero that synthesizes to John Wayne and Rambo with a touch of simple - not simple - humanity, and who experience lived in the interior of the Nakatomi building has been reason for marital reconciliation (the kiss in the back seat of the car). A final which converges with the home. THAT is telling a story. And it is not a question of taste, but to know the fundamentals of the narration. There are no more words. A millimeter dash harmonized to perfection in which needless to him nor lacks nothing. A fun action toy that goes beyond genre to tell us a story full of tenderness, irony, good dose of bad milk, homages and cinematic events, and reformulation of clichés. A reformulation has not yet found a model that goes beyond. Surprised that a genus so prude as does the action film based on the figure of the &#8220; tough guy &#8221; can offer as much as it offers the masterpiece of John McTiernan. We are dealing with a genuine film miracle, mainly thanks to a script that articulates a variety of themes and structures without this variety hinders the fluidity needed in this type of movies. Current filmmakers (and especially the writers) should take note. Die hard is CANON, the rule and the model to overcome. Every product of action, at the very least, not close to the quality of work (work writing, especially), inventiveness and characterization of characters exhibited in die hard, will be, at least, a mediocre product. Good work and dedication in previous works was not to fall into the complacent anecdote or oblivion, but to be revered and try to transcend (exceed) their achievements. These are the rules for a quality action cinema, although some insist on denying it. </body>
</review>
