<review author="Cp" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very good for the connoisseurs of the previous installments, and much better than the rest of the Billboard of action, for all others. Hopefully after a break we have new Jason Bourne movies.</summary>
	<body>First distinction. There are two types of person watching this movie. Those who saw the first two and which not. For the first film is a continuation of the previous two, and we cannot justify his script is much easier, or at least history not be overly complicated. If we just this film, seems to be simply a Chase at full speed, without just history, and where we do not understand very well by the things that happen. But well, rare will be the audience that goes to see her without having enjoyed the previous.As I have seen the previous two, I liked the movie. I agree that history is no more than an extension of the previous, and almost more an epilogue. Maybe I'm wrong, but it does not give the impression of being an error, but it has been raised so. Obviously, after the great level of previous installments, third weakens a bit in comparison, but even seeing it as a separate film, continues to draw a great advantage to the rest of the tapes of action that we currently have.We again have a realistic and coherent film where the bad guys also think and they are good ideas, and the protagonist is achieving its objectives for so doing even better, or with the help of a little luck. Again, very well directed, and alternate the wildest moments with your camera, others where the more general image allows you to follow the action without any problems. There are who criticizes electric Chamber movements in fighting hand-to-hand, and Yes, I agree that allow that Matt Damon seems much more fast and lethal, but they have already become a brand of films. If Greengrass used these movements also in the shootings and the persecutions of cars, I like nothing, but as a sign of fighting melee, close and brutal, I admit that I love. As actors, again perfectly, although in this case, script shortage leaves us with a bad new that we barely got a glimpse, and that perhaps is the greatest sin of the film. In such stories, the figure of the bad is essential, and the better villain is the Algerian murderer, which does not say a word just, but always draws attention when this on screen. Also reappear other brands in the series such as scenarios in European cities and persecutions of credible cars, although brought to the limit of the possibilities, as well as any other electronic gadget and some trick of Bourne to mislead their pursuers. Finally, I can't help but quote the Matt Damon, that when asked by the Bond films, please do not hesitate to respond, that James Bond would one of the bad guys in the Bourne series, becoming our imagination a cameo of Daniel Craig.En summary, very good for the connoisseurs of the previous installments, and much better than the rest of the Billboard of action, for all others. Hopefully after a break we have new Jason Bourne movies.</body>
</review>
