<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="La hora fría" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good proposal for a fantasy film, which, coming of Spain us adventure, custom Elio Quiroga, something interesting and guidelines which could be marked or continue in the future.</summary>
	<body>I do not know very well by that reason, me I striving in the press pass was completely different elsewhere, so after 15 minutes. waiting in the center of Madrid as a "pazguato" and FRY to SMS to the webmaster of muchocine.net (which is ultimately who allows us to go to these "pass Peacho") have finished learning me (thanks Quetzal) where noses was the pass, so there I was completely delocalised to Madrid, looking like pieces of Spain reach Bravo Murillo in just 15 minutes. (taxiiii!), luckily the great Spain Kiko I was waiting to take me to the movies (blessed who invented the mobile and viva the mother who bore), well, after this stuff than anything has to do with the opinion, but that remains of wonder in this, my blog, we are going to the mess: sincerely I had certain reservations concerning this film, I don't know why whyproduced me the feeling of unease that I produced something so regrettable as "More than a thousand cameras." (now I promise not to prejudge Spanish horror movies) and at the beginning of the film, one hoped that sooner or later are they involved in "flour", which, if the tape has a downside is the slowness with which develop the events and the first initial confusion; Once the presentation of characters and the explanation of the whole plot is much more easy to understand and digest.Interpretive level stress Silke (which this time not teach the breasts), Jorge Casalduero and July Perillán (the latter has kindly come to discuss the film with us just end the projection), is true that Perillán this completely unknown, with a beard, glasses and extremely thin and light years of as he is in person, quite serious and enigmatic Silke and Jorge Casalduero (I've been thinking their similarity of much of the footage) (with Fran Perea), also the young Nadia de Santiago ("Alatriste") other than me I pulled much of the footage trying to know where noses had seen before.Elio Quiroga consists a dark tape, who plays the dismissal with the Viewer, that manages to put the bad feeling in the body almost from the first minute, which uses not the typical topics of always, and where appear from the bugs (brilliantly recreated digitally) to zombies, though neither film is bugs, or zombies, but they are both a mere excuse plot for a tape that just giving you a punch in the stomach of the spectator.I admit, and I have to say with some embarrassment, that expected another kind of end, more light, more than trumpeting, oops, more Hollywood, I found with a finish that partly and as I have already said hits (within the fantasy genre sci-fi) awareness of the patio of armchairs.In short, that I do not want to lengthen too, a good proposal for a fantasy film, which, coming of Spain us adventure, custom Elio Quiroga, something interesting and guidelines which could be marked or continue in the future.</body>
</review>
