<review author="Plissken" title="Death Proof" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excellent new lesson from film of the best American director of the moment.</summary>
	<body>With 'Death Proof', Tarantino does more than (re) influencing their common places from the start: ambiguous, when no delinquents moral characters; action measured sparingly (except 'Kill Bill vol. 1', clear); soundtrack and atmosphere that referred to the 70's, without locating the story in that decade; and most importantly, the flag of his film: the dialogues. Endless, inconsequential, trivial, "cool", bizarre, and of course, essential to understand the characters that trigger them. We know something of Joe Cabot that not reveals its authoritarian anger to 'Reservoir Dogs'? We guess to understand that Jules Winfield forgive life to two half morons thieves if before we not learned of his intention to leave everything? Would the revenge of the bride the same magnitude if soon not hear, own voice of Bill, the reasons which had to destroy his life?The argument of 'Death Proof', true, is summarized in a line: crazy steering wheel stalk incautas young and pursues them until death. This anorexic synopsis allows Tarantino to do what pleases with the Slasher genre, and unlike his colleague Rodriguez avoids clone others regarding the gender. Breaks the initial premise of 'Grindhouse' (at the bottom, first, and in the form below) and Bill almost two hours of references to all the films that he is interested in, but in the way that he likes: through the dialogues. Yes, endless, inconsequential, trivial, "cool", bizarre and essential to understand the characters that trigger them. Can you shorten? Of course. But do is renounce its main feature as an author. Or not the conversation about Madonna at startup 'Reservoir Dogs' can cut and the film "understand perfectly"?With regard to technical level, Tarantino, simply doesn't know to do a vulgar movie. A first part in accordance with the crappy spirit of the project gives way to a second part a lot more stylized, but both leave patent power of the cinematographic vision of the director. And no need for CGI, or epatantes levels from a helicopter. It's start-up scene, use of color and originality of the points of view choose. The persecution of cars is a good example of the visual capacity of of Knoxville, but not the only one in the film. Notable high debut of Tarantino as director of photography.And in regard to actors, Excel a huge Kurt Russell, able to give the two sides of his character without problems, and the almost-rookie Zoe Bell, double for Uma Thurman in 'Kill Bill' action; both give a tremendous charisma to his characters at key moments, not easy mission by contradictory nature (and pathetic moments) by fierce competition from the rest of females of the second and the first. Very large, also, the as usual Michael and James Parks in a small but important role, because with its funny dialogue (again the dialogue) allow Tarantino return to rethink the exciting game that has been proposed from the outset, but with new cards and close the main plot of the film.And I know that many it seem empty, and many seem an autohomenaje, and many others that Tarantino is no longer what it was. I left excited about film, humming the song credits, laughing at me still the excellent end, agreeing the dance of Vanessa Ferlito, trying to retain all those details that I still liking this guy film. Mainly, the dialogues.Excellent new lesson from film of the best American director of the moment. a 9'5.</body>
</review>
