<review author="Naty Buqué" title="El perfume" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film adapts very well Süskind novel in several ways. It is a very successful film without being - or try to be - revolutionary or even rupture, and excellent aesthetic care.</summary>
	<body>If the perfume, Tom Twykwer, fails to be a great movie to my taste, (because of eccentricities, rants, something to really draw attention to in the narrative level and the fall in some other cliché in the script - that did not appear in the novel-; certain setting errors that occasionally bothered), would get annoying and pettifogging if not assume that it is a 1-very successful film(((, without being - or try to be so - revolutionary and even rupture, 2-excellent in aesthetic care, above all in what it does to a) camera, b) election and characterization of actors and c) choice / creation of locations - even at this level if, as I said, some that another error.1-the film very adaptable Süskind novel in several ways. Firstly, the voiceover adds, moves and deepens the story without becoming unbearably recurrent and abusive. The Narrator, on the other hand, does a great job. Secondly, times are very well measured, and the film, covering a period of time and a series of very large incidents, never bored, never rushing, never lacks or enough you information. Thirdly, there is a great deal of respect but not blind, dogmatic for the novel, which is faithfully followed, with the necessary changes for optimum adaptation to the screen (and fidelity I am only interested in the level of ethics and not the reproduction of everything that happens, clear). What is important, I think, is not betray what says the work, or, do, do so explicitly. ((The novel, in this sense, no appeals to a negative moral evaluation of the murderer, and that seems to me that it is respected in the adaptation).2-a) beyond the beauty of certain levels and, above all, of certain camera moves, there is a very interesting use of the same (parallel to the use of certain literary resources on the novel)((, what is eloquent about the success of the adaptation): the camera as subjective, but in this case, not reproducing what the character sees but transforming, as in a delirium sinestésico, what it smells like in image b) another success in an adaptation not stupidly tied to the original: the protagonist of Süskind is ugly, horrible, deformed and disgusting. The film, without being a beauty, it is a normal guy - up with some attractive-, except for a slight limp when walking. It is true that this is a step backwards in the inquiry that makes the text about the beauty, but however, it seems to say the film that Grenouille anyway is ugly because it is poor. And that is also interesting. Por_otro_lado, the beauty of the girls is also very well achieved: without being perfect, have a particular beauty, hypnotic. c) the House of the perfumer in the middle of the bridge and the popular market levels are fa-bu-lo-sos (errors, today we are good, better not to mention).And add another point, perhaps not on the film but as proof of the excellent aesthetic care of the film: the posters. Very different each other, all beautiful, are also a great - and laudable, because nothing have to do with ideological hegemony or economic domain - marketing tactic.</body>
</review>
