<review author="Naty Buqué" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In short, I believe that the film was successful. But of course, I am not who to determine. I am like a woman talking about football. Non--listen to me.</summary>
	<body>Well, as one of the few people no-fanáticas of the series who already saw the movie (as well as fans children's parents, but do not count), I am in a privileged position to say some things it above a radically subjective cloak of fanaticism.Firstly, I do not know what expect fans of a film series. A longer chapter, a more closed structure, some a little more transcendent fact, the limitation of the chistes-códigos, as sectarian, which always leave me out. And nothing more. Expected that Homer had in the film some transcendental truth that exposing to the world, were it acting course irrationally due to fanaticism. And they will be left disappointed.I think that the appeal to a different audience in the film than in the series clearly. A wider audience, not necessarily following the series, most children of a time. This is seen especially in quotations and allusions to the real world - action characteristic of the series if any-, which are in the film much more accessible than in the series. In this last swarm American characters maybe not so known out quotations from films more or less worship, etc. In the film are Spiderman, Harry Potter, Tom Hanks, Green Day, Titanic. The difference is clear.An aggregate to the obvious change of the series for the film was the constant reference and allusion to the film as such. Not only through the use of certain cinematic clichés but through explicit jokes, from the mouth of the characters. I thought it was an interesting and above all reliable resource as soon as he became auto-parodia.Finally, I believe that there was a good dose of transcendence in the film for the series. Breakdown of things in the TV series always stayed the same, I say. A surprise effect well implemented and measured. I will not give you examples to not say that Bruce Willis is dead.In short, I believe that the film was successful. But of course, I am not who to determine. I am like a woman talking about football. Non--listen to me.</body>
</review>
