<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El Club de los Suicidas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another worthy but failed sitcom the many coming to us each year. That Yes, I think that posts to see a failed comedy is better to see one made in Spain than one made in the USA, although only for supporting our industry.</summary>
	<body>Despite being one of the more complicated to deal with and that few times ago, comedy remains one of the most common film genres in our cinemas.This time the proposal comes from Spain and comes signed by Roberto Santiago (&#8221; happy men &#8220;, &#8220; the longest penalty in the world &#8220;) on a script written by him along with Juan Vicente Pozuelo and Curro Royo.Por unfortunately, not on this occasion the result is satisfactory.The plot premise of &#8220; club of suicide &#8221; is the most interesting, although credit should be attributed to Robert Louis Stevenson, author of the &#8220; self-titled debut collection of short stories &#8221; from which the writers extracted the central idea: a group of people without value to commit suicide decided to found a club that play every week who is who kills another Member and who is that dies.One of the problems is that the film does not end exploit the comic possibilities of such a premise, focusing more on making this kind of jokes &#8220; style comedy television &#8221;, which unfortunately fashion are in our cinema. In fact, does not end define openly as a comedy &#8220; of the of stalks are &#8221; and, occasionally, opt for a darker tone that not curdled altogether.The result produces a clear mismatch between the comic moments and the dramatic addition, nor are so comical or as dramatic as it would be desirable.The players trying to save the function but just do. Fernando Tejero, possibly capable of larger companies, needs a change of urgent registration because I see pigeonholing forever in the same role while making Lucía Jiménez, again, of morbidly attractive woman which, in his case, has no excessive merit.Ultimately another worthy but failed comedy of many coming to us each year. That Yes, I think that posts to see a failed comedy is better to see one made in Spain than one made in the USA, although only for supporting our industry.</body>
</review>
