<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="La hora fría" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I try to be benevolent and look for the positive aspects of &#8216; the cold hour &#8217;. However, find none, except in any case, the laudable intention of making film genre in Spain.</summary>
	<body>The only thing that has given me this film fear, that it opens Friday 14, is thinking that I will receive after my negative criticism, with the well that has been of Elio Quiroga in this blog. Why try to be benevolent and look for the positive aspects of &#8216; the cold hour &#8217;. However, find none, except in any case, the laudable intention of making film genre in Spain. A more suitable approach for a short film for a long shows how living a few people after a chemical warfare. The protagonist, Jesus, a boy of eight years, presents all his companions in exile while recording with a camera video moments of his confinement. The death of a chicken indicates that it will occur at night, a cold hour, which will have to lock in their rooms to which &#8220; the invisible &#8221; not attack them. When we almost half film arises the need to go to a store to pick up food and medicines. And there for the first time shows a threat: &#8220; strangers &#8221;. It's beings that function as a chemical weapon because they are infected and can infect someone healthy with just touch it. Much later, outsiders will have to be removed because the protagonists discover that they are approaching too the place they inhabit.It seems he had summarized the argument with bad idea, making it sounds ridiculous to purpose. But it is not. During the greater part of the footage nothing happens. It is not that we find ourselves in a conflict derived from the own situation of forced survival, that might be good, but there is no conflict. Because strangers can attack them only if refugees violate certain rules and to hide from the invisible is so easy, there is nothing to fear until the final moment. And everything we see are sequences about the everyday life of these survivors. The time could be detained and could even build a film without twists in which envolviese us an atmosphere of panic or distress of an imminent end of the world. However, it is not the case and none of the scenes gives the slightest fear. It would and could alter the order in which the sequences are mounted the same, which means that nothing that takes us to the next and that everything happens there is because Yes, as for example, sudden changes in the psychology of the characters.Everything is attached with thread in &#8216; the cold hour &#8217;. One thing is not to justify the sources of fear, that already today it is accepted in many films, especially if they are Asian. Quite another to include numerous dialogues in which explain these origins, but pass through them are treated as stepping on eggs to not risk to mess up if something deepens. In addition, the tricks for dosage information-not tell everything to the viewer of coup, but little by little, are too brazen. A very shallow approach, at the same time, it is believed deep and as a sign of pretentiousness, biblical names puts them to the characters: Peter, Paul, Lucas, Maria Magdalena, Jesus, Judas, Saulo, etc &#8230; along with the weak script, the worst aspects of the film are interpretations. Not be go naming one by one to the actors and actresses who do bad, removing children and adolescents, are very evenly matched, at which one worse than another. Silke, Pablo Scola, July Perillán, Pepo Oliva, Omar Muñoz, Jorge Casalduero, Nadia de Santiago, Marco González, Carola Manzanares &#8230; are some of their names.The aesthetics are perhaps the most visible of all. It is likely that readers, if they are very fond of terror, appreciate something the film, due to the lights and shadows of his photography. But Quiroga not only fails the script and the direction of actors. As a filmmaker nor cannot ignore you some things. The few action scenes that are shot with a surprising lack of pace and verve. The author is more attentive to transitions that look that narrate, inter alia because there is nothing to tell. With the steady-cam try to give packaging that has no, but these movements of the camera, in addition to being clumsy, don't fit fluently with formal decisions generic, closer to the own of the shorts that aspect of any feature.It is true that the budget of the film may have been low, but is not obstacle for best results in facets, such as the script and acting work, which I have mentioned. Other technical aspects are poor. Although the film is Spanish and has shot with live sound, there's always fragments that it is necessary to bend because the voices were not taken with the right conditions. However, bent parts are out of sync. There are Z series films which are very bad and that is precisely why you can enjoy for a laugh. Occasionally I've confessed that I have seen more than one of Uwe Boll with that intention. But &#8216; the cold hour &#8217; &#8212; on that link you can see trailers and more information &#8212; not even brings these minutes of morbid joy. It becomes long despite not being and bore up to the pointer. If it were something better, would talk about what little original which is his starting point, for the amount of similar films &#8212; as &#8216; the thing &#8217; Carpenter &#8212; that exist. But hopefully this would be the only bad thing the second film by Elio Quiroga after &#8216; photos &#8217;.</body>
</review>
