<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is clearly the worst of the three adventures but this is not, or should not, no surprise.</summary>
	<body>This is one of those projects that have never interested me too much. The huge opportunities lost as a result by previous deliveries had removed any possible interest in seeing how remataban slaughter.If above, we add the terrible criticism, even from fans of the previous chapters, we have the causes of my tardiness in pay the entrance fee to see the film. But at the end, I decided to. &#8220; Caribbean Pirates: at the end of the world &#8221; is clearly the worst of the three adventures but this is not, or should not, no surprise. Because, at the risk of repeating myself, I have to say that it has the same defects and the same virtues than its predecessors. The problem is that defects appear here more accentuated and the virtues are less noticeable.Continues to be Johnny Depp the best function although her character begins to be somewhat tiresome at times. To such an extent they knew those responsible without Depp there is no film that, despite how it ended the previous delivery, does not take nor a sigh to appear on it. The rest of the characters are mere comparsas and painful to see how wasted actors such as Geoffrey Rush, Jonathan Pryce and Stellan Skarsgård. the script remains almost non-existent, with fairly empty dialogues and even ridiculous; a mere excuse to create situations that require visual effects, that itself, spectacular. Not stories finish well off, disappearing characters without saying or m3u and it gives us one of the endings more tontitos recent history. And that if one gets to see the credits at the end, which I always do, but those who have stayed only to see that scene have since emerged from the room with a monumental anger.Again the confusion between dramatic and spectacular is the Queen of the function. And it is because, in reality, the tape does not have too many scenes of action, adventure or drama or comedy &#8230; its great merit is that, not offering virtually nothing, get that their two hours and three quarters is not excessively long. But that is a very small achievement for a film that was intended to be much, much more.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 4 out of 10.</body>
</review>
