<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Shrek Tercero" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is the strongest points of the previous entries, where the tape does not stand the comparison with its predecessors.</summary>
	<body>Again premiered a sequel, again, is one-third of a successful franchise and new criticisms have been unanimously negative.Against this background went to the cinema to see her, thinking that it might not be true that this year all (or almost) released sequels were so disappointing. Again I was wrong.It cannot be said that &#8220; third Shrek &#8221; is bad because it would be a lie or exaggeration. But with two great films on their backs (&#8221; Shrek &#8221; and &#8220; Shrek 2 &#8221; without me looking like great seem to me very good) one hopes to keep the quality in the script, grace and rhythm. But it is precisely there, the strongest points of the previous entries, where the tape does not stand the comparison with its predecessors.To give a few examples, I would say that trying that with a couple of intimate scenes with Arthur, Shrek discovers his paternal instinct is something ridiculous and bad thing is that it shows too. In addition, force of wanting two actions parallel (the adventures of Shrek and Fiona) both just for not having enough entity as to engage the Viewer. I fear that this is due to a working inexplicably little (or bad) script.Nor the rhythm is right for hooking, and sometimes indeed cansino (the beginning and everything that happens in the University City). Despite this, get back something the flight and it just proving entretenidilla (although by the hairs).Perhaps ballast in excess by the absence of rhythm and a good script, what more is missing in this installment is the spark. This subversive grace became famous and that has created some school, has totally lost and, although I don't believe they make me case, I do not think that it is time to throw the bolt to the series.And it is the excessive repetition of elements that make a play, original just eliminating the originality and the ability of subversion that gave it its value. A lesson in Hollywood do not stop learning.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 5 out of 10</body>
</review>
