<review author="Dragon negro" title="Los ojos del mal" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a great film it, or anything that will renew the genre, but if that uses patterns of this to at least do something with a bit of face and eyes, on all eyes.</summary>
	<body>A group of young offenders will be part of a new collaborative project between reformatories to gather a group of boys and girls for a few days in the sanitation of an old hotel. For kids it is an opportunity to do something different and leave the prison a few days, but guardian monitor them are a time bomb that can explode at any time. But what no one expects is that in the old hotel is found a strange man that will make your stay becomes a nightmare, a man whose past is closely linked to the guard.Juvenile horror is a genre that ago long time is spent and with a clear lack of new ideas and innovation, and is limited to repeat patterns again and again changing the environment, the murderer and their weapons, and offering us a series of deaths always predictable and in the best of cases, something original and showy. At most that qualifies a film of these features is to have a notable achievement, have a backstory interesting enough so that what is happening on the screen will have something of interest and is not just a mere succession of death, and that her murderer is something original minimally and is minimally defined.The eyes of evil has the previous factors that make an horror film youth pass to be directly bad to be something fun and entertaining to see without much further. Her killer has an imposing presence, technical Bill is well resolved, and despite the fact that during average film we think that everything that happens is caught by the hair, at the end everything seems to have a reason of happen. It is not a great movie this, or anything that will renew the genre, but if that uses patterns of this to at least do something with a bit of face and eyes, especially eyes.</body>
</review>
