<review author="Plissken" title="La extraña que hay en tí" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Failed history of revenge, with a pair of joke notable and not a few moments. And again, quite boring.</summary>
	<body>Already 30 years of the Spain of 'Taxi Driver', the movie premiere that he put on the map to Jodie Foster. Now, it is Iris who plays to righteous overnight in New York of the 21st century, and not his "beloved" Travis Bickle. Ironies of fate. 'The Brave One' ('The strange there is en TI' will be called around here) tells the story of Erica Bain, radio announcer to the "green dog" in the Big Apple that is dragged to a vendetta against the worms that live in it. But now their main enemy is not the offender, but the law, personified in the detective Mercer, a relentless police struggling to overcome her divorce. Good, and catch the night watchman, also.Irregular Neil Jordan launches to go with ex officio and little more it seems an adult review of the popular righteous saga of Charles Bronson. The typical situation of the character that crosses the line unfolds with the traumas it brings such tremendous decision in a normal and ordinary, citizen trying to convince us that all we can happen the same. But to do so, 'The strange there is en TI' uses all topics of this type of film: everything is evil around Erica, their executions are never unjustified; Police officers, although they want to capture the murderer, in the background are happy someone clean the streets; the righteous is never betrayed by victims who rescues. and clear, realistic proposal of Jordan just resembling, and too much, this jewel of ochentera dandruff of video store called 'Angel 2' or the above-mentioned films of Bronson. Because if this is a reflection on the (in) therapeutic usefulness of revenge, you left this incredibly orthopedic end. And if it is an exaltation of the same, prefer to Paul Kersey with a missile before that to Erica Bain with a 9 mm.The technical aspect, that Yes, it is well maintained. Photography Philippe Rousselot is dark enough (not blue) and realistic to immerse ourselves in the progressive collapse of the protagonist. For my taste they emphasize too much the mental instability of the speaker with these swinging movements of camera, but that said, matter of taste.And as it is normal in a film produced by Jodie Foster, she is the main attraction of the film. It seems that he intends to seek another oscar via 'Accused', and at times (his stories on the radio and some moments) shines. But the transformation of his character does much harm to their interpretation: trembling apprentice killer goes to Mrs. Majestik (including lapidary phrases) in only a handful of assassinations, and takes away much, but a lot of credibility to the tortured announcer. Other, with a correct Terrence Howard at the helm, are just that, others. Well, it must mention Naveen Andrews, which in only a film has become sensitive and exotic lover of scientific cortapelotas (Planet Terror).Finally, failed history of revenge, with a pair of joke notable and not a few moments. And again, quite boring. A 4.</body>
</review>
