<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El último tango en París" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Classic film that I have not heard of it will, but that leaves Marlon Brando before inflating like a toad and a well loaded mat moza. Found me a suckling pig of grade 8.</summary>
	<body>This is the typical movie that most people have not seen, but that sounds us a series of frames that have been in the history of cinema. Has who not seen Marlon Brando take butter for repasár are out there to the girl? Or the scene of the bathroom with mat included in which spinning Marlon with her on top? I could say any more, but all are sexual, is that we have the ages of Lulu to the American? I prefer ours, that at least I learned what was going.The film is about a girl who goes walking through Paris and crosses with a type that is clarea carton, and must take you a hundred years. Total, to the two frames are again to rent the same. And typically, for thee, for me, Pumbaa (which would say my baby) are already quilando as monkeys at the zoo. And she begins a relationship of submission between Marlon Brando and the young lady, takes us through a script which I did not understand anything. Luckily out numerous nudes.Direis, the Titus does not know more to do in the movies to the aunts in pelotas and is capable of tarnish to the classics considered works of art. That is true, but it is the girl hit a few yawns than rieté your Leon of the Metro. I can not criticize, that I have not enteradod and that goes. I think a sequence of situations, around a type weird, weird, weird (I say the deceased papuchi) but that I don't see the link between them. So if you have a series of sequences that have been to to the collective film retina.In short, classic film that I have not heard that it will, but get Marlon Brando before inflating like a toad and a well loaded mat moza. Found me a suckling pig degree 8.Me stayed with that face fool when all is laugh at a joke and you do not you've heard.kisses.</body>
</review>
