<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Un Corazón Invencible" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An invincible heart is a film whose only reason being is the showcasing of Angelina Jolie, and not even reach that goal</summary>
	<body>Make a film based or inspired by a historical event always has its risk, mainly the controversy may cause if it is reliable or not. This applies especially to the films based on historical facts more important and longstanding. But Hollywood also leads to the big screen most recent real life stories, some of them recorded in the memory of the people, which must overcome a serious handicap: the public known in advance to the final.An invincible heart narrates the kidnapping of an American journalist in Pakistan in 2002, and does so through his wife (which by the way has provided its unconditional support to the film). It is a terrible indeed, but unfortunately in the world are kidnapped and murdered dozens of journalists per year, which is why the Daniel Pearl case isn't very remembered outside United States. Has then, why from the international distribution of the film was he stressed both emphasize the fateful outcome of the kidnapping? Leaving aside such digressions, it is difficult to recognize in A heart invincible so provocative as Michael Winterbottom film. It is not that it is Saint of our devotion, but it would have been very thank that this story would have addressed a very unconventional look like yours. Instead, the film is not more than a mere vulgar police investigation with the family drama as a backdrop. In the film is foreshadow the serious conflicts that led to the tragedy, but fails to deepen them. The reason that this story has come to the big screen is that it would provide a great opportunity for showcasing its protagonist, but not even that is achieved. Angelina Jolie does a good job, without fanfare, but neither is that his character has shades, depth, or emotional or dramatic development.An invincible heart is a film whose only reason being is the showcasing of Angelina Jolie, and even reaches that goal. The rest is simply a more disguised as historical complaint film police story</body>
</review>
