<review author="Alex Largo" title="La vida de los otros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>No one will deny that it is not a "great" director, because, in addition to its height, the German should recognize the undeniable merit of having written and directed this small wonder.</summary>
	<body>Fair winner of the award for best film at the European film awards but unjust (in my opinion) Oscar winner for best foreign film. For me, the fair winner in this category was the film by Guillermo del Toro, who had to settle for carrying three Oscars of the 6 that played.Let us continue with this German film whose director is about two meters. No one will deny that it is not a "great" director, because, in addition to its height, German (Florian Henckel von Donnersmarck) should recognize the undeniable merit of having written and directed this small wonder. And in one way rather than outstanding.The film does not have any conjugation defect. Moreover, few things are can be blamed on this film, very few. One of them, and perhaps, that more plays against is the lack of pace.Don't get me wrong, the film never is guilty of being boring, but his pace lapses at times making it appear heavy, I repeat: think.Otherwise the film is an exercise worthy of praise in all or almost all fields. From a magnificent script to some more excellent performances. In fact, the work of Ulrich Mühe and Martina Gedeck have been very winning in a multitude of contests. Although that does not mean not to be the work of all the staff side more than remarkable.Perhaps one somewhat disappointment aspects of the tape is the music composed to two hands Gabriel Yared &amp; Stéphane Moucha. And precisely for having the name of Yared, it is already disappointing. I expected more from composer of their stature, and all I find is with a simplistic music, not bad, but that seems more accompaniment than anything else. Not enhances the images, not it gives them more forces, simply avoids that we will not hear the silence sometimes.Usually a great film, worthy of Grands Prix, but which, in my view, does not exceed in quality to "El laberinto del Fauno".</body>
</review>
