<review author="Plissken" title="Caótica Ana" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Medem discovers his letters to the end and confirms that both formal chaos hides a childish simplicity in speech.</summary>
	<body>The people will and ripping the robes with 'Caótica Ana', the new film by Julio Medem, the poet of the Spanish film, the King of the Palindrome. That if unrecognizable, that if chabacano, that if disjointed, which if absent sense. I don't know what is so surprised. It seems to me, 'Caótica Ana' the natural evolution of its film bet, which although it has moments that I liked ('pelota', something of 'Land'; I have pending 'Lovers of the Arctic circle'), mostly seems already worthy of the same apítetos engaged you now so happily. Me I bored a bit with 'Earth', I much bored with 'Sex and Lucia', because now I I'm bored a lot with 'Caótica Ana'.Initially conceived as a tribute to his sister, painter who died in car accident, 'Caótica Ana' has the initiatory journey of Ana, a young painter which is carried to the city by a patron (do?) and discover love, sex and a vast amount of lives (and deaths) of young women in the depths of your psyche. Open the doors to these women will mark its destiny as mother of the Hombres Buenos, able to challenge the powerful lords of the Guerra. There is that.Since very soon, Medem has started to use symbolism to a server catches the first: the Falcon and the Dove, Cave and light, del mar as uterus, doors. all that stylish between naturalist and pedantic that often permeate to the characters of the director. Later, the thing gets worse: the portrait of the young prodigies of the school hippiesca where he studied Ana (more than acceptable Manuela Vellès) is frivolous and away from the reality in the extreme (do patron? here is patron?). The secondary characters, little more than stereotypes with legs: the Arab artist young tortured/súperdotado; amigaza odiahombres (normalita baby); the "provocative" performancer; Gay full task. gives all such creeps that appears to be last of the director intended to criticize this superfluous scene in which allegedly involved his deceased sister. Often tribute.Then comes the supernatural plot development: Ana discovers, accidentally and in the presence of a famous hipnotizadora, one of their previous "lives" and decide it is best for her to hypnotize her to find out more. The task falls to a young disciple of the hipnotizadora, an American who speaks as the blond of los Morancos. In full hipnotizadora work, Ana feel the impulse to break with everything, and suddenly (literally), is located on a ship bound for New York, where culminates its search in a grotesque scene that hides all who actually cares tell Medem: "I shit in the USA". And they say that Tarantino is empty.Of course, there are plenty references to the 11-S (with metaphorical plane of the destroyed twin towers included), because it is set in 2001, nor the war of Iraq, or the Western Sahara conflict (blame also the States). Medem discovers his letters to the end and confirms that both formal chaos hides a childish simplicity in speech. But at that point, the truth is that the vital journey of Ana I mattered little.Technically, Medem is capable of mixing powerful images visually (the "flashbacks" of Ana, tables) with the tacky look of digital video of low-end, something which has also recently made David Lynch. The difference between the two is that Lynch builds an atmosphere thanks to such material, and Medem jumps from form in format, without more.For little else gives this 'Caótica Ana', one of the most high-profile slips of recent Spanish cinema. I, for my part, hope that Medem is able to someday make a movie to someone rather than for himself. A 2.</body>
</review>
