<review author="Naty Buqué" title="El libro negro" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Black Book avoids Manichaeism implicated in many nazis with face of serial killers and a full of blessed resistance without difficulty, but brings this possibility to a mere surprise effect.</summary>
	<body>Do Black book,? inspired by real facts? (sic), follows the story of a Jewish Dutch (very nice, by the way) in the (endless) vicissitudes suffered during World War II, and beyond.In reality, what is said vicissitudes, not. Aristotle defines the Peripeteia as change of luck or situation of the characters, that fortune passed to misfortune or vice versa. In this case, everything that happens to our protagonist is moving from misfortune to the very same shit, and the very same shit to shit worse. And so many times more of what the Viewer is predisposed to see, in a film that does not understand what a blow low or how to avoid it (at times felt outrage that I undertook more or less by the second hour of against wind and tide, when the poor emily watson, the good woman of the universe)(, not only she was raped six times, he believes that her husband is dead, they treat it crazy, throw you stones, the priest accuses her of a bitch, but that also kill her seconds before that I could find that her husband was indeed alive and avoid his own death).(Turning) Black Book avoids Manichaeism implicated in many nazis with face of serial killers and a resistance full of Saints fallen on Earth without difficulty. But instead of that possibility carried an interesting reflection on the war, populism, charismatic leaders, fascism, biopolitics, the aestheticisation of politics, the place of women during the war, or any, but anything, the film becomes a banal film of suspense and mystery, of those that 10 minutes before the end to tell you who was the real killer (obviously)(which one least imagined). Black book is constructed as nine Queens or Scream. And the bad guys aren't necessarily Nazi, but have face of evil at the time reveal as such. In short, avoiding the obvious that the nazis are bad for a surprise effect.On the other hand, the film is a clear example of the typical structure yankeehollywood of historical movies where the plot depends on a grupete of protagonists, and the happy or sad, end of their respective destinations. And where course, such a fate should represent to some extent the fate of the people or social group to which the group belongs in fiction. I.e., in a film about World War II (where the doxa says that the good are allies) and the protagonists are a group of Jews or opponents of Hitler, the protagonist is most likely save, but will have to make many friends and family dead, because we all know that many Jews were killed in this conflict. Namely, the end, although the protagonist to be saved, it cannot be entirely happy, because it would be unethical. As in all film hollywood, even knowing that effectively killed thousands and thousands of people, our interest lies in our protagonists to be saved, and if that happens we stayed quiet. But as our protagonistan are the replacements of an entire social group, their destiny must represent to some extent to it. And if they represent Jews, we know that there will be blood. And incidentally, our social concern is transformed into one individual. I know all of these were killed but the cute blonde is saved (or not) and that is what matters.On the more technical side, should have warned the director that the music of Robocop is last fashion, and which is also not good put it in all the action of the film scenes. And to the inverosimilitudes to the hard to kill, where chance becomes almost magic, in a historical film, do not close at all (only reflection that opens the film I think that it is "Someone can have so much but so much bad luck?"). And when someone Unveils be bad you don't have to put face of Hannibal Lecter. And that corpses cremated in the foreground to begin a conclusive scene, relaxed, descenlace post climax, is not necessary (and unethical aesthetically).</body>
</review>
