<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Wolf Creek" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Healthy renewal of the genre of teen horror with psychopath.</summary>
	<body>There are disturbed behaviors that matrimonian well with true cinema commercial temperament, film that favors the theatrical to the austere or sensible approach. Wolf creek is the archetypal investment of this rule and leads its plot between the postal to the National Geographic, the Dogma of Lars Von Trier and, of course, its syncopated final, the pure slasher, that body count of adolescent resonances here allowing contaminated by a renewed perspective. The directorial debut of Australian Greg McLean dismantles the schematic pattern of similar budget films tromba and poses a more than decent study of characters and a verisimilitude that surprises, unexpected, when it expects a view uneasy poster, is a massacre, one of those modern entertainments that exploit the morbid and erected the truculence as most striking claim.The script of the own McLean offers nothing new: everything is already more than seen. This is what we have written many times, but what is surprising and what rings this film special is the ability of its author to maintain some kind of balance that only is altered with the predictable, necessary and attractive side final, rigorous and heir to all the heritage aesthetic lighting by Boorman, Hopper or Craven, founding masters of the genre.The Australian landscape incorporates a progressively hostile props, influencing many of the sensations caused by the development of the plot, but not to the way in which Aja uses in the hills have eyes. Here the naturalism has an interested delinquency, an accomplice of the leisurely tour of the script. McLean obvious the offal and mounts a worthy, new product in that it is impossible to be entirely, but higher than the infamous flood of juvenile horror films, reventonas of meat, mostly always satisfactory numbers of "hot" scenes where the psycho turn desmembra personnel and stored in a basement the viscera as hunting trophies.</body>
</review>
