<review author="Caty" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is a brutal experience after a seemingly serene first half an hour that does not give rest to the nerves of the Viewer</summary>
	<body>The remakes, especially in horror movies, are the order of the day in the Mecca of cinema, some better adapted, other worse. We have to take into account that in the seventh art, and especially in this genus, all, absolutely everything is invented, so all we have left is know playing with the elements that already specifics and make something really "visible". We saw in his day for example with productions as "Dawn of the dead" How can return to bring an idea to the big screen with enough dignity to the original, as well as to my opinion happens to this "the hills have eyes" remake of the production of the well-known Wes Craven(con_detractores_y_defensores_a_partes_iguales)creator of sagas as Scream or nightmare on Elm Street.La story is told the journey of a family vacation, at one point in the journey, will lead to a desert area that previously had been a Government nuclear test area."After an accident with the car that leaves them momentarily abandoned in place, realize immediately which, despite the apparent vastness depopulated land they observe, after those stones, after those hills, live"something", or"someone".""The hills have eyes" is a brutal experience after an apparently first serena half an hour that does not give rest to the nerves of the Viewer. Not revolutionizes the horror film, that is more clear, but it is an injection for that part of the genre we like many of terror sordid without scares sweetened for the teenage audience, but with the brutality that entails the fact survive to a / a pursuer is serving not reasons.The fluidity of the direction, incredible photography and sharing that, despite consist of names not very mediáticos(quizás_el_más_en_boga_hoy_en_día_sea_el_de_Emilie_de_Ravin,_Claire_en_la_famosa_serie_"Perdidos") know slipping into an argument - with critical social included - where the adrenaline and the feeling of claustrophobia carried some results more than correct. When I left the room, I stayed with the same feeling that in his day when I saw "Kilometre 666": he hoped to find me a 15 pigswill and left with the pleasant feeling of having attended as usual, but with a way to combine the "clichés" as sufficiently well as to make it fun and intriguing. Again I repeat: do not expect to find anything original, but if you like the genre you pasaréis entretenidísimo awhile.</body>
</review>
