<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Wolf Creek" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A wonder of terror that will delight all those who they love to eat the nails of pure nervousness. What take advantage! I, for if the flies, don't think tourism go to Australia..., at least until that forget this film.</summary>
	<body>Despite being an exemplary film in the horror film it is concerned, the Australian Wolf Creek reaches Spain with a couple of years too late. It translates Dante adventure experienced by three youths during a summer vacation in Australia. Two British girls and a young man from the country who, on Board of a second hand car, straightest in the most inhospitable places of the land of kangaroos with the intention of admiring the beauty of its atypical landscapes. But a stranger. out of darkness and midway through its route, Wolf Creek National Park, just decided to cut the planned touristic route clean.Wolf Creek is a clearly indebted to the massacre of Texas film made in Hooper and the first the hills have eyes. The arid and solo scene in which passes the action, and the ruinous and rusty scenery that unfolds the vicious and bloodthirsty character of Mick Taylor (almost, almost, for his brutality, a first cousin of the atrocious Leatherface), they are the main tools used by its director, Greg Mclean, to create an atmosphere so agonizing as unhealthy.Fear and insecurity which feels the trio of teenagers to the unknown, are sensations transmitted alike to the Viewer. He senses that something strong is about to take place, although unknown exactly what, how and when. The shaky camera sigilosidad, ambient cold that breathes and the negrísima darkness of the Australian night, part of the psychological and tense decorated with that rookie Mclean influence, subliminal way, on the bulk of the audience. And so, just when the movie enters bag in one of the episodes more agonizing and brutal of the genus, the public inevitably feels identified with the impotence and dread of some victims to them costs us absolutely nothing to guess their macabre future. Skin of chicken, cold sweats, and calambrazos in the backbone, we are.The routine way that begins the history? through a topical presentation of three young people and demonstrating some conscious effort to the tourist postalita of rigour-has nothing to do with the rest of the footage. Step by step, without haste, forgotten landscape and focuses only on the form. The entrance to this deep Australia, as described in Wolf Creek, is similar to a slower descent into hell. Nasty insinuations that loosen the two girls, the parishioners of a dirty bar in the middle of nowhere, serve mode of presentation (or preparatory) which then it will be the appearance on the scene of the Satan himself. A demon which, initially, will be shown to the newcomers as an Angel salvador and charming. A true film chocolate; Although a chillingly sinister and bitter chocolate. Reads a sign (both in the promotional poster and in the opening credits), the film is based on a true incident; a truthful that entrecomillaría personally, despite its chilling look real and the credibility that offer your images, seems to me as another cryptic trick to raise the restlessness of the spectator a few degrees more. Rather than a real event, bet on the fanciful reading the director and screenwriter done on the disappearances of a number of people in Australian land. Or, at least (and without falling into any spoiler), that is what lead me to think his four final notes and a cast on one of the protagonists in particular.No more: a marvel of terror that will delight all those who they love to eat the nails of pure nervousness. What take advantage! I, for if the flies, don't think go tourism to Australia., at least until I forget this film. And that the canguritos me hungry.</body>
</review>
