<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The jungle 4.0 is a big, without pretensions and fact with true grace.</summary>
	<body>In the times, who put the limits in the action film? No one. Now more than to worry about the ingenious and funny action scenes, producers are looking for that called spectacular. Jungle 4.0 is the clear example of the second theory, a show big, without pretensions and fact with true grace. Gentlemen, multiple action sequences are served by a chef so far well unknown (at least for my): Len Wiseman. It may many of them (or rather all) be literally incredible, but the truth is that this man knows shooting with effectiveness and grace which, although you sounds strange, few current directors know them filming. It is clear that this is a feature film made to enjoy, to not worry or the least such basic things in adventure films such as the reasons for the villains, personal relations between the protagonists, etc. Yes, the film in question appears in all this, but it is simply introduced to fill basic points. If the third mission of Ethan Hunt the objective of not sinteresaba bad a cumin, here (despite being raised grandiosely, and very well achieved) that Timothy Olyphant plan concerns us less. In the jungle 4.0, therefore importantly its above-mentioned visual aspect, the impossible stunts and bestialidades McLane carried out and sentences that this loose. And you can, as I say, that the terrorist attack (carried out by the director of respond way) is very well achieved (the Assembly of Presidents, of the White House?), but here we come to see the return of our dear John McLane and not a simple movie of terrorists. And that, without doubt, Bruce Willis is practically all the jungle 4.0. We could say that we are at a real blockbuster, a palomitera film to every rule that fulfills its mission. And most important of all is that my, that I am not, nor much less, fan of the saga, has seemed really trepdiante. A correct exercise exclusively dedicated to the return of a policeman in 1988 caused real furor with this wonder of entertainment titled the jungle of glass (indeed, painful the translation to the American title of this fourth installment). If the first, as I have just mentioned, was a brave, highly intelligent and claustrophobic sample of action cinema, following two deliveries were limited to continue its success and therefore did not show such enthusiasm as in its predecessor. And, fortunately, this last (I hope!) delivery is limited to participate in what today dominates: the technology. Many more action scenes a recuperadísimo Willis (the best of the tape) and already have the final dish. And in this, rather than being Samuel l. Jackson (great choice of McTiernan) which accompanies the poly hard kill, is the youngster Justin Long, that just makes what we must: complaining and four computer words. Also is "replaced" to an interesting Jeremy Irons with the aforementioned Olyphant, which is not to be kill by having too much charisma.Mr McLane has returned, and in a very satisfactory manner. This is an unusually good action film, but it is also a form of entertainment without the slightest depth (and perhaps too long). But for now, Bourne and it seem the very best of the summer. And remember: Yipee Ki Yay Mo!.</body>
</review>
