<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Hairspray" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Imagine a musical film in which there nor an only moment of relaxation, nor a single moment in which the rate decline, and that almost most of its footage you enter a terrible get up seat and get dancing desire.</summary>
	<body>Imagine a musical film in which there is a single moment of rest, nor a single moment in which the rate decline, and that almost most of its footage you enter a terrible get up seat and get dancing desire.Well, thats Hairspray.Salvo Christopher Walken (which, as said in the journal news images, is somewhat clueless) and John Travolta (it's funny in all of his appearances, but expressivity is zero), all the cast, especially young people (although Zac Efron not convinced), is immense. Note that James Marsden that passes it big, and a Michelle Pfeiffer playing his character perfectly.All give the size in a musical where the discrimination of any kind has no place. That is precisely the message of a film that is all optimism, color, sense of humor and rhythm, much rhythm. Because the soundtrack (winner of 8 Tony, the Broadway Oscar Awards) is a real delight within the genre of musical film, and there is no number that do not move, at least a couple of times the skeleton. Highlight of the entire film Good morning Baltimore, I can hear the bells (hilarious musical numbers that serve as presentation of the character of Tracy Turnblad), Nices kids in town, Welcome to the 60's, Run and tell that, Big, blonde &amp; Beautiful, Without Love, and an Orgasmic finale of more than ten minutes to the rhythm of the best song from the musical, You can't stop the beatIt's worth its three puntacos in the final grade for the film.It is a movie for you pass it well, and leave out any movie buff prejudice that you get to have normally in a movie theater.Some of the drawbacks without much importance in the film are some plot inconsistencies (a crush sudden, as if by magic), some dialogues and situations a tad corny (though I think that dubbing has much of the blame. Although it is not a voice for nothing wrong) and topical, something disneyanos, but you forget everything nothing more start any musical number, because these are the real driving force of the film. Or also all the music belongs to the score of the musical, and that not be smell anything at all music of the sixties and its freshness, as it could be in the original movie of the same title by John Waters.Respecto to the differences between the original of John Waters, and this adaptation of the Broadway musical, are obvious: athe original, is, as told me a friend on MSN, more hardcore and perraca, with a more irreverent and politically incorrect humor, mark of the House of John Waters, the King of the film garbage and/or freak (title who has won at pulse). And most recently, as it has much to do with the original, but at the same time not. It is the same story, but in terms of music, and much more sweetened and politically correct than the other; but social criticism is still present. Me of John Waters, despite Divine and some comic points quite aplaudibles, not me eventually convince, but it does. For something as simple as me I had better seeing it.I am convinced that many people will enter the room with many prejudices, for several reasons. To begin with, is a musical, and that is something that in our country do not like too, and I do not understand why, if they are a joy, and the ultimate expression of what is likely to do in a movie (that operates almost all media existing in the film). Would then be the same prejudices which criticizes the film: physicists and racial, but above all physicists. I bet a hand to someone loose a derogatory comment out loud to see how hypnotically menea skeleton Nikki Blonsky, or see how a guaperas guy prefers a fat girl to a blonde despamanante. and already qualify for the film of directly shit. Because people are so of garrula.I am also convinced that many people allegedly movie fan will not accept the film because it is so optimistic that spreads. And clear, the optimistic and even repipi, which is full of colorful and preaching the flower-power, it seems fashion for those who carry glasses of pasta. Unless it comes signed by managers typically turn cools.Since they lose it.</body>
</review>
