<review author="Bloody Will" title="Superman returns" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I'll stick with that sweet taste of seeing again to Superman, and that bitter too deepen in the characters and their relationships</summary>
	<body>If this altitude, if it is not. If too much romance, if not. If the approach of Synger is wrong if you have made the best film of the year superhero? have been several weeks discussing what Brian Synger has devised for the return, highly anticipated, of the last citizen of Krypton, and we are 60% of excited, and 40% of not so much.With this I want to say that nobody, absolutely nobody has been to give birth the film, nor even I. The only thing that has been done is reel off piece to piece a film, which created expectation, could not claim otherwise. Same thing has happened with "X-Men 3", or "Cars" and will happen to "Pirates of the 2 Caribbean": are the perfect vehicle for the corners to what is sold as a round film.Sitting this Declaration of intent, say, to begin with, that I thank eternally Synger for having given to Superman a fund that previously did not. A fund human, vulnerable and with concerns that go beyond bad search and arrest them. My adult side is satisfied. The child something confused.Nobody said that Synger copied a Superman comic book and give us punches without ton nor. As it did in the two incursions into the world of the X-Men, gives more importance to the emotions of the protagonists, avoiding that the action sequences are the only thing that will fill the screen during the footage. Visually it has no comparison with the latest incursions of superheroes on the screen. Technology at the service of the character.In "Superman Returns" there is action, not all the desirable, but there are many. The plane scene is something demanded for years. Thus, when you finish seeing her, you have left the impression that you've not only seen a film of special effects, but you've attended the presentation of a new Superman, different from the 1980s, and that will be for the next few years.What I like: Brandon Routh did a great job. The greatest success of Synger has been hiring a real stranger who, in a minute, and you identify with the man of steel. When deciding to put poker face, so borda (the scene where spy from afar the home of Lois), and in the latter part of the film, the most dramatic, makes you really believe that "Superman" is vulnerable, something that seems to be the goal of the director.I don't know that it would have been the film without Kate Bosworth. I now understand because they have chosen her as the best Lois. It is without doubt the reincarnation of the Lois of the comics, a strong, independent woman, in love with until the bars of the hero. Of Kevin Spacey I can only say that it is the best actor of villain in recent years. Otherwise could not be who give life to Lex Luthor.Y now, not so good.There is no round movies and special effects cannot save everything. Perhaps the longing to see again in the film Superman causes that history does not have the speed that you want.I do not like the absolute silence on why Superman has been missing all these years. I know that Synger saves it for the sequel, I hope so, but had not been badly some flashback, or at least a preview. If by the production company it was sold as a continuation of "Superman II", was seen not as Superman therefore was not is why again.I don't like the plan of Luthor. A continent made of rock?, and obliterate the U.S. for what?. Luthor has always been well in conjunction with some supervillain to put the force, and in the absence of this, must be depriving Superman of his powers for Lex him from a beating. We saw in "Superman", but with less cruelty. Do do general Zod will be the villain of the sequel?, more'd better you to Synger.Por please, I hope answers in the sequel on the "surprise ending", already you know? if above I do not hear of where he's been, nor tell me when? this.Now you turn you comment on the film. I am left with that sweet of seeing Superman again? and this bitter taste that made the mistake of "Hulk", deepen too in the characters and relationships you distracts from what really pretendías to see.</body>
</review>
