<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With difference, the worst movie of the short (but intense) Quentin Tarantino as director filmography... but oh!, hopefully the worst movies of the best directors were so enjoyable!</summary>
	<body>Quentin Tarantino has suffered its first setback as director. You do not alarméis, it is not what it seems. Death Proof is one of the best films of the year, and unparalleled enjoyment, but it is the first film in which the tito low Q a tad than usual level, and committing excesses that the average viewer hardly can endure (for what I have seen in the cinema): he is extra footage. That is the first thing I thought of at the end of the projection. There are too many scenes of dialogue quite thick. Nothing more start, there is already a, and is not of those dialogues, also thick, but digestible, mythical, as those who open Reservoir Dogs and Pulp Fiction, but of those who sin, an alarming irrelevance and a pretentiousness that sees the Duster from where Christ lost the hat (as if wanted than any of the frasecitas release the girls protagonists)(, they pass to the history of the celluloid), they last too, and end up causing a considerable tedium; Although you may be something unimportant for the most fanatical of the American director, that they probably aguantarán - with a tad of patience - blissful dialogues until you get good thing really, as enjoyable as Orgasmic.Because Death Proof can err on the side of what I have just said, but we are talking about one of the most fun, entertaining films (ignoring the dialogues of the devil) and gamberras of the year, when not taken too seriously to itself (which is something you should not do you). That is also very "tarantina" (something that wasn't, for example, Kill Bill, being a medley - disgustingly hilarious, everything must be said - of thousand different genres that seeping commercialism on all sides), and it shows in all its frames, in how QT moves the camera in how lives and breathes the film alone. It has, in addition to the best action sequences shot of the year, a thousand details and references, as in every movie Tarantino self-respecting, you must not miss, as well as a few well chosen songs for the scenes of turn (priceless scene between the character of Vanessa Ferlito and specialist Mike erotic bailecito).Kurt Russell, very playful. I liked his performance, although it is not to throw many rockets (what would I see how would be the specialist Mike character - a tad missed, incidentally - played by the actor who had to do so from the outset: Mickey Rourke). The girls, in its point.Basically the argument is simpler that the mechanism of a botijo and why maybe spare you a few minutes of footage, the film seemed to me quite funny but me I had very well, despite its flaws, is what really matters.By far the worst movie of the short (but intense) Filmography of Quentin Tarantino as director. but oh!, hopefully the worst movies of the best directors were so enjoyable!Attention to the details of celluloid wasted expressly for the Grindhouse experience (here mutilated) is more realistic. and this sudden and unexpected The End, simply master of menace that becomes.</body>
</review>
