<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Sigo como Dios" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tontorrón festival of topical familioedulcorados that adds absolutely nothing to the adult world, but who enjoy Yes or Yes children.</summary>
	<body>In summer of 2003 was released throughout the world like God (or Bruce Almighty, which is as it would have to be called if the Lords that "translate" the titles had deigned to respect the original title), a film directed by Tom Shadyac (director of authentic pastries as a compulsive liar, Patch Adams, or Dragonfly: the shadow of the dragonfly, but also of genius as Ace Ventura)(: Pet detective), which starred Jim Carrey, Jennifer Aniston and Morgan Freeman doing himself. I.e. Dios.La film had its successful comic points, and was funny despite the cloying Catholic aura that wrapped around, but was literally to hell to become half the typical and unbearable comedy romantic desktop, predictable to say enough is enough.Since God was a success, and quickly confirmed the sequel, but there were difficulties with the cast, since Jim Carrey could not repeat because he was busy with other projects (which were then canceled.) and, if there was no Jim Carrey, obviously (and fortunately) there would be Jennifer Aniston, no continuation of the plot established in like God. So Tom Shadyac came up with the idea of exploiting a character which, a priori, seemed interesting, and was pulled out of the sleeve a story around it. It was nothing more and nothing less than Evan Baxter, in like God gave life now known Steve Carrell.En Sigo as God (or Evan Almighty. continue with titles invented.), Evan Baxter has just been elected nothing more and nothing less than Congressman and moves of Buffalo with his family, to live in a residential area of Northern Virginia. Once there, his life suffers a major turnaround when Dios (Morgan Freeman, how not) orders him to build an Ark, because the flood is coming.The result ends up being little more than disheartening. The tape is boring and makes rather little grace. 95% Of gags and jokes or humorous situations, are children's and clear of facile (to Carrell makes you want to kill him when he does that "do the dance"). And to make matters worse, it happens something more serious than its predecessor: it becomes a typical and repelentemente family comedy easy moralina, and to political and ecological. In addition, the history is absurd nonsense: God announces a deluge, and assigned to Evan Baxter to build an Ark, while a couple of copies of each species are arriving to the place where it will build the piece of pot. At the end (and eye because this can be considered SPOILER), the flood does not exist as such, and one jeto checkered is left to wonder what's the fuss for absolutely nothing.A tontorrón festival of topical familioedulcorados that adds absolutely nothing to the adult world, but who enjoy Yes or Yes children. A pure and simple crossover between as God, Vaya Santa Claus!, and an inconvenient truth.The only thing salvageable from my point of view, the Visual effects (which, although they sing occasionally with the bugs, the Tutuki Splash part seems quite successful) y. credits end, friendly and fun.</body>
</review>
