<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Like half of the fans, and will disappoint the other half. It entusiasmará to easy laughter, and above all will be very enjoyable for the smallest of the House. Lucky.</summary>
	<body>I do not deny that the Simpsons is one of the best series that has borne him the television throughout its history. Nor do I deny you of great moments that made me pass this yellow family throughout my life. One of its great advantages is that the vast majority of chapters pararías not see them (believe me, is a certainty: Antena 3 puts us to test for millennia.). But series is not having a good time, in what regards to the quality of his scripts. The plots are becoming increasingly silly and jokes are becoming increasingly bad characters lose charisma and bellows as they go through the seasons. And just at this moment, the film of the series in theaters around the world, ready to make a hole between the most blockbuster of the summer (because it has been designed for that) lands.And note, it is quite noticeable in the quality of the product offered by the time in which this has come.The Simpsons: The movie, felt me very anecdotal and unreal. One parida mildly funny and entertaining, which fortunately did not offend nor deceive anyone, but overly light compared to the chapters of the golden age of the Simpson family on television. A few lol, jijiji, other many pffff by - most abundant - bad jokes, and some other sonrisilla, caused mostly by the grace that makes you see some worthy characters from the series on the big screen.But and already is. Some other gag lucky and anthological (Spider-Pig, the integral naked Bart on skateboard, home and end credits), and let for.Like half of the fans, and will disappoint the other half. It entusiasmará to easy laughter, and above all will be very enjoyable for the smallest of the House. Suertudos.se thanks be a film, and that rather than the feeling that you are watching an episode long and stretched.He is also appreciated that it is more or less to the height of the average quality of the series, and it is, to some extent, worthy of it, but one has not been avoided this strange sweet and sour sensation out of the film. and forget much as seen after five minutes.</body>
</review>
