<review author="José A. Peig" title="Objetivo Birmania" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Formally effective and accurate in carrying out, perhaps the script suffers from schematic, logical consequence of obvious discourse, without involving a a setback as a paradigmatic.</summary>
	<body>In 1945, Raoul Walsh directed this paradigm of war movies, representation of the manifestations of essential war devoid of evaluative excesses as usual in other products of the genre, whether patriotic pretensions or anti-war proclamation. Perhaps the genre in question is his State of purity when the film material is limited to show the war and their obvious attributes. It is a story of hierarchies, of how those responsible for a higher hierarchical order using a group of subordinates to clear the way and begin the invasion of Burma in optimal time and place. The subordinate group - led by Errol Flyn too encorsetado in their militar-paternal role - progresses through the Asian jungle without being aware of all the ins and outs of the operation, develops a survival process dotted with moderate drama, and without falling into excesses sentimentaloides. The war is a collective strategy and a single drama, and Walsh puts the emphasis on the permutations of the soldier in the battle (various attacks on villages or ran up control centres) and the idea of strategy, repeatedly described the movements together with a visual composition that spared no patience and tempo in the appropriate details. In the end, an air army appears to save the heroes suffered, moment in which the covert plot reveals the manipulative nature of the hierarchy. The high command congratulates Errol by having fulfilled his mission, to which this replica showing plates of dead soldiers: "here is the price to pay". Does it worth?. The essential issue, and on which Walsh does more than suggest and open the question without driving the consciousness of the Viewer to the ideological field (as opposed to Spielberg in his "saving private Ryan").Formally effective and accurate in carrying out, perhaps the script suffers from schematic, logical consequence of obvious discourse, without involving a a setback as a paradigmatic.</body>
</review>
