<review author="José A. Peig" title="Los duelistas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do perhaps the biggest problem of this film - and will be for this reason that fails to be at the height of the great - is the purported connection between professional, intimate and loving life of the protagonist with his? afterlife? perpetual confrontation with the character played by Harvey Keitel.</summary>
	<body>In film the verisimilitude of the narrated history often sustained in the knowledge that the Viewer may have the motivations which animate characters and situations. This directorial debut of Ridley Scott, often proclaimed as the best work of its author, it is tempting to fall into an easy criticism rationale on the fact that the conflict held in the footage between the two male protagonists is not accompanied by explicit elements inherent in the same. Or that we know that Keith Carradine and Harvey Keitel spend life challenging violent duel but we don't know to what comes so much history, as the riot it initial it triggers the dangerous cycle of violence, for the average viewer, it is hardly relevant. With this argument, therefore, could throw away a product that aims to sustain one greater offense.Now well, and to be fair, should not be forgotten that this is a film in which the implicit theme (the need to rid of the offense through the defeat of contrast in a combat sword and blood) is the only raison d ' être of the same, according to the initial sign that gives home to history, and, therefore, require something more explicit would be like asking del olmo pears. And all this makes "The Duelists" in a perhaps much more strange film than it seems at first glance, revealing that after the camera had a filmmaker's most unique within the blockbusters of the past two decades. "The duellists" is not a history of simple malice and revenge in perpetual quest, is a vital, unhealthy, obsessive process, but that relates to the need for the liberation of the two main characters, victims of an honor code strongly rooted in the era and in the military context of Napoleonic Europe. We do not need to know why so much barbarism, verisimilitude is given in the "spirit of the age", and that Scott is very explicit by creating sequences of bitter violence, as repeated duels to sword, or death, the freezing and the solitude of the troops in the ice of Russia and murky. Visually, the film is a magnificent showcase of "pictures" of the time; costumes, landscapes, forceful setting and introduction in this social context, with an excellent use of chromatic resources, brightness and the decoration.Perhaps the biggest problem of this film - and will be for this reason that fails to be at the height of the great - is the purported connection between professional, intimate and loving life of the protagonist with his "other life" of perpetual confrontation with the character played by Harvey Keitel quite crude, and the consequent deprivation caused by the obsessive ballast. As I said before, the confrontation between the two meets a need of Liberation through the "cleaning of the honour".The connection between the two areas is hinted in the montage of the duel on horseback in parallel with images of professional, intimate and loving life of the protagonist, but not emphasized enough that internal conflict of the character to achieve the proper emotional intensity - and the dramatic meaning of the periplus of duels - which will lead us towards the climax due in the last minutes of the film. The film, therefore, peca of low intensity in the crucial moments and the tone of the general drama, above all in this splendid end reflecting the successful liberation pardoning the life of the adversary: in this crucial Act of consciousness, both fighters reach freedom and a new State of being, beautifully represented in the final sequence, with a look at (the Keitel) covering a large and beautiful landscape (which comes to mean that freedom)(, the emergence of new horizons), although do not know for sure if everything has ended or you are thinking about restarting the duels. A magnificent open end, despite the aforementioned absence of an emotional factor that raise the intensity of the whole, avoiding a certain aftertaste of coldness of feeling that a good story deserved higher dose of emotion.In sum, a good movie, although we must not sobrevalorarla because it is not certainly the best film Ridley Scott, taking into account that there is "Alien".</body>
</review>
