<review author="José A. Peig" title="La jungla 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that offers a banal spectacle, but entertains from beginning to end. Indeed, John McClane fans don't need much more than that, but the script lacks wit and the characters are pure stereotype without personality.</summary>
	<body>The sound of the landing of a plane returns to open the story, John McClane waits for Holly at the airport in Washington, again we are at Christmas, and without time or respite, appear the same elements as in die hard (Die Hard). Engabardinados men and armed with a flawless plan that will not leave nothing to chance. The passageways, smoke, electrodes and devices of the Nakatomi building are replaced by an airport that at times becomes the interiors of the ship Nostromo (aesthetics of Alien) (again).And finally, McClane is the smartest of the courtyard and is the only one that seems to realize what is approaching at a policeman spent the entire film pasting screams until the adaptor metrallazo you turn on the Tinker Bell. The bad, in this case, not intended to emulate the polyhedral wickedness of Hans Grubber, intentionally becomes a musculitos with skull face, bland and predictable.In principle, the sequel directed the very mediocre Renny Harlin, has all the evils that may have a sequel: repetition of the schema and the elements of its precedent, but treated to a banal, is reduces to the cliché, to predictable and self-satisfied, just opposite to what should offer the second parts; a progression towards some field of meaning, explore the possibilities of a specific genre that had founded the new idea of action hero.McCtiernan, through a superb script and a carrying out meticulous and evocative, created an action cinema epic (perhaps Crystal jungle can be defined as the first - and only so far - epic action film) in which the different characters and elements harmonize in a fun and overwhelming "action-Opera". Renny Harlin is almost limited to filming a vulgar film shot and call, which could not differentiate themselves and any movie cheap if not for the reference (John McClane) used by some moments that reached a laudable dramatic tension, or revisitan the profile of the hero with dignity; Perhaps no other scene better defines the profile of McClane to the time of the landing of general hope, when it opens the door of the plane and said: "freedom", then intervenes McClane before the stunned eyes of the fugitive, "but who are you?".The man who comes to the site and less timely, but which, unfortunately for some and fortune of others, is the element that breaks the course of stipulations. And that is the kind of hero defined in the saga of Die Hard, someone that works wonders from his humanity. In the same vein, it must be said that at least respect the essential McClane personality and images of hysteria at the airport to recover part of the tragic sense.In short, film offers a banal spectacle, but it entertains from beginning to end. Indeed, John McClane fans don't need much more than that, but the script lacks wit and the characters are pure stereotype without personality.</body>
</review>
