<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Os declaro marido y marido" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A crude imitation of comedy characterized by uncouth humor, bad taste and lack of class which often distill the pseudocómicos roles of Adam Sandler.</summary>
	<body>As the world had little punishment with Jim Carrey and his zafias grimaces, Hollywood was considering sending a second Angel Avenger, even more repellent and anchored at the time as the first. This specimen is named after Adam Sandler, and can be seen by the charts each certain periods of time, which comes out of his burrow to remind us all that always there can be something worse than the last thing that we have seen.On this occasion, appears on the screen together with Kevin James, that helps to the nonsense is still greater than already in itself represents a film that uses homosexuals to laugh and not with them. I say this because I declare unto you husband and husband is nothing more than a series of collected topics (and not of Geyper), which is not repaired in offending the dignity of whoever necessary in order to try to boot a smile to the Viewer, although the result causes displeasure more nose than anything else.Grosso modo, the story tells the adventures of two gulfs foolish (and heterosexual) who after coincidentally decide to marry to get a grant that is awarded to the couples gais. To impersonate this, they resort to all the stereotypes of bad taste, surrounding himself with reinonas and histriónicos characters that riánse you Paco Martínez Soria dressed in coat of fur and estropajosa wig in the aunt of Carlos.Para more inri, your advertising campaign in United States includes allusions to the defence of the normalization of homosexuality claiming to represent the film. Come on, claiming over make believe everything do to combat homophobia. At least not have the impertinence to use this argument in Europe; Maybe it's because the people here still think. But after two or three years of education for citizenship and other educational reforms of the various Governments (of all colors) perhaps shit like this end up being considered masterpieces in the old continent.</body>
</review>
