<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="El Elegido" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A missed opportunity to create an interesting product idea that is you could get much more party.</summary>
	<body>The chosen is one of those horror films modern, which has now been called psychological horror (as if there is another). Starring one deliberately afeada (although neither wanting to get) Monica Bellucci, tells the story of a single and lonely woman who adopts a baby from a Siberian orphanage. When it has eight years, appears in his torso a brand, which is associated with a legend of a tribe of his native territory, and since that time, they start to happen the murders, disappearances and strange.With a fairly successful atmosphere, favoured by the aura of mystery that alone it covers the Russia mother, is a production that is would have been able to get much more juice of the retrieved and have formed a film much more round and finished that represents the chosen. Starting with an interesting and intriguing idea, the truth is that the tone is falling to become boring at times, leaving a sense of dissatisfaction and missed opportunity.The alternation between the Parisian stage and the Russians will not just transmit the feeling of uncertainty that should, encourages the Viewer to the why of things is posing in a continuous manner, nor is the motivation that moves the characters that are parading across the screen unfinished contribute anything really worthy of a call. When in a film of intrigue, one does not feel the need to think and guess about the answers to the questions raised, we have been astray.For this reason even the presence of the immortal Catherine Deneuve manages to give the film the consistency needed to convert a good proposal in a tangible reality and easy enjoyment by a spectator that no doubt will be disappointed to disappointed expectations, as little more than nudity, fleeting and unexpected of the Bellucci will be for the annals of the seventh art.</body>
</review>
