<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Moscow Zero" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another one of those movies that could have been interesting but the incompetence of his writers and director become boring and strange.</summary>
	<body>Moscow Zero is the second mystery or horror film set in Russia I've swallowed this weekend. Like the chosen, it is European capital. This, in particular, is one of those strange co-productions of a few countries, which leads to weird situations such as the emergence of actors as my countryman Alex O'Dogerthy Cadiz (known as unsympathetic coffee camera driver) with the increasingly more swollen and deteriorated Val Kilmer (little remains of those who played the Saint).Narrated in a tone somewhat sinister but not at all credible, tells the story of an expedition of scientists and a priest who travel to the catacombs of an ancient Russian monastery which has apparently disappeared a classmate that entered previously and solo them. According to popular legend, among the recesses of this underground labyrinth, is the entrance to hell.Little more can highlight of another missed opportunity to achieve an excellent horror film, that as in the chosen, the promising start is giving way to a Cadence charisma, slow and developed in some environments as dark hard to follow the thread of events that are losing interest as it progresses the footage.One of the aspects that really stands out is the obvious (to me seems it) parallelism which is established between the symbolism of a supernatural demon and another that could well refer to the human being, in its most raw aspect. This possible analogy reached its zenith when narrated the sequence of a kid who sees what they did the demons in a 1920 Russian convent, while background shows a refertorio in flames. Perhaps I'm wrong, but I think it is much coincidence that display such an affront to the religion set at a time so close to the October revolution, which led to the establishment of the Communist regime of the Soviet Union, which led to the prohibition of religious practice and the destruction of many buildings dedicated to it, while it refers to "demons".</body>
</review>
