<review author="Bloody Will" title="A todo gas 3: Tokyo race" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If the first two you you already hartaste see pranced in Tokyo is skidding. Your partner will appreciate you that don't think therein to accompany you to see her.</summary>
	<body>Film ideal for conducting film to your summer League and who know first that tí, films with emotional content and script worked, or fu fa. In the first ten minutes a busty blonde auction between her boyfriend and the prota for who win a street race to stay with her. It takes longer. It is thus easier to make criticism of this film as saying there are rows of seats in the cinema.Sean is a kid of Institute (do your interpreter Lucas Black has 24 years?) who, after getting into a mess of illegal races must take trip to Tokyo to live with his father and avoid prison. There conocero another type of car racing, rather more dangerous, where the Japanese mafia is the last to have the word.Translate the original title, Tokyo Drift, its literal sense would be "Tokyo drift" has been avoided in Spain. This is the movie, if the first two you you already hartaste see pranced and nitrosa injection, Tokyo is skidding, and this third part has a race between the bad maloso and the good Bandit is just stalling in a parking lot. An ode to safe driving.Not be if there in Japan is the card points, but only the protagonist must already be 300 points before the end of the film. The grace of the film is to make all infringements of traffic as possible, as if his Commission was a synonym for "I'm the best". If the protagonist flees the USA to avoid prison, in Tokyo he perpetrated offences twice, so well you would need a jail of those that went to Claire Danes and Kate Beckinsale movie.Nathalie Kelley debutant is Neela, the log that is metera between eye and look at the prota until that her get carreritas and spinning tops. Normal, being the sister of the malo-mafioso, a graduate in mathematics you won't.It was irony, to see this film must go plan of Homer Simpson: empties the brain and take a beer. Testosterone out on all sides, the script is null, and macho is as a film of pajares-esteso, but repeat, empties the brain, take a beer, and is the week peliculón.It has been # 1 on the Neanderthal Box-Office. Your novia-esposa - couple will appreciate you that you don't think therein to accompany you to see her.</body>
</review>
