<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Un Corazón Invencible" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a superb film, but good, with good editing and excellent soundtrack and photography, to get what he wants.</summary>
	<body>Interesting political drama, based on sad facts in elaño 2003. It happened in Karachi (Pakistan), and enter in the multiple events that occurred following the destruction of the twin towers in New York (USA.)(UU).Surrendered and painful tribute to all those people who gave their lives for ideals and love of work well done, and that given by banner to the truth, they tried in find out the causes, connections and ramifications of the cancer of terrorism which ravaging and continues to plague the world.Winterbottom, uses its particular rhythm narrative, that is, to catch-up, measured, care during much of the footage, especially in the scenes intimate and everyday, full of great sensitivity, and explosive on the (several raids by the police and pakistani army) action scenes. And get this great truth, by giving realism and ability of conviction to the bleak history, with moments of love and affection, and other violence and cruelty, although we never see it explicitly.Excellent commissioning scene, that was said there that tends to the coldness, although I do not agree with this. It is possible that it won't excite, but Winterbottom runs away from the plague of the easy tear, although its final minutes could contribute to this, but more by the intrinsic force of the images, as because the director search them at all costs.Good performances, especially of Irfan Khan, as the captain, and Anjelina Jolie, a very sober except when already can not more. In my view, it is not a superb film, but good, with good editing and excellent soundtrack and photography, that manages what it intends to pay tribute to people that I quoted at the beginning of the comment and expose the hard days of a woman who has lost the person who wants more.</body>
</review>
