<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You can be considered as a long (and fun) episode of the series.</summary>
	<body>Just finished the first season broadcast on Spain, my opinion was that it was one of the best series in the history of television.Time has shown that I had fallen short. Because "The Simpsons" is also one of the most important series in influential in the history of television.For the same reason, the idea of transfer to theaters the formula that worked so well in the small screen has been a constant temptation to those responsible for the series. A temptation which were waged for lack of the appropriate script, of sufficient desire, of the needing or, simply, value.Finally, in 2007 comes "the Simpsons: the movie" ("The Simpsons Movie"), whose importance in the history of the cinema is far than it already is in the field of television. In fact, and to give an example, stays away from the level of the "South Park" movie, rather than in my opinion.The fundamental problem is that television and film are different means, each of them with its own language and its characteristic tempo. Put another way, the formula that works on television doesn't why work in the film.In this way, although the movie is quite funny (laughs are insured) and entertaining during his 87-minute, his pace is not appropriate and, on this particular point, does not stand for a moment the comparison with "Ratatouille", competitor at the box office here in Spain. Me left with the question of if the assessment would have been different from the film have been released in 1989, before that nobody had never seen a single episode of the series. But what I have no doubt is that, seen now, her can be considered as one episode of the series, with the difference that lasts three times than usual.The Simpsons had deserved something more but, seen the impoverished level of film for this year, I think we can (or must) be satisfied.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 6 out of 10.</body>
</review>
