<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Los ojos del mal" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A terrifying film which, despite being directed by a Californian, and North American production has been shot in its entirety at Australia.</summary>
	<body>The type is a very careful geek. It serves by the name of Jacob Goodnight. Of great stature and extremely cabezón, it distinguishes itself from the rest of the human by hold a hole in the back of his huge skull. He likes walking accompanied by his axe - the weapon of choice among all the tools of his precious workshop-DIY, which moves with the skill of an alien by labyrinthine corridors. Debtor of the misdeeds of Leatherface, unhealthy and solo character is marked by a compulsive collector passion; While some treasure glass marbles, he captures the eyes of their victims in jars filled with formaldehyde. They have evil tongues that morbid instincts and his angry chifladura drag them from an early age. In my times, the priests claimed that masturbation secaba brain; Surely, the Knight of the perforated testa never studied at a College of priests because, already very young, killed to straws to the naked Playboy, Penthouse and similar. And this has been.He that Jacob, in short, is the undisputed star of the evil eyes, a terrifying film which, despite being a production directed by a Californian, and American has been shot in its entirety in Australia; specifically in a few film studios of the Gold Coast of Queensland, which could mean a veiled (and deserved) tribute to the soundness of the current fantasy film in that country.The eyes of evil has many points in common with the also stimulating for enter to live, the telefilm made Jaume Balagueró for movies to not sleep, the series coordinated by Narciso Ibáñez Serrador. Like this, most of her footage takes place inside a squalid, gray and dilapidated property, at the time that one of the main coordinates of its argument connects directly with the title of Balagueró.</body>
</review>
