<review author="El mágico" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Classical action of our times, excellently filmed by Paul Greengrass film. Pure entertainment.</summary>
	<body>This is undoubtedly the consecrating role of Matt Damon. Beyond that has been rewarded with his friend Ben Affleck for his writing in "Good Will Hunting" with an Oscar, Damon is not a writer of weight in the industry. If it is, without a doubt a versatile actor whose talent lies in the ability to adapt to the skin of any subject you can imagine (and I am not exaggerating at all), it is flexible, dominates your body and its mark is of total commitment with each interpretation. He has done many supported by favorable impact at the box office works, ("The talented Mr Ripley", "Syriana", "The Departed", and recently "The good shepard"), but however the massive global comes with this, his saga. The story already know, is Jason Bourne who returns to action when two journalists investigating the missing CIA Treadstone section are removed under mysterious circumstances in an attempt to erase the last pieces of the puzzle of its past. We know those who follow the story, which Bourne shows the dark side of American security agencies and ruthless in its role to defend what they believe are legitimate interests of his fellow citizens. The victim has been (or not, will have to see the end to find out!) of a nefarious agenda of brainwashing that transformed it into a killing machine. Now, when the services they learn the news of its existence appears in "The Guardian" (famous English tabloid that specializes in research notes), will begin to pursue, control, monitor, and eventually eliminate anyone to contact Bourne, to neutralize any political implication of the Treadstone program (which made of Jason, who Jason is, a perfect spy)given that it is not what is said to be "politically correct" (!). Damon is Bourne, from head to toe. Feel and breathe like him, transmits the bewilderment and the strength of its presence even during the time it is silent meditating (that is worth seeing). This ex-spy without past will try by all means accessing information that different connections bring him to discover who is and how he came to be who is now. On this trip, the fight against the bad guys will be fierce and ingenious every moment of the way. "Appear several familiar faces of the second part (well the ensemble of the roles of Joan Allen and the enigmatic Julia Stiles, who make an exact contribution to the plot), and as always, there will be persecutions incredible, both on foot and vehicle, shots, explosions, murders, etc.""Bourne: the ultimatum" is a classical action film of our time, excellently filmed by Paul Greengrass (who also made the previous), well-known director among us also by the very good "United 93". This filmmaker you passionate about the almost permanent use of a nervous and intense camera to make us feel at the epicenter of the action. Greengrass he cares that its viewers are part of the visual deployment and integrates them through cut, multiple levels and outlets on movement that add tension to the general frame of the plot. Does not reach the superlatives levels of "Live free or die hard - 4.0" (perhaps a little less deployment, perhaps.), but is there. It is a magnificent proposal for pure entertainment, with the only caveat that much of what appears in this third part, has already appeared, as well as his characters evoke much history, with which should have already seen the previous thus enjoying more. You must not miss it at this point in the year, they must not be more than four films of this genre that reached the rating of outstanding on our blog. Do tell: what time are you going to go today? You do not have to miss it!</body>
</review>
