<review author="Bloody Will" title="Un Corazón Invencible" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tape that this stage of the year seems to me almost perfect. A jewel among so much garbage millionaire and is able to with your images that you feel the emotion and pain of the main protagonist.</summary>
	<body>Well who I would say: the first movie of Angelina Jolie that I like in years?Daniel Pearl, journalist of?The Wall Street Journal? He disappeared on January 23, 2002 to investigate radical Islamic groups and their links with the terrorist network Al Qaeda in Pakistan. In February of 2002 Pakistani police received the video of the execution of the journalist, which still circulates on the internet, and wasn't until 16 may when found body decapitated on the outskirts of Karachi. Impressive history, and similarly it has resulted in the screen.Michael Winterbottom (? does 24 hour party people?) he has done a great job to print the feeling that history, deserves this drama (finally) ceases to be the typical Hollywood product to deal with the drama of the Pearl if they release a documentary, and with that I am not saying they are going to flood data, dates or political issuesmuch less?A mighty heart? It is a film which tells a story of unconditional love truncated by stupid fanaticism without bore us explaining how many terrorist groups there are in Pakistan, or who are the good and bad.I have to say that without doubt the use of flashbacks to tell in a way parallel the final journey of Daniel Pearl and the intense search for Mariane print to tape a pace which would have easily been void in case of first having the kidnapping of journalist and later the two months of investigations and interrogation until the fateful outcome.With how easy that was falling into the cakes melodrama of a pregnant woman who collapses when her husband is going to die insurance, the result is the opposite: a woman who fights without barely shed a tear to pull the wire and reach the captors of her husband, while maintaining an unprecedented strength. He is appreciated.All the credit goes to Angelina Jolie. Do chop jumbles has marked the actress for that now, under the production of Brad Pitt, firm his best role since?Do girl, interrupted?, there is nothing. Imitate the French accent is often a genuine jod ** nda for who gets involved in a role that it requires, but Jolie makes it as natural that only you know. The reaction of the protagonist when he receives the news of the death of her husband is a scene so round that I was her he recorded Jolie in the butt to remind you that there are roles that are worthwhile. It is brilliant, and I promise that I never thought that I could use bright and Jolie in the same sentence.Now that you know that if are you looking for the truth about why Daniel Pearl was murdered it is not going to find in the film. In the film is given to understand that it was the Jewish status of Pearl and even because they confused it with an agent of the CIA, however investigations that the journalist was still two months after the attacks of 9-11 are the cause of that is now tell their story, but of course, one thing is to make a film with few Mexico claims and other is condemning it to eliminate the Chambers at the first opportunity.Anyway, leaving the inaccuracies in the script that are imperceptible to us that we do not live the media barrage mounted in the USA, we have a tape that at this stage of the year seems to me almost perfect. A jewel among so much trash millionaire and told through the eyes of a director, which marks a before and after in his filmography, and is able to with your images that you feel the emotion and pain of the main protagonist.It has caught me at a very low point, or possibly is the very best that premiered in months in the Spanish charts.</body>
</review>
