<review author="Naty Buqué" title="Zodiac" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film can be read, rather than as the terrible and terrorizing story of a murderer very, very bad, as a reflection on the media and the role they and the information in a modern and hiperglobalizada society.</summary>
	<body>One can not standing up to the DVD to see this movie without thinking "I'll see a Fincher film, I'll see a Fincher film" (emotion) or even "want to see the fight club / Seven" (choose your favourite). Well, that's a shit, because it is and see the new Wong Kar Wai wait in a spirit of love. Or end of read in search of lost time and expected that Proust has had time to write something else. Conclusion: One should not be so demanding.So I'm going to forget about the past of Fincher, and I will remember Zodiac, at the earliest, in the context of the genre to which it belongs. Zodiac is a very good police-thriller about crazy Yankees gutting people.The film, which is long, is true (and while it is obviously cut off by all parties and the little signs of "x" later go faster than the end credits) follows the story of a murderer "serial" (the series is not so obvious) over a few years who do not can grab, basically, because it does not move under any pattern nor have any mobile to kill people.The interesting thing about the film, which is not noted for revolutionizing the cinematographic language in any sense at least, lies, first, in the constant tension generated not so much with the prior suspense murder scene but in an atmosphere of strangeness is not confined to the space of the crime that expands throughout the film, even in its moments of humor and calm. And also follows when you apagaste the TV.On the other hand, the film Dodge all the clichés that fall systematically the police/trhillers on serial killers. First, the murderer is not an invincible genio-loco who commits murders following a pattern that has more to do with quantum physics than with the victims. The type makes mistakes, lies, shows certain weaknesses, platitudes in his personality. It will be crazy, but he is human. Secondly, I'm going to subtly say to not ruin the end, the detective is not an idealized character nor the justice and truth necessarily succeed. But neither triumphs crime. The film also avoids the typical structural bipolarity of the film. There is a good and a bad: there is a killer course (perhaps two, or only a madman who has been awarded crimes), a number of suspects that can not be discarded entirely, people who claims to be the Zodiac but obviously isn't the police, press, a kid who is interested in the case and wants to solve it, and there is a power struggle between them, and there are bureaucracies that suspend the alleged justice or the possibility of accessing a supposed truth. And the story is taking different points of view, which is very interesting because, adding the end (which I will not tell), everything contributes to a very strong and quite radical reflection on the possibility of knowledge and certainty of justice.The film leaves a feeling of uncertainty (redundancy), something that is diluted. The murderer cannot exist, they may be two accomplices, or he/they could have not only committed crimes but also awarded others who have not committed, or have been only awarded unsolved crimes. The killer can only be a specific order of speeches that he collects and organizes knowledge, the description and the award of a group of crimes. The film can be read, rather than as the terrible and terrorizing story of a murderer very but very bad, as a reflection on the media and the role they play and information in a modern and hiperglobalizada society, or even, as a reflection on the idea of truth (the film does not use, as they tend to do all of this genus)one thing that is the truth and is a person and should be getting it. The truth is not evidence that moves, changes of place between the characters, as a power. (It does this tranquility to the Viewer.)I mean, the film adds to the paranoia that persecutes these Yankees of "there are assassins loose everywhere" but that on the other hand, functions as a critique and a deep reflection on how this phenomenon and what place occupy different institutions therein. Finally, as one no minor detail, I thank Mr Fincher avoid me the very easy and free little blood-filled scenes.</body>
</review>
