<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Are what were thinking those responsible for casting when commissioned to that role to Timothy Oliphant, an actor what dan rather than fear eager to cuddling him?</summary>
	<body>How easy it is for the critical load a film like this "Jungle 4.0": is not a sequel, but quarter of a successful commercial saga but little depth in the movie fan class; director only has, so far, the diptych (soon triptych) of "Underworld"; It stars Bruce Willis, which in recent years almost all critics (myself included) are giving a somanta sticks by his declining career.But, if we do a minimum mental gymnastics exercise, the truth is that this fourth installment in a series continues to be a good commercial product, properly dosed in his constant "crescendo" of action seeking mass segregation of the viewer adrenaline (and, probably, of testosterone?), but with a decrepit, prematurely aging hero who has to complete his exploits with much pain and bloodin a sort of indisimulable, indisimulado, masochistic instinct that makes the protagonist detective alive its particular "via crucis" over thousand and one disasters that would happen. There are, in addition, some details when least curious: on the one hand, the fact of entrusting the role of director of the FBI, a man of power administrative quasi-judicial absolute, an Arabic features actor, albeit really New Zealand. Things, so we have the head of the Federal has a pint of moro quite striking, that, as it stands, I do not know if you consider it as a stroke of humor or, why not, an antixenófoba claim that should be applauded. The issue of the so-called chaos Total (theory that imagines an absolute collapse of all systems on Earth) is also interesting, although it is not particularly original, and even less in the literature (see, without going any further, the penultimate novel by Stephen King, "Cell"). But the tone of this "jungle 4.0", which announces disaster ("crack" software) which repressed in their own title Spanish, is acceptable, with a hero who is falling apart as it has to leave the face with bad, a teenage daughter with revolts hormones that he hates (not without some justification), and a pipiolo which will serve as an Assistant with a shawl of radicalism were more or less updated.Len Wiseman, director, confirms that it is especially gifted skillfully choreographed action fleeing from current trends to the embarullamiento that are destroying the genre; probably this could call virtue comes from his past as artistic director, but the truth is that he is appreciated that our pupils do not have to do extra hours to find out what is happening on screen in the ultraviolence scenes that are the mark of the House in this type of film. Do the grading of the action scenes remain some plausibility (always within the usual improbability of the genre), until, with the hilarious sequence of the persecution of the protagonist for the hunting, the credibility goes directly to hell, not to say another word of equal number of letters and stronger? We must also mention the evolution that the own character of John McLane has suffered in these almost twenty years since that premiered the initiatory "Jungle of glass" John MacTiernan. Then it was a slob with emotional problems with his wife (or ex-wife perhaps already: memory for such details do not ask me), but still a man facing life from "pole", if they may use me the car analogy fashion. Now, nearly two decades later, that mighty hombretón, with a considerable hair mata and wanting to eat the world, is a rickety cincuentón, that shaves his head to disguise their problems of alopecia, at the end of the path and already with the retirement next horizon. That muchachote has become a cynic, a skeptic cured of fear, two beings in a same body which, however, only unites them their aching suffering to defeat the villain and his bad relationship with his ex-wife and daughter almost ex. Speaking of bad: what casting makers were thinking when commissioned to that role to Timothy Oliphant, an actor what dan rather than fear are eager to cuddling him? Man, please, the supervillain of this fourth installment may not be a guy that seems to come out of "The Blue Lagoon"? Well, nothing, to see if we fix it for the fifth (do will have, to be sure: the box office does not lie?).</body>
</review>
