<review author="JohnTrent" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The jungle 4.0 is a good action movie, a good show without more pretensions that provide a decent entertainment to those who come to see her, but from there to pay tribute to her as the very best of the year, not.</summary>
	<body>Already almost twenty years ago was released a film called Die Hard, here known as die hard, causing sensation at the box office and creating what today we already know as a popular icon of action cinema. Its protagonist, Bruce Willis, fresh out of the successful series light of moon, portraying a police officer named John McClane in a position limit. And it is that while visiting a large building to see his ex-wife, the building is taken over by terrorists, so McClane ended becoming a hero and the only hope of the people kidnapped in the interior. Formulates it created school, coming after so many films that they based their plot in a closed place, terrorists and a hero that faces them, but almost always with lower results, or at least not so mythical. Only two years later came the inevitable sequel, which in this case would be new (and lower) director John McTiernan was replaced by Renny Harlyn, and step what happened, than Die Hard 2, aka the jungle of glass. Red alert, despite overcoming the first fund-raising figures give, flojeo of artistic results. But already in 1995, no less than five years later, he gave back to McTiernan by take charge of the saga, placing after the cameras of the third, the jungle of glass. The revenge, which became a commercial success and, at least from my point of view, the best of the first three. If there are people who think that something is already five years later to continue with a series, imagine that they must think the same of what he then analyze: Live Free or Die Hard, i.e., jungle 4.0, the fourth installment of the adventures of McClane arriving twelve years after the third, with a Bruce Willis already well entered the fiftyno hair and without showing its classic white suspenders shirt that will disfigure as it progresses each one of the previous films. Do it this last by age, or by a leap of costume to the character?. Do whatever the case, what is clear is that Willis is no longer the thirty years that I began in this action film, and that for any mortal would be a detail to take into account when it comes to pick up weapons, hold, running to all host, skip, Peel melee or? mounted in the wing of a jet fighter in mid-air and without pilot. Agreed, but in case this is not a film, it is not magic? Therefore ¡que viva magic! The plot is not something important, because basically tells us about always in this type of movies: very bad terrorist (or rather, than any other seems to come out of a Disney movie) plan to give a devastating blow to United States through the "absolute cases", i.e., a computer process that basically destabilize the country completely. Without giving many laps, called Willis quickly before it comes into action. The case is that, at this stage, it is the best possible option. Let me explain. If so first, without knowing anything to the character and as the first installment of the saga, we saw a police cincuentón and bald, quite crushed to be considered as the only hope for the country facing a threat as destructive, we would sound a joke, but those responsible know well that they play with a complicity by the fans, and that will make anything, or almost anyone can be valid without having to extend the presentations. It is why the fifteen minutes we have to McClane distributing estopa forcefully, and 1930s reached one more overly spectacular sequences of function (collision of the car against the helicopter, vista already so many times in the traileres). The good thing about the jungle 4.0 is that, far from losing bellows after those impressive first minutes, maintains the sense of the show until the end, although between scene and scene of action, the moments that connect them are flojillos, so it lost the pace and let interested what this happening, it blames also have on-screen to a villainplayed by Tymothy Olyplath, as such leaves a little to be desired, which intimidates not the slightest. Having said that, is clear in the jungle 4.0 what really matters are the explosions, shots, gaps of action hero which is marked an even more powerful McClane in the heroic sense that the previous (for what to be adapted to the new times, although the McClane always remains in the background). Heard shit of all kinds, but also many good things. There are those who claim that you it's the best four deliveries, a return to the height of the saga and the best action film of what it far this year. But also there are those who say that this is a hoax, a betrayal of the series and the character of McClane, who has lost everything he had. Let's say if I have to position, not I would be with any of the two parts of the discussion, because the jungle 4.0 is a good action movie, a good show without more pretensions to provide a worthy entertainment for those who come to see her, but hence to extol her as the very best of the year not, and neither of the sagabecause I I still staying with the third, although it is by far better than the second and almost put her at the first level. What the alleged betrayal of the spirit of the McClane character I think Dante soplapollez. Where do see those people treason?. What more has remained in the series in this installment is certainly the spirit of the character: his irony, his bravado and their tacos are still present every minute, and the only thing that has changed has been the age. If you can miss more blood, more violence graphic (and not so stylized), but it is what has the desire to make more money by producers (hence the rating PG13 in United States instead of the expected R, which prohibits entry to persons under 18 years if not accompanied by an adult)(, and a charismatic character who accompanies Willis, as it was Samuel L Jackson in the third installment, and here it is replaced by a more bland Justin Long). So, which you have not yet seen the film, and if you are fans of the saga, remember these words: the jungle 4.0 is action, only that. The to look over what I have commented so far, look another proposal on the Bulletin Board. Finally point out that the work of Les Wisseman, new director in the saga, and formerly architect of that thing called Underworld, is pretty decent, and maintains the bluish and gray colors that were already in the aforementioned film of vampires and licántropos, providing a change of look to the series and demonstrating that, in its own way, is something akin to an author. That if, here at least takes the best of his opera prima, the action, and elevates it to the cube.</body>
</review>
