<review author="Bloody Will" title="La sombra de la sospecha" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He had seen hundreds and hundreds of times in other films of the own Douglas, or the last of Harrison Ford, it begins to make merits to be bland in this decade.</summary>
	<body>The worst enemy of this film is the release date. Premiered in the USA in may, and better you iria the box office if you driving in October here in Spain. Have they decided no, and I think that you did you a favor?.I'm going to go: Michael Douglas is Pete Garrison, a veteran agent of the secret service responsible for the safety of the omipotente Mr. President of the USA, but when it is discovered that there is a "mole" within the body of agents, everyone is suspicious of everyone, and the Garrison agent desfallecerá to find the traitor. All this, along with the veteran agent run also Kiefer Sutherland, director of research at the service, and Eva Longoria, rookie agent recommended by the protagonist. Kim Basinger plays the first lady, who doesn't have much to say in this plot.The truth is that it is difficult to anticipate more argument, because the little "surprise factor" which owns the film, takes place precisely in the first 30 minutes. I'm going to be good and not chafaré the movie if someone decides to see her (best when Miss in the plus). But if you notice the following: from the half hour, nothing. And I say nothing because the rest of the film had already seen. He had seen hundreds and hundreds of times in other films of the own Douglas, or the last of Harrison Ford, it begins to make merits to be bland in this decade. And hey, you also her haven't seen, because the plot, after those early surprises of the principle, becomes a succession of situations that have been recreated endlessly by the film, and even the TV movies on Saturdays at 15: 30 of Antena 3. Nothing helps, by the way, that its director who carried the "Swat" screen "The men of Harrelson", that really seems a masterpiece next to it, and therefore repeats identical scheme of action, and in some moments, even in the history.I am not going to say that I like Michael Douglas, but I must say that in this film returns to drawing the same character in "Ni una palabra" and even that "Perfect crime", and with this I mean that their faces and gestures of concern or anger are identical in all these films. It is already very far away his impeccable "Wall Street" Gordon Gekko, and is that with the time Douglas has lost the charisma to finish playing characters very, but very flat.Perhaps the best is Kiefer Sutherland. Of this kind if I can say that I never liked. Up made me hate "Line Mortal", however I I've swallowed each and every one of the episodes of "24". While it is true that here Sutherland takes the protagonist of the series, Jack Bauer, and so calca to detail, is therefore truer that it makes a tontorrón to which Mr. Douglas will give a lesson of how being a good American secret service agent. At least it is the only when you wielding the gun makes it without resemble Woody Allen.De females what to say. As always, when a film comes to rest, and secret agents all ladies are intended to mourn the death of the hero or at palmarla as soon as possible so the prota copper revenge to the beast. Here not even that. "Eva Longoria, hiperfamosa to be the Sra Solis on"Desperate housewives"as well as megarepetidos cosmetic spots", appears in the film to attract unwary that they are created will wear outfits like that it looks in the TV series, and that they will see something pissed that their presence on screen share is lower than knowledge in Geophysics of Van Damme. Of Kim Basinger better not think. Were it not for, in my opinion, overrated "L.A. confidential" this woman would be now announcing on TV sauna belts at 5 in the morning. Say your paper, simply, there is no role.When said at the beginning that best release in October, I was just referring to one plot at base requeteconocida and some interpretations rather than manidas, seems to me difficult that you can raise some minimally acceptable at this time for this type of americanadas.The penalty is that if I was premiered in October and surrounded by Spanish films, is lining!.! The film is as well.</body>
</review>
