<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film of an analog hero in a digital world. Call, dialogues testorénicos and technology, mixed, shaken and cocteleado. Pure fun.</summary>
	<body>There are actors that are guarantee of success when it comes to choosing a film, at least in our humble home. For example, the largest is Robert De Niro, that makes my hair like hooks to hang a Guernika each of them only mention it. Then there are others who I direis are not actors, such as the of the current Governor of California (not me pillais partiendome a phalanx by writing its name) that I love all of his films. Without more. And on the road between these two major, is Bruce Willis. Impressive, both primary and secondary.The film is about about John McClane, a COP in New York, which is assigned to a simple mission, to police station to carry a computer hacker. In these, a terrorist group is killing the latter, so it starts a flurry of call, shots, persecutions, etc, around an all-out terrorist attack based on global connectivity and the unit that has the modern society of telecommunications and informatics.Let's see, the movie begins rather well, not you've sat in the armchair and have already died some few. The theme I like, with a solid technological script. As the thing is advancing, started to make a few of waters, but as the mamporriano level increases exponentially, so nothing happens. We have the usual boasting of John McClane who, along a joke of patterns, does overwhelm the testosterone in the room. What can we say bad? I nothing.In short, film of an analog hero in a digital world. Call, dialogues testorénicos and technology, mixed, shaken and cocteleado. Pure fun.Besitos.P.D: Certainly the plane scene is a passivity, but what else does?Pd2: The use of special effects is not the usual. I would say that the majority of scenes are specialists, what gives added value, at least for me.P.D.3: Vale, the sentence of the analog hero is not mine, but to have been like a gentleman? Hahaha.</body>
</review>
