<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="This is England" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A recent masterpiece that we should not miss under any circumstances and that leaves in diapers and pacifier films - more or less - the same theme as ' American history X'.</summary>
	<body>' This is England', the new film by the British director Shane Meadows, shows us the lives of a group of brewers, revellers, authentic skinheads and lovers of good Jamaican music, to host a child of twelve years, without any kind of social relationship, and become you one of them. Everything is twisted when returns Combo, an old friend who, influenced by nationalist and racist ideas, try to sow hatred and xenophobia in the group. The film is shot in an austere manner that comes as a ring to the finger. It has a perfect rhythm that no lapses in no time, and the address of Meadows is exquisite in every way. The story is a blow emotional tremendous, moves to the coldest of men, and that touches on topics as thorny as nationalism, racism, and the delicate moments that went England in the Decade of the eighties, without falling into any kind of partisan discourse. The film shows successful and crudely, almost documentary, the personal consequences of each of the characters before the war of the Falkland Islands, and (one of) the political movements of extreme tendency that emerged by then. Interpretativamente speaking is a joy. All their players look as if it were the last role of his career. Thus, until the protagonist who is twelve years, Shaun (Thomas Turgoose), passing through an inmensísimo Stephen Graham playing the lunatic Combo (fine character: it seems that you're actually seeing a skinhead of "crappy", which caresses dangerously insane that Graham manages to capture with a resounding success), until the tiny group of skinheads protagonists. All are very natural, credible, and on no occasion outlandish. A recent masterpiece that we should not miss under any circumstances and would leave in diapers and pacifier films - more or less - the same theme as ' American history X'.</body>
</review>
