<review author="Tyler" title="300" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very film adaptation for a story to pedia screaming to be once.</summary>
	<body>Adapt is a difficult exercise and easy at the same time. The cinematographic language is closer to the of the comic than to the literary, which not signifia that is the same or that it looks much, and more if we talk about Frank Miller, who used many literary devices to define their stories.The case of 300 is very specific because the story is very specific, is something very specific. Attack and defense. Point. But that is not bad, this is very good, because it gives the author a big canvas in which Curran. The history of the 300 SPARTANS Leonidas fighting the Persian king Xerxes troops is real, or at least seems. But the reality need not be very film (or very comiquera), the obligation of the author, is therefore not be faithful to the facts and turn them into something kinetic.The story about the comic, is in this case, already pretty film by its rhythm and its duration. It is relatively easy to adapt and Zack Snyder does absolutely fantastic transfer work, making a movie of a fucking great comic cojonuda.300 has a fast-paced beat and a script very consegudo, despite some errors of structure and adaptation. For example the fact to get a plot on the wife of Leonidas of the context of combat, that you a little breaks the rhythm of the constant tension between the Spartan warriors. It is possible that a subplot was necessary to enrich the movie, but I think that this was not the most appropriate. The subplot of Ephialtes is perfectly built and does not disturb anything, for example.SIN CITY, it opened the way to adapt to Miller grace to his success, that we should expect sequels, some of them directed only by the same Miller. 300 uses the same technique as one, perfected and tailored to the plot, with more copper coleres and contrasts more dry. This was the most efficient way of bringing this story to the big screen, because exigia a modernized version of the movies by Don Chaffey esapecie. It is a game of artifice, unreal, extreme and violent. Almost musical, is a species of concert rather than a movie. You can see the movie sequences, and alone they make sense. Because they work so many directors now. They work their movies by pieces, like pieces of a puzzle that you works if same. As a mosaico.300 it is a very good movie with some elements that make it sideways as its extreme duration for a movie that may require something of brevity by what it is telling.The action is fast but the plot sometimes slow and the script suffers a little. In spite of everything is one of the best and most fresh movies of the year, easy to see and easy to enjoy. If you're not a person requiring fidelidada historical facts, which I repeat, in film should not be, the reality can be a fucking great basis for a story, but its development does not have to be kinetic. Who criticized the movie for its lack of historical accuracy, that don't see movies, and read history. Highly recommended thing on the other hand. It is a movie to watch in the cinema, part of its charm is there. It has that old movie made for the big screen feature. Well used technology of today is the cinemascope of our generation. If not a well, you get a real cagada.300 is an easy comic adapted by the fact that history is there, it isn't as adapted, for example, SPIDERMAN, in which you qye have many things into account, because there are thousands of comics, villains and moments. Spider-man is, therefore, less film and, possibly, more television than film, because there is much to condense. 300 for tells you a story in the same comic, and point to the contrary. And it is not because it is a graphic novel, because not a comic is easier to adapt, hell from failed and from the beginning was I knew fallaria. It is not by the adaptation itself. Many say that this story was"to Tim Burton". Tim Burton had happened the same, because a story is not good for the aesthetic you give, a story begins good crew in the script and not to give an aesthetic very cool is saved. Hell, the comic is long and has many moments of research, many coversaciones which, in the language of the comic, you can reduce to two or three drawings and long dialogues. But in film have to dilate, because one doesn't read at the same pace that listens, and the concentration is not the same, nor the image fixed distre both which is in motion. FROM hell it was endless, slow and vague.The same will occur with WATCHMEN, or posiblemnte worse. WATCHMEN is a story that only works in the comic, why is a classic. It is the perfect story for the perfect medium. So dense and complex is that you can not put in two hours of movie, you need much more. WATCHMEN will be unsuccessful, as opposed to 300 which is a superb, fun, extreme work and satisfactiria as a film.Very good.</body>
</review>
