<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Spiderman 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It has its big bugs, but I appreciate much, at least I have entertained enough. I am minimally satisfied with it, but I can not help the true sweet and sour regustillo that has left me.</summary>
	<body>World premiere of 'Spider-Man 3', session golfa (00.15) in the Lauren Viladecans. Despite the time that was, the crowd was considerable. On the floor below, at the entrance of the room, the overcrowding was such that what seemed the entrance of a concert in the Palau Sant Jordi, something that my eyes had ever seen, not least since the boom that was 'The Lord of the Rings'.Definitely, 'Spider-Man 3' raged and had already become a taquillazo. The desire for see it were many, and expectations, very altas.¿Mis expectations? At a midpoint. Throughout the day I had heard all about the movie, and already did not know with what body would come to see her.The fact is that 'Spider-Man 3', I had liked and disappointed in equal parts. The bar was as tall as the Empire State building after the outstanding 'Spider-Man 2', but they have not been able to overcome it. The ingredients were no doubt prepared on the table, but something has failed when it comes to cooking and conceive a succulently satisfying dish.The script and, above all final Assembly (scissors sing la traviata from Plutón), make water: are there really is an argument for a purpose other than the close as the trilogy? Everything is a sequence of sequences like "cause and effect". Now this happens and therefore passes as another, and that is why one has to pass what will happen then. As a soap opera. In fact, 'Spider-Man 3' could be considered a soap opera, as the relationships between the characters (Peter-Mary Jane-Harry) are too present, so much that the appearances of Spider-Man are anecdotal, almost cameos. where does Spider-Man in a film that is specifically entitled 'Spider-Man 3'? Where is this sublime and exquisite planning plot, with a memorable action sequences well vague over the footage, which was 'Spider-Man 2'? In 'Spider-Man 3' sequences of action and wafers that, let us be frank, is what you want to see people (and not) to Mary Jane off-key as one descosida in a Jazz club, you can count on the fingers of one hand SOLA.It disappoints almost null argument and they disappoint the villains, cartoons that Raimi already we had used the first Green Goblin and Doctor Octopus mauve Alfred Molina in the second part. There are important gaps and incomprehensible behaviors with the Sandman (huge and memorable,) on the other hand, the birth of his powers, in a sequence where are only actors images and the beautiful score by Christopher Young, with the new Goblin (if it can be called so) play as they want (now am bad, now good, bad, good, bad, good.), and the symbiote and Venom is the igualicas. And is that they sell us the film as an internal fight between Peter Parker/Spider-Man and its darker side, but said hand, like Venom, is seen and not seen. Twenty minutes of treats and bailecitos (Yes, bailecitos) and au, ahuequen wing.Ultimately, Raimi tries to cover too many things (characters, sub-plots.) in one movie, and it has just saturate itself and without knowing where to throw. Note the pressure suffered by producers director to include with shoehorn venom (it does not look anything,) to the delight of the fans, who were (were) looking forward to. The result. the consequences. This is what you can see on screen: since that the symbiote is Peter Parker (do Spider-Man? does that who is?), that everything happens because Yes (how Earth know Venom to the man of sand O_o?) and too fast. When it comes to the final battle climax, from Peter gets rid of the symbiote (great scene, on the other hand) not have been able to remedy thinking a major "already?".It has its big bugs, but I appreciate much, at least I have entertained enough. I am minimally satisfied with it, but I can not help the true sweet and sour regustillo that has left me: could have come out of 'Spider-Man 3' something really great, possibly one of the best films of superheroes of all time. but not.</body>
</review>
