<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Kill Bill: Volume 1" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A divertimento round from beginning to end, deliciously well written and interpreted.</summary>
	<body>' Kill Bill: Volume 1' is the perfect example of the admirable and incredible talent of Quentin Tarantino. It is not his best work of his short filmography as a director and writer, but it is one of the best. Turns out to be a clear shows the capacity of this man, no longer only directing and writing, but when it comes to putting in scene, which ' Kill Bill: Volume 1' is having the best and brightest of entire Filmography of the American (followed closely by others, clear), resulting in a film with a fresh rhythmlight (thanks to the Division into chapters and a few messy temporary jumps very well written) to excessively frantic, full of extravagant humour and violence graphically explicit, exaggerated and sometimes unpleasant, marks of the House tarantiniana.If wasn't enough, the first volume of 'Kill Bill' turns a delicious homemade cocktail of delicious styles and favorite film genres of Tarantino, which fortunately do not make the mistake of crossing the fine line between homage/allusion and more blatant plagiarism, to adapt effectively and without complexes - turn of - exciting and epic history to not own audiovisual stylescourse of the action films made in Hong Kong.Otra of the countless virtues and Sergio Leone, Akira Kurosawa, Bruce Lee films of ' Kill Bill: Volume 1' and Quentin Tarantino is that no need for grandiloquence to describe the characters (except the de Lucy Lyu. but is this Yes needs it / deserves). You only need an own visual aspect to serve as a single move on the chessboard to describe the personality of the character being treated, although you run the risk that his characters end up being of a considerable emptiness.The only defect, if it is that you can be considered as such, is that ' Kill Bill: Volume 1' is the film "less Tarantino" this man has provided us. There are no dialogues of those that make you ask yourself what the hell is smoking the tito Quentin, and wish him xD, as the mythical "do you know what is Like a virgin?" 'Reservoir Dogs', or any 'Pulp Fiction'.In short, a round from beginning to end, deliciously well written and interpreted divertimento (enorrrrrrrme Uma Thurman). Not recommended for sensitive stomach and movie fan conservative gafapastería.</body>
</review>
