<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Nana" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>As a curious addition to the universe of the countdown, there it is. As a completely independent film, fails.</summary>
	<body>One of the sleeves I enjoy most lately, is 'Nana', and at the end to see his film version in flesh and blood, I can only say that I am disappointed alarmingly.The fact is that this "film", "adaptation" of the fabulous Ai Yazawa manga, has shown me that 'Nana' is only compatible with the universe of the countdown, as to delve into the film to fail miserably. or the universe of 'Nana' or those responsible for the boring and incomplete script of the long before us.Everything is quite mediocrillo: most of the sequences are little more than "anti-cinematográficas" with a totally insipid fixed sequences without music, where the mounting is disastrous, and the word movie looks everywhere. Only a couple of few sequences are saved for this, and are the sequence of the farewell of Ren in the train and the last song of the concert of the Trapnest.El cast is penalty. Not only are fatal characterized, but that casting is pretty inappropriate for an adaptation of a manga where abound men and women seemingly attractive and guapetes in the face. Ren and Shin, among others, NO SON NI DE COÑA Ren and Shin. Nana Osaki that appears is the Coca-Cola Light of evil, and Nobu and Yasu lack completely overflowing personality that enjoyed in the manga. And Junko and Kyosuke? ANDEANDARÁN!The only people that give the paste moderately are Nana Komatsu, Leila, Sachiko and Shôji. Ah! Do not save what nobody is in the performances. All very little College Theater and quite cumbersome, so as a function of cosplayers that little Act.As adaptation, regular. The essence 'Nana' is there, but is very missed and no sense of humor none, as if it has the manga. In addition, is a victim of the newly-invented-for-a-server "syndrome Alatriste": wants to cover taaaantas things (volumes), history is just going from the hands, and quite bundles. That it is good that I am reading the manga, if not I do not think that I have learned much.I came to the same conclusions as to the "live action" of 'Death Note': as a complement curious of the universe of the countdown, there is. As a completely independent film, which is what I appreciate in these cases, fails.And now finally, as the only element remarkable to 100 percent, the soundtrack.</body>
</review>
