<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Death Note" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is absolutely disappointing and disheartening a story so interesting and so exquisitely well thought-out as the 'Death Note' be missed the most in its film adaptation.</summary>
	<body>'Death Note' has been without a doubt the countdown phenomenon that stronger has stuck in the country of the rising sun in recent years. Its original and addictive plot has caught many mangaka throughout all this time. An army of followers has emerged and that has noticed. especially in the portfolio of the creators and editors, seeing the percal, adapted in record time in a fabulous anime manga. But, no doubt, those who were more receptive to that hunger were those of Warner Bros.. Japan, which quickly put the batteries and premiered in 2006, the year 'Death Note' par excellence, two films based on the manga by Takeshi Obata and Tsugumi Ôba. is absolutely disappointing and disheartening that a story so interesting and so exquisitely well thought-out as the 'Death Note' be missed the most in its film adaptation.Directed by Shusuke Kaneko, 'Death Note' has a few characters desdibujados to the core, without any notion of soul and charisma, simple caricatures of what was we presented in the manga or the anime. Mere ghosts wandering, expressionless to say enough is enough (Tatsuya Fujiwara or Asaka Seto reach the Nirvana of the caradeparedismo), who are unable to connect with the spectator at any time. It is terribly sad that transmit thousand times a monigote computer generated as it is the shinigami Ryuuk (which, incidentally, sings La Traviata from Moon.), not their own cast.But that is not the main failure of this film. Really serious is that as adaptation it is really painful. While I watched it, I put in the situation of someone who hasn't heard of 'Death Note' in his life, and I was wondering if it really diagnosed something. It seems that someone you were counting the manga or the anime so very on top, without just going into details that, while they may seem insignificant, are vital.Well, this film lacks the true essence of 'Death Note', and is positioned as a simple complement (and nod to the fans) to the entire universe being built around the phenomenon.The pace of the film, sometimes frantic and sometimes tedious as a day without the internet, does not help.Nevertheless, highlight the work of direction in the final minutes of the film, very correct and vibrant. though arriving late. Also the work done by Ken'ichi Matsuyama as L, the rival of the main character, Yagami Light, who captures with a resounding and rewarding success to the character. And in conclusion, to underline the prologue of the film: with L (for a change), best of all, no doubt.</body>
</review>
