<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Tiempo de Valientes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Action comedy without great special effects, but with a dash of high quality that reminds us that not everything is based on the money</summary>
	<body>My friend the Toxic Avenger recommends is film in his blog, and since is that he likes to taste subtle frames before clotted films, we said see. These Argentine comedies also tend to like us, not be if by what they say, or as say you. But the fact is that we usually stalks us with them. So what, with these magnificent premises not could only give her a chance.The film is an Argentine psychologist (who would say Sabina) who is sentenced by the judge (also Argentine, is an Argentine film) to do social work for the community by a traffic accident he suffered. So, it is a federal policeman who is depressed by his wife he deceives another to attend. So it is a very odd couple that has to solve a case of enforced disappearance of two types is complicated to lay bare the shames of the Argentine courts.That good panzá to laugh we got between chest and back with this production. For starters, I love the strength of the script, given that without large hisses gets you very quickly in the film, you wrapped subtly and finish very stuck in it. Things that happen have their speck of credibility and, although quite sad and hard (harsh reality) are with this much-needed funny dot. Change of roles faced the two protagonists, that trasmután is also very interesting their identities. And the final outcome, with that little bit of nonsense and the inability that has, I also liked. It is not very credible, but it not inferior to the rest of the film. Notably, the scene is that they smoke marijuana in the car, which is totally subrealista, and the dinner at home of the psychologist. Very large both.In short, comedy action without great special effects, but with a dash of high quality that reminds us that not everything is based on money and you can make magnificent films with not too much.</body>
</review>
