<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="María Antonieta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Stress, of course, in pink fosforito, chord for the occasion, that 'Marie Antoinette' is not a film for all palates. Cannes attests.</summary>
	<body>Sofia Coppola closed his "pop" trilogy on women, preceded by 'the Virgin suicides' with 'Marie Antoinette' and ' Lost in translation'.In 'Marie Antoinette', the daughter of Francis Ford Coppola demonstrates, once again, his talent behind the camera, providing his unique vision on life at Versailles was the last Queen of France, Maria Antonieta Josefa Juana of Austria, who was beheaded during the French Revolution and that triggered a war between France and your country of originAustria.Pero that is not what we are discussing. Coppola gives us a first hour of footage with a mise en scene exquisite and hypnotic art direction. Shows us every day in Versailles, almost like travelling in time and put a film same camera, but with the particular vision of the Coppola Miss, that breaks with all topics of time film and shows, to cite something, a young Marie Antoinette despilfarrando money with dozens of sweets, wigs and dressesto the beat of "I want candy" that, like the rest of contemporary music that appears in the film (which is not to be much) goes like ring to the finger at what is happening on screen.Fortunately for my mental health, and from my point of view, 'Marie Antoinette' does not fall into extreme gafapastismos as he was afraid that it was going to happen. However, Sofia Coppola makes a mistake that is the major drawback of this film: it is stretching the gum nauseam and from a given point (Ballo in Maschera), the pace so characteristic that he carried the film (paused but addictive) drops to the small final act.About Kirsten Dunst, two things: that would have liked the real Marie Antoinette as she (basically because, judging from some portraits, was more ugly than the shit), and which is a lost case.Bass guitar yet and thus my point of view, good measure of the "coppolita", although less to ' Lost in Translation'. Also stress, of course, in pink fosforito, chord for the occasion, that 'Marie Antoinette' is not a film for all palates.Cannes attests.</body>
</review>
