<review author="Naty Buqué" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A crappy for drug addicts with little imagination.</summary>
	<body>The fountain, Aronofsky, is about fear, the fight against and the concept of death, in a film divided into three independent diegéticamente parties, means-tested, however two of them, from the meaning, a main.Here are the reasons why this film is radically horrible, hackneyed, stupid, corny, unbearable: 1. The two minor story lines work as an allegorical representation of obvious and unnecessary that underestimates the capacity of understanding of the Viewer, that is to not only see how are repeated in the form of allegory (i.e. correspondence to one of the main elements of the central plot and these two) exactly the same meanings as in the main, but, as if it were not enough, in this same part must hear, from a scientific course, atrocities (due to its lack of verisimilitude say it) like "death is a disease like any and I can cure it" (we are going already understood that the man the death does not sit well, but they won't of say stuff). 2. Aesthetics ochentoso-futurista in one of the minor stories causes nausea. It seems that we are seeing a video clip of low-budget Daft Punk instead of an Aronofsky.3 film. The radical mixture of concepts, beliefs, religioso-filosóficas trends operating in the film as a "everything gives equal". The important thing is to oppose the Western scientism (bad bad bad) anything. Do and then put to the Mayans and a peeled meditating as good, total? the post is to accept death, else are unimportant details (which makes me doubt the seriousness of the treatment of the kabalah, which nothing know, Pi). 4. The thematic trite romanticista-antipositivista (i.e., at most, 19th century, gentlemen) anchored in a trite love tragedy, without input of any kind to any of the two clichés (except, of course, that man becomes a peeled and women in a tree in one of the three stories). 5. Several monkeys appear to have been tortured during the filming.In short, a crappy for drug addicts with little imagination.</body>
</review>
