<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Ella es el chico" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>All the criticism I've read of this film agree that is rubbish, which prevents me from completely say what think of it, i.e., the sensational, entertaining and stimulating that seems</summary>
	<body>Viola, you can not break me, tells his ex-boyfriend, nobody breaks for football. But Viola thinks that football is a good reason to stop this guy. He is a liar who alone tells him that she plays well and publicly tells him that he can not play as a boy. Viola needs to know a man as it is. And on the other hand she believes that you can play football as well as a man. Viola can get two things when his brother escape from home two weeks and she ranks in the male boarding school. Thanks to his disguise of chico, Viola has access to the Sancta Sanctorum: on the one hand can inform men from within, without having to endure the costume are placed in front of the girls. On the other hand you can train on the men's soccer team.More fun "She is the boy" is to see the girl trying to disguise what is, perhaps because it lays bare an inevitable truth that we're not the same.The comedies of Shakespeare, and this more, are always stories of love that bind. Viola, the protagonist, is the glue of all couples. The handsome, Duke, takes three years sighing for the beauty, but achieves nothing; the beauty, Daphne, has come out with all the boys but remains the same of sad, the ugly girl in the story does not come out with anyone because you have the ugly label. All missing something, and it seems that Viola has a magic wand. Daphne lets you read one of the poems of Sebastian by mistake. In his role as man has an appointment with the ugly and it ceases to be ugly. Seems able to even join their parents. It is a girl if they put it in a convent makes it a matrimonial Agency.All the criticism I've read of this film agree that is rubbish, which prevents me from completely say what think of it, i.e., the sensational, entertaining and stimulating that I think. Sometimes critics are like the nutritionists, priests, doctors, Governments, prohibit you all you like.Francisco Mariner: the comical is limited to the predictable the girl's plight when he has to go to the showers or when her voice betrays. Roberto Piorno: She is the boy is the proptotípica posh teenage, corny and romantic comedy that House as well usually with the tastes of the American public of that age.</body>
</review>
