<review author="José A. Peig" title="En la ciudad de Sylvia" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>On the terrace of a café, various compositions of faces, with a profusion of shadows and reliefs, draws with his eyes words lost in incomplete conversations, fragments of reality which constitute the great search puzzle.</summary>
	<body>The new film by José Luis Guerin urges us, once again, to interfere in a search of the significance of the film and his role as art or means of communication, with subtlety and enormous formal coherence, their work is for the movie buff cause for reflection in order to try to glimpse an ontology of cinema, a glance sustained in the analysis of the evolution of cinema since it origin until today. Film is poetry of the image, or the image is the reality of the pristine look before all the tricks with which the aesthetic effort has been burying the supposed original truth?. We have a lyrical work or it is pure realism and document a moment in a corner of life?.Minimalism requires a certain amount of ambiguity, but in the city of Sylvia is a film that does not hide any of their features and responses appear in a simple act of understanding. Indeed, is a film about corners of life, in particular, a city that darkens and dawns governed by the routines of every day in the different neighborhoods, premises and belongings of the collective and individual life. The long flat and the travelling along its streets built an exploration of the urban landscape, subordinate to the spiritual search contained in the history of the young artist subjected to a female Epiphany, a ghostly object that acquires the uniqueness of the Palindrome, a maze of female faces that form the multifaceted image of an obsession of the dream (from the billboards starring beautiful women to the graffiti that constantly appears on the walls of the city;) (Do j? aime Laure, reference to the loves of Petrarch). Thus the city is not a "real" space as a reverie of the artist. And when we talk about the artist, we mean to José Luis Guerin and Xavier Lafitte, each one of which it personifies the subjective gaze of the camera. La ciudad de Sylvia is only a fleeting image created by the artist, a space of symbols that concentrated the various manifestations of the dream. It is therefore, lyrical film based on a real field.The subjective gaze unfolds in two layers, one metaphor for the other. The expressiveness of the face of Xavier Laffite (emphasized by the blue of her eyes, beauty element introduced with the purpose of attracting the attention of the viewer and do involve search) is the best instrument to represent explicitly suggesting the visual composition of Guerin in the formal-estética field. The camera sets the abstract narration that the central character translates into immediate sensations. In this way, get the proper symbiosis enters two eyes a complementary relationship from which emerges the concept a couple clearly to the precision and simplicity of each level. Film material such as the representation of a State of being in search of beauty, or the past, of itself cannot be interpreted. In the sequence that opens the story, we see Xavier sitting in bed and absorbed in an idea. He is the creator becoming aware of their need for artist, and then goes out to the street to find (any creation implies a process of searching). On the terrace of a café, draws with his eyes (and here Guerin melts the two perspectives in one, with which we are dealing with the use of subjective camera) various compositions of faces, with a profusion of shadows and reliefs, words lost in incomplete conversations, fragments of reality which constitute the great search puzzle. The memory, the past, love, beauty, are so ephemeral and undefined as the puzzle in the real image subordinated to a subjective assessment. The scene in question is meritorious by the narrative tension deployed in a single set but of enormous complexity when moved it to its abstract meaning, which reaches its maximum expression in the image of the supposed Sylvia reflected in crystals of a café or in the Windows of the tramway; the Evanescence of remembrance and anguish which puts an end to the search. The creator was looking for his art in a woman's face, and it teaches a polyphenic and elusive character of the same substance which intended to endorse. Finally, one might wonder whether this impeccable exercise of cinema, which aims to take us to the original meaning of the film through an exploration of life, has more force and narrative value by the mere fact of being. No one can deny the perfect use of film by Guerin, but beyond the formal adjusted to the millimetre working in order to articulate the meanings, it is obvious that the idea developed stumbles with its inherent schematic, and there comes a time in which representation is in the foregoing preceding images. In the light of this, we raised the question of whether dramatic progression of meaning not encalla at any given time to fall in a static address, without involving a setback to the values exposed with effectiveness.</body>
</review>
