<review author="José A. Peig" title="Jungla de cristal 3: La venganza" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tape fun at times, well done, but lacks dramatic force and real ingenuity that goes beyond efectistas beats in a script full of tacos and vulgar claims for little demanding audiences.</summary>
	<body>The hallmark of Die Hard was John McClane, hero improvised in unexpected situations. The precedents were still the same idea, and in particular the second already was a bland repetition and the beast of the masterpiece of John McCtiernan. It had its logic rescue the hero and placing it in new circumstances. This time no longer in place and wrong time, but in his city together with the colleagues and weekend hangovers. As always, McClane a normal type, but the plot, in this case, does not seem intended for the character in question, and indeed, the screenplay for this film suffered several modifications due to the theft of ideas towards other similar productions. The home is quite overwhelming, someone claimed the presence of McClane while blackmailing by placing bombs. Soon comes in Zeus, character played by Samuel l. Jackson, sour character and an acid sense of humor that will collide against the no less deadpan vehemence of John McClane. Simon says.A macabre guessing game that allows to establish a triple chemistry between the duo McClane-Zeus and the cynical coldness of Simon (Jeremy Irons). In this area, say the script presents a wit and a fluidity that, at least, it works pretty well in the case of an action film encorsetado film genre that hardly can offer us something creative or worthwhile from an aesthetic and intellectual perspective.In reality, little offers the film apart from the dramatic scenes and the correct implementation of McCtiernan, which manages to keep pace in a story that extends for too many minutes to tell us a story too simple and worthy of any typical pigswill gender (a story suitable for filming a bad sequel to the "Lethal weapon" series). Dialogues are reduced to things as ".the of I do not touch the balls you put lightning in the ass" or "I'll put the truck in the ass" or "am like the duracell muñequito.". Be that as it may, it seems that these expressions have penetrated in an important sector of the spectators, and described as "ingenious script" to what is nothing to be funny in an area of serie B, and in case of necessity of vacuous entertainment for not squeezing the fontanel. History, as we have said, simple, predictable, repeated the idea of the first jungle. Like Hans Grubber, Simon feigns psychotic ideals to mislead and cover up a robbery. The plot then divided the action in different sub-actions which are stretched and often lose intensity due to excess of superfluous details, and that is the main problem of the film; a poorly structured script - by what have too you and what lacks - posed various actions (the persecution of McClane on the one hand, that of Zeus on the other, the theft of the federal Reserve Bank of New York, and school under threat of bomb) without articulate them in a dramatic all cohesive. Precisely, lacks it dramatic incentives that will do justice to the vicissitudes of McClane, which in its two precedents were always involved a commendable dramatic tension. Or think a product worthy of Steven Seagal or Stallone more humanized and portrayed by Bruce sum Willis.En hero, tape fun at times, well done, but there is a lack of dramatic force and real ingenuity that goes beyond efectistas beats in a script full of tacos and vulgar claims for little demanding audiences.John McClane in the first Die Hard of McCtiernan meant to raise a genus with a tendency towards mediocrity as it is that of action cinema, to the epic and Crafts category. McCtiernan returned to take the lead and brought us the harsh reality. As already discussed, Die Hard is a film miracle, and the genre of action - twenty years later - still expecting a response that will do him justice. Because we insist, masterpieces which have slum to a specific genre have not to be revered and back to them, but to get closer to them or, in the best of chances, be overcome.</body>
</review>
