<review author="Yojimbo" title="En la ciudad de Sylvia" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Stay in one of these so-called exercises "of copyright" that will delight the unconditional gafapastas and will twist in his armchair and rebufar several times to the viewer who wants to give him a chance to another type of cinema.</summary>
	<body>Those who had the opportunity to see the film the day of the premiere in the CGAI (La Coruña), presented by its director and accompanied by a "Press Conference" by way of presentation of Cahiers du Cinema in Spanish, have seen several things. While the director says that "no longer have film critics in the mainstream media", I understand that I can be here and now, one of those who perhaps heed or some consideration. Ironies aside (and in my other blog), the film is an authentic boredom. What the director considered "simple" is simply simple. His previous film, "under construction", with an enviable collection of about 700,000 euros, was a documentary that smelled of fiction. This last film seeks to be upside down.However it does not manage naturalness. Its reality is cardboard, they are actors who can't interpret, which has not been able to or wanted to shoot in a natural way. Extras seeking to be a fictional town are horrifyingly aimed, so the city seems rather taken by geeks and people that circulate with astonishing regularity and above all, disturbing.But despite the boredom of an hour and a half, I have to praise the good taste of the director has chosen to be an actress as a pillar. Although its presence in the "plot" is entirely accidental and therefore short, is the only one that can respond to the intention of the director to the viewer find the beauty supposed search the protagonist.However, and for those positions as "reflective" which presumed perpetrators of this type of films, the beauty of Pilar is obvious. And many enjoy it on screen. But one could say that it is a contribution to the culture of the idealized beauty that many criticize posters with "unrealistic women". An effort of the director for having achieved an anonymous actress would have appreciated (can perhaps the waitress?), with a particular beauty and have portrayed its attractiveness to the protagonist (well handsome too, what a coincidence) and we, the viewers, we sorprendiéramos with reality. What has happened to the era of the wonderful "brief encounter", in which we thought the relationship of the characters and they were, as banal, physically very corrientuchos?In any case, although the story that moves this film seems the portrait of a stalker, stays in one of these so-called exercises "of copyright" that will delight the gafapasta unconditional and will twist in his armchair and rebufar several times to the viewer who wants to give him a chance to another type of cinema. And not only me retorcí I recorded. I had more people to the side.I do not recommend this film even for those who want to see a great actress as the pillar on screen again. Wait to the dvd or any pass in the Doré cinema.</body>
</review>
