<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If a charismatic player very well assisted by a handful of good actors added to a perfectly planned and carried out action scenes, the result cannot be other than the consecration of Greengrass as one of the greats of our day action film.</summary>
	<body>As I said on occasion, "The Bourne ultimatum" (The Bourne ultimatum) was with "Ratatouille" one of the last hopes film of the summer, in American cinema.It was not easy Paul Greengrass. After having made "The myth of Bourne", one of the best action movies that they remember, and have shaken the expectations before his new film "United 93", they were high.Finally, as was the case with "Ratatouille", I believe that Greengrass has left happy up to the most demanding.Some will attack it by the script, excuse usual to attack the action film, but it is not the script most importantly a tape. Despite this, it works perfectly and has interesting details. With respect to the history that counts, suffice it to say that we we have the resolution of the identity crisis of the agent Jason Bourne (Matt Damon), known by all those who have seen previous deliveries.Really impressive in the film is his, so frenetic pace that I must consult the IMDB to verify that it lasts 111 minutes which to me seemed a sigh. A rhythm that is supported, not so commented camera movements, in a stunning montage and a perfect planning of the action scenes.An example of the spectacular takes place in Tangier and persecution that deserves a place of honor in the Pantheon of the great persecutions of cinema. By the way, to me the resolution of the scene reminded me what that said Hitchcock how difficult that is killing a human being and that it shaped in stunning images in "Torn curtain".But back to the subject of camera movements for a second. The most insightful will be thinking: is this the same Jeremy Fox who criticizes movements of Chamber of Michael Bay and its excess levels?Yes, I am, and I think that we must differentiate between wildly move the camera and move it frantically. In the first case, you will lose the reference of what you see on screen to the point of that if we intent the image even would say what they are seeing. That is what is happening in much of the film of Michael Bay and the fights of robots of the recent "Transformers", on the other hand of more content of Bay, would be a good example.Instead, with Greengrass happens just the opposite: there is not confusion but binge. We know at all times what is happening. One of the reasons why I think much better director to Greengrass that we add a charismatic player very well assisted by a handful of good actors and a really powerful soundtrack to Bay.Si to a perfectly planned and carried out action scenes, the result can not be other than the consecration of Greengrass as one of the greats of our day action film.I could not have found a better place to demonstrate his talent in this conclusion is, possibly together with the initiate "Jungle of glass", the best action in the history of the cinema trilogy.Final rating: 9 out of 10</body>
</review>
