<review author="Bloody Will" title="Hairspray" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I openly admit that I was about to plunge into the corridor of the room to hit me four meneos. For some time he enjoyed not so much in the film music within, with a film.</summary>
	<body>Music pure and hard. Rhythm, rhythm and more pace. Do with these two sentences could be summed up basically what you'll find yourself in?Hairspray?.I begin this criticism synthesizing my impressions about the movie because I warn you previously that this is a tape completely different to which they are accustomed to seeing in the film.Do is not an action film with stratospheric explosions and gunfire to navigate, ni nor a drama desquiciantes dialogues, not even a light comedy of topical or clever, jokes according to the tastes.?Hairspray? It is 100% a film musical adrenalíticamente, which in the profane or not supporters of the genus them may be weary to such succession of vocal temazos and electrifying, chained dances with minimal linked phrases from script, but that the megalomaniacal hardened will probably seem a best gift for your eyes and your ears. I openly admit that I was about to plunge into the corridor of the room to hit me four meneos banned at the frenetic pace of the songs performed by Nikky Blonsky, Elijah Kelley or Queen Latifah, the best cast for my taste.But we must also recognise the outstanding contribution of the rest of the actors (special mention do also guaperas Zac Efron, medio-reconocible John Travolta, James Marsden surprising and even the elusive incredibly Christopher Walken), which makes one have the desire to get out of a jump seat. The continuous movement of the feet under the seat from the second song (?)(Do The Nicest Kids in Town?) does you it no one.And it is that one cannot help getting as much positivity and divertimento transmitting the film. There is no rest for the melodic neurons in our head. Only a story a tad child that it takes place in a world of pink (including the racial issue), whose importance lies only in that serves as a link to the next item, interrupts the evocative magic of?Grease?.Does no one can deny that the soundtrack of?Does Hairspray?, slightly reminiscent of that mythical tape of 78. This is due to the clear setting at the beginning of the years 60 Americans from the film of Adam Shankman, with dresses Princess carded impossible filled with lacquer and engominados Cambiar. What did however, Randal Kleiser with?Grease? It was a work of art on all four sides, and its classic shade is very long; In short, an insurmountable barrier.Pity that?Hairspray? not going to have the same impact. Is the music scene now very different from what known?Do Grease?, but it is commendable that Shankman has wanted to get with his film to new generations; Besides the fact that many many teenagers go to see her only to stun with Efron phenomenon (I had a few back whose drooling felt in the neck), the rest will enjoy a few topics with very cane arrangements, by the work of producer Marc Shaiman, despite his sixties style.Really, for some time I enjoyed not so much in the film music within, with a film. Most of the soundtracks of the films today are simple instrumental accompaniments of suspicious similarity who come rarely to become real actors in his career in the market of the CD; However, the soundtrack of?Hairspray? It is the true engine of the film, with the added value that its interpreters are those that reveal face and body (and go bodies, in all sizes) to the peculiar characters of this film adaptation.On none of them are there noticeable objections despite the ensemble cast of the time on camera. The choice of Nikki Blonsky has been perfect; This aunt is a pure nerve and it seems incredible that with his physique can move that way. His voice I put no buts.Amanda Bynes makes wonder that dangerously suggestive rebellious schoolgirl. Attention to her extremely tight dress in the final dance. Michelle Pfeiffer I said I was amazing at his age. And bad or I tell you.Christopher Walken breaks radically with its gloomy and serious image and draws smiles often. Dancing with John Travolta, priceless. Latter it goes without say that it has an incredible merit; getting around so well in that bag of rubber is commendable, and make credible his role as troubled mother of Tracy is quite an achievement.James Marsden is unrecognizable in his musical facet. I was pleasantly surprised by its versatility. Zac Efron makes no tiresome chulito, just what you need to thread the tape. Elijah Kelley is a machine; you only need to see him in action. And Queen Latifah plays a great matriarch of color luxury. Your interpretation of?I know where I? ve been? It puts the willies.Do ultimately, it did lack the usher put us a dropper to put us in vein mesmerizing rhythm of?Hairspray?. Suffice to say that since I left the cinema yesterday not I could take I head the catchy dance song of the great apotheosis end of the film titled?Do You can? t beat stop?. Tátan, so, so, so, so, so, so?. biiiiiiiiiiiit. Here me I am rehearsing a few steps.</body>
</review>
