<review author="Bruji" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After twelve years, fans of the series deserved much more than a succession of trailers without sense.</summary>
	<body>Along with the Crystal, the jungle loses the ability to entertain; main objective? if not only - of the action genre. The specific scenes shot with specialists and the charm? in other scripts, irresistible - Willis - MacClane, unable to avoid the bankruptcy of a thin plot line of cheap Americanism. After twelve years, fans of the series deserved much more than a succession of trailers without sense. What was that phrase of Samuel Goldwing, uneducated and unusual magnate of the Metro?, "Last night went to see Hamlet." "It is full of citations". Comes me to mind everytime I get bored in the film, and is a smart way to repay the more than thousand pesetas cost, the search for "dates" that can be remembered. Here are two memorable: "O tell me everything you want to know, or you since Gee in your own house", and "Going to be Yipi-qui - Yei, son of a bitch". That no one bother looking for more in a jungle so limited.Once again, the American movie industry back to underestimate the Viewer. After twelve years, fans of the Crystal jungle deserved much more than a succession of trailers or sense offline, much more than this hint of a quarter is intended to be and ends up not being. Neither more nor less than what usually happens when any script "worth" to insert "total chaos" scenes of Independence Day, without taking into account that this was never the spirit of the jungle, reinventora of the action genre. Ultimately, that no one forget that Willis is a full and lovely cocoon because the writers invented to John MacClane so wanted.They are welcome, however, the action scenes that are shot with specialists, unique tribute to the original story of 1988. In them, no surprise short and cheats levels including Wiseman to convince bad chinita skilful martial arts, but the male chauvinist, xenophobic, and derogatory comments that dedicates the mythical detective from New York, now unknown. The script fails while the scenes of hit and punch are replaced by a tireless dance of special effects of latest technology, again that end up doing credible the risky lies of James Cameron. Ultimately, Americans love to be in danger, and his cinema continues bad ideas to achieve this. Obsolete, but bad. And is that the story of computer attacks and the certainty that "anybody, from a garage, with a computer, can win the game to security systems, absolutely incompetent" already knew them thanks to products like the network, conspiracy in Ditto, the test or the recent e infumable operation Stormbreaker. We are not unknown starts cheap patriotism; interpretation, perhaps misguided, famously said of President Kennedy, or that another Monroe calling "America for the Americans", which can only add that this type of cinema, also for them.This is a story without its own identity, in not few occasions, presented as a bad collage of topical frame of the genus. A story based on a brittle script, son of an outdated argument that fails to capture the attention of the respectable. Between ridiculous dialogues of sea bream, pathetic monologues and secondary actors in movie, Bruce Willis is feeling as a new Marlon Brando, producer and estrellita, who, with troubled face, does not hesitate to get their hands on a screenplay? already lousy - to complete the sentencing him. And commented the devil that, of all his virtues, vanity was the most satisfied; and with an assertion like this: "If there were someone else, it would let you do it, but we must not" are revealed the actor claims. As he said that genius, there can be a good film if there is a good script. The de La jungle 4.0 is responsible for directly undermine the figure of John MacClane, seductive of the 1990s, annoying entity in the areas police, not to grant any premise that help you to understand the purposes of his adversaries, nor the role of his companions. Although it was not easy to resist the temptation to mention 9/11, stating that the end of USA is the end of the world, that lousy shooters are always on the side of the bad guys and the angels of custody in the of the good, that of the FBI have no idea, and that all flights have landed to avoid suspicionsonly get to precipitate the death of a Guild, the writers, that, in the present century, fails to leave his own incompetence.</body>
</review>
