<review author="Tyler" title="Seven" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A masterpiece by one of the geniuses that we can enjoy those who are of this generation.</summary>
	<body>Which are those movies that one is you come to mind when speaking of this concept is that of "modern classics"? It is a strange concept with which lovers we are constantly. You can't believe in him or not, but it exists. Many have respectable opinion that a movie should survive for 20 years as a cult movie to become a clésico, others think that there are movies that are born so.In one way or another, the movie which I mean, Seven, is one of those movies that we come to mind. The head. The movie of "the head in the box" for many, in the same way as for other many American History Xfué film "the mouth in the kerb". So many movies of the nineties are the memory, and it's funny. Everyone remembers Seven.David Fincher is that indispensable (along with Quentin Tarantino) director to understand cinema of the 1990s. That of "reinventing" the film is a lie, it is a hoax. Film not reinvents itself; the film is recycled it is copied or is still doing the same. Because the film is defined long ago. So it cannot be said that Fincher, what you can say is that it revived the film. He took a classical script with the cliché of the poli old about to retire and the young and energic poli newcomer to the city, and turned it into a reference title. A cult movie and a masterpiece. Andrew Kevin Walker, which is a magnificent craftsman of the script tanning in the tv series "Stories of the crypt" or movies as "Brainscan"(una_serie_B_fantástica), wrote from a simple idea, seven deadly sins, seven murders. It had relatively recently that "El Silencio de los Coderos" had returned to fashion smart serial killers. A.K.Walker thought it would be a good idea launch this project and try to sell it. The perspective he gave to the script was quite unique in the sense that was much darker and more perverted than any other movie of assassins in series. David Fincher came from fighting with the producers of Jeunet and was desperately looking for a project that vent. Originally Seven not noticed you until arriving at the time that John Doe, the murderer masterfully played by Kevin Spacey, is delivered. Fincher thought: in that movie a serial killer given him?. That was what pushed him to go.Because of course, that can be quite garrafal script failure, but everything has its because, because behind the script for Seven there is another script of the own murderer, which is weaving his history and his crimes so ultimately charged sense.Seven has a nearly perfect script. But it is not. What happens to Seven is the first half something caught with pins in some respects. The action forced at some points in the script to make it as shown, being quite improbable. But the second half is perfect. Round. And if a guióle give an audience a second half like that, the public forgets the bug has been able to see, if esque has seen them. Porue despite having many traps, Seven better than anyone conceals their mistakes. For example, it is a little forced as Somerset (Morgan Freeman) discovers the writing on the stage of gluttony after the refrigerator. Through a few small, tiny, plastiquitos found in the stomach of the unfortunate who forced them to eat until you burst. The detective takes these plastiquitos to the scene of the crime, and in no time discover what are soil, specifically of having moved the fridge. A little improbable, but Hitchcock said that you one, when working the suspense, does not have to be totally plausible, therefore does not have to be a mistake. This also the fact of and discover the House of Doe. Mills (Pitt) and Somerset (Freeman) flock, by the hand of the latter, a seller of confidential information from the FBI, which seems to be that it controls all the books that takes any citizen. I.e., to see if the peña read about Hitler, how build crappy murders or atomic bombs. So they get a list of names, which lead directly to John Doe. This is a very risky resource, because people might not believe it, but as it is something about what we do not know anything, which makes the Governments with our lives, quite extreme licenses are permitted, and in the script conceals very well putting a small comedic conflict between detectives.The development of history it marked the murders, and it is made from the point of view of the detectives, giving us only a perspective of the crimes. We only see another point of view at the end, when talking about John Doe, but we see it from the point of view of the detectives. The only secuendcia that is from the point of view of the murderer, possibly that which occurs in the same House. The House almost, provides the sickly view of the sequence.Fincher opts for a crude and depressing movie. Something very risky, because it is not pleasant to see, not enough to the public nothing in what you feel comfortable. Everything is dirt and rain. Something typical of 1970s, and cinema for a movie in particular Klute, Alan j. Pakula. In which Fincher supported as a reference to tell the story so sickly way. The movie itself does not show much violence, only suggested and not voi to say the that pollada "what our minds can imagine is much stronger," but the tone of the movie makes the suggestion of violence much stronger than violence itself, and above all, the attitude of the people before the same; very well represented by the owner of the puticlú where he died the victim of lust.Photo and mounting and, above all, the Assembly of sound, are master. The hopeless, absolutely brutal, very own Fincher's atmosphere cut you the body. And it is also joined by a secuenci of credits worth millions, something totally brutal, which seems taken from a mondo movie. It really tells you the tone of the movie, and from the beginning you are with the knotted stomach. You do not want to eat when you finish seeing her, you are disgusted to be person. Same as with the fight club.The end better than a zipper closes, is absolutely round. The crimes charged sense, and you feel fatal because, somehow, you understand the murderer. And you no guilt you. You are like him, even being atheo. A masterpiece orchestrated by one of the geniuses that we can enjoy those who are of this generation and who are still alive.</body>
</review>
