<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El fontanero, su mujer y otras cosas de meter" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film S with women of truth, when the silicone was placed in joints and not her tits. To descojonar a time of laughter. I do not speak of sexual themes, that my girl scolds me then.</summary>
	<body>Well, today is a glorious day. Titus Chinchan will publish his first criticism of a porn movie, and this is historical. Certainly it is not the first thing I see, but yes to more I laughed. Although I have to say that I did not know that it was porn, but that he had put her, it is going to do. If I've seen things like the nun or Rotwailer, as I am not going to see this?The film is about a plumber who is in bed to his wife with another guy, which coincidentally is his best friend. Total, which is mosquea and will fit women of the friend that quickly make it. Total, this leads to a picha-coño - teta-mouth non-stop in the 75 minutes of film. At the end passes as the 2 sides of the bed, but well past, without half measures. I feel I have been the end, but it is to avoid that you say that you have only seen the beginning.Well, this movie is the cane. It has everything you can expect from a film. Nipples everywhere and insured laughs, nothing of special effects and varied scenarios. The script is sober and fits very well to the pre-established idea that you take by simply viewing the poster. No surprises or upsets, but retains the narrative tension very well until the final surprise. As the film sketches, I tell you a scene. The plumber is with a girl. Total, that you made a powder to the above without lowering the zipper of the monkey (an Iberian male is 100%). She tells him that he has left half (the stays to entire) total that makes him a cunningulis. He says that after the mantecao, ná de ná. She, neither short nor lazy, is going to the bidet and "Czech, Czech, Czech" leave it to eat soups in it. The Lord recula, but in the end accepted. But as it has become to go without removing the monkey, she takes a quick decision. Grab the plunger, so click on the floor and gets to gallop on it, which encourages the plumber to one afiladita Sable. Crazy.In short, movie S with women of truth, when the silicone was placed in joints and not her tits. To descojonar a time of laughter. I do not speak of sexual themes, that my girl scolds me then.Besitos.P.D: I was going to put a classification based on cocks of gold, but I do not want.Pd2: now, traspasamé, traspasaaaaaaameeeeeeeee!!!!!P.D.3: Public this because my girl has given the go-ahead to but I would not dare.</body>
</review>
