<review author="José Córdoba" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A pleasant surprise, a spectacular, short film entretenidísima. Recommended, although far from the level of the first three.</summary>
	<body>The success of films such as the star wars or in search of the Lost Ark changed the world of cinema at the end of the 1970s. Its influence not only was circumscribed in the genres of science fiction and the adventures, but it is also noticed in the 1980s action genre. Gone are realistic films, distressed characters of the police genre of the 1970s. It was the time for normal men transformed into heroes reluctantly of solitary police able to wipe more bizarre and lofty plans of the bad turn. In the mid-1980s until the mid-1990s, the new genre of most spectacular action, more violent enjoyed its golden age. These were the years of jungles of Crystal, lethal weapons of predators. Its main feature was the spectacular nature, his incredible ability to destroy the most diverse scenarios.Directors such as Richard Donner, John McTiernam, James Cameron and Renny Harlin reached its greatest appreciation during those years. During these years were all very poor but also great movies achievements, almost always coming out of the hands of these directors. In the field of interpreting its protagonists were, without doubt, Bruce Willis, Arnold Schwarzenegger, Mel Gibson and, to a lesser extent, Sylvester Stallone. Unfortunately with the passing of the years the genus deteriorated giving entrance to by-products starring Steven Seagal and Jean Claude Van Damme. Two failures, one absolute and another relative, gave end to that stage, in what also influenced the entry of another style of directors like Michael Bay. The two failures are the last great hero (Last Action Hero, John McTiernam, 1993) and lies risky (True Lies, James Cameron, 1994). The first was the great hope of the year 1993 Columbia, one of the most expensive films of the Decade, with a promotion that came to place the logo of the film on the ship Columbia; everything in order to stand up to the great enemy of that year, Jurassic Park (Steven Spielberg Jurassic Park). At this point everyone knows who won the race. The film of McTiernam, an autoparodia tribute to cinema and the own genre of action, did not end to find an audience that did not expect to find with a film, a pity, as it is a film very estimable, full of action and with a great rhythm and sense of humor, knowing always laugh at himself. Lies risky, the failure is relative, the film ended up being profitable although it did too much money, not taking into account that it was the most expensive film of the story (something common to Cameron, a good director unable to control the shooting). After these two films major studios threw the brake elefantiásicos for this type of film budgets, and were gradually disappearing from the box office. Managers, their careers were disparate, McTiernam would not have full confidence of a large study, still later shot glass jungle: the revenge, by request of Willis; Donner has continued rolling with some success, although increasingly less ambitious films; Harlin, on the other hand, after the failure of the island the heads cut, was relegated to serie B by-products; James Cameron after Titanic disappeared, although it is currently working on his new project, Avatar.Todo this stuff is beside the point of the premiere of the jungle 4.0, which is an attempt to return to the roots of the genre that has been invaded by managers unable to provide rate or personality to his films, that fold under the orders of the studies without complaintpeople like Rob Cohen or Bret Rattner. Michael Bay on the other hand, seems increasingly of the genre, in search of other areas go rebelion.Because as I said, again John McClane, who we saw from the last jungle, not more than ten years ago. At this time, the character has changed city, has divorced, while his rank or his socarronería are still intact. His new mission is to escort a hacker to the headquarters of the FBI in Washintong, which is suspected of having carried out an attack on the intelligence services. What was to be a routine mission, soon turns into something much bigger and more dangerous.Jungle 4.0 is the return of the spectacular and improbability to gender by the front door. In that sense not disappointed, everything is the norm of the more difficult still, however impossible and, believe me, there are many scenes that are beyond possible. On the other hand, the physical violence has been reduced, barely there is blood on the screen, the bad guys die off screen or in an immaculate manner (with the resultant saving in dry cleaning) and also the level of swearing McClane dropped ostensibly, especially when compared with the last film.On the other hand the direction of Wiseman is a pleasant surprise with regard to planning of action scenes, followed in an impeccable way, leaving breathing levels and with some very successful time. On the other hand the director fails to provide emergency, tension to the story. Everything is very spectacular, very big, but the viewer not reached the tension, it overwhelms you, you have fun, but it does not involve. Also not shown very successful with comic points, being these scenes and, in general, all those who do not have action (few Fortunately, loose most of the film).As for the actors, we have a bit of everything. Willis is perfect as McClane, noticing that enjoy playing it. Timothy Olyphant is very weak as a villain, certainly the worst in the series. Justin Long as fellow sufferers of McClane is also very weak and somewhat heavy. On the other hand Maggie Q is stunning as evil, but give little Court.In the technical sections the film is more than correct, highlighting a few very successful Visual effects. On the other hand the music by Marco Beltrami is the worst of the tetralogy, functional, but far from what has been achieved by the late Michael Kamen in the previous.In short, the jungle 4.0 is a pleasant surprise, a spectacular film, short, entretenidísima. Recommended, although far from the level of the first three. In spirit would be closer to the third, although therein the hectic pace and how it was shot compensated outweigh its flaws. And it is that McTiernam is very McTiernam. Even so, Wiseman has gone well project.(hehe, it shows how long ago I do not write, go longer post has left me)</body>
</review>
