<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Disturbia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Disturbia is a thriller of adolescents where blends intrigue, suspense, testosterone and the easy scare in equal parts.</summary>
	<body>The great masterpieces of art history are considered authentic jewelry, a world heritage site. Nobody conceptualize a painter to perform a new version of paintings by Goya and Rembrandt, or a sculptor to update the Venus de Milo or the Discobolus of Myron, or a musician to compose a new piece based on Vivaldi's the four seasons. But when it comes to the seventh art, it seems that there are no problems that are distorting and wrecking real masterpieces.There is no doubt that the window indiscreet, Alfred Hitchocock is one of the films of all time. For this reason, what sense is now doing a remake? Well, not even Disturbia is a proper remake, but it conceals in the magical definition of inspired en. It must be very rewarding to some filmmakers believe that they are capable of improving a movie like the window indiscreet and overcome a master such as Alfred Hitchcock. Disturbia is a thriller of adolescents where blends intrigue, suspense, testosterone and the easy scare in equal parts. The tape takes horrors to boot, being its director deeply concerned to show the viewer the inner and outer world of the protagonist. And incidentally, let the camera will delight in the figure of Sarah Roemer, new Muse of American teen film. D. j. Caruso all efforts made to distance themselves as much as possible from the lengthened shadow of Hitchcock, and in that search is when the film sinks final and fully. The only moments of true intrigue are due to the appearances of the character of David Morse and his disturbing performance far superior to the of a pamphilus Shia LaBeouf.Disturbia is a remake of hidden in one of the best films of all time intrigue, the window indiscreet. If someone was so naive to think that the film of D. j. Caruso could even give the size in so unequal comparison, in the film you will find the sad truth.</body>
</review>
