<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Salir Pitando" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Leave fpm is a comedy without grace or spark that is masked as a tribute to one of the situations more comic has given the football in recent decades.</summary>
	<body>The cinema has always sought stories to tell in the sport, successes, failures, or simply draw a series of potentially comical situations. Most sitters sports on the big screen casually are those who have a greater number of fans in United States. On the contrary, football has been with the dubious honour of being a sport that cannot be a good movie.Perhaps so, but yes can be good films of everything that surrounds the world of football, and if he is not enough to be attentive to the soccer news. One of the more memorable moments is the famous phrase of "not fuck me with, Rafa", phrase that has gone down in history as "Rafa not fuck me with". With the idea of emulate this scene is born out Pitando, a comedy which aims to exploit the comical of one of the groups most despised of the sport: the arbitral establishment. The big question remaining one after seeing leave Pitando is how Álvaro Fernández Armero has been able to waste such humorous potential to finish telling a story anodyne and vulgar. Football and the arbitration claim has been the greater commercial asset of the tape, but is nothing more than a mere excuse to develop a bad comedy of mess in which the main protagonist is a love triangle. The script there is where catch it, and instead of being bundled the blanket to the head and have thrown down the road of absurd and surreal, it passes through a myriad of platitudes and tired situations. Few situations that could have given more than itself are poorly conducted and worse resolute. Actors comply with his work, which already has much merit due to the infamous characters and dialogue that they have fallen in luck.Leave fpm is a comedy without grace or spark that is masked as a tribute to one of the situations more comic has given the football in recent decades. But the sport King is nothing more than a mere excuse, and is that the film would have been just as with any other profession.</body>
</review>
