<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Os declaro marido y marido" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The flag can not be removed gay and four slogans of fashion on sexual freedom in the midst of a product whose humor is to flatter the male chauvinist instincts of the less demanding public.</summary>
	<body>It is not surprising that homosexuals held a gay pride day since the heteros are celebrating the other 364. The boys proclaims his happiness be boys in the half of the jokes that makes, and, until recently, in their institutions. The idea that all possible couples have the right to join in holy marriage is as serious as the idea that all soldiers are entitled to an award but not to go to war. However, gays defend it tooth and nail, and in Spain, Canada, Belgium, South Africa or Netherlands her have conquered. Defend things as this part, according to some, of modernity. Why roll films to look modern. But they are not, the speckles of dandruff falling everywhere.John Ford seems an unusual case. Ethan Edwards is not a citizen outraged against the racism of his country, is the own Ford trying to wash their dirty laundry in public. Why is us more authentic when he shoots in the eyes of a dead Indian and denied entry into heaven than just when accepting her niece. The criticism of racism us is authentic because it comes from a racist.A similar mess, but at level chavacano, that became the creators of "I declare you husband and husband" with the world of homophobia. Adam Sandler is a firefighter as friend of his friend who is willing to marry him to secure the pension of their children. The problem of Sandler is that he is not gay, but more out of the world man. Something like Andrés Pajares in Hollywood. Instead of showing his testosterone desmadre with Adriana Vega, Nadiuska or Susana Estrada, Sandler has Jessica Biel. The endless scene where Jessica Biel lets you touch her tits thinking that he is gay and he wallows in front of the audience that knows that he is not gay is without a doubt one of the conditions put Adam Sandler in the contract to produce the film. Lack of inspiration, the idea of Alonso Millán sentences in "Will not want the neighbor of the fifth".It is not only that the film has no grace, which has little; the problem is not clear to whom it is addressed. The flag can not be removed gay and four slogans of fashion on sexual freedom in the midst of a product whose humor is to flatter the male chauvinist instincts of the less demanding public.</body>
</review>
