<review author="Bloody Will" title="Disturbia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A correct juvenile thriller, Bill good, middling performances, but that surely will have the favour of those who are still in the age of Turkey.</summary>
	<body>One of the surprises of what it far this year in the United States.UU. -as far as box office is concerned - has been, without a doubt, the film before us.Do in its first three weeks of display to the general public got staying in the number one position, either by their own virtues, by the loose jurisdiction of releases or its blatant similarities with the master Hitchcock classic?The indiscreet window?, and therefore causing, the curiosity of knowing if it was a bad copy more or not.Will soon land on our screens, so you can judge for yourselves which is the reason for its unusual success. For my part, I can only explain my humble opinion, which I hope will serve, at least (not intend more), to become a idea of what the tape DJ. Caruso offers us, and not so much influence the predisposition of the possible future spectator.The first thing one should try to avoid to have to see the movie, and later judge, are the obvious comparisons that raises to the work of the King of suspense.First because, analyzing it from the comparison?Disturbia? it lost by a landslide, thereby making it possibly one already is deprived to enjoy. And secondly, because the Caruso film is not so much a remake, but a teenager update of their well-founded bases, past this time through easy and purely commercial product. Does this not say that this film don't be a blatant copy of?The indiscreet window?, but Needless to say that it intends not to equate to it.In this case, the protagonist of the film is the young Kale (Shia LaBeouf), a normal and ordinary, teenager whose quiet life is truncated after the fateful death of his father in a car accident. Instant implications of this fact are noted in the radical change of the personality of Kale, who felt partly responsible for the tragic event, encloses in itself, becoming a rather shy and solitary person.Kale, after hitting a punch to a foolish teacher, was sentenced to 3 months of arrest at home, confined as well between the suffocating walls of his house, trying to kill time-based video games and TV cable. But the monotonous daily routine will change with the arrival of some new residents to the neighborhood, whose attractive daughter will lead our prota voyeuristas logons.But not only the neighbor of the side will be object of observation, but also the rest of its neighbors, including Mr. Turner, whose strange behaviour disturbed Kale, to the point that we suspect that he is a serial killer wanted by the police.It will be from there when what started as a mere entertainment, will become an addictive game for which possibly Kale is not ready. A game that to advance the plot, become more dangerous. So much so that it will not be a game to become a real nightmare.The premise, but is nothing original, at least if it is interesting. The beginning, idyllic and topical in the initial minutes, already contains one of the most impressive sequences of the film. At the same time, it is also one of the most dramatic moments of the story. I am referring, obviously, to the turning point that will change the life of Kale: the death of his father.What follows is the adaptation of Kale in his confinement at home: how time passes, how begins to spy on their neighbours and learn their habits, routines and secrets; how they begin to emerge - not only sexual feelings - towards its neighbour; and how begins to become obsessed with su, in appearance, calm neighbour, Mr. Turner.En greater measure, we can consider the greater part of the film as a teenager comedieta, with the typical obsessions of the youngsters of today day (with a mention, the more the better, on the heritage of these, such as an Xbox, iTunes or YouTube), mixing certain dyes of suspense (with its almost unnecessary and false scares)with that touch of juvenile humor and some dialogue, at times, superficial.Do so could say without fear of plausibly, that?Disturbia? It is a product addressed directly to the younger audience, but why not be frightening to the rest. This is, by all means, that the viewer feels, in one way or another, identified with the protagonist and his friends. And it is movies for teens do not always have to be them?American Pie? turn and their substitutes; or they have to always be portrayed as some junkies with triggered hormones (be them, any, of course) so the director labra the way developing interpersonal relationships between the protagonists (some more than others) for later, reach the final climax of the film. Unfortunately, most of the characters are defined by a few already preset canons, without greater depth than that, so finding the friend rarete and funny, the solid neighbour, the mother working but unable to connect with his son (being the character most loose and untapped), etc.Kale, interpreted by a more than convincing LaBeouf is the character more elaborate, getting the empathy of the viewer nothing more start function. It is also, who supports the entire weight of the film, which is not easy taking into account the few spaces in which occurs it.His enemy in this case, is the mysterious Turner, played by the versatile David Morse, whose appearances in scene are rather specific but always grateful and constant anxiety-laden modestly.Somehow, we could even say that both characters share certain personality traits such as shyness, the loneliness that surrounds them, their social bookings?And little more than say for not gutting you nothing, although he could not reveal too taking into account the predicable is everything, or almost everything, though, and that itself is welcome, is free from final turns absurd and without coming to tale, as they come being usual in thrillers of last generation. We will, for once, do not take the Viewer by silly or they Jeer him.In short, a correct juvenile thriller of good invoice, middling performances (However, highlighting the good work of LaBeouf, and ultimately, the Morse) to which can blame you leave the action to the end, but that surely will with the favor of those who still are in the age of Turkey. Humor, a little bit of intrigue and uncertainty and modernilla and commercial music (except some that another topic) for little more than 100 minutes of simple and conventional entertainment. be the neighbor of Kale really a serial killer? Or is any product of his boundless imagination and his boredom?. If you want to know it, the answer in your nearest cinema from next Friday.</body>
</review>
