<review author="Antonio Bret" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that takes very seriously itself, which takes its time and dosed deaths, incredibly dry in the initial third and that no wallows in the blood or her adorned with cheap theatrics.</summary>
	<body>Premiered in the U.S. the last Rob Zombie movie, after the good taste that left us all to "The Forsaken of Devil", sequel to the lower "La Casa De Los Mil Cadaveres" and marked a regression to the dirty and dry film horror that is both practiced in the seventies, sponsored by the huge success of "The massacre of Texas". As you must know, it's the remake - prequel of the seminal "the night of Halloween", precursor of the slasher (with permission of the previous "Black Christmas" by Bob Clark) directed by John Carpenter in 1978 and that until the arrival of "The project of the Witch of Blair" was the most profitable movie in the history of the cinema.As happened with "Hostel 2", a workprint network has been leaked. Since its premiere in Spain will not take place, at least until Christmas (1), already I have been able to take you a look, Amen of sank through the gender forums to see how well they had seated the fan this new "assault" to an "untouchable" work. Read until now, everything or almost everything are negative reviews. It must not ignore. "Halloween" is, luckily, radically different from the Carpenter (2). And luckily because what is a remake, at least, is that the "author" contribute something other than what has already happened, not limited to be a photocopy or, much worse, a deformed reflection, bastard, aseptic, correct and adapted to the times, as almost all the films of terror from the end of the last decade has been up quite short, because of, for another wonderful part, "Scream". "Halloween" is divided into two distinct parts: the first has the children of Michael Myers. It was necessary to deal with this issue? While it is true that Zombie naive peque placing unhappy Myers in a muddy environment, alienated, corrupted and rotten to as well, at least, "justify" the reason for their actions, can not think, however, that this is another nostalgic tribute to the modes and forms of the terror of the past (see if not as it freezes the image to insert the title of the film).Myers presents as an isolated child, a psychopath in power, however does not remember his vile acts. It is locked and his psychologist, a magnificent Malcolm Macdowell full and happily recovered after passing through "Heroes", leaves the skin trying to delve into his twisted mind. After an unfortunate incident in the hospital, escape fifteen years after those unfortunate events, and what follows now you can imagine: a typical correctly directed slasher that shines with special intensity in two of the deaths, a particularly successful through the glass of a door. "There a special decompensation between the two parties, although we can glimpse a certain domestication by Zombie, no doubt due to the pressure of the MyersWeinstein bosses.""Halloween" is thus a competent sunset on the verge of a character drowned in the parody of its vomitivas aftermath. Full of expensive known by the lover of the genre (Dee Wallace, Brad Dourif, Danny Trejo, Udo Kier, Ken Foree) a film that takes very seriously to itself (3), that few times treats the Viewer as a delayed mental (hence can come the bad criticism), which takes his time and dosed deaths, incredibly dry in the initial third and that no wallows in the blood or her adorned with cheap theatrics.(1) the official Premiere will not take place until next month of October in the 40 Edition of the international festival of cinema of catalunya which is held each year in Sitges.(2) despite to this Zombie homage to the original explicitly in a scene that we will not disclose.(3) so much so that no doubt to fuck like crazy to the youngsters before giving carnage and trufar the film of juicy naked, something unthinkable in the avalanche that we suffer from terrors of design</body>
</review>
