<review author="Bloody Will" title="Poseidon" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you ask someone has seen her you think, you referred to see it on DVD if it appreciates your friendship</summary>
	<body>There is nothing worse in this maelstrom of remakes nonsense that try to copy a movie unforgettable for its time. "The Poseidon Adventure" of 1972, and turn it into a palomitero product that even bored.Wolfgang Petersen will not repeat the relative box office success of "The perfect storm" with "Poseidon". It will rather have to apologize to Warner Bros.. by the millions in losses that this film has caused. 160 million budget, 60 million fundraising. Is why I talk about fundraising?. Because it is directly proportional to the content of the film.Another day in Antena 3 think that they put a movie remake of the original of the 72. They could issue this version of Petersen and you have that it is also a telefilm. The situations are so mascadas that it's scary to ask how much has claimed its screenwriter.No emotion, less interpretations. From the beginning you know who smells like dead, and on top, the scene of the overturning of the transatlantic, main part of the story, it is millions of light years from the scene of the sinking of the Titanic, and that separate them almost ten years. A waste.Kurt Russel has always me fallen sympathetic. Its peak is "Blow to the Chinese small". Here is a character that splits the horns to come to the surface. Nothing relevant.But it is nor his companions make much. Richard Dreyfuss passable passable Josh Lucas, Emmy Rossum passable. This whole set of mediocrity has led to its poor fundraising, because if you ask someone that the seen that it feels, you referred to see it on DVD if it appreciates your friendship.Otherwise, and accidentally end up paying the entrance of this by-product do an experiment. Ends of seeing her and throw that has lasted. You seem an eternity its hour and a half of duration.Perfect for at home with the possibility of going to the bathroom, take pipes, and smoking you a couple of fags. Keep the money for the pirates, who have two weeks left...</body>
</review>
