<review author="Yojimbo" title="Death Proof" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>As Soderbergh wanted to emulate the classic film to the Casablanca with the good German, Tarantino falls into the same trap and wants to make a tribute bypassing many of the elements that characterized those works. And in addition, bored.</summary>
	<body>After that the director had given birth one of the calving largest modern film in two parts, it is now that it enters the homesickness for the film little budget, crushed in countless projections and demented arguments.But the Soderbergh wanted to emulate the classic film to the Casablanca with the good German, Tarantino falls into the same trap and wants to make a tribute bypassing many of the elements that characterized those works. And in addition, bored.Because honor and have nostalgia for those works is not to make "your movie" adding dots and stripes with the digital effect of shift, putting posters of missing horns and using special effects which at that time were impossible. Soderbergh wanted to do something similar, but except for black and white, the rest of the film seemed one thriller which occur every day. Movements of camera? Perfect. The "chroma" or "souped" funds"? Impeccable. And sex scenes with a treatment that is not old at that time. I.e., a tribute to decaffeinated and chip now.Tarantino along with his friend Robert Rodriguez, have tried to do the same and get himself in trouble, although not precisely at the time of writing the script. Choose an actor unjustly undervalued as Kurt Russell and they put him in prota. And then a lot of very good girls see here and there and scenes of action with special effects of the first order. And it is already.The first part of Rodriguez, have not seen. But the Tarantino's if. And they are the 2 worst invested hours of these weeks. Bla, bla, bla? jijiji, lol, nonsense here and there, a final joke, conceptual and stylistic atrocities on the old movies, a part becomes black and white, another has no spots, the other many and even lost fragments?That Yes, what looks like a fact is that Quentin is what happened pipe surrounded by beautiful girls and drink with the money of the unwary who saw Kill Bill and they now will leave the rooms with this insult. And sure Quentin tells each dollar or euro with a sound of laughter.</body>
</review>
