<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>She is forgetful, of course, as the second, as the third, but well met claims and current expectations. The rest is generational nostalgia.</summary>
	<body>On the basis that "The jungle of glass" is one of my 10 favorite movies of all time and also my number one absolute in the action genre, is understandable to understand that the consequences of this saga only have managed to get me a smile an accomplice and little else. Someday I will speak of the first part of the original, the forerunner, the great and far better film of Mc Tiernan, but now it is the turn of the fourth installment of the saga that exalted Bruce Willis to the top.Many say that this quarter is a fairly cold film without charisma, conventional, that the script is predictable, schematic, this time the bad guy is very wobbly, it lacks more nasty than the rating for all ages has been a burden and that ultimately does not seem "the jungle". They are right. But I said that actually none of its previous sequels already resembled in its essence the master part.2 Jungle was a kind of commercial calcamonía and without the first talent, a chapter any James Bond nonsense that pulled by land the terrifying feeling of realism and authenticity of the original story. The jungle 3 was elite, again spectacular, vibrant, but of others and that it could have happened also perfectly as any part of the saga of "Lethal weapon". And we get this quarter and I really don't expect anything beyond a good action film, like its predecessors, and they actually offer us a light script, something so a bit like "Eraser", that it was like "Terminator 2", and they mix it with another bit of "Risky lies" and. Nothing surprising in this wave of plagiarism, sequels, remakes, you prequels, grindstones, caries and fillings Hollywood. Do even rumored out there that the script of this fourth installment was, not so long ago, a guioncillo sad action that took time collecting dust and stains of coffee by los Angeles Studios, while it is decided or not to action saga is could recycle, "Transporter 3"?, does "2 risky lies"? And at the end they thought that if they managed to put Willis in some way in the project could sell as "The jungle 4" and make sure the taquillazo. Not be whether it will or not true, but the result knows exactly the ingredients of this urban legend and the taquillazo this be ordago. Still, the truth is that this is a film that resists, entertains more than and powered by empathy and nostalgia for the character of John Mc Clane, its irony and this sentiment so witty, gross and close. The action is fast-paced and the show visually very attractive. She is forgetful, of course, as the second, as the third, but well met claims and current expectations. Else is generational nostalgia, because we see that Willis aging along with his saga and recedes in each attempt a little more and quite possibly already forever of the origin of the starting point, the first adventure of a good man caught in the wrong, the birth of a work place and the exact time of teacher action cinema.</body>
</review>
