<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Cabeza de muerte" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not, however, a negligible movie?Head of death?: the atmosphere of earthquake terror, splendidly supported in the vast, primordial Irish forests is well achieved, and the action follows with interest.</summary>
	<body>The seed of "The Blair Witch Project" (by call it somehow) has permeated some of modern horror cinema. Now is the Irish film that dares to do its bit to this already quasi venero within the genre of fear, and do it with some aplomb. Paddy Breathnach us interested in recent years with their entangled comedy thriller "Disorganised crime", and now demonstrates that the terror nor given wrong. As in the usual "Do the project?", here there is also a group of rather hatched guys (sorry for the redundancy?) interned in a forest, for the occasion with the intention of "hang" with psychedelic properties of certain mushrooms of the Earth. But a spineless group eats fungus which should not, one that uncovers usually asleep human faculties as the precognition, or that directly removes any type of inhibition acquired by the social animal which hardly we are. Do all this with a legend in the background, with a kind of reformatory governed by an insane and sadistic monk and a few pupils as to found them at two in the morning just around one corner? The truth is that the film works, within its conventions, reasonably well, with some scenes of percutante tension, such as the death of the memo of the group, or some final moments in the abandoned boarding school. Does shame that Paddy Breathnach at the end her annoy way with a twist with built-in surprise which gives a new perspective, already somewhat forced, as until then us has been seen, abandoning the supernatural explanation by another much more land, even pedestrian? It is not, however, a negligible movie this "head of death": the atmosphere of earthquake terror, splendidly supported in the vast, primordial Irish forests is well achieved, and the action follows with interest, although the viewer knows that, according to the unwritten rules of this type of films with carajotes group in a hostile landscape, they will fall one after another.</body>
</review>
