<review author="Bruji" title="Gal" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is incredible what encourages thinking world fiction "without claiming it". It is not all the men of the Chair, but a bet, when less, interesting Spanish cinema, in which no shortage nor patriotic peaks or chillingly ridiculous monologues.</summary>
	<body>With an argument that exceeds the best American political thriller, (which would have given Oliver Stone for being Spanish!), this production of world fiction, focuses in journalistic investigations that uncovered a scandal "without precedent in the history of democracies", according to its makers; who has been curiously, called her "Gal".GAL is, indeed, a package consisting of the story, the film and how did, does not rule out the possibility of becoming a trilogy, so Paco Ariza could become more famous than Torrente.Evidentemente, if the such Ariza says in the interview that "there is much more" and that "more" is not included in the film, it is because Melchor Miralles (a charming gentleman where halle) could be preparing the second part, Gal: the story Interminable.El story airs during two consecutive days prior to the premiere and maximum audience, by a regional channel schedule, and its objective is basically gutting the film with surgical precision.There are two fascinating moments, derived from the lines of research followed by journalists and that lead to a revealing zulo, as well as to inform the alleged lover of the peculiar servant. Similarly, Paul, director, tells some interesting conversations with certain politicians.I am inclined to think that the "evisceration" is done without ill will, presupposing that nationwide recalls the ins and outs of the case, but forgetting that it does more of twenty years were many Spaniards that we faction, or paid taxes or read the press, having no age to do so. Of course, also came to the conviction that knowing the silhouette of the argument and each and every one of the details of the Fund, since it makes no sense paying 5,80 turkeys in the film.The six million euros invested in this production, translates into a modest picture, with certain dyes of television series, lousy photography and improved atmosphere. However, we are facing a well told story, impeccably simple structure and screenplay loaded with clichés of the genre, which makes the mistake of insinuating a sentimental roll that is beside the point, nor offers attractive to the footage, nor provides a pepper to the plot.Over the projection and, once again, because of the Ripper story, my movie fan memory flies to the Olympic Games in the year 72, makes me remember how the Government of Israel split with the command of Munich and forces me to think that the members of the Spanish secret services do not have a hair of ready. Meanwhile, the historical memory I shake when it is fact that Juanito, the Minister, enters the prison for being the organizer of the anti-terrorist band... I remain convinced (what delusional!) that was due to an issue with the reserved funds.With a Natalia Verbeke, at times, incredible and José García credible at times, the sole protagonist is only the building appears "seven years later", in a stunning foreground and retaining his true name; a curious aspect of a film in which Pedro is called Pablo and Vicente called Louis. It is not all the men of the Chair, but a bet, when less, interesting Spanish cinema, in which no shortage nor patriotic peaks or monologues chillingly ridiculous, far removed from that "Let justice be done, though open land" the unforgettable JFK.The making keeps me awake until four in the morning, but I must admit that it is worthwhile for the question posed: "what is hidden behind this film?.." Of course, when I start to think that this is the Da Vinci Code and that there must be some strange message that I has been overlooked, the voiceover reaches the conclusion that "the only thing that is hidden behind the movie is the desire to overcome the success of critics and audiences of Wolf". Is here where I understand that "honest subjectivity" which speaks Miralles (a charm of Lord ever there), but I am disappointed as movie fan, because I expected a lot more from him as a producer. In any case, I don't feel I quiet. Suddenly, seeing the movie, I get to think that any negotiations with the terrorist group is unthinkable, even for the sake of a peace process; that if there was a democratic Government that lied, this may become again, if it is that it is not producing, at this time; and that those who were able to uncover the greatest scandal in this country when all denied, they may be true trail of another conspiracy, far-fetched as it sounds today. It is incredible what prompts me to think World fiction, without claiming it.But as mine is the cinema, what interests me most is that he has written of Gal who said that the last movie by Oliver Stone was "television film". Whatever the case, I hope their sincerity, because there is no Diario 16, which was that said goodbye.</body>
</review>
