<review author="Bruji" title="Déjà Vu" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do we deal with a hyphen? open?, understood as such, one that, offering multiple possibilities, always ends up happening that does not cover the minimum expectations of the viewer moderately critical.</summary>
	<body>Thrilling fast-paced action and an abundance of special effects impossible is the attractive offer of this spectacular Ribbon of Tony Scott. A few accurate claims seeking to remedy the evident fragility of his script, cut from a bright idea, he strives and manages to land anywhere. Fund, a tribute to the people of New Orleans and the Hollywood call things by their real name fear: Desidia.Es possible that lovers are the beings that majority of "déjà vu" reached experience throughout our lives. Blame it on too many producers, filmmakers and, above all, writers contemporary who, in the absence of their own ideas, do not hesitate resort to old tricks that others operated them in the past. When these events occur, the criticism agrees unanimously described as resulting Mannerism as "wink" or as "plagiarism", normally, according to the name of the director who signs the film. There are always exceptions, see the case of Brian de Palma, which still have not been agreed.History before us, American critics found cinematographic references from the mythical Laura of Otto Preminger. A fact that I do not entretendré for obvious reasons: nor Tony Scott cares a pepper the arguments of his films, nor to me either. Its peculiar universe is based on other aspects. "I think it was Robert Altman who said that the current film was the closest thing to a video-clip, clear, not told anyone."If you knew that not going to believe commenting on an unintelligible argument to which you yourself do not find meaning, what would? "." To follow the designs of the movie, my answer is "so he would try". An arduous task if we take into account that we are facing a "open" script, understood as such, one that, offering multiple possibilities, it always ends up happening that does not cover the minimum expectations of the viewer moderately critical. I only wonder what size would the stone thrown into the River, capable of achieving not only that it lost its channel, but also to move the continent. It is too cruel to ask the writers of Disney's learn to discern between travel in time and flights on carpet, but? I said-that should not be so difficult to put together a story that they themselves have decomposed. Did those responsible for back to the future, those of the passengers of the result Tiempo.El is a product close to the delirious The Jacket of John Maybury, who neither understands the protagonist, or the public, or the luminaries that guarantees the libretto.I must stress that Tony Scott all this cares the same as to me the bobbin lace, i.e. absolutely nothing. Filmmaker still struggling to overcome his agoraphobia film, and it is that every time you wheel in open spaces, makes sure to enclosures to cal and singing with an infinite number of architectural elements, sometimes non-existent in the own level, to ensure that the viewer has the feeling of having been swallowed by a fireplace. That is why the list of the members of the artistic direction of this film is endless.With that and everything, I like this degree in fine arts, as a simple matter of empathy: if I were to shoot a scene in bed, would also make it to three millimeters of actors, more than anything, to fray the nerves of those who saw the film. When he does, it is impossible to distinguish a nose a hand or anything else. Even has a foolproof trick to mislead those who enjoy a special visual acuity: take fog. Also does film prudery?.What it does have is certainly Lair to its beginnings. Do to make a video clip to George Michael, discovered that a handsome man with sunglasses, becomes interesting and, since then, has not ceased to repeat the invention: Tom Cruise in Top Gun, Kevin Costner in Revenge, Denzel in the fire of the Venganza.Dentro of the cast (excellent casting), we find ourselves with a Val Kilmer? with the face of loaf - which continues to believe the asterisk (long left to shine) "talent only surpassed by the number of zeros ()"(a_la_derecha) from your bank account "(this he said Robert de Niro). With a pretty girl (does it matter its name?), with the charming Denzel, that I cannot speak objectively (I like too) and Jim (sometimes James) Caviezel, who refuses to accept roles that include sex scenes, but don't mind being the terrorist that sent to 543 people (my entire village) at a better life. Curious vision of Catholicism!.For his opposition to the Bush administration, Robert Altman, the last rebel, had serious difficulties to finance his latest films. A problem that is familiar to directors such as Oliver Stone or Spike Lee. Therefore it is not surprising that the conjunction Scott - Bruckheimer has produced this convoluted bullshit to avoid having to say that the tragedy of New Orleans clearly demonstrated the apathy of a more concerned Government in abarrer outside homes to sweep his own.In any case, "Satán reason as a man, Dios thinks on eternity" and this is a production of unmarriageable and director script "agorafóbico", candoroso and videoclipero that, however, it manages to entertain. An important merit.</body>
</review>
