<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="Sicko" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Moore put again the finger in the wound. And does it so in the only way that can do: waking up to the Viewer. This time focuses, more than ever, people and how is attentive to the only inviolable right: life. Of course in a country where the death penalty is in force, the rest is smoke.</summary>
	<body>The doctor kills because there is a system that endorses, supports, and rewards it. Michael Moore put again the finger in the wound. And does it so in the only way that can do: waking up to the Viewer. So his speech becomes extreme, with all the dangers that entails. Moore is, in this sense, honest. It proposes a hypothesis and is, by all means, show it and forgetting demonstrate this. And this is, possibly, his virtue, and for many others, the cause of their discredited (is here when we speak of "manipulator" Moore).The Moore character, in a media-globalized world, has transcended the borders of its complaint. Something local, such as problems in American society (arms sales as cause of the high levels of violence the corruption behind the invasion of Iraq; the relocation of companies.), globalizing in relation to an occidental-capitalista society - consumer. The drawback: a feature of a society become everybody's problem. And it is that that country called United States, as a rule, is the main transmitter of Western values. Hence, the main speaker of the criticisms of Moore have produced in Cannes, Toronto, etc. And, do in his country not hear you? To refute this idea, Moore presented these days in Canadian land CAPTAIN MIKE ACROSS AMERICA. Once again, Mike tries to "show" the tour against Bush in 2004, 62 cities toured in 45 days and in which came to meet, in a single night, more than 10,000 people. Moore tired of being the only one in speak up, tells us that it is not the only one in his country to have a critical view.Critique of Moore always to the system. A system which acts on how pernicious and alienating people. Simplistically, an American buys arms because the system "sells" fear. Now, a doctor kills because system rewards you for that reason. Moore shown in SICKO. Behind, business linked to a system of American health care, by all means, is the greater profit against the health of their clients. All the constraints to not treat a disease in extreme situation, not cure the "Heroes" in the 11-S. absolute privatization of a company in the conglomeration of a country that forgets to persons and advocates the benefits of an elite (the same that selling arms, give the order to invade countries).Moore tries to show. To do this, it is able to compare: public health in United Kingdom and France; and how are "cured", for free, the American heroes in hospitals in the greater enemy, Cuba. This time focuses, more than ever, on the personas.en victims. And how is attentive to the only inviolable right: life. Of course in a country where the death penalty is in force, the rest is smoke.</body>
</review>
