<review author="Torbe" title="Stars Wars III La venganza de los Sith" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The sits and giving vader</summary>
	<body>The other day I went to see "the sioux" as I said my friend. The six movies trilogy comes to an end, and I will not go into considerations if it is good or bad, suda me, 2 hours and average of movie with good moments, and other soporíferos moments, and therefore cannot be said to be good, because endure these memos two his speeches in the nidito of love is a tochazo, and who get political another roll. But the war stories and some things are cool.The most outstanding of all is the mental shortage of the colaluca of Anakin, appearing in all the previous films as a ready guy, and here we see as it is bundled by Palpatine with burda chantajeadora, and is talk like a fool. Is anaquino sees (comes from Ana and quino, joaquin) has a dream and Palpatino tells that if you pass to the dark side (before is wrote with a B before the S) find remedy.Come on, I'm going to now go on the street to ask the good aunts see to see if they have dreamed of something bad and tell you that I have the solution to your dreams if they let me get them the tip. Already should be tolai to fall in a game so, because Anaquino falls as a Blackbird transalpinoBueno, and by that not talking about Palpatino, the evil emperor maloso? Often liante this made the old. not you have noticed that all this stuff there with the strangely reminiscent Mr Bush and his action in Iraq?That stating that you killing everyone will bring peace, that which is not with the, it is their enemy, and entangled people thing bad, even becoming with the power of his army of clones. Come on, I take my hat off to such Web mounted taking as an example what did Mr Bush in Irak.LOS JEDAISHarta grace makes me thing say JEDAI and not JEDI, as life has said. Return of the Jedi was said when we were children, and if someone said "the return of the jedai" was given two toñas by marica. 'Ve already talked previously about these beings that eat or fuck (someone has been fucking a jedi? and eat something?)I wonder, that pussy is habra inspired Daffy to do one thing well. Also gives equally whatever, a jedi can be a good aunt with big blue tits, or a guy fuck ugly esmirriao, or Yoda, which is a pepper green of Tudela with bastonLos Jedi are anything, until Jabba the hut could be jedi if I hurry, jajaDAR VADERMe catches attention changes give vader's hairstyle of a movie to another. If in the episode two seems a niño bien, aplicadito with his full of lacquer hairstyle, now we get done a few foxes, leif Garret crazy plan lost.Short hair to long hair, you know, long hair is synonym of bad guys. From there that said: "the Manes, the terror of the girls". Making a brief introspection about the character of Dart vader, dire that suit, inspired by the ancient samurai (especially the helmet) and all the stuff that are mounted with the espadita is calcada to roll with your katana Samurai (nothing to do with the child of the katana, by God!).The lightsaber laser are katanas, and it is not a sword, it is a samurai katanon.I miss what war stories as the beginning of the movie, which is the cock in vinegar (cock in vinegar). To see if they do more things of those, what bores me because they are the struggles of sables lasers, because you don't see a posh and it's always the same story: when the director wants to give, if not, it does not give even one.Do example: when this obiwan surrounded by thousand and his mother doesn't give even one, instead, when the clones rebel against the Jedi, saw that even two killed you one, but not had the Jedi a sixth sense that smell the danger?This movie has more holes in the script a cheese Gruyère (), but entertains, except for talks between anakino and pamela, often suckling pig, the Virgin, but it is all false that a wooden euro. Well, and now this, does not give for more this movie to suck out there, or better, that they suck us out there</body>
</review>
