<review author="Victor Omar" title="Munich" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Too shallow, simplistic and didactic</summary>
	<body>The new film by Steven Spielberg is such rare cases that become a dilemma for who writes this. It is difficult to outline the tape without giving personal points of view on the subject in which attempts to deepen the script. So we will try to explain two things. Spielberg develops the tape with the consequences of the event, following the chain of violence that, far from a problem simply perpetuates and exacerbates it.At the beginning of "Munich", Spielberg recreates the terrorist attack, during the 1972 Summer Olympics in Munich, ending with the death of 11 hostages, five Palestinian terrorists and a German policeman.Golda Meir, first Minister of Israel, then begins a secret operation called "Wrath of God", where five ex-agentes of the Mossad (Israeli secret service) carried out a campaign of revenge, killing the 11 ringleaders of the Palestinian "Black September" terrorist group.These men were part of a Palestinian nationalist command which was called "Black September", named so in tribute to the three thousand dead and 10,000 wounded left as balance the operation of expulsion of Palestinians mounted by the Jordanian army in the month of 1970.La film does not show those events, but it is obvious that they are part of the chain of violence and revenge took a new turn from Munich and arriving with their dramatic effects to the present day. The Israeli hostage-taking at the 1972 Summer Olympics was, perhaps, the first terrorist act broadcast live worldwide on television.And it was the seed that gave rise to a new type of Israeli, different from the conventional military response and which led to the adoption of methods of counter-terrorism which, in many cases, are assimilated to the enemies.In this way, we continue to Avner (Eric Bana) and his group of agents around the world for months, while carried out its work, getting information about a mysterious French man and questioning the usefulness of the mission at each step.Obviously executions are sending a clear message to the Palestinian terrorists, who also respond with violence; and, worse still, kill the leaders of the terrorist organization cannot be the dismantling of the same. "Do murdered chiefs are simply replaced by even more violent men and militantes.¿A who benefits the chain of violence?""Munich" has received severe criticism for its alleged historical inaccuracy, but must take into account that his screenplay is "inspired" in a book that is also "inspired" by the alleged facts.Since then the main points of the story actually occurred, but the plot and characters are probably fictitious; and I see no reason to criticize this attitude, because the purpose of the tape goes beyond being a mere educational tool; Instead, he dares to offer a much more important message, raw and clearly denouncing the vicious circle of violence generated by terrorism and the so-called war on terrorism.Certainly one of the more mature Spielberg works, because it manages to complement the narrative with cinematic style, which emulates the visual plastic of the thrillers of espionage of the seventies, immersing himself in that decade, but without falling into childish exaggerations.In the same line we have the accurate way as recreates the violence of the attacks; far from falling into empty visual spectacle, the violence occurs naturally and even prosaic, thus giving much greater impact and realism to these scenes.The work of the cast is outstanding, and applaud Spielberg the decision not to use "stars" in the tape, but authentic actors capable of transforming into their characters.And although always maintained their anonymous position behind the scenes, we must make special mention of the dynamic duo of Janusz Kaminski as director of photography and editor Michael Kahn. No doubt much of the "magic of Spielberg" comes from these two constant partners.I wish I could say the same of John Williams, whose music is now so soft and anonymous as it was spectacular and noisy in past decades.His work on "Munich" is not bad and works reasonably well, but we would have liked to see what some more innovative composer (say, Elliot Goldenthal or Graeme Revell) had been achieved with the tense scenes and ambiguous emotions of "Munich".Beyond of courage (narrative, dramatic, and especially politics) of his proposal, "Munich" has everything to irritate the different segments of the public.</body>
</review>
