<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El ultimátum de Bourne" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More than recommended tape of action. Greengrass prints the appropriate pace, the plot does not lose time on useless issues and Damon, in his role, serves modern action hero with sobriety, without excesses. Nor do I believe that he knew.</summary>
	<body>Valuable of this blockbuster is that it does not fool the viewer and poses a direct intrigue, refugee in a series of codes that facilitate the understanding of the complete series. Bourne is not the hero of the traditional western ambushed a reality that surpasses him: is Shane nor William Munny, vulnerable and sensitive adults gunmen still relevant resources of bully made them fearsome. The plot of the trilogy leads the story upside down. Bourne flees not from the past: what he wants is to understand it. The plot is more complex than usual in these cases, but either need a crash course in semiotics or a closet full of Cahiers du Cinema in native language. Bourne, a correct Matt Damon, is the James Bond of this 21st century, the action hero oo7 could have been case that his writers had covered the stories of a more careful invoice. Here there is bad and there are good: the difference from similar doneness cinema is that it ensures the fidelity of the Viewer (in the style of 24, the exceptional series television or even Collateral, the last great thriller) thanks to a fine of causes and ups and downs warp, pieces well-organized whose sole purpose is to dilate the outcome and entertain, and how, during the proposed trip.Detailed biographical reconstruction of the murderer Bourne offers a greedy itinerary: journey almost half the world to complete the puzzle. Nothing new, but what fascinates in this installment (and to a lesser extent in the previous two) is the stubborn pursuit of truth, the epic breath that infused the argument of heroic connotations and us friendship with an ambiguous character, past reprehensible, but honestly compelled to find its name, its history, the reasons for which kills and it is sought to make him kill.Without respite, the droves of action scenes complies with more than the usual ration of technically perfect, eye-catching images to new American cinema, needed a loyal clientele who pay the entry and buy on the way, the enormous flood of merchandising to use us customary.In these times of terror alerts and abstruse cybernetic stories of viruses and Trojans Imperial (the jungle 4.0) touches the domestic closeness of the series, his melodramatic indisimulada vocation. The Bourne Ultimatum is a recommended film that sees burdened its primacy in these rankings of best films of the year by being included in a genre often ignored, which turns confidently to make box office and sounding box. I have contributed with taste.</body>
</review>
