<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La maldición de la flor dorada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about conspiracies in the medieval Japan palaciengas. An absolute delight for the eye of the Viewer, but it falters much in history who wants us to have. Recommended by the visual spectacle, which is the greatest thing.</summary>
	<body>Many times one dreams of moving to an era of these in the past, where the emperors and kings lived as such. But well thought out, I think that the thing should not be both. To begin with, the Empress can not be peer without having an attentive lacayo there to shout "the Empress is has I, smell the extract of his divine essence". Then all live subyogados a gentleman, so are more slaves than anything else. And the emperor has no grace if you are not a cabronazo, in addition to having to take a sauna seat that should leave you the almorrana after riding the brava that spicy chillies of the Eroski.La film is about the wife of the Emperor (I remember that he was Emperor) that has a little fucking life. Her husband is committed that it has a disease, which gives a few herbs for 10 years to improve. For some time, a new ingredient is doing him turn into something crazy, so it decides that it is time that one of his sons (three only one is yours) take you the relay to the cabronazo, I say to her husband.Well, visually, the film is incredible. In many moments you remember with great tenderness of spirited away, with these colorful amazing scenarios. The costumes and make-up are outstanding, it gives you that thinking that more than one would die or stifled among so much clothes, or boredom in putting the colors, or skewered with a fork of these giants. So the visual level makes us crazy and we put in the history. But here comes the problem, given that the story does not end we get. Not is if it is seems incredible and distant or simply because it is not attractive, but I've not liked. And the final Fireworks, in addition to not know where can come from so many human beings, I thought was ridiculous. That if the fight scenes are very original.In short, film about conspiracies in the medieval Japan palaciengas. An absolute delight for the eye of the Viewer, but it falters much in history who wants us to have. Recommended by the visual spectacle, which is the greatest thing.kisses.</body>
</review>
