<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Guardianes del día" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film that is worth seeing and that eventually will become a cult film.</summary>
	<body>Timur Bekmambetov director of Soviet origin, attacks again after his success with "Guardian of the night" (Nochnoy dozor) releasing "Guardians of the day" (Dnevdoi dozor). If the first film in this series was good, this is even better. Particularly the way in which the director has embodied this Russian legend on the equilibrium of the forces of light and laoscuridad to my seems fascinating to me. Gives you a totally realistic perspective within the context fantastic Hollywood will serve to place securely between one of the most talented of the moment.Taking into account that a production is Russian, and the "limited" media and budgets that have these productions, "Guardians of the day" is a real achievement and success, as well as pride. Two and a half hours of footage that has made me enjoy as a dwarf, not only because faithful follower dce is this genre but because it is a film in which meet good special effects, good script and excellent interpretation.Talking about actors, as I have already said the direction of these seems fantastic, I can not put any but, because I can not find, all the characters from the fantastic point of view are accurately built and each of them has his personal inner drama, which enrriquece the plot of the film NO APTA PARA TODOS LOS PALATES.Aleksei Chadov is the great discovery of this saga. 25 years old and 15 films since 2002, has been an unstoppable career since it jump to fame thanks to "Guardians of the night" (Nochnoy dozor). For the moment is limited to productions Russian, but I'm sure that the talent of this Moscow will not go unnoticed by the Hollywood industry. Its freshness and naturalness to give life to the vampire kostya, make his face is unforgettable.Very notable interpretations of Mariya Poroshina (Svetla) and Konstantin Khabensky (Anton) both Russian and like Aleskei focused on cinema of this origin, although in the case of Konstantin has already managed to make the leap to Hollywood (thanks to the director of the saga) and currently shooting with Angelina Jolie and Morgan Freeman "Wanted", directed by Timur Bekmambetov and which will be released in Spanish cinemas on April 4, 2008.Para enjoy this film must be understood within its genre and context, as well as experience the flair of each of the creatures that make up the legend. Inexplicably critical eyes or the earthly public might perhaps find it strange or even boring, but this is no more than a sample of a low adaptive capacity and knowledge to what you see. "Guardians of the day" is a film that is worth seeing and that eventually will become a cult film. Concerning the past battles scenes, are very well shot and flat really beautiful General. I would like to mention the moment "Shower" of the two girls, that it seemed absolutely original and exciting. The soundtrack on occasions can be excentrica, good pro is typically Russian and as we do not have the ear accustomed therefore has a little bit.</body>
</review>
