<review author="José A. Peig" title="Un tranvía llamado deseo" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Superb photography in black and white is the perfect medium to visualize a world whose lights and shadows appear to reflect the State of mind of Blanche, character that encompasses sadness and hope, represented in the dark corners of the home that uses to hide their truth or sporadic moments of lucidity.</summary>
	<body>Elia Kazan, faithful transcription of the work of Tennessee Williams film, has a female soul which becomes real thematic axis in a story that goes beyond its appearance of melodrama about life as a couple, which is only a collateral subject to the furious and multifaceted female expression that contains in its great momentsfocused from the first images in which we see Blanche DuBois (Vivian Leigh) to appear between the sinister smoke surrounding in the platform of the New Orleans station, until the conclusion of the film material, accompanied by a psychiatrist who offers you the security of understanding and cordial gesture before a soul that seeks to sensitivity to the rudeness and chaos prevailing in the suburb. His past is so foggy and cloudy as the smoke that comes into the story, equivalent to the March to madness by deception.Hypersensitive, jovial and manipulative, Blanche is the element that stimulates keys, because it is a character whose gestures and words range from the more sensible sanity to child daydreaming that leads her to weave a network of deception and autoengaños that at the end, she, and only she, will be the victim. Throughout the story, behind the impulse which refers to the struggle between femininity and masculinity. If Blanche represents the idea of femininity taken to its extreme vulnerable and unbalanced, the character known as Stanley Kowalski (iconic and immeasurable Marlon Brando) provides a counterpoint of rude and insensitive masculinity.The duel of tensión-contención between the two is the real drama of a primarily descriptive film of a situation in progress, that, in the last section, the tensión-contención State transmutes in another action in a physical and verbal confrontation with clear sexual connotations which until then remained implicit in the subtext. The confrontation culminates with the violent expressiveness of a mirror broken, a female alma rota figuration and bound to its self-destruction in the hands of the verdugo testosterónico.Superb photography in black and white is the perfect medium to visualize a world whose lights and shadows appear to reflect the State of mind of Blanche, character that encompasses sadness and hope, represented in the dark corners of the household that used to hide the truth or the sporadic moments of lucidity (often exalted) are its visual reference in a small yellow light the night or lighting his face first flat, an Impressionist that synthesizes and produces rhythms of the image in line with the contrasts between truth and lies, past and present, reality and pretense, male and female.</body>
</review>
