<review author="James Wallestein" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film knows on numerous occasions to do tribute to the John Carpenter film and the screenplay, making numerous winks, and even adapting their plot in a very similar and reliable way. I take my hat off to this phenomenal and intense work of Rob Zombie.</summary>
	<body>I know some I wil by fingers fat of the feet of the top of a mast of a boat verlero. But is what I say and I say why, and more taking into account that I am a fan of John Carpenter, of his entire champion which I venero and his unforgettable night of Halloween that I've seen countless times, but this precula-remake is higher without a doubt to the original. For me the histrionic director Rob Zombie, eccentric and wild like few others, has reached a point of maturity and talent already very clear, forgetting their previous films mix of theatre, antics and gore. Take charge of a film as the night of Halloween was not feat. We are talking about a classic among the classics between modern horror movies, so having so many fans and fans, after 29 years garnering admiration, worshipers and critical love, reinventing the franchise, and most classic which originated was not easy. Rob Zombie focused this remake raised a number of very interesting questions posed by the original. What can encourage a child to kill his sister? Because that is what we see in the original film. In the remake, she kills sister, her boyfriend and his father. Michael Myers is a young girl who lives in a home broken, dysfunctional, full of misery, insults, violence, humiliation and pain. The child does not much shelter at school where is mistreated and persecuted by abusive partners. Michael explodes in this hell in which they live thousands of people to their regret, and unfold your mind. He first meets his frustration killing animals, something that relaxes you. These attacks of violence make her feel better. Why then he kills a fellow of the College brutally in a clearing in a forest to sticks. Then massacred anyone there in his house, but it leaves to the baby alive. We see that Michael is not a nutty narcoticized or silent. It is a sensitive child, with the mind broken and very bitter. He is then arrested by the police. Admitted to a psychiatric centre. How a child was going to be a lot of years silent and staring out a window?This prequel tells us of a paterno-filial relationship between Dr. Loomis and Michael. The doctor understands that Michael apparently is a good child, kind-hearted and until something shy. But know that it contains a dark and wild side that splits in two to be a mask, which is its dark, uncontrollable and homicidal side. The mother of Michael is next to the child trying to help you. But after a visit session child brutally attack a nurse, degollando her. After that tragedy and four deaths, Michael Myers is declared a high risk. The mother looks like the brain of the child has been bursting, has burned it a fuse, possessed by the dark side, and then enters in a State of shock, staying silent and until something stunned. The broken mother by family tragedy and his life commits suicide at home hitting a shot. The child grows and becomes a bicharraco which has not entered by a door, played by actor Tyler Mane, a wrestler in lucha libre, of 2.03 metres in height. And here begins the film the night of Halloween, taking about an hour to tell us why Michael Myers is the monster that is, their motivations and why massacred his family. Just in the middle of the film begins the film by John Carpenter, who of course, with the current cinematic language the duration of the original film, 91 meters, would be either very long or very slowly, by hand is counted as the stories are now and that means greater pace and plot density. Why the second half of Halloween is quite rightly condense all the old film by John Carpenter. At that point I did not destriparé too many things that I have uncovered many on the first hour of film, but I will say that it is excellent and vibrant. Michael Myers is a homicidal and almost mythological Monster at the height of the original, leaving all their past incarnations in a lot of sequelae of diverse luck in the shit. The film knows on numerous occasions to do tribute to the John Carpenter film and the screenplay, making numerous winks, and even adapting their plot in a very similar and reliable way, but knows also take their points of departure and originality not clashing, to give an interest added to the film. The film has many impressive moments. The tension is bestial and murders are very realistic and hard. The murder of the child are chilling. Wayne Toth make-ups are impressive. Is that John Carpenter film is elegant and mysterious, and that blood (despite several deaths) is conspicuous by its absence. But this remake - prequel has notable amount of gore and visual hardness, but I think that they are adequate. The film is raised as a trilogy if this succeeds, by which all actors have signed by three films in their contracts. Hopefully Rob Zombie makes them all and have the level of quality of this powerful film that to me I loved during their nearly two-hour. A new modern classic without a doubt. Despite having been hacked by internet you are having some excellent collections in the USA, the film deserve without doubt. I take my hat off to this phenomenal and intense work of Rob Zombie. Not you the Miss!</body>
</review>
