<review author="Bloody Will" title="La última legión" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Seems more a movie than a job for the big screen. More palatable if it is accompanied by advertisements between twenty minutes and twenty minutes of footage. A pity.</summary>
	<body>A good disastrously missed opportunity. This is the phrase that more often has repeated in my head while watching 'the last Legion'. And is your television director, Doug Lefler, has pulled by land the basic material of luxury he had in his hands: a backbone plot of bells as it is the bestseller of the same name written by Valerio Massimo Manfredi and a workforce of British actors which are the flower and cream of U.K., in their different generations: Colin FirthBen Kingsley, John Hannah, Peter Mullan, Iain Glen or Thomas Sangster.Si above has a very exotic touch as the presence of one of the Queens of Bollywood, Aishwarya Bai, of impressive beauty, this film did not have to have disappointed anyone. But it has disappointed, at least to me, for several reasons: first, the adaptation of the script is very poor. Manfredi continues in his book a fascinating trajectory of the last stirrings of the Roman Empire, imaginatively linking this period with the start of the do legends? Arthurian, whose maximum stronghold is Excalibur, and using as vehicle mediator the story of the abduction of the young (Sangster), the new Western Emperor, Romulus by barbarian troops. Come to her rescue a group of Roman soldiers led by Commander Aurelian (Firth), and accompanied by the Druid Ambrosinus (Kingsley) and the beautiful sights (Bai), Warrior of the Byzantine army Allied of Rome, to try to release first to Romulus in his confinement on the island of Capri and then resist the embargo in the distant lands of Britania.Sin, Doug Lefler makes a slow and boring by the original story tourwith a plot mounted catch-up that resembles scraps of the inspiring work of Valerio Massino saccade and forward enough to follow the thread. On the other hand, the lack of attention to the subplot about the appearance of the mythical sword of King Arthur, their minimal relevance to the plot and the accelerated outcome that gives rise to his legend makes the promotional phrase of 'the true story of Excalibur' a joke.Secondly, the staging of the film flirts dangerously with the series B. Exceptuando some shots of fight with weapons and hand-to-hand alleged intentions of big production reflected half, the rest of the scenes are clumsily developed so missed locations, in such small studies and with very limited visual means and without frills that take away the film this epic character that should have a minimum success. Lies in that regard light years of great films which have left their mark in the genre, said is 'Troy' or 'Gladiator', and even the correct 'King Arthur', talking about our most recent film, and 'Spartacus' or 'Ben-Hur', in the classics, to give some examples. Gives the impression that the budget which was has been directed mostly to other seemingly more important meneteres, as it is the cast. But even with these.And this is the third reason for the disappointment, an interpretation of the actors of unacceptably low profile. It is not conceivable that as respected interpreters in the UK, with an indisputable international relevance, express their emotions with so 'little blood', figuratively speaking. The feeling they give is have been bucket without caring the project at all.Colin Firth forgets that he is in a passionate film and remains the same of sosón, even in scenes more 'hot' with Aishwayra Bai, the motif of the film which brings a physicist, in all aspects, spectacular.The boy Thomas Sangster still has shooting to have a much more remarkable presence that has, and will also do need to lose that air of repellent caused antipathy. John Hannah, Peter Mulan and Iain Glen are those who have benefited more bucket, not only because of its limited presence in house but also by its infíma and repeatable acting contribution in the minutes of glory. And finally, the most bloody, Ben Kingsley is a shadow of that actor that has captivated us in 'Gandhi' or 'Schindler's list'. In some scenes it verges on the ridiculous, aided by a characterization of primary school little theater.In short, 'The last Legion' looks more like a movie than a job for the big screen. More palatable if it is accompanied by advertisements between twenty minutes and twenty minutes of footage. A pity.</body>
</review>
