<review author="Lady Winter" title="Sin reservas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It has all the basic ingredients to get a romantic comedy to use as a result. A sincere movie that promises no more that what he gives and it works.</summary>
	<body>Without reservation has all the basic ingredients to get a romantic comedy to use as a result. Their argument, as in every movie of this genre, is summarized with certain simplicity. Girl meets boy (or vice versa) and fall in love before passage of a series of drawbacks and altercations that put you a little pepper to the relationship. And all this cooked over low heat, for that the protagonists are chefs and the film takes place almost entirely by between fogones.cuenta with all the basic ingredients to get a romantic comedy to use as a result. Their argument, as in every movie of this genre, is summarized with certain simplicity. Girl meets boy (or vice versa) and fall in love before passage of a series of drawbacks and altercations that put you a little pepper to the relationship. And all this cooked over low heat, for that the protagonists are chefs and the film takes place almost altogether between Firebox. Catherine Zeta-Jones serves as Queen of the kitchen in a restaurant with great success where the customers crowd at the gates in search of a table free in which to taste his delicious creations. A life fraught with professional success, but empty personally. What forced to attend visit a psychoanalyst to help you improve in the face to face on a regular basis. With a schedule squares and organized to the smallest detail, any novelty can make his fragile emotional state unravel. That is why the intrusion in his life of his niece (that has to take charge after the death of his sister) and a companion of pans fond of pasta will make change the course. Zeta-Jones, and only she, is the real protagonist. Superb in his role of young beauty and cranky control load on his shoulders the weight of the film, in which Aaron Eckhart guaperas course (for tastes the colors were made) puts the histrionics to the plot with its outputs everything. History does not give much of itself that it endorses, as it is usual in the romantic comedies, the principle that opposite poles attract. From there, everything are topicazos the spectator has seen over and over again and which will see not in much. Hard girl which a crazy young man is able to soften. Girl that awakens the tenderness of his responsible for aunt. The stress of modern life. The difficult task of reconciling work and professional life. And so on. And all dressed with an Italian tone that is breathed in every level (music and food mainly). The best advice that can be given to those who come to the cinema to see without reservations is that go with a full stomach, since, otherwise, they will leave the theater with an insatiable appetite. This and that they go with the security that will be found with a sincere movie that promises no more that what he gives and it works.</body>
</review>
