<review author="Bloody Will" title="Cabeza de muerte" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do the best example of what is called? crappy film?: a story on an acrid basis can extend during more than an hour and a half.</summary>
	<body>Dead is as I am as soon as you have finished the film, and that had fallen into the coma of stupidity in the 40.Con minute only 30% of the comments of our illustrious readers already I do a script 300 times more attractive and coherent than this absurd movie has no where to take it.This is the best example of what is called 'crappy film': a story on an acrid basis can extend during more than an hour and a half. We proceed to the analysis.The basis: is borne by six tasteless characters seeking to make camping and put at the top of hallucinogenic mushrooms. Apart from that I do not know very well why travel together from the USA to Ireland if they are not supported between them. That Yes, have no better idea that doing so in a forest incommunicado and with mobile phones confiscated (?). Seen and requetevisto.The threat: ancestral story about a killer priest and a boy hooded put the 'imminent danger' point for the encamped. The figure of the 'slasher' appears from nowhere and without any originality. Now everything begins to smell to rotten.The turning point: puts it the protagonist, that without coming to story eats a mushroom called 'head of death'. I look at until the peppers when there to cook them, and the girl in the film gets into the mouth first thing found in the forest. Very logical, Yes.The rest is to get out of the armchair and say enough is enough. A cow who speaks, an axe that comes to know from where, the girl group appearing after a career of 10 seconds to two kilometers from the camping area or the main reason of eating mushrooms that disappears without any explanation.Above, to finish the story sold me an only possible ending in case appear Alan Cummings in his role as night Painkiller of the X-Men: I do 'chas' and appear at your side &hellip;.Not to criticize a film has no script, and whose interpretations are exceeded even by some contestants in a reality show famous. Not afraid, has no suspense, has nothing to keep the viewer's attention, and to make matters worse there are to pay 6 euros and peak to see it.Luckily Yul B. eliminated the category of classification of criticisms &hellip; didn't have the's ' piece of m ** da I've seen '.</body>
</review>
