<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Sin reservas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Scott Hicks confirms that theirs is not precisely this genre in which, as in any other that they populate the film, it takes quite more personality than that demonstrates in this forgettable story clearly dispensable.</summary>
	<body>Increasingly, more film is more predictable. Isn't that the "trailers" the almost entire movie, nor the press releases that facilitate the distributors to give you all the keys you have: is that a mere twenty seconds television advertisement tells you exactly what you will see. In this case, a romantic comedy, with prestigious completely overturned a New York restaurant chef in his work, without social or sexual life worthy of the name, their dose of sentimentality with girl unexpectedly resigned, and the intruder will be unsolicited kitchen Assistant, which finally Doña Perfecta (destripamos nothing: in these stories the happy ending he is inherent) is pleased the pajarillas. With much benevolence arguably that the protagonist learns to live while trying to exercise the putative daughter mother (at times daughter of a bitch, is true) and the emerging chef girlfriend, but it would be too grandiloquent, because we really are facing a roma, flat, romantic comedy with little chemistry between the actors, with the Catherine Zeta-Jones that not even imagine as a perfectionist head of kitchen, and that Aaron Eckhart, usually expert in villain roles, here with a beard of two days and hair imitating a coconut, pint of gañán who does not know nor open a tin of canned foods, the less be a chef. The director, Scott Hicks, whose highest level as such was reached because too many years ago with "Shine" (to make known to the great Geoffrey Rush, who later gave both as villain game), confirms that theirs is not precisely this genre in which, as in any other that they populate the film, it takes quite more personality than that demonstrates in this forgettable story clearly dispensable. That Yes: the character of Zeta-Jones begins the film by describing his psychotherapist recipe for its exquisite quail saffron sauce, the end and the Cape a bird batter in some concoction; If, as we say, ends brighten the pajarillas, is that, in addition to exquisite gastronomy, sobrevenidas maternity and unexpected romances, the thing also goes Ornithology "avant la lettre"? Sorry, I've not been able to resist &hellip;</body>
</review>
