<review author="Bloody Will" title="Sin reservas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>New example of misleading media promotion. ?No reservations? It is a dramón in his first 45 minutes, and an unclassifiable genus in the rest. If you want to laugh, or at least smile, this is not that looking.</summary>
	<body>If anyone wondered where was the romantic comedy of this autumn, which continue to seek, and I do not say because 'No reservations' is good or bad, is that it is simply not a romantic comedy.New example of misleading media promotion. 'Unreserved' is a dramón in his first 45 minutes, and an unclassifiable genus in the rest. If you want to laugh, or at least smile, this is not that looking.Perhaps we can approach more closely to what this movie is if I apuntillo that its director is Scott Hicks, who ten years ago captivated us with 'Shine' and his co-star isn't Mr. Eckhart, but Abigail Breslin, the girl of 'Little Miss Sunshine' who here has lost a few pounds, the truth. Also, we have a remake of 'Bella Martha', German film of 2001, and that seems to be (I have not seen) has suffered a renewed worthy of Hollywood, IE: doesn't look like anything.I must admit that I am very frequent to see romantic comedies, and 'Serendipity' is one of the best I've seen in years, but in 'No reservations' I had a good part of the footage waiting for the comedy began, and in the end I gave up: despite a couple of very captivating scenes, the rest is basically depressing. Kate (Zeta-Jones) is a chef in a restaurant in New York, addicted to his work and perfectionist in their dishes. When the trip that his sister and his niece to the City turns into tragedy should take charge of Zoe (Breslin), and adjust their care with their work, rather complicated when assigned as Assistant to Nick (Eckhart), a chef quite eccentric and radically different from its form see the kitchen.What we had sold so far in trailers and television spots was the relationship between Zeta-Jones and Eckhart perfect, and a kind of history to the 'first rivals-after lovers'. Well, I'm not saying it's not part of the film, but certainly it occupies at most half an hour and its development is not only predictable, but that its protagonists become authentic slug. Now, when we discovered that this is a family drama and change the chip, everything is somewhat better.I will not cheat, and situations live characters are the mandatory when there is a girl orphaned and one boyfriend more than sympathetic, but what makes it special and avoids to be an acrid product are two of his actors.Performances by Abigail Breslin and Aaron Eckhart again be outstanding. Both earn more and more sympathy. You can have next to such I mujo (Jesus said is of fish without facial gesture) as Catherine Zeta-Jones make best, but it is inevitable that the two eat Mrs. Douglas, who seems lost in the screenplay and signed a performance worthy of a cheap telefilm. Patricia Clarkson, as head of the protagonist, has only scenes, which is why I am going to avoid the waste of a very charismatic actress.With both dish to the novelle cuisine and presentation worthy of Ferrán Adrià, 'Unreserved' is me has antojado more as a 'take away', where you consume food without distinguishing the ingredients very well, and which in the end strips container knowing that you thou only when there is no more remedy.</body>
</review>
