<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Dialogues are in memory, a character not only funny, also nice and human, and a few scenes so memorable as the dance in the kitchen.</summary>
	<body>While the proposal of Viscarret is not too risky, because the idea or the outline of the film are nothing compared to the imagination of patriotic Coixet, Amenábar or Almodóvar, is welcome to, this being a debut, get go branching paths until now never explored, apparently simple and very realistic. Dialogues are in memory, a character not only funny, also nice and human, and a few scenes so memorable as the dance in the kitchen. Under the stars is a title which I believe that it will happen to the history of the Spanish film, well because it is too independent (sometimes antonym of bad), or simply by telling a story that her we have heard more than once. But as I say, is the grace of the set and magnificent interpretations make, this, an exemplary debut.The beginning is somewhat typical, with the protagonist (a great Alberto San Juan) lost means that changes of aires when they tell him that his father is very serious. It is then when he travels to the town where he spent childhood and, as it is recalling, is exploring and opening in a freer world. You will also know the always wonderful Emma Suárez, which here proves that theirs is the drama. But also presence a comic air in the film, that touch that makes it simply delicious, while the surroundings where it is not precisely so charming. Also highlight the charming presence of small violet Rodríguez, a well-written paper and changes the lives of our beloved main character.And already by the way mention the correct script, which sometimes exceeds trying to address too many issues at once (for example, the story of the brother agonies spare, although in the end helps round out the main plot), but at the same time get a really successful melodramatic line. And it is not that this is a great movie, one of these masterpieces of cinema homeland such as labyrinth or Sampedro, but it is certainly a courageous proposal, something simple and very obviously creating something really charming. Under the stars is one of the most beautiful films I've seen in time, and this is appreciated. I have no more obliged to add the name of Viscarret in the list of Directors that promise. And it is that start is already much.</body>
</review>
