<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Death Proof" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will delight the good lovers of the talks, the stories something geeks and good film, because if something knows how to make Tarantino (so far), is good cinema.</summary>
	<body>Quentin Tarantino returns to movie theatres, with a jewel that has divided audiences and critics. As it can be deduced, I am among those who have been left to fascinate with its new proposal, with its clear style, and even more so when it has Kurt Russell as the protagonist. Yes, the husband of Goldie Hawn (and father of Kate Hudson) is one of my favorite actors, and see him in "Death Proof", with his car to the test of death, is a point that impairs the balance.Taking this film as a unique (to come separated from "Planet Terror"), I have to say that Tarantino presents the same story twice, which are two groups of girls which are subjected to the macabre game of the "Mike specialist", although with different results.While I most liked the first one, the second is not to get lame, that both are filled with magnificent dialogues, clear references and winks moviegoers, and memorable characters.Another point that makes me tilt the balance, and I do not know if many will be noticed, is the appearance of the shirt which leads Jack Burton (Kurt Russell) in "Blow to the Chinese small", great masterpiece by John Carpenter, and appears a few seconds in the bar manager of Warren (the own Tarantino, who in addition to acting has been commissioned to photograph)(, like Rodriguez in "Planet Terror").The action scenes have a very great importance in the film, but unlike "Kill Bill (volume 1)", in which action abounded in detriment of the dialogues, "Death Proof" gives us these discussions tarantinianas, in which a myriad of topics, with prose as only the director of "Pulp Fiction" knows write. Attention to Kurt Russell reciting you the poem to "Butterfly" Vanesas Ferlito, talks of the girls in the car and in the bar, the great Michael Parks and her son "number 1" in the hospital cafeteria scene "Reservoir Dogs" touch to the scene about sex in which Rosario Dawson seems to embody her role as teenager in "Kids" againLarry Clark, or conversations between "specialist Mike" and Pam (Rose McGowan) prior to show her that your car does honor to the title of the film.There are people that has been unhappy and it is bored, while it is true that the version we have seen in Spain is the extended (because of the incomprehensible far to destroy "Grindhouse", that should be seen in all its glory, and this is with "Planet Terror" and the fake trailers that created for the project), but even so, "Death proof" will delight the good lovers of the talks, the stories something geeks and good film, because if something knows how to make Tarantino (so far), is good cinema.</body>
</review>
