<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El señor de la guerra" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It shows a scary world, but that is there. Five hours by plane from our comfortable lives.</summary>
	<body>We writing a few weeks ago that the American cinema is living a glorious moment in such a way that many of the great films of the time are showing an admirable level of analysis of this society globalized in which we live and a stimulating political commitment to the cause of truth, freedom and justice. "Lord of war", written and directed by Andrew Niccol, represents a step further, another link in a chain that we forwarded to recent films like "Syriana", "Munich", "Crash" or "good night and good luck". Where are the weapons with which millions of people walk wars every day, to entire width and length of the world? That is the question. And as cynically tells in first person the character played by Nicolas Cage, it is not a trivial matter.The film starts with a powerful and impactful sequence that shows the path followed by a bullet since it is not only a piece of metal on a machine of assembling unless it is embedded in the head of a poor African kid, splashing it all blood. At that point, all spectators we look back in the seat. and we took not already off the eyes of the screen during the two hours of projection.Among the best finds of the film is the point of view adopted by Niccol. And may have chosen a third impersonal and analytical person that escrutara, Deus ex machina, an arms dealer activities; opts for a more complicated but much more stimulating solution: giving voice to the despicable character in first person. Gives voice to a sinister dealer which, moreover, is the absolute protagonist of the story. A drug dealer that the audience hates and despises, of course, but which also he is a certain sympathy and to a point of admiration for his coolness, their professionalism, their determination and their capacity to succeed even in the most complicated situations.Nicolas Cage, an actor that has never been my devotion santo, is superb in its recreation of the cynical businessman that conquers the woman of their dreams through a clever ploy that tries to convince himself that his activity is not as bad as others think, it is justified with the "If did it not I""", do any other ", which makes a mockery of all that you are trying to leave him to step and comes to avenge cruel and ruthlessly of their enemies.""Lord of war" shows us a scary world, but that is there. Five hours by plane from our comfortable lives. All African sequences, Liberia and Sierra Leone, dreamy, very harsh, shocking, are masterfully shot, transmitting all the horror describing already Conrad in "Heart of darkness".An excellent film that puts the finger in the wound of one of the most distressing situations we face in the world today. "As says the character played by Ethan Hawke, the real weapons of mass destruction are not atomic or hydrogen, but the AK 47 bombs, the popular Kalashnikovs, these goat horns, so simple, until the kids can be real butchers with them.""Lord of war" is based on an excellent script that brings you a smile, a moment later, left you her frozen face, turned into a grimace of fear. A script full of memorable phrases - "the bullets change more Governments than the votes"-, Manichaean whatsoever and with an apotheosis end which, fortunately, is at the height of the rest of the film. A film that forces you to constantly talk to your Companion's armchair, to make comments and Apostilles, which annoys you, you turn on and you upsets. "Lord of war", in short, is one of those movies that, passing in a sigh, invited talk, reflect, discuss and think. Nothing less.</body>
</review>
