<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Mataharis" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good film of Icíar Bollaín, both from the formal point of view and of substance. A very nice movie liked very much to the public.</summary>
	<body>Good film of Icíar Bollaín, both from the formal point of view and of substance.Bollaín, which has special eye to show the human qualities of the ordinary mortals, known on this occasion take the story in a very interesting way (impeccable magnificent music of Lucio Godoy), resulting in addition, very entertaining as it did in its superb "Te doy mis ojos".This is less dramatic, or at least it has less violent dyes, but also human feelings come into continuous conflict with ethical and/or moral aspects that can make explode into a thousand pieces harmony, love, respect and trust between the beloved people.Thanks to a splendid script where the three main stories are complemented by other, seemingly more light, but just as substantial, the film tastes as a small delicacy, leaving therefore a very good taste. Interlinked different stories that show attractive form States the love of a couple passes along the years: the budding infatuation, the first glimpses of crisis and the death of love, dam of the tedium and empty coexistence of every day with nothing to say.Great interpretations, where stands once more Antonio de la Torre, this time in a small paper with a different log of what you were seeing it lately, and Nuria González. The scenes between them are the best of a movie with splendid and simple dialogues, exists an endearing humanity in the stories that show the best of humans and also, if not the worst, yes more grey and sad.A very nice movie liked very much to the public, having loud applause.The press conference, with the Director and Diego Martín, María Vázquez, Nuria González, Najwa Nimri (beautiful and with a dress that cut the hiccups), and Tristán Ulloa, had no waste, showing a Icíar Bollaín, very safe road undertaken behind the camera. We wish you every success, as well as the film festival. Although there are still many films by compete. We will see.</body>
</review>
