<review author="Antoni Messa" title="Disturbia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The formula is served. Now it is question of enjoy it. Well worth, even if only by his almost total claims lack and the beautiful face of Sarah Roemer, the girl in the House opposite.</summary>
	<body>Disturbia, purely and simply, it is a new twist on the history espoused by Hitchcock in the window indiscreet. A product to use, simple and predictable, although effective. Clearly aimed at the teenage audience, it is a nice way of approaching the classic of the orondo British filmmaker and, to my taste, much more correctly than the pretentious, overloaded and bizarre double body, review of the same title (and Vertigo) made a Brian De Palma in hallucinatory State.Its director D. j. Caruso (a type with a not very good film history), bet by approaching the subject from the coordinates of the serie B, as did John Badham, in 1987 and counting with a similar premise, from his entertaining illegal procedure. And it is, ultimately, Disturbia, at the time that pays homage to Hitchcock masterpiece, turns to a visualization and narrative very own of thrillers youth that were made in the 1980s; something similar to what recently has condemned Michael Bay with his Transformers (unexpectedly) visible, also starring Shia LaBeouf and, apart from the film we are discussing now, recently he could be seen in the splendid memories of Queens and already form part of the cast in the highly anticipated new installment of Indiana Jones.Buena part of the effectiveness of Disturbia is due to the brilliant interpretation of this actor; a young promise rising for the time being, whereas, a pleasure to see him on screen. On this occasion he gives life to Kale Brecht, son of a renowned writer died in a terrible car accident, an unbearable feeling of guilt, it will become a teenage problematic to Kale. He was the driver of the car at the time of the fatal and inevitable mishap.A sentence uttered at the wrong time by his master of Spanish (Italian version dubbed in Spanish) and an unexpected and violent reaction from the boy, will lead him to a three-month house arrest; time that will invest in a State of total restlessness in hanging and spy, after the Windows of his home and to the astonishment of his mother, the comings and goings of members of your neighborhood, a quiet residential area of Pasadena, California. While a plaster leg was the impediment which restricted the movements of a voyeur James Stewart, an artifact police ring-shaped, equipped with a sensor and placed in the right foot, will be the delimiter of the possible displacement of Kale. Soon, as well as discover the presence of vecinita tempting and newly arrival to the neighborhood, you will begin to have strong suspicions of having a wanted serial killer hosted in your own neighborhood.D. j. Caruso tape works on two levels, and both one and the other, makes it correctly. On the one hand, through the nice touch of comedy awarded the character of Kale Brecht and relations with his new neighbor and a schoolmate East - paragraph that highlights, no doubt, by its agile dialogues and, first and foremost, by comic of the splendid skills LaBeouf-and, on the other hand, entering fully into the thriller; treatment, this one, in which their predictability makes too noticeable. Despite this, their development, it shows a good mastery of suspense and intrigue, without diminishing nothing disturbing touch that always know give their perfidious and evil characters, David Morse, a secondary luxury that well deserves a leading role as soon as possible.Make the following mathematical operation and get the film Disturbia as a final result. Window indiscreet more body double. Whilst remaining double physical body giving title to the work of De Palma, add few drops of the very teenager Club of the five. The formula is served. Now it is question of enjoy it. Well worth, even if only by his almost total claims lack and the beautiful face of Sarah Roemer, the girl in the House opposite.</body>
</review>
