<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="¿Y tú Quién Eres?" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Y tú Quién Eres? It is a sentimental, tear and overly sweetened melodrama that is right at the bottom, but fails miserably in the form.</summary>
	<body>Semantically, there is no big difference between both words, but is not the same be timely to be opportunistic. Life is full of people and appropriate things, although unfortunately abound more opportunists. Films also happens this same, there are some who come at the right time to open or continue a debate in society, and there are also taking advantage of certain circumstances, good or bad, to seek a better reception or commercial career.And that a film as Y tú Quién Eres? , whose title and gives many clues about the development of the same release day world against Alzheimer's is a tremendous and shameless tasteless. It is justice that tell a story about one of the worst evils that have arisen in the last century and especially victims who suffer and suffer, directly or indirectly, but also is true that a history of deep depth and significance should be told with more tact and sensitivity, and not become a cheap melodrama. Very little remains of Antonio Mercero addressed to the cabin, and if her previous film, fourth floor, already sinned soft, in Y tú Quién Eres? It launches full childish sentimentality and the easy tear. The film lacks dignity and respect and spare you the sentimentality and the edulcoramiento of Mercero. The script is full of clichés, with some rancid dialogues and some even more acartonados characters and absurd situations. Emphasizes negatively the family character of Cristina Brondo, with the character of the father to the head. Obviously the actors are all very well, with a Manuel Alexandre and a José Luis López Vázquez doing brilliant work without any effort and in spite of the script. Well Cristina Brondo, able to stand on the same footing with these two monsters of the interpretation. Y tú Quién Eres? It is a sentimental, tear and overly sweetened melodrama that is right at the bottom, but fails miserably in the form. And Antonio Mercero should have shown more respect before addressing an issue of such magnitude as Alzheimer's sufferers and their families.</body>
</review>
