<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="En la ciudad de Sylvia" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the city of Sylvia is a failed experiment to show to the public the search undertaken by a man to find a woman, and along the way, offer the throbbing heart of a city.</summary>
	<body>Scarcely a month ago he concluded the 64th Venice Film Festival of cinema, the best edition of the Biennale in many years. There is nothing as the wounded pride to react and straighten the course. Unfortunately, very little Spanish film could be seen at the festival, with honorable exceptions, having only a homeland tape in the Oficial.Dicho section film was in the city of Sylvia, the new work by José Luis Guerín, filmmaker that amazed and excited many for his documentary under construction. Barcelona director returns to his roots to a fictional story, closely linked to the physiognomy of a big city, its places and its inhabitants. A boy (Xavier Lafitte) recalls the encounter he had with Sylvia six years ago, and decides to undertake his search in places frequented, one day find her believed, and begins to follow her. It must be said in advance that in the city of Sylvia is a type of film that seeks a very minority audience, and must go to see her with an open mind, without bias or ideas preconcibas. However, aren't needed many minutes so that the viewer feels invaded by a terrible feeling, the of the here what I paint? The film oozes so much pretentiousness and pedantry can up with the painted. It is not only the complete lack of dialogues is annoying, is that Guerin spends almost all of the minutes trying to demonstrate his great handling of the camera with flat impossible, at the time that aims to show an accurate reflection of what feel and live the inhabitants of a large city. Even has the support that would offer two major interpretations already that Pilar López de Ayala is limited to be, while Xavier Lafitte is something soft and very little credible.In the city of Sylvia is a failed experiment to show to the public the search undertaken by a man to find a woman, and along the way, offer the throbbing heart of a city. However, you will only get numerous spectators who come to see something different, to flee terrified as soon as the room lights are lit.</body>
</review>
