<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Desmembrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is no exaggeration to say that this movie (to some extent) does for the survival horror which in turn made Shaun of the Dead (2004) by the zombie genre.</summary>
	<body>Despite the fact that it has come to our charts with nearly a year of delay, dismembered (2006) landing at a very appropriate time, not only by the fact that in Spain has released in a double session seeking to capitalize on the failure of the Tarantino/Rodriguez Grindhouse phenomenon, but also because the recent proliferancia (with its consequent tired) of survival horror and torture-porn makes that we necessarily have to welcome a film which takes all a topicazos series and the parody in a way only we can qualify as brilliant. And best of all is that at no time feels that a contempt for the genus there is in particular, but just the opposite: humor is so well run and the conventions of this type of story are so well managed (and reverse) that it is no exaggeration to say, as he has already been said since its premiere, this film (to some extent) makes for the survival horror which in turn made Shaun of the Dead (2004) for the zombie genre.Also taking advantage of the recent rush to shoot low-budget productions in the countries of Eastern Europe, the story of Desmembrados part of a same premise of all these films: a group of people trapped in a strange land where one by one are massacred by a local threat. The difference is that this time the protagonists are not horny teenagers or an idyllic middle-class family, but a group of executives of a multinational of weapons which have begun to prove violence which can cause the industry of death which are engaged in their own flesh. Such social satire, in the hands of more "serious" had been laughable and adoctrinante, here is a field of laughs thanks to the use of the most hackneyed Office estreotipos brought to the field of horror: from the useless leader of team until the ball corporate, from the guardian of political correctness to the fingered in the joints and fungi, all must work as a team for the first time in their lives if they want to get unharmed from that experience. But clear, unlike other attempts at parody, dismembered never ceases to be a horror film (and in fact, there is a good piece of the film in which laughter conspicuous by their absence), offal and graphic violence levels are quite high, courtesy of the British Christopher Smith, who had already given a preview in when its least interesting Creep (2004). Perhaps the only downside that I can put to Desmembrados is that, in the end, its ambitions remained short, that history gave to much more. The disaster of the corporate spirit in a real survival situation could have reached epic instead of staying in a few specific references proportions (the Chief is a tough guy at work proves to be a real coward arrival time of the truth), which makes me think that Christopher Smith has not wanted or has not been able to give his film a greater thematic resonance. Even the original title, Severance, refers to Deliverance (1972), which although it is not a film of terror to the use, it is one predecessor to clear the survival horror. Instead, we have to make do with a very good cross between The Office and Hostel (2006), with including Hungarian macizorras.If something can be attributed to him is that, occasionally, his humor can be somewhat bufo and too basic (which does not get to the levels of mastery of Shaun of the Dead, for example), but despite its flaws is appreciated, it is a tape which I, in particular, did not expect much. In a year in which the really outstanding premieres of terror have not been many, a movie like Desmembrados comes to fill a void. I also believe that, with a little more promotion and separated from his partner of double session, sheep you asesinas (2006) could have been a very pleasant surprise.</body>
</review>
