<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="The host" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The average viewer is warned: If you have a little patience with its peculiar rhythm of narration and its deliberate dosage of horror, is one of face to face with one of the most interesting of gender of what far this year.</summary>
	<body>It may not be the definitive monsters tape The Host (2006), the most successful film in the history of Korean cinema and the darling of the latest edition of Sitges, but there is no doubt that this is a serious competitor to be among the best the genre has given us this year. That Yes, this is not a film of creatures in the style, and many of its features could leave cold to the average viewer who goes to the film waiting for a repetition of the classical scheme of the majority of the monster movies that come to us from United States, where virtually the only thing that changes is the nature of the bug to remove.The truth is that tape Bong Jon-hoo is not a typical copy of this genre of film, to start because it is not focused absolutely on the monster, but also on the tribulations of a dysfunctional family in Seoul, which necessarily bind when a horrible Monster (product of a mutation caused by chemical waste from a U.S. military base) emerges from the waters of the River have and cause a massacre between the peaceful passers-by of an idyllic sunny afternoon, after which takes the little girl of the family clan for later consumption. After declaring the national emergency, the family discovers that the small is alive somewhere in the labyrinth sewers of Seoul, and passivity official decide to undertake a search which Quad Final Fantasy in pursuit of the girl.After this initial attack, the Ribbon leaves take a while before we see the monster again, and rather focuses on the pain and the Union of the family, a drama that is seasoned with samples of a humor that sometimes reaches levels of real bizarrada, as for example the entire stream of a night vigil in memory of the victims of the mutant of the have. Also, the personalities of the members of the family clan are disparate over not being able to, and the movie takes its time to follow each in its particular search the small; It is the entrepreneur grandfather and natural leader of the group, the reckless and irresponsible father, hardened and unthinking Uncle (which also has a past as a leader in University riots) and silent aunt and quasi-champion of archery. All the discourse about the family joins the not very subtle environmental subtext which of course not let very obvious criticism to American interventionism (is not chance, as the event which begins the story actually happened in the year 2000 when an officer of a United States base dumped illegally in have hundreds of litres of adulterated formol), but at least not product of this no mutant has gone. (yet). But beyond family dramas and eco-sociological criticism, there is something unavoidable, and is that a monster film, the real protagonist has forcibly that the creature. In this sense, Jon-hoo is her played to show the apparitions of the monster in full light of day, eluding accustomed for subtlety, on many occasions, to conceal the failures of special effects. Such a thing does not happen in The Host, in fact, the monster far from being perfect at a technical level, although miraculously these defects do not influence anything in our appreciation. The appearances of the creature are so well managed that they produce an authentic and genuine tension that does not go away when we see him again. While it is true that the appearances of the monster are not so frequent as we are accustomed, it is also true that this creature is laid at the service of a story that goes in other directions, and that their presence is not only to ward off the staff, something that this film shares with which no doubt is one of their sources of inspiration and point of comparison of a large critical sector: the original version of Gojira (1954), by Japanese Ishiro Honda, a film on which it is necessary to return as soon as possible.Either way, a viewing of The Host is advisable, but the average viewer is warned that you will not find therein another exemplary more typical film monsters (reason why has not found, apparently, the enthusiasm that triggered in Sitges). But if you have a little patience with its peculiar rhythm of narration and its deliberate dosificiación of horror, is one of face to face with one of the most interesting of gender of what far this year. And hurry, because the storm is coming: the corresponding American remake is already inevitable.</body>
</review>
