<review author="Robgordon" title="Disturbia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Light and entertaining film. Well made, but unoriginal and which can be enjoyed without time for boredom.</summary>
	<body>The cinema of orondo genius ahead of his time, Alfred Hitchcock, has always been a reference inevitable for much of the suspense film, since he himself created the genre as such. From the effrontery to Brian de Palma in its arguments and its Visual imitations to this fun hodgepodge of moments purely hitchcockianos that was "what the truth hides" by Robert Zemeckis, which used, among other things, ideas and sequences of the "Rear window".Confined in your room, with a plaster leg and profession photographer, James Stewart was the voyeur Hitchcockiano of that model film of 54, a study on the alien curiosity of the human being, on watch without being seen as desire.Precisely now, that same film, "Rear window" provides a good part of their original material to that covert and not confessed remake which is "Disturbia", starred by the new young figure of American cinema, Shia LeBoeuf in the role of James Stewart. "Disturbia" far become a revamped and educated review of the Hitchcock classic, is a guarantee and enough practice directed to a teenage audience, who probably not know the film on which "Disturbia" elaborates his argument, in the same way that won't be a totally predictable but entertaining film for the viewer more prepared, not only to know the tape of Hitchcock but also because "Disturbia" runs through land hackneyed by the genre of suspense and the teenager moviesthat this already know to imply.There are certain eighties aftertaste in "Disturbia", exemplified in the figure of LeBoeuf, a star emerging on which to build the typical character of adolescent revolutionized hormone that is involved in unexpected adventures with attractive girl of by means, as we have already seen in "Transformers" and as now happen again.In his first piece of footage, "Disturbia" recalls that family film of the 1980s and can remember more to the recent "Monster House" (another eighties revival) that to "Rear window". Moreover, there is a very large difference between the tape of Hitchcock and d.j. Caruso, which demonstrates the intentions of both movies. "Rear window" was the particular analysis of Hitchcock to one of the many obsessions that surrounded him, voyeurism, and the facts in one, arose as a result of a need for physical and/or sexual. The character of James Stewart maintained a relationship with Grace Kelly, but did not seem too pleased. Hitchcock, inteligentísimo as anyone, we were taught a small discussion of this couple, after which Stewart would seek through their binoculars and the Windows of their neighbors, a means of evasion, but also replacement made su, a priori, deteriorating relationship. Stewart was looking for the outside miseries, to not do you feel him so miserable, the beauty of a female body, before the impossibility for that of his girlfriend (Grace Kelly), or the passion of these first-time bride and groom that he makes time who had lost. Nevertheless, it was in the lives of their neighbors in front.In "Disturbia" nothing of the sort happens. Shia LeBouef is a mirror of the current, full of entertainment of last generation and delighted young have a neighbor newcomer to the neighborhood that is attractive in their eyes. Rebel and with a detector GPS prevents him to leave his home, LeBouef mira to neighbors as secondary and residual activity of the punishment that has been imposed (his mother, the actress Carrie Anne Moss, prevented play networked to the console and watch pay channels) and as a result of this new neighbor good looking.It is this difference which away from the Hitchcock film, but her close to the new audience. A maneuver which adapts with expertise to our times plot of "Rear window" with current suspense and family and juvenile 1980s comedy film and is the key that "Disturbia" has been a success at the box office in the United States, and one of the "sleepers" of the year.Characters, moments and elements of "Rear window" are repeated with great thought in "Disturbia", which will not be enough so that the director D.J. Caruso, knows to create good doses of suspense. That's why "Disturbia" will simply not find rebound a murderer in the House opposite (good work of actor David Morse), but you need to leave this home detention to which LeBouf is bound for entering clichés of horror (grim basement, serial killers, etc) that end up being tense for the Viewer.However, "Disturbia" is an entertaining and light film. Well made, but unoriginal and which can be enjoyed without time for boredom, where in addition, confirmed the talent of Shia LeBouf, which gains to major player in the not too distant future, as there is also a new young actress to keep track, Sarah Roemer.</body>
</review>
