<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Disturbia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A Hitchcock recycled (and sweetened) for teenagers. At least entertaining.</summary>
	<body>Alfred Hitchock premiered in 1954 the rear window, starring James Stewart and Grace Kelly. The film told the story of a photographic reporter, forced to sleep with his leg escayolada, and sometimes accompanied by his beautiful girlfriend and her nurse, it seeks to escape the tedium of his convalescence looking from the window of his apartment at the other side of the courtyard, collecting meticulously, and with the help of binoculars, fragments of the lives of numerous neighbors. until that, due to a series of small actions, voyeur reporter begins to suspect a neighbor before the sudden disappearance of the wife.Disturbia, which premiered in our country last Friday, is built at the base of the legendary film by Hitchcock. Someone who is forced to stay in a place and begins to spy on people. Here, James Stewart is obsoleted by the omnipresent Shia LaBeouf, a problematic teenager who, due to a fostión Lord who sticks to his professor of Italian (Spanish in the original version), condemned him to be under arrest world.The problem of Disturbia is that it does not offer nor adds virtually nothing new to the genre, because until that not it gets slightly serious, the film turns out to be a typical, forced ("I was going to condemn a year of reform, but as I know what losing a father, and give me a shame, because it hala, a month of arrest world" do!?!!!) and topiquísima whole life teenager film. The foreseeable, and those with fat script failures (tuned to a MONUMENTAL shit, related to the character of the mother of the prota, played by Carrie-Anne Moss; do remember Trinity matrix?-, when he begins the final climax). A Hitchcock recycled (and sweetened) for teenagers.Saves narrowly from the burning that is entertaining, that final climax tachycardia and quite achieved judging by the times, and a majísimo Shia LaBeouf returns to nail her role.</body>
</review>
