<review author="Plissken" title="Amor y otros desastres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ñoño, but nice, homage to the "nottinghills" and "bridgetjones" and "loveactuallys" and "cuatrobodas" that flooded the screens during the 1990s.</summary>
	<body>Another decade we're going racing, and the writers making watermarks to recycle all recyclable. After exhausting the "standard" English romantic comedy (all a sub-subgénero) Philo, the voracious reescritores of Hollywood began to spin to the concept, and have brought the penultimate straw by squeeze: 'Love and other disasters' (miraculously, the English translation is accurate: holiday of the Titrator?).The synopsis will not blind with his brilliance, precisely: Emily "Jack" Jackson, a young employee of Vogue in London strives to both fix the love life of her friends never has time to deal with yours, quite ruined, incidentally. The appearance on the scene of an attractive Assistant of Argentine photographer will be the opportunity that his friends sought to return the favors to Jacks. But in the 21st century we live, young, handsome, and single usually amount to gay. Or not? Or Yes? Or not?The disappeared in combat Alex Keshishian (which only left front "In bed with Madonna"), which Simon Phoenix, has been defrosted and put back into circulation to write and direct this curious attempt metacine, romanticón and speech, but modernillo to the end and Cape. The first thing that makes Keshishian is situate ourselves in the same starting point for the typical sentimental comedy british, but with a monísima and correct Brittany Murphy instead of Hugh Grant. Murphy's character is a calque of Audrey Hepburn with clothes (or without it), but there is no worry, because it's the metacine thing.The simplistic plot progresses, with a gallery of characters we all know from an 'Enchanted April' or 'four weddings and a funeral': rich and dumb friend, friend gay sickly and sensitive, perfect stranger. Everything is modeled, but, Oh, the metacomedia!, in today's world almost all friends of Jacks are perfectly integrated into their community gay. Go change of scenario, eh?And the element perhaps more importantly of what proposed Keshishian is the roommate of Jacks, Peter (also correct Matthew Rhys). screenwriter. And speaking with Jacks continuously on romantic comedies, repeating themselves sobados schemes. This allows Mr. Keshishian spun gags that Yes worth seeing "Love and other disasters", that ends up being ñoño, but sympathetic, homage to the "nottinghills" and "bridgetjones" and "loveactuallys" and "cuatrobodas" that flooded the screens during the 90.Aparte of this detail, that Yes, nothing to highlight: routine address, photo routine, routine music. just takes off a little artistic direction, which gets us worldwide impossible of simple servants of Vogue who live in simple and centrally located lofts and have simple friendly multimillonarias. But as said Galileo: ".""And yet it moves!" Not much, but moves. a 5 pelao.</body>
</review>
