<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Guardianes del día" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excessive, boring, lengthy, unnecessary exercise exhibitionist with the single mission of paving for its mediocre director, the way for the conquest of Hollywood.</summary>
	<body>With an apocalyptic fireworks of vampires and evil people live a few producers with bundles fat of banknotes in the briefcases and desire to emulate the technological expertise and the commercial success of the sons of Hollywood fragua guardians of the day, second - feel - part of another story between magic and how embarrassing that a couple of years ago dropped the dolby surround of the cinemas of the world and then stayed on the shelves of the video shops for the greater glory of the ametrallado teen public of strong emotions and scenes of very expensive and high-voltage. There are (threaten) a third party: something as well as guardians of the twilight. I did not see the first attack and I lost the second, that comes to tell us the issue of light and darkness. Nothing to Bram Stoker knew not, for not going further back. It is the almost immediate certainty that the costly and devastating visual apparatus is going to cut - sever is a more useful verb - all narrative interest. In fact, the film leaves see forward when we are already blinded enough by the devastating machinery of special effects: the Ferrari - was a Ferrari? -climbing a building that all gas, more than amazed us, produces us a hilarious effect because it does not (simply) is beside the point. To me made me think in those unnecessary nudes that encabritaban to the staff in the very kitsch payroll of casposas tapes of our glorious transition, but not us away from the track for more.The anthologies between good and bad battles have given to film glorious pages. If the breath that ignites them of epic comes from the literature the outcome usually, except for incompetence of director or budget, dignified poverty, how much less. Nothing disturbs here: everything can be seen with a neutral interest. The Moscow inhabited by supernatural creatures, this contemporary Moscow which could have been an incentive for the Western Viewer, leads to boredom: everything is superficial, devoid of any memorable trait. The bad guys are as flat as the good guys, and that Manichaeism impostado Russian film with pretensions yanks the marvelous display of software (are talking about this since that I started this review) adds nothing new. The American friend is still ready friend: Russian is a flattering type, which has grown by the side of a film that programmed too much violence and too frivolous about violence. Neither his name I could remember to write this review.Guardians of the day satura, that is, saturated as few films of this genre so gratifying for the large majors and the public of low demands and money to burn in strong experiences. More or less strong. Over time, this chronicler of their vices is doing most. Notes it with more evidence in these fantasmadas vampire, these formidable invoice videocliperos outbursts but non-existent interest. It is now when one in the unfathomable ways of random thought: perhaps - I say perhaps - destiny wanted that I miss (so to speak) two hour and some of my time in this medio-bodrio so can compensate me tonight with some jewel of the film. I do not know: I am thinking of Nosferatu in Murnau, long step fear (of truth) is not to watch a movie. I will report on the outcome.</body>
</review>
