<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Plauto, recuerdo distorsionado de un tonto eventual" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Coto Matamoros film about a multiple murder in a circus that haunts the sole survivor, a clown called Plautus. A professional had done so, I would say that it is like hitting a parent, but as the work of an amateur, I would say that it is like paste God. First, and last, hope drama geek.</summary>
	<body>Tonight I wanted to see one of those movies that you can get hundreds of bad jokes, amazing (of bad) scenes and things like that. Why I have the deuvedeteca jewels like this of Plautus. So saying seems an interesting film, but if you say that the writer is Coto Matamoros entendereis front had a juicy reason to adorn me. But it turns out that the cast of geeks who go through the screen, do so in dramatic roles. I swear, Nuria Bermúdez felaciona (come on, that the chupa) dramatically. By my children.The truth is that you admittedly you screenwriter documented on the subject greatly, trying to get a moralina on how bad the cocaine that tug of war not accustomed sphincters. Or well, perhaps was not the idea, but if metiendote by the napias finish Tertullian selling miseries or making movies geeks, not was I if the message was "drug you like me, that look at the far have come in life". Country gentlemen, that country.The film is about a crime committed in a circus, which is not live or the bearded woman, nor the Human Cannonball, even the bombero torero. To the bewilderment of the police, a clown called Plauto, occurs as a culprit, allowing two seconds to become a reporter. So they put us a flashback to tell us what has happened.Little remains for me to tell. Since Santiago Segura you gave to bring their buddies in the movies, anyone believes you can do it. Here we have those characters who passed by the television selling their miseries. Well, at least I have brought clear that what they say on TV is true, that as bad acting everything must be true. It has left me cold film, as the photo of the espatarrada women who say that not having sex and believe me a pixel of Japanese porn movie, I wanted to uncouth jokes and humor lumpy, and it is that they have gotten them into a drama. As if you put an elephant in a China shop.In short, Coto Matamoros film on a multiple murder in a circus that haunts the sole survivor, a clown called Plautus. A professional had done so, I would say that it is like hitting a parent, but as the work of an amateur, I would say that it is like paste God. First, and last, hope drama geek.Besitos.P.D: Seen from the distance, has subtle touches of humor, how to put lamepenes to Nuria Ber, call the Dioni vans, or take a drug dealer with more nose than Dumbo.P.D.2: the paste to God is a phrase from the movie, that would not be me occur a blasphemy as well.P.D.3: I forgot, Nuria Bermúdez dies of a camouflaged on the cheek, that from Karate to death in Torremolinos and the ninjas sacándole casings were as a kind of coarse rope, I have not seen anything worse.P.D.4: Good things is, the apotheosis of naked women. Not to mention the Dioni in his underwear. Art in motion.</body>
</review>
