<review author="José A. Peig" title="300" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>300 is a representation (again) of the epic of the war, makes use of the usual reasons in this topic using the battle of Thermopylae as a basis from which to develop the show with good pace and an absorbent staging.</summary>
	<body>Against a product as before us in these days, the first thing is to define the scope and the spirit that gives life to the film directed by Zack Snyder. Combinatorics of elements and colors, it is a pastiche that breaks with the texture itself the historical folletín and epic fantasy, he synthesizes both to find its raison d ' être in a mesmerizing spectacle that justifies itself despite its flaws. 300 is a representation (again) of the epic of the war, makes use of the usual reasons in this topic using the battle of Thermopylae as a basis from which to develop the show with good pace and an absorbent staging. If we look at history, we can consider it as a historical account in key Pulp (and bias that entails from the point of view of historiography), trivialization of a genre and style to create a universe akin to the work on which it is based (the comic book by Frank Miller), maintaining fidelity to the original andat the same time, the narrative force in its transposition into the film.With regard to its possible artistic values, dominates the shape on the background, the use of photography and the composition of mythological and historical elements that encourage in a landscape close to the epic of Wagner that Homer's, no doubt we are before a film visual above any other attribute, dotted with sporadic oniric tables or others in which the battle takes on biblical intensity and bombast. Although, as a result, its imbalance between form and substance from an irregular set ranging from sublime moments until Mannerism efficiency and the most vulgar clichés, cannot be denied that there is some consistency between tonality and development of the story and the expressive configuration in the use of photography and other plastic resources. The voiceover, which often contributes significantly to strengthening the dramatic meaning of the scene, it ends up minimize narration a single-issue and repetitive exposure. There comes a time in which redundancy is produced by the joint use of visual representation and Word, very common problem in movies that make use of the Narrator absent from the scene. The characters are reduced to a crude gesture and a few images of violent outpouring, but based on the nature of the story and the preponderance of aesthetics on content, this is a film of profiles and archetypes, and is therefore not necessary demand much more, while it is true that with complex characters it would gain in depth and narrative dynamism in concordance with the range of reflections and socio-cultural pretensions to be learned of a war drama.The story becomes an elegy for the fallen heroes thanks to which a civilization perseveres in its own myths and faith by the sword and the homeland, and for the love of the family.The realization is the real Builder of the original spirit of the work, with a profusion of Visual tricks very close to artifice developed by the Wachowski brothers in Matrix, which, in perfect concordance with the various records used in storytelling - violence testosterónica, hemoglobin to abundance, sex, electronic music alternating with the Wagnerian epic, world freak and dream - configures the coherent idea which gives itself to this banal product uniquenessno doubt, but that does not exclude the fact that possesses a spirit itself and legitimate film expression. In short, the operatic pop is consistent and brilliant, complies with the sequence "the idea idea-ejecución" quite accurately and without pretensions to go beyond itself. Superfluous and Mannerist idea in many respects, therefore conclude that its flaws are inherent in the characteristics of the product, but at least it has squeezed all its possibilities with honesty.</body>
</review>
