<review author="Bruji" title="Sin reservas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The interpretative duel arriving to engage actors actresses, the proven melomanía of the director of?Shine? do and flawless adaptation of the screenplay, end up doing's?No reservations? a film treat? comme il faut?.</summary>
	<body>American version of "Delicious Martha", the German production which, in 2001, we not only conquered by the stomach. The interpretative duel that arrive to engage the actresses actors, the proven melomanía of the director of "Shine" and flawless adaptation of the script, they end up doing a film "comme il faut" recipe "Without reservations". If we remember the guapa-francesa - drawing-animated appeared in Ratatouille, we asomamos the character of Martina Gedeck in Sandra Nettelbeck's original story, and look at the determination with which the great Lady of Douglas statement that "all their dishes culminate comme il faut", we came to the conclusion that all the "chefs" of world cuisine are women of arms taken. It is possible that thus are all great professionals from five continents. And it is also possible that this attitude towards life not adept at a natural instinct of protection, but a studied survival exercise. More, as Ortega y Gasset said, "the River opens a channel and then the channel enslaves the river", accurate explanation that could justify the misnamed work addiction and his worst result, fear for life, itself, which has not given time to Gregory. "There is no cookbook for life." First of all, we should not confuse the Viewer. Although so you've marketed, no reservations, American version of "Delicious Martha", is not a romantic comedy, because neither it was the story on which it is based. If seek gender is, just indicate that such recurring argument must be understood as a vital witness, like everyone, take implicit drama, and the sense of humor as a necessary mechanism for compensation. Its purpose is none other than the approaching that subjective and abstract, concept that is constructed from the inside, called "happiness". "The soft breeze that, occasionally, clears you face", as used to define what flags, International Malaga. At this point, would be irresistible to think that such an argument, - by everyday and massively exploited - could be so insubstantial within a film adaptation as the own production that it contains a inconsequential "romantic comedy". And that is where all the predictions fail. Paraphrasing his exquisite script, "life is unpredictable" and, fortunately, the film also is, so the recipes some invented, against all odds, stand as the best. Bless are managers that, even in our days, are capable of entering a genus overused, stripped of its clichés and unpretentious protest, achieve elevate it. Obviously, when talking about "some" we are not referring to "any". Scott Hicks marks a milestone in the history of cinema with Shine, have the biography of an absolutely unknown pianist, to make him famous. Otherwise, would typically be echoing the biography of a musician already enshrined. No reservations, it confirms that his foray into the world of music was not casual or timely, given that one of the major successes of the film now Orchestra, is based on the proper use of the soundtrack. The score by Philip Glass - of itself, overwhelming - it will be wisely mixed with important pieces of Opera performed by the Pavarotti himself, that, seasoned with various popular topics, they erected it, in not few moments in the footage, in absolute protagonist. In the good kitchen, so masterful ability to find the key to the perfect dose, so only an example of the interesting combination that houses the rest of the tape between the various technical and artistic aspects ending her composing. The restrained use of voice-overs; accurate photography of interiors, which makes the most of the few outdoor spaces that allow filming to capture the beauty of an unknown New York, and a careful art direction that recreates the ins and outs of a non-existent restaurant, alternating with spectacular interpretative duel between the naturalness of the little Miss Sunshine and professionalism of one of the biggest divas of contemporary cinema. "The magic enters in scene," exclaimed Jack Lemmon rather than lowering the clapperboard. The magic comes from a scene of Traffic, in which the Ballerina beauty, that many believed Latin blood, pronounced with plausible coldness a "Volar him the head" which impacted in the retina of many moviegoers who we swore her loyalty. The magic that makes absolutely expendable to her male partner. When she fills the screen, even keeping in mind Lords of the stature of Connery or Clooney, who it is not?</body>
</review>
