<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="En la ciudad de Sylvia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you want to spend a nice time stirring the drawer of the bedside table, looking for something that you know you are not going to find beforehand, but knowing that the search will return to life forgotten objects? This is the film.</summary>
	<body>Jose Luis Guerín has more to do with the painting, with the trade of cabinetmaker of images with the search for purity in the chaos, that with the film, and therefore worth approaching his work. Already in his film "under construction" sat the bases of its modus operandi of his relationship with the world. The images that give off their films are portraits of perpetual motion that puts in the same epistemological plane waves wind draws in the mane from an unknown woman and the dance of trams, passers-by and bicycles that dominates the current pulse of any European city. Jose Luis Guerín seems to have condensed inherent to the world and to the people, to the gestures of each, to present reality pills. "En la ciudad de Sylvia", his latest film, gives vent to his self more voyeur, and embelesa in the search for an ideal of the perfect image of womanhood, of the faces that do not know or we will know. What the director get, therefore it is one of the most unsuccessful and at the same time beautiful searches has seen in a film, and that is too much. With exceptional naturalness occurs mimesis with the main character, of which we have minimal, if anything its diseccionadora look, but not their motivations (and that's an asset, since the spectator inevitably creates his own world, their own stories that will enrich the that shows the director) is perhaps preferable to not talk too much about the plot. Perhaps this film isn't too important to do so, because the argument is the search, search in uppercase, and the self-absorption that produces its viewing. "En la ciudad de Sylvia" is a film to enjoy in silence and with respect. In silence because his footage is practically silent: a few lines of dialogue slip in a slow, quiet, montage at the same time requiring a complete concentration, because each gesture is important, every gesture carries a full identity. With respect, because it is as the director tries to humans and their complicated networks of interactions between people and the world, between the city and people, and finally between people. If you want to spend a nice time stirring the drawer of the bedside table, looking for something that you know you are not going to find beforehand, but knowing that the search will return to life forgotten objects &hellip; this is the film.</body>
</review>
