<review author="Pablo López" title="Hairspray" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>'Hairspray' is, without a doubt the funniest movie of the summer, and very probably, year-round complete.</summary>
	<body>Skeptical I was during this time as a musical film adaptation of a King of the trash film John Waters could be as geek who could not distinguish if I had loved or wanted to hit me a shot they had given me. I already alone I am fairly geek, I do not deny, but he feared that this musical I determined, land the absurd, the grotesque, the monstrosity and stay in one more than multiple adaptations of Broadway musicals to cinema failed. But you can rest assured, because it is not well. 'Hairspray' is a real candy for any lover of the more playful music and adrenalínico: musical number relentlessly, frantic dances and colorful and attractive aesthetics all this at the mercy of a brutal band sound, catchy over not being able to and to do that you're moving in the armchair from the beginning until the end.Shankman performs a work of more elaborate adaptation that we put as an example, Susan Stroman in 'The producers' and much appreciated. Freedom of movement and choreography of actors and dancers gives the film much more eye candy and allows to produce a much richer in flat scenes and others, but I'm not too bored.The actors are superb. The great discovery of the movie, Nikki Blonsky, the borda, the cast of young people headed by a hilarious pipiolos James Mardsen, a justito Zac Efron, Amanda Bynes and Elijah Kelley are they go out, and less are not the most experienced as Queen Latifah, an unrecognizable Christopher Walken and the lovely Michelle Pfeiffer. Special mention to John Travolta, turned into an entradita Lady in kilos, without a doubt, the funniest of the film character.I cannot conclude without doing the required compared to the original. John Waters film was much more politically incorrect, much more disruptive, and Divine was much Divine, this history is simpler than the mechanism of a jug, the script has some tricks that may confuse, but does that matter when they are looking forward to is get up and get to dance? 'Hairspray' is, without a doubt the funniest movie of the summer, and very probably, year-round complete.</body>
</review>
