<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La Carta Esférica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I have not read the original novel by Arturo Pérez-Reverte on which this film is based but I'm beginning to think that poor Arturo, writer nothing insignificant, is hexed film.</summary>
	<body>I have not read the original novel by Arturo Pérez-Reverte on which this film is based but I'm beginning to think that poor Arturo, writer nothing insignificant, is hexed film. "The spherical letter", despite being directed by the prestigious Imanol Uribe, author also of the script, it does not escape this gafe.Several are the problems and defects that bedevil the final outcome of the film. The first of them and against all odds is the main actress. Aitana Sánchez Gijón is a beautiful talented actress but is not the most appropriate for the role. What the character needed was a magnetic woman, attractive and mysterious; a genuine "femme fatale". Aitana is beautiful, Yes, but theirs is not being "femme fatale". In Spain we often confuse sensuality with beauty and is not necessary to be a bellezón to interpret a role so we know all those who, to give just two examples, remember Marlene Dietrich or Barbara Stanwyck. The worst is not not giving the role Aitana, worst thing is that in fact the plot is absolutely amazing if one does not believe that character. It is ridiculous that a man experienced in life as Coy (Carmelo Gómez) and even Palermo (Enrico Lo Verso) have been able to be crazy of love for her, to the point of leaving his wisdom on one side and put his life at risk.Perhaps because of the lack of credibility of the most important role, the characters in general appear to be not nicely drawn. Thus, deprived the film of much of its attraction, we feel that not nothing happens during much of the footage: there is no adventure, no physical nor emotional journey that would justify the duration of the movie that could have been cut enough (and that) despite several strange ellipsis which spare us a couple of important moments. For example, eliminating two quite free sex scenes, even though they are there so that we better understand to Tangier (Aitana) and its relationship with Coy (Carmel), they fail its purpose.When it seems that the word adventure will look on the screen, the film accelerates up to reach a hasty end and a tad silly that does not fit very well with the rest of the film.Of course, the technical invoice is impeccable; from the artistic direction of photography, through the soundtrack. The problem is a lack of substance, of soul, chicha.As hope is the last thing that is lost, the next time that release a film based on a novel by Reverte I will be there to see it. Sooner or later someone will do justice to one of the most prolific and entertaining writers of our country.Final evaluation of moonfleet.es: 3 out of 10</body>
</review>
