<review author="Calaf" title="Domino" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite having interesting elements, spare you half an hour and too many small side entanglements that spoil</summary>
	<body>Thanks to my cousins Louis and Alfonso de viajarfacil.com for inviting me to the preview of the last of the director Tony Scott, brother of Ridley and author or producer of action and success of recent times always interesting tapes. Theirs include Tristan and Isolde (2006), the fire of vengeance (2004), Spy Game (2001), fan (1996) or the magnificent red tide (1995) and Top Gun (1986). Simplifying things is well known in film, or you have a good story or you can enforce the by the way to tell the tale. Master Hitchcock was more interested always in the how to in what this expert. An example, psychosis. Had not happened of mediocre a linear story of a schizophrenic masquerading as his mother to assassinate his motel customers. Hitchcock raised to the altars by his way of telling her, hiding details to the public and resolving at the end.What can not be in any way is having a complex plot and walking laps with the Viewer. If to this we add the unique visual style of Tony Scott (with rapid movement, close-ups, filters, etc), once again, valid as spicy in poor stories, without this being the case, the result is that in the middle of the Ribbon you have to more than half disconnected room and no real interest in the resolution, that anything is possible.The true protagonist is Keira Knightley, a character too cool. I dare say that the rest are secondary, including Mickey Rourke, that looks like of echo dust and finish when he saw him with sunglasses in the program Isabel Gemio.La peli has his good punches, as theories of miscegenation or the stellar appearance of 2 members of the series feeling of living by themselves. The visual dominance of Scott (poor editor) and the ability to put music is notable, but this movie, despite having interesting elements, spare you half an hour and too many small side entanglements that spoil.</body>
</review>
