<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Perras callejeras" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film kinki on a band of women in the Decade of 80 in Spain. Worst Infinítamente to its male version, can be seen, if only to be able to boast of having seen such tape.</summary>
	<body>The film of the 1980s in Spain was a true melting pot of styles and themes. From the films of social complaint, as "The crime of Cuenca" of the ill-fated Pilar Miró (Incidentally, that pathetic me is his son), until the despelote all already know. Making a hole between them, emerged that we could define as film kinki, which are histories of the suburbs of the large Spanish cities. Counting as exponent "Strays" tape, this director wanted to make a tribute (called arrimo my sardine to the Ember of others) and released this "street dogs" which has cost me a horror to find the given poster that has name of porn movie (perhaps I should see some of the latter).The film is about three girls (look like older paper interpreted) together to form a street gang and thus escape from the street with their drugs, beatings and prostitution. Things are going pretty well, until starting to think at levels higher, that does not cause them if not serious problems.It goes without saying that it is worthwhile to watch the movie to see the showcase of young breasts coming out, which are when the silicone was on the boards of the Windows. What level pechil, my mother. The argument is not that it is a wonder, but is not at all bad. The actors are a bit loose with some corrupt policemen that surprise you torrent, although we have some very good actor in minor roles. Dialogs are great, very old-fashioned, but great. For those who want to go through hard and actually are pure poetry. My average Zucchini was listening to the movie and I occasionally came to ask "Did say...?". Buenísimos. Resumiendo, film kinki on a band of women in the Decade of 80 in Spain. Worst Infinítamente to its male version, can be seen, if only to be able to boast of having seen such tape.A classic of the video store at the end of the 80.Besitos.P.D: "There are people who do things with his head." Other than with the heart. I nothing of the sort, I do by that asks me the pussy. Yes, Yes, fuck, what? "."Pd2: by the way, do the sexual act with underwear, what things.</body>
</review>
