<review author="Caty" title="Mystic River" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great movie, highly recommended and will be in the annals of the seventh art as a classic.</summary>
	<body>Three kids, Jimmy, are and Dave are playing in a typical street of a worker suburb of Boston when they are interrupted by a policeman (or what looks like a police officer). The man furtively teaching a plaque, waged to friends by be writing their names in the wet cement of the sidewalk, telling them that you have to take one of them prisoner. After asking them where they lived, the man decides to take to Dave, this is which lives further away and thus will have opportunity to tell his parents the acts of vandalism that is dedicated to his son. Jimmy and they can do nothing and are limited to observe as the car goes away with a Dave inside, that not to look back, to his friends. The man, who was in fact a pedophile, for four days is dedicated to abusing Dave in all imaginable forms while keeps you locked in a hideout. Dave manages to escape, but his life will be marked forever, as well as their friends.This is the start of Mystic River, Clint Eastwood film based on the eponymous book by Dennis Lehane. Eastwood is like the wines, which as it ages grows its quality. It is also an example of how a star, after a successful career as actor, chooses to be behind the camera to direct their own films, made in the style of their mentors Don Siegel and Sergio Leone. With Siegel, he learned to make films quickly and cost-effectively, filming you need and maintaining an organized set. Leone, Eastwood absorbed the more artistic side and his tendency to tell epic stories. Brings together a great cast: Sean Penn, Kevin Bacon, Tim Robbins, Laurence Fishburne, Laura Linney, Marcia Gay Harden., and not only stayed in directing this excellent cast of actors, but that he was also in charge of producing the film and - surprise - for the soundtrack.Twenty years later, the three friends back together under very sad circumstances: the daughter of Jimmy (Sean Penn), Katie, is brutally murdered. The police in charge of the case is be (Kevin Bacon), (along with a Laurence Fishburne playing his partner). To further complicate the history, the last person to see Katie alive was Dave (Tim Robbins), in a night bar with a few friends hours before his disappearance, and reached home late in the morning, with clothes full of blood and very scared before the puzzled eyes of his wife (Marcia Gay Harden). After so long, we excited Jimmy as the youngest of his daughters going to communion, but his daughter mayor Katie will not just appear at the ceremony after a night partying with her friends, Sean is shown as a competent policeman who has been the only one to be able to flee their old neighborhoodleft six months ago by his wife, it is called every day and stays silent, listening as are tells their concerns and what he has done throughout the day; Dave appears as a good father and husband, because quite recovered but still very marked internally by the hell had to suffer during the four days of continuous abuse in her childhood. It is amazing as an actor like Sean Penn, which began as a rebel of the American cinema in films of low budget and low-quality film, it has become over the years an interpreter solid, firm and which is able to transmit us the intensity of Jimmy, a father whose daughter has been murdered. Tim Robbins, as always, sublime, count with the guarantee of at least a certain quality, and Kevin Bacon, is to make a film already eternal supporting actor, this film is probably the best performance of his career.Make special mention at the end, full of tension and metaphors, wondering what would have happened if instead of getting Dave twenty years into the sinister car, Jimmy had been or are. Great movie, highly recommended and will be in the annals of the seventh art as a classic.</body>
</review>
