<review author="Caty" title="Lost in traslation" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Basically, the story of two people in different appearance in a culture and in a different city: Tokyo. Will when I saw the first images of this film, I was really impressed with the feeling of loneliness, be? out of place?, which transmit their characters, though in one of the most populous cities in the world.</summary>
	<body>Basically, the story of two people in different appearance in a culture and in a different city: Tokyo. When I saw the first images of this film, I was really impressed with the feeling of loneliness, of being "outside place", which transmit their characters, though in one of the most populous cities in the world.In a hotel in Japan's capital, Bob Harris (Bill Murray), an American actor whose career ranges from layer fall, passes a season to Japan to shoot an advertisement for Whisky, disenchanted, in full crisis 50-his marriage is boring, pointless and boring, and her acting career is no longer what it was, this back everything and anything already surprised, living day to day by pure inertia- and in which the culture shock that involves travel to the country of the sun rising, only does accentuate this crisis. But in the midst of all this apathy is a young American woman, Charlotte (Scarlett Johansson), also lost in the huge hotel, in the huge city, who travels with her husband, photographer by profession, and seem more enamored with his work that his wife. They can't sleep, they cannot ask "what am I doing here", and clear, so lost two people just for being in the bar of the hotel bar, where every night is equal. The first dialogue of the two protagonists, which begins with the phrase of Bob Harris Lough Charlotte: "I have prepared a plan to escape from this hotel, then escape the city and finally in the country, will be dangerous, but I need an accomplice" is clearly revealing the feeling that unites them. From this moment, the two realize that, despite the age, they have much in common, and begin to be known and to take refuge in the other, walking the streets of Tokyo, speaking late in the hotel.transformando room at the complicity that occurs when, in a strange country we find a compatriot and this seems to be the only reference to our everyday world (if you have travelled abroad and you have) (after this, know that I mean) in a very special relationship (because of the remoteness of the home, giving to think that two people, in their usual worlds, or had met), not being anything carnal, but more protection, support. The argument is as simple as that, many people may think that simple that it is boring, but the truth is that during the two hours that lasts get hooked to the screen, despite having a pace rather slow. Bill Murray, taking as it has clear talent for comedy, never seemed a good actor, but in this film is quite convincing. Scarlett Johansson, with a clean look, fits perfectly in his character. Anecdotally, tell Sofia Coppola conceived the role of Bob Harris thinking exclusively of Bill Murray, demanding that if he did not incarnate the actor been unless in Japanese land, not he shot the film.With a mixture of comedy and drama, much of the tape seems a documentary (attention to photography, very good) about the curiosities and peculiarities that Westerners can find when traveling to Tokyo: the language is totally different (attention also to the dialogue in French which has Harris with a Japanese in a night bar at wee hours of the morning)television programs are different and shocking to our tastes, striptease clubs are different forms of entertainment, in conclusion, far from the average of all that nuestras.en, the complicity between the two main characters will building with delicacy, fleeing from many clichés perhaps, in which another type of director, had fallen. Sofia Coppola was consolidated with this film as Director after "the Virgin suicides" (another film with good enough criticism to be an opera prima). For me, a film that leaves you with a very good taste.</body>
</review>
