<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Mataharis" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Icíar Bollaín tells us a small great story full of force that moves the Viewer by its veracity and the simplicity of the Mise en scène.</summary>
	<body>Spanish Cinema of quality this year is shining by their absence to the point that becomes really difficult to draw up a list of the five best titles of 2007. It is ironic that some of the proposals that would fall in this list would do it more for the rest than on their own merits demerits. It is also the less shocking that several of these films are operas materials, and even more in a year in which filmmakers have released as Gerardo Herrero, Imanol Uribe or July Medem.Esperemos that in the coming months the picture dates, and the turning point can mark it Icíar Bollaín with Mataharis, a story of three detectives fighting for revealing the non-secrets and keep yours safe. But to confuse anyone, Mataharis is not a film of intrigue, full of glamour and conspiracies, but that it is a realistic portrayal of the situation of women workers in our country. The great script would have worked just as if instead of detectives they were journalists, for example. Icíar Bollaín reflects with great realism, the problems faced by couples and especially women to reconcile their professional lives with the family, even more so if there are children from through. Donostiarra filmmaker tells a small great story full of force that moves the Viewer by its veracity and the simplicity of the Mise en scène. You have had three different at the same time stories without any stay lame would not have been possible without the excellent work of mounting with Mataharis, since at no time the tape becomes heavy, or lapses the interest by any of the characters. The interpretations are all worthy of applause, but it is impossible to not highlight the three protagonists who do superb work characterized by its sobriety and restraint.In Mataharis, Icíar Bollaín returns to claim as one of the best stories of the Spanish film counters making a film very consistent with what feels society in our country. Undoubtedly, one of the best titles of the year.</body>
</review>
