<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El asesinato de Richard Nixon" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unpleasant, desaprovechada, sometimes formidable, heavy at times, the assassination of Richard Nixon is saved by a recommended Sean Penn and its history, which interests itself, although we have the certainty that the director her desastra by err on the side of right, of educated, simple...</summary>
	<body>According to apesasumbrado this Chronicle on American disenchantment autobiographical, the story is written in the margins, on the outskirts, others textbooks and the political literature. This is the story of an American medium, tasteless and boring, sad and cordial, but violent and misaligned. Samuel j. Bicke (a sobreactuado but attractive Sean Penn) acquires sufficient despair as to find in the hijacking of an airplane and its subsequent landing at the White House the only way to overcome the anonymity, fear, pain and gain the respect that seeks his personality not to by more than, stubbornly, he strive.Payne, Di Caprio and Cuarón financed this product almost indie not lasting, mature, cold impostado documentalism. The assassination of Richard Nixon speaks of the American dream, of the promised land. The landscape is sick. What is relevant, what is the most notable success of this ochre film of good intentions and acceptable consequences is the description of a fading, affordable, marketable, society reduced to objects of consumption. Bicke is not the type without integrating De Niro mauve with its immortal Travis Bickle, but shares with him a similar mismatch: both are perfect amateurs, a teenage sentimentality, needy of affection and constantly skirting the pathos.The charisma voiceover of the omniscient protagonist clogging in excess: disarm the information capacity of a sober pictures, filmed with asepsis and inspired by tapes as the aforementioned Taxi driver or all those so counter-cultural seventy realistic material. Nor the secondary material is exploited: some very briefly profiled characters, Elmer Bernstein as recipient of the daily spoken of the confessed psychopath and that Bicke reviews, with surprising depth the ups and downs of a country wounded in Viet Nam and disenchanted at home, épicamente installed in a land of promise but devoid of references heroic. Bicke, in this sense, reluctantly, is not a pioneer, one of those thrown the founding western jeans, when the side of a river, a grass or a vein of gold were growing cities. America, in the late 20th century, cela morons as Bicke: seems that you take care of them, you train them to burst the system with infamous acts or impossible to domestic terrorism. Only be reviewed the sentimental doctrinaire of weapons of fire and snipers with University card rogue geography. Thoughts spoken aloud are determined to interfere with a simple, dull plot in excess, but effective in their skilful demonstration of cancer crosses, as bitter patina, the footage, everything what counts.The Sung true, decomposes the coldness with which we contemplate, but sets stricter their sustainability, not the film, which is flat, bit so ambitious and sadly missed. We will not know what would have happened to this project in a world without the 11-S. Because, ultimately, what are are the reasons for the Wolf, the arguments of the killer Wolf that he wanted to spoil the State of the welfare of the herd</body>
</review>
