<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Shootem up" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A spectacle of action in the total service of Clive Owen where the script and others is absent, but that time and peak of footage that lasts goes flying and noses, can be enjoyed from beginning to end.</summary>
	<body>One of those weird movies of action that one can contemplate without having to think too much, and is, no mistake, "Shoot'em Up" is nothing more than a well built and quite well shot (and achieved) entertainment serving the masses, one of those shows that you will like the chavalería and where one of principle to end the only thing you see is Clive Owen doing the cafre (in a sort of like character which already played) (in "Sin City"), the always great Monica Bellucci, everytime he spoke Italian with her sensual voice interspersed something in my interior and my exterior enjoyed as the dwarf that makes them company during the footage and a Paul Giamatti total off-road, given the same do Santo (in "The girl in the water" for example your character hovered Holiness) and here is the villainsomething tontorrón on duty.Note the construction of characters, extremely sharp, where the bad guys are very bad and the good. !VERY CAFRE! Since then, and trying to change the third, the tape makes no sense in much of the lances of the same, but who is going to ask you sense something of these features? Besides, bothers me especially that extrañaa prevailing fashion why loud music (starts the tape with a theme of Offspring) action tapes, it is true, as I have already said, is for enjoyment of the chavalería, but! tired! (to noses) and is that already, at certain ages, one does not have the ears (and the ears, which are about outside) to withstand both burned-strident burned to but not power.Anyway, I am not going to extend much more a show of acciónn in the total service of Clive Owen where the script and others is absent, but that time and peak of footage that lasts goes flying and that nose, can be enjoyed from beginning to end.</body>
</review>
