<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Días de cine" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Really good, delicious and very chilly strawberries with milk and sugar that I went to to see if it away me the bitterness of a comedy becomes tragedy and destroys the Viewer. Laugh, cry, drama comedy not unimportant.</summary>
	<body>I remember some time ago a news that came out not be where people who sought to make the poster for this film. How to put an ad "Wanted Designer without charging a penny to a film poster" it seems not encouraged to staff, they decided to give him another touch. "Contest of sketches for the film days poster." "The awarded will be to make the poster of film days". Which does not run here flies. I'm going to do a contest "Contest of licking the penis to the Titus." "The winner may make him complete fellatio" if something falls (a host of my girl as read the blog).The film is about a theater director who wants to make the leap to movies with a political script in the Spanish transition. On the other hand a producer who knows what he wants to the Viewer (as they knew it Ozores) wants a musical with a girl a year above prodigy and naked unnecessary. On the other hand, the star wants to a role that catapulte you back to fame. And on the other hand we are somewhat stunned spectators.The beginning of the movie is fine, with moments in which you ries and don't understand how so many people has branded patatero roll and the Spanish film in low hours. Then advances the film, ending the gracietas and a pain in the ass drama begins but not power, with situations sad (as seen Fernando Tejero do as he cries, the saddest thing that can be seen in the film). The idea of making a film about the filming of a movie is not new. But this in particular is supertriste over not being able to. I mean, a few years ago, the Great Khan released a comic book Super López called the great blockbuster. Coincidentally was the filming of a movie that unfolded in a mine, that everything was a disaster, a girl wanted to be despelotar and ending with all the films congratulating the director (Super López) for his great work. By chance, do not think so (Iker Jiménez dixit).In short, great, delicious and very chilly strawberries with milk and sugar that I went to to see if it away me the bitterness of a comedy becomes tragedy and destroys the Viewer. Laugh, cry, drama comedy not unimportant.This type of comedy is that I can not stand her.Besitos.P.D: why they run to the end of the film? That thing more silly, really.</body>
</review>
