<review author="Calaf" title="Superman returns" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>By romanticism, so rhythmic pause (and feature) and a vulnerable Superman, not you like a lot of people, even though it was not my case.</summary>
	<body>Tonight I've seen return to the screens of the classic among the classics. And I can say emphatically that I liked, I enjoyed and that this continued (which not version) is higher than the first for many reasons that I am telling you if you want to.The synopsis I do not because it is better to leave to bring, and to discover the chicha of history, which is not to be much. The prism of my childhood distorted for good memories of the Superman of the 1980s. It was enough to see her major to check as film was pretty bad, but saw a revolution in its time.Superman Returns has to go from below by being a sequel, and not original, a film saturated films of comics, Workbench to only the special effects. Moreover, the only thing that usually me draw the attention of them is how superheroes gain the powers, and in this there is no such a possibility. Even so, from the very beginning there are details that Bryan Singer (director of Habituales suspects and the 2 former X-men, as well as House producer) is with respect to the public, telling things with simple gestures (the dog in the bed of the ricachona or the mysterious silence of the child). We would appreciate that not you give everything mascadito it. It has fair action scenes (that of the aircraft, spectacular). The weight it are the characters with some very successful additions, such as the child or the secondary girlfriend the wrong. And I liked Brandon Routh as Superman, although Christopher Reeve left an indelible mark. Which Yes that improvement is it, Kate Bosworth (hated the character of the original) in a risky role, the triangle Centre. The two look very handsome. I don't like however the partner of her, a pringao, however much you want to. Kevin Spacey as Lex Luthor meets.Not everything are successes. The rescue of Superman sequences are not good (with so much misfortune, saves money in a Bank, and elsewhere, except the aircraft, have not been very creative). I have read that it lacks sense of humor, but I prefer when they tend to spoil rather than contribute.There will be some that you do a little slow and long, and the end to leave open the continuations, I do not like, but get moments of emotion (such as the romantic flight) with a beautiful aesthetic.The express messianic touch with religious analogies of Superman as Savior and positions reminiscent of Jesus Christ is debatable. By romanticism, so rhythmic pause (and feature) and a vulnerable Superman, not you like a lot of people, even though it was not my case.</body>
</review>
