<review author="Caty" title="Dos hermanas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Are narrated in a very leisurely way, one could say that?Two sisters? It is a film that like and dislike in equal parts, taking equal true genius that unexplained slippages in the script details and that they could be resolved easily.</summary>
	<body>Directed by the acclaimed Kim Jee-Won. Based on a known Korean folktale (Janghwa and Hongryeon, pink and Red Lotus, carried the big screen numerous times), it tells the story of the stormy relationship between two sisters very United and his stepmother, with the figure of a father absent, lost, dolido.por behind the interpretation of what constitutes the central triangle of the plot, the two sisters and stepmother. The sisters Su-Mi (Im-Soo Yung) and Su-Yeon (Moon Geun Young) arrive at the family home after a long convalescence in hospital. In the House are with his father, a taciturn man concerned, and their stepmother Eun-Joo, a woman constantly changing nature, and which seems to save a species of hatred and resentment towards the two sisters. Su-Yeon is the suffering, above all, the consequences of the fire of wrath of Eun-Joo, to be more weak due to a traumatic event he witnessed when his mother committed suicide in front of her. Su-Mi (which is the most strong and which always protects her sister) takes charge of the situation, tired of hold man by the stepmother in order to satisfy his father. The atmosphere thins in the House, in which begin to happen strange events, and where the tension is palpable every time with more fuerza.en that time, the stepmother begins to act with unusual violence, especially against the usual focus of their attacks, Su - Yeon. at that time, there is no turning back, and Su-Mi are available to find out what really happens at home.Narrated in a very leisurely way, one could say that "Two sisters" is a film that like and dislike in equal parts, taking details of true genius that unexplained slippages in the script and that they could be resolved easily. Although the film has a picture, a few effects of camera and an exquisite atmosphere, suffers from lack of consistency in many of its parts, especially at the end. Director Kim Jee-Won, in its efforts to "loop the loop", get the main plot are subdivide into sub-plots are not going to stop anywhere, and making that many viewers take face of astonishment, to the only have sensed vaguely that history will. Very dramatic "scares", and with the corresponding "Fireworks plot final" (very devalued due to the continuous ups and downs of the script), and with three actresses really excellent in their roles and credible extremely (in my opinion, the best of the movie mode) .but I repeat, all these artistic elements are relegated to second place when we can't really distinguish the true story and giving us is thatWhat could have been a 10 film simply becomes one entertainment.</body>
</review>
