<review author="José A. Peig" title="El Espejo (Zerkalo)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>As a work of art is indisputable. Although it is possible that the poetics of Tarkovsky not is the most adequate to express a Mystic of the image, at least has tried an approach to the phenomenon.</summary>
	<body>Tarkovsky introduces an enlightening prologue, in which we are witnessing the amazing healing by hypnosis, a stammering boy. Often, the viewer of this film has been somewhat baffled by the abruptly and the lack of relationship with the rest of the story that, apparently, characterize such a sequence. Although nothing further from the truth, that little that we ask minimally by the meaning of this passage, we will discover without difficulty some what healing by hypnosis shown in him we want to indicate is, above all, the willingness to speak clearly, openly of any kind, the director and its main character. Recovery, indeed, «smooth speech» by the aforementioned boy represents the final confirmation of Tarkovsky that is willing to reveal his interiority, to encourage; In short, to exorcise those ghosts, memories and other concerns that have been growing in it for many years. (Excerpt from the study prepared by Pedro A..) Cross Sánchez) the eccentric Russian filmmaker Andrei Tarkovsky obliges us to reflection on the film in relation to human consciousness and the facet of the artist of a model author film images, and certainly questionable, despite the artistic bravery and courage that Tarkovsky created a Visual compositions more disruptive and disconcerting in the history of the seventh art. We are open to all kinds of interpretations and evaluations on the film that we are now discussing, from qualified artificial Wanderer and pretentious to say it is the top of the film understood as the transcendental art (the most momentous of all) for which ones allow us to represent life or, according to the own Tarkovsky in images and words, the only art that we can "sculpting in time". The mirror not tells a story, is intended to be a reflection of a State of being that it flows over time. The State, therefore, contains many States of the spirit according to the images subject to the intuition of the author. The traditional narrative logic imposes linear time structure and actions with the aim of offering a coherent and understandable product in its entirety. When Tarkovsky linking images and seemingly disjointed sequences, what you are doing is forcing the Viewer to be at another level of understanding, more risky yet, in another State of being different to that required in a conventional narrative, (with which we have that is the own spectator who must should) "become" the work envisaged. Because of this, the film has no significance any more than within an intimate, transcendent, hidden to the vast majority of the public, that this is not a product, is, in itself, a State of consciousness. Man is alone and isolated in that each of us are part of a unique phenomenon and a unique way of perceiving the world and ourselves. Art emerges as a need to break the isolation which contains the uniqueness of the individual and makes it can not leave itself, such as fear and insecurity represented in the stuttering boy. The art, therefore, is the Act of communication by which we build a bridge between the self (the filmmaker) and others (spectators), we universalizamos and share a piece of intimate truth by the mere joy of doing so, because it involves transcending the State of loneliness. Tarkovsky wants his film to be a reflection of himself, a mirror in which to recognize and in which the public can understand him. A communicative miracle that cannot be realized through the conventional channels of communication. For this reason, we insist, there is art, which can be defined as the voice of the universal transmitted through creativity codes that allow "translate" - through the sign and symbol - idiosyncratic phenomena to a representation that invoke the essence common to all human beings, which requires an immediate and emotional apprehension. The problem is that Tarkovsky is one Mystic rather than a filmmaker, and is possible that the language of cinema beyond limits of which cannot represent it with adequate accuracy all the strength and accuracy of a mystical vision. In that case, the only way out is to renew and reinvent the language of cinema, and a discussion on which there still is no response in the various theories of aesthetics and the semiology of the film would be opened at this point. Therefore, to continue the debate, until then the critic only film touches him optimize the understanding of the work. According to Tarkovsky, the reality of life is too complex and cannot be a faithful representation (vivid imagery) if we use narrative and conventional codes. Life is perceived from la mirada, passing by the emotion and reaching the spirit, where charged full meaning. The meaning of a film meets more intuitive construction that a concept prefixed with treachery. Tarkovsky doesn't want to display images to convey a concept, wants the Viewer to live in images that become part of the meaning and the creation. We set ourselves the following question: being true that the ambiguity and polysemy of all the framework of sequences evokes a mystery, something as indefinable, inexpressible, sometimes specifically, in other elusive, as life in time and memory, are really the human phenomenon of life only can be represented in all its truth and glory through the poetic suggested by Tarkovsky?. If buceáramos in the history of the classic film akin to conventional narrative schemes, we would be a handful of works that manage to represent a piece of truth with clarity and strength required from a purely artisanal work (Murneau, John Ford, John Huston, Elia Kazan, etc, etc). But of course, it is a problem of intentions and radically opposing conceptions. Classical narrative, daughter of Homer, formulated a scheme of life in its most worthy parts and better define the essential human attributes. The expression of Tarkovsky is the Mystic of the ineffable, puts the humán in time making humán and time the same State of the universe represented. With this, we come to conclude that the author inevitably condemned his work to stay within a "elitist", without involving a serious says to his art to his effort to try to make universally unproblematically what is non-transferable part of his being. And idealists always deserve recognition and applause. In any case, the film material consists of a thread very clear, as it is the figure of the mother in his conversations with the spouse, which gives rise to an interesting dialectic on the identity and the conflict involving the family. The mother is the epicenter of the flow of memories and the leitmotif of departure and arrival. For that that "the image that opens the story and the image that closes define the meaning of the creation", ultimately, find a feature that makes it more conventional. And also, it makes it better. Read another extract from the text of Pedro a. Cruz Sánchez, which explains it very well and offers an interesting interpretation: arrived at this point, and with the maximum important certainty that "the present is only a projection of the past sunset manifesto by memory", is forced to ask: does this - memory - is a comforting earner of happiness or?do, on the contrary, its exercise is achieved only suffering, pain? Question, although somewhat some mode of this primordial question deserves an answer developed due carefully, that, indeed, Alexei, memory and the search for itself that it allows you to search anxiously happiness. In fact, in the foreground of the film, after the ubiquitous prologue of the Stammerer, a camera movement brings us the figure of the mother - sitting on a fence while waiting for her husband--for once to its height, continue his career forward and die in a full picture of the nature. Or what saying that, with this care and master level, Tarkovsky has tried to leave clara, already from the outset, the «madre-naturaleza» identification, based on the correspondence of its main attributes; in other words, «juventud-eternidad». Through them we are offered a contemplation of life as 'event without end', typical of a period as children, in which the consciousness of death isn't being born still and, therefore, each element in the world is apprehended as enduring and full. The mother, consequently, and within the iconography of the mirror has to be inferred as the representative of this world of children, conceived as a stage of life characterized by the idea of the eternal and the happiness. Now however, this joyful youth that the mother, this interpretation of life as an incorruptible and perennial value, makes gala cannot last, unfortunately, forever. And the proof we have in a scene which took place at the end of the film in which we see how a warm and sensual movement of camera travels the luminous home of the grandparents of the protagonist, to finish in a window that you can watch the now elderly mother with her two small children. It can be seen, therefore, the matching of two moments spaced over the course of the narrative, that while the first anyone - the madre-joven-in the window to wield the power of the gaze, in the second, which previously acted as "vital and eternal subject", it has now become «decrepit and deadly object». And - it seems say Tarkovsky - who looks and comprises remains young, but who loses this power and happens to be seen, just die. Finally, given that the mirror is a film that breaks with the usual schemes, there is no sense qualify on the basis of theoretical formulations on what a movie should or should not be, what have left you, what is missing, etc. As a work of art is indisputable for the reasons outlined above. Although it is possible that the poetics of Tarkovsky is not the most appropriate to express a Mystic of the image (that is something that only can be verified or refuted by the evolution and the history of the cinema), has at least tried an approach to the phenomenon, and this is confirmed by the witness to millions of viewers who have seen the movie and have felt the time of remembrance. </body>
</review>
