<review author="Alex Largo" title="Furia de Titanes" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ray Harryhausen hoeing to "impregnate" magic to this film, something which, if they had carried out the computers would not even half of charm.</summary>
	<body>"Clash of the Titans" is a classic. Could it be the (totally dispensable) work of the director? or with the actors? No and no. The answer is (if someone didn't) special effects, work and grace of Ray Harryhausen, hoeing that them to "impregnate" magic to this film, something which, if they had carried out the computers would not even half of charm.Let us start from the beginning (where if not?).Director (Desmond Davis) work &hellip; bad. Making the moments in which the hand of Harryhausen does not appear the movie Miss bellows in an incredible way. Thank God, the special effects are present on the tape, making the "damage" caused by the director to pass unnoticed.In the script, is more than obvious that he has written that Harryhausen look (and in what way, everything is said), making the (practically only) strong point of the movie special effects. Another matter are the actors.Harry Hamlin, in his role as Perseus is, frankly, to bring him to a concentration camp. And it is that man is bland and deadpan as a Boulder. A disaster, more if we have is the protagonist.The only that dazzle with their own light are brilliant in their roles of gods and Burgess Meredith, perfect in his role as old Guide Maggie Smith and Laurence Olivier.The rest of the cast is pretty good, although not especially noted none. In fact, all seem to be very good next to Harry Hamlin.Los special effects, as I have been saying from the beginning, they are impressive. Attention to the magnificent Pegasus, Medusa, kraken (perhaps the single most "without grace"), the Raven/Turkey giant, the Harpies &hellip; the magnificent work of Ray Harryhausen will be certainly remembered for this film and for many others. But this, no doubt, assumed the showcasing of the filmmaker to levels &hellip; Titanic.</body>
</review>
