<review author="Bruji" title="Salvador" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do with the already classic? bed comedietas? directed by them and performed by them, for the sole purpose of justify and receive State subsidies and with the clear intention of insulting lovers - it is possible that, from time to time, to do a good movie; and this is it.</summary>
	<body>Few, few years ago, in this country, "the good people" had authority to decide on the life and death of human beings. In this way, killing with impunity was unfeasible. In the same country, current date, it no doubt to judge other dictatorships. Nor be fret to review the proceedings of their own. Surrounded by controversy, the story told by Mediapro is more than a film, a historical document.Sometimes I think that there are two different versions of the film Salvador. One would be that the Spanish Academy has shortlisted to compete at the international level, the same was long Ovation and was thrilled in the Claude Debussy Theatre, which enjoyed a good reception from the press authorized in this Festival. But there would be a different one, which, according to some, enters Cannes through the back door in the section "A certain look", which unknown character that portrays, and that distorts the historical epoch in which fits. I can't remember another film that has so radically opposing reviews. It must be because I am not the only one who has a tendency to judge films from their arguments. On this occasion, it is just analyze history from various angles. In principle, it is encouraging to know that there are people that strives to make cinema in the national panorama. From the classic "comedietas of bed" - directed by them and performed by them, for the sole purpose of justify and receive State subsidies and with the clear intention of insulting the moviegoers - it is possible that, from time to time, be made a good movie; and this is it. On the other hand, I have always believed that cinema Spanish has an outstanding debt with the historical genre. Only there to look at the glorious American Studies who have told in a thousand different ways the little story that have, or have been invented. In that sense, this film could open a way in which are beginning to pay off these debts, not with facts or characters of the past, but with ourselves. People of my generation, for example, knows who is Hurricane Carter thanks to American cinema, but we never hear of Salvador. From the strictly cinematic point of view, the production of Jaume Roures has important successes. I would like to emphasize its unbeatable action scenes, the impeccable narrative structure that accompanies the tape, the direction of actors, the scrupulous staged, its poignant dramatic load or intelligent dialogues. Let us remember the long flashback, accompanied by the sweet voice of hispano-alemán Daniel Brühl, who answers the question asked a prison officer: "You who you're intelligent, prepared, good person in the background, how you've got this?". We should also remember the fantasy guided the Salvador before his little sister with respect to air travel, the view that has the protagonist of its parent and the terms in which is addressed to him, or the essential conversations in Catalan, a language "which leaves us without wanting to". There are many frames that are unforgettable for its aesthetic beauty, without forgetting those other levels dealing with contrasting the serenity of who wrote "I wish blood not shed needlessly", with the professionalism of the executioners. Another important fact is to know the end, is not without prejudice so that the director knows to keep the soul of the viewer in the air.We, therefore, have decisive factors that make this a footage not only able to compete with the best, but win. Indeed it is, such as defined by the producer, a universal film. At the plot level, it is true that this film is characterized by certain "political asepsis" which reproaches him for, but this is also a success, a trend which is used deliberately to show the human side of the character. However, not deepen in the ideals of the M.I.L. - so romantic as sleepless-, or not go into detail on the various ways of opposition to the Franco regime, are not sufficient grounds to state categorically that "neither is known to the character nor the time". We bear in mind that all those responsible for this film, since the director until the creator of soundtrack, passing by the writer of the novel Compte enrere on which is based the script, are people living in the Spain of 1974, arriving to become obsessed by the figure of Salvador, which it dealt with in all its dimensions and that show a story that is taken care of to the most insignificant detail. I can think of C.N.T.E abbreviations that appear on old phones. The essence of this film is summed up in the phrase that has been marketed: "In a time that was eager to freedom, he dared to live without fear". This is a key message that manages to reach the public in a clear way and without distortions. Lose in other directions would have not led to any place. The director says that "this film is due to the latest generation who fought for ideals". Let me add that this story also due to the following generations, who we first met Salvador thanks to a trailer, which maintain intact the innate spirit of struggle against injustice. Without forgetting that, above all, Manuel Huerga tape becomes a history lesson for teenagers in this country. Perhaps, those facts, help them understand the letter of the modern melody - cara Al sol - of your mp3.Remember and, in this case, know, is the best way that history will never repeat.</body>
</review>
