<review author="Bruji" title="Juegos secretos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Overrated film of the highly regarded Todd Field. Invention of American critics, who, perhaps, desperate for a Stephen Frears English or a Pedro Almodóvar Spanish to ensure its own identity in the last years.</summary>
	<body>Movie made from an exhausted argument, outdated material hosted a narrative technique as expendable as unnecessary, irregular and sticky rhythm that, after two endless hours, holds the dubious redemption of its protagonists. Especially recommended for the more conservative readers of the NY Times.En film of recent years, "Amélie experiment" worked, so far, on one occasion, in Amélie. The presence of a narrator who provides its services to the length and width of the tape, only makes sense if its intervention contributes to the introduction of images that explains and supplements. If it is not, if this is not your work, your contributions are redundant, annoying and, in not few moments, incitadoras of the tedium.There lies the difference between making a determined approach by necessity or whim. And this freak, remaining brilliance for long courtship Sunday of the same director, leads to the failure of script in the recent adaptation of the Perfume, and constitutes the main error of the film that we discussed today.In this case, recourse to an inadequate structure, it relies on a tireless voice in off anything brings to the story of the screen, not only eternalizes the narrative rhythm and despair to the lovers of the characters well built, they get to be ridiculous in unnecessary descriptions. Remember the "presentation" of Jennifer Connelly, to which we have been seeing more than one hour in the movie or scene that occurs under the table.Caprice - and not the necessity-of avail themselves of this technique, is also responsible for that surfaces the abysmal gap between the dialogues - terribly mediocre - and exquisite phrases that make up the auxiliary narration, i.e. between the script of the film and the novel which item. Only suggesting that we we have an acceptable writer, Tom Perrotta, and a very bad adaptation. Nominated adaptation, however, great prizes, which also has - like almost everything in life - an explanation that I do not understand.Despite starting from a wrong premise, develop a cinematically exhausted argument, escape for a decent movie subplot, and indulge in unrealistic situations, the film reaches the resurrection when he tends to humor, sometimes, black British comedies, when it recreates the own funerary S.A. or the calendar girls scenes, as it happens in the Book Club gatherings or snacks in the Park.Yet again to lose the pulse wanting to convert to a woman of the 21st century in the protagonist of a soap opera Victorian of the sleepy James Ivory, to cross on the path of the American 1960s comedies and use the method of the game and shared screen (confidences to midnight), to show a timid attempt in the destructuring of the script at the time in which "the hermetic personita that crazy Kate" It is still found within it.And dies, inevitably, in the countless and endless scenes that transmit - and contagious - boredom and monotony of empty lives to the Viewer.Many of these aspects is could have been avoided. If you take a quick look at the history of the cinema, we discovered (the Filmography of Stanley Kubrick corroborated) alteration of the order sequence only should be applied at the request of the own history (it is not the case) and when it justifies it. Ashes of love found in 1941, in which to King Vidor him enough three flat to show the routine, the boredom and the existential crisis of the protagonist, (would have spared us the amuermantes pool sessions). And we came to the conclusion that the improvisation that characterizes the tapes of Robert Altman ensemble cast is not credible in other filmmakers. Ultimately, when the movie buff sense hopes remote attend a final Paul Haggis which cushions the unpleasant feeling of having lost time, we find ourselves with an inconclusive ending, open to multiple interpretations, does not exempt an attractive unable to save a condemned from the nineteen minute film that leaves an uncertain message. A message that offers much fabric cut, but that, out of respect to the reader, I take to the tomb of thought. What I would recommend, in this same line of social criticism (little criticizes games secrets), a production USA-UK in 2001, directed by Rose Troche, released in Spain in November 2003 with the title of the security of the objects. Theme similar, less pretentious and more accurate hereby guarantees an impeccable development and a magnificent interpretation of Glenn Close as icing on its extensive cast. . And this is the story of an excellent photography and an appealing art direction, obsessed by watches, working on Little Children, which failed miserably at the box office. A reality that contrasts with the overrated film of the highly regarded Todd Field that we have sold American critics, who, perhaps, desperate for a Stephen Frears English or a Pedro Almodóvar Spanish to ensure its own identity... who knows?. Knowing it or not, I have the conviction that the Lady of Sam Mendes is one of the best actresses of all time, that high school is wicked "pretty, pretty, of long legs", that the life of Emma Bovary does not cause a catharsis in his twenties as they did twenty years later, and that day come when thatPerhaps, discover some interesting mystery in this footage. For the moment, this - and not other - is my humble opinion.</body>
</review>
