<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Los burdeles de Paprika" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sincere praise of meat, lit portrait of prostitution under the ironic and humorous prism of a director vocationally equipped to eroticism.</summary>
	<body>Tinto Brass, in a sense, is an old green with a camera: one of the type that changes the annals of Tacitus or the complete works of Giacomo Leopardi by a saccharine Playboy issue, although perhaps the magazine Queen of the Guild is not his ideal erotic. The pattern that governs their indisimulado Vice is the bombastic woman of meats, morbid, reasonably female, but without falling into excesses, stereotypes designed by fashion. This voyeur you passionate about the sunlight seeping through the blinds, the bidets, the big ass under a narrow waist and depilatory laziness among a groin and another. All his films - and brothels of Paprika are a perfect example - scales between realism kitsch and tacky that it here outboard Bigas Luna cafre and hyperbolic realism of Russ Meyer. The aesthetic concerns of this gourmet of the lúbrico go a miss without underwear walking bike against a group of candorosas nuns to the most genuine portrait of brothels, absolute temples from sin which tends his rampante spirit. Tinto Brass voyeur and filmmaker was first law degree and up was an Assistant Director of a heavy weight (do not look double meaning) of the world Cinematography: Robert Rossellini. None of these lines in your resume betrayed the director that was to come, the man that looks as it is also called one of his many films, the passionate eye that captures the light, their size, their most burning volutes to illuminate the female body, which is always an absolute devotion.Except Caligula, torrid pornographic aspirations and, in my view, falsely historical and unusually excessive exercise of Tinto Brass film is generous with the Viewer. It seems as if he just wanted the chiquillada of making the film that he himself would love to see. I.e., a delighted its own type. And somehow, he meets his intimate Word. The deliberate abandonment of glamour, the provincial Canticle of the romps in the NAPs, the colorful parade of bizarre characters, lunatics, cynical, savvy are recurrent in all its sweet work, paid to the controversy, to the scandal. Anything that dislike you in excess.The brothels of Paprika is not a good movie to the way in which it isn't gentleman without sword, the law of desire or breeds crows, for bringing the magnifying glass to the own field, but in these jewels of the seventh art there is no praise of meat and that, like it or not, is part of the discourse of serious cinema or frivolous pajilleros propsprompting Brass term. The Ascension of the accidental slutty Paprika to the throne of the Italian brothels (just as they are more seriously threatened by the Government) and the ups and downs of this libidinosa crusade is the fundamental issue of the tape. The same breath that arrima tape to the Olympus of the erotic film (chabacano erotic or erotic scurfy, if prefer you the gentle reader) is that the departure of aspiring to one higher quality, but Brass narrates with sobriety and advances without prejudice by the plot, deploying his recognizable eccentricities (these bidets, those close-ups of always bristles sex of their females)(, this breast wealth of the protagonist over-farmed) and offering, as colorful soundtrack, moans of pleasure escorted by songs happy talk of happy Gelee. It is impossible to not feel stunned by the cast of women of hasty nudity and tongue. The movie buff also joins, could say Berlanga to dignify the genre. What happens is that the abuse in definite stuns: that happens. The carnal desparpajo can be considered at its absolute, even counterproductive end for an erotic film who knows at all times that public to which it is addressed. If we see a porn tape, we understand that the film does not exist, so there are mechanisms of industrial production in place make cakes of Alcázar or Albacete knives dedicated filming of some dedicated athletes of the fornication sweats. We know to what we come from and Tinto Brass, in this exclusive mercantilist aspect, not disappointed. Nor misleading. No I have the Italian Director as capital piece of my you aversions cinematic nor am I Berlanga in my remarks, but I distinguish personal traits that give preference to his film against the infamous barque of Brats with budget and high definition cameras that are released to record episodes of eroticism light, unbearable and bigoted for chains like Playboy or the always hungry corner of rated DVD.There is no pornography in the brothels of Paprika: everything is supercharged hormones, everything is lean and trophism demonstration of a pair of great tits formidable weight. Beyond, nothing, the fields of strawberries forever John Lennon, walks on the shore of a river in autumn, verses of Neruda and york with Flash cure cheese ham sandwiches. Madness. I have no doubt of the cause.</body>
</review>
