<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Sin reservas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This romantic comedy-drama is a cocktail very well mixed in the sense that combines several genres of right way and is able to keep the pace (almost) anytime.</summary>
	<body>I did not see delicious Martha, the acclaimed German film Director Sandra Nettelbeck. Moreover, he had never heard of this film until that Hicks decided to make its American remake. He painted as a dish without salt, an americanada to all rule without a shred of originality. But the truth is that the director of Shine, has made unreservedly an appetizing dish with a more aromatic than that acid taste. Its chef, a correct Catherine Zeta-Jones, presents, in the beginning, the film as a melodrama with culinary dyes. And it is the beginning of the film is its best and tasty dish, a starter made with grace and enough originality. Then, after the introduction of the small Abigail Breslin (unforgettable in little Miss Sunshine), the film becomes a family drama that later, the spectator (rather the spectator) sits attracted / by Aaron Eckhart, in her first scene (only), little right. Maybe the tape is, without a doubt, the talent of the young Breslin, without too many efforts you eat (never better said) to the two protagonists, and not so young, they make that his work is a seemingly senzillo effort to pretend to be more dramatic than usual, more credible (Zeta in particular, the Miss Jones). No, aren't bad, but the girl debora as the delicious spaghetti zampa in a scene. A story at times comic, dramatic moments, other unconvincing and, in general, very correct. Does not exceed, but it won't either below mediocrity; It simply is what it purports to be, virtually no manipulative emotionally. This is appreciated, as well as the brilliant score of an already formidable Philip Glass (touching the main theme), an accompaniment of five stars. Although this unqualified has one weak point, and I think that considerably large: the two sides of the story (the girl and the romantic) do not know merged correctly, because when the writer deviates to one, the other forget about (usually of Breslin leave more secluded and forgotten it). And then when you do not know if what he wants to tell you exactly is a love story between two chefs or responsibility for a woman, until now alone, perfectionist and cold, before the appearance of his niece who has just run out of mother. But above all, this romantic comedy-drama is a cocktail very well mixed in the sense that combines several genres of right way and is able to keep the pace (almost) anytime. And finally, a plate (plane, forgiveness) end of a delicacy rarely seen.</body>
</review>
