<review author="José A. Peig" title="La extraña que hay en tí" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film, ultimately, brilliant, great interpretation of Jodie Foster, fluent and well-structured narrative and a marvelous staging.</summary>
	<body>A broadcaster of radio express using the word the reality of social change by putting your eyes lyrical in the city that loves, agonizes over the change inevitable, its vital structure and how people's lives evolve or involucionan, the nostalgia of a memory, it was before and now blurs in a mind foggy as the distorted images that occur on a par with the creditsan urban landscape seen as a mirage of the reality that seems to suggest that the world is going to give a qualitative leap towards insecurity, fear, let flow the violent instincts and, therefore, doubt the principles of law and reason.Erica Bain (Jodie Foster) normally lives a simple life until the violence imposed by the change of perspective and a new understanding of itself. Life is not simple and the fabric of ideological principles that subject and sustain the belief system collapses. The pulse not trembles when you've lived violence de facto. From another place, Sean Mercer police represents the principle of reason and subordination to the dogma of the law, but from the prism of who sees violence as a set of forensic data subsequent to the Act of violence. She is witness to the reality of injustice and he takes refuge in the belief and the formalisms. A policeman kills, but can not grasp the bitterness caused by the set of visceral and psychological phenomena in an act perpetrated from a wild executioner to an innocent victim.Thus, the structure of the narrative part two characters who gradually walk towards a reversal of values that, until then, they had believed, describes the friendship that emerges between the two with dialogues that expose counterpoints on crime, law and the subtle line between the duty of the need, Justice legislative of self-righteousness. The complicity that arises between the two characters as one is aware of the role played by the other, and the dilemma that faces the police is particularly successful.But clear, we not only live in post 11-S society, but in society the image recorded on devices within the reach of anyone. Before the revenge, images of injustice, which hitherto only had meaning in the memory of Erica, moving to the mobile phone are, and that is the crux of the issue. are we to a speech that justifies the crime regardless of the law somehow?. At all. Erica is a dam soul of fear, in its infancy violence is not a revenge as a visceral reaction to potential aggressors. Then, when you feel the support of some citizens who support the figure of a vigilante, mata on behalf of Justice and, therefore, their actions are the result of revenge, abstraction that goes beyond the visceral reaction. The film, therefore narrates and displays the grounds while a psychological process, process which, set against the figure of the police, tells us brings to the table the eternal debate of always, nothing original, and since then have become best movies on the subject, much bolder and more raw than this. However, the truth is that it is an exhibition that encourages reflection on the basis of a history of changes and psychological processes, perhaps too simple reasons, but without proclamations or unilateral formulas based on what the global discourse refers. See what. A group of thugs records the fact of crime, an act that will turn against them when Erica, in an act of conscious of self-justification against the friend, farewell and send the recording to the mobile are in the camera of a mobile phone. This includes images of reality - a reality that goes beyond codes of ethics and forensic data-, then happens when a change in his conscience. The phrase, devastating, - "I've seen what you did" - reveals the hypocrisy which maintained the principles are ideological agent. It is the importance of the real image with the concept and prejudice ex post. In this modern era of use and abuse of all kinds of devices that allow registering reality, many acts which, in the past, could reduce dismissed trials of the real event, today can be experienced de facto. With the modification of conscience that this implies. This is the new substrate - adapting to changing times - used by filmmaker Neil Jordan to return to the question. However, deal with Jordan not exploits to the maximum the possibilities of a complex issue, and the treatment given to the last scene remains somewhat childish by predictable of the Act, while it is coherent by the above arguments. Film, ultimately, brilliant, great interpretation of Jodie Foster, fluent and well-structured narrative and a marvelous staging.</body>
</review>
