<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="The messengers" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>apparently the Pang brothers have decided to go for the easy way and emulate each and every one of the old tricks of Asian terror hoping to start an easy shock to the Western Viewer</summary>
	<body>Earlier this year The Messengers (2007) caught some attention being the entrance in the West of Danny and Oxide Pang, the twins hongkoneses that have risen to the chariot of the fashion of the Asian horror films as the (for me) ill-fated The Eye (2002) or the (new to me) much more interesting anomaly (2003). His arrival in Hollywood was marked by some hype to wonder more what they could do with such film machinery at its disposal. The result, however, is not the most desired; Although the film fails to be so disastrous to make your viewing torture, it is probably the largest cluster of common places of Eastern terror ever brought to the screen. Made almost as if they followed a formula at the foot of the letter, the English language and the American setting rural is the only thing that the direrencia of their counterparts from far Oriente.Parte of the error was coming from far behind. A pretty crappy advertising campaign, much highlighted the alleged thematic Center of The Messengers that children have the power to more easily contact the spirits who wander through the world of the living. This phenomenon is not the center of the film, which rather focuses on the experiences of a teenage girl who, after moving with his parents to a farm of sunflowers in the middle of North Dakota in search of a new life, begins to perceive the presence of a few ghosts in his new House, apart from making the impossible lifeThey seem to take it little by little to the resolution of a secret that comes from the past. If it sounds familiar, it is because this same plot has been reproduced endlessly virtually unchanged.Forms should be new, but apparently the Pang brothers have decided to go for the easy way and emulate each and every one of the old tricks of the Asian horror hoping to start an easy shock to the Western Viewer, mainly in what refers to the ghosts of white skin moving in staccato. The twins have even resorted to the auto-cita to include, at a certain point of the footage, a scene exactly equal to one that gave more fear in The Eye, without any change, and who had worked not having been used already five years earlier. Cheap scares nor help a lot, to tell the truth, and the final twist that takes the plot is coming to leagues.It is a pity that the start in Hollywood of these directors has resulted a film so vacuous and so expendable like this. Its zero originality and its plot half-hearted betray her as little more than the vehicle for showcasing for teenage actors, in this case Kristen Stewart, whom I always remember as the androgynous daughter of Jodie Foster in panic (2002) room. Any other consideration is incomprehensible. The Messengers is not a remake of any Eastern tape, but may well be.</body>
</review>
