<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Fido" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An original tape in its approach, which however just entering too many clichés.</summary>
	<body>They said in "South Park" that Canadians have something special, and since then, it cannot be otherwise that coincidentally in Canada have decided to make a very special comedy, while Edgar Wright has already done something similar with "Zombies Party" (Shaun of the dead) where the mythical duo Simon Pegg &amp; Nick Frost have become "world famous", this is another way of seeing things, and integrate the happy 50 years in the States with a tape on zombies is an original way of doing things.Highlights in the cast, Carrie Anne Moss, the mythical Trinity in the series "Matrix", as the mother of the boy protagonist, as well as the eccentric Billy Connolly, here unrecognizable as zombie, that gives title to the film (Fido), as well as one of the side of countless films, Dylan Baker, not to mention the appearance of one of the familiar faces in the Cohen Brothers film, I speak of Tim Blake Nelson, that here is a neighbor that has a curious (and sexy) Companion.It seems less curious, as Andrew Currie knows how to integrate into American Society of the 1950s a group of zombies, as pet and that a few minutes of footage can even pretend "normalcy", with a home that reminds the Romero films, or more specifically their 1st big success "The night of the living dead".In some lances the film comes to remind other tapes of the genre, such as "An amazing gang" or "Do not kill." "to the neighbour", as well as "pleasantville" and is much more ingrained component of this comedy (and little original) what one pending, and in some bars one has the feeling of what to show on screen, although original (therefore no doubt) has a "aftertaste" to "already seen".In short, a tape original in its approach, which however just entering too many clichés; by the way, I understand that its premiere in Spain occur only on the shelves of the video shops, go, which will go directly to DVD.</body>
</review>
