<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Líbero" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An opera prima close, concrete and intelligent, so is the debut in the direction of an actor that coexists with the need to tell stories that, since simplicity, trap even to the most elite Viewer.</summary>
	<body>When premiered a production of our neighbours, I do not know you, but I always think of all the other tapes that have fallen by the wayside, so to a certain extent is understandable to all the films of Italian invoice that we receive provide a remarkable level of quality.This mosaic of feelings rebuilt by a clever and endearing little in keeping with a new way of communicating that it is giving as a light counterattack to the cinema of mass consumption: actor Kim Rossi Stuart has clear ideas and has the precise mechanisms, as well as the necessary experience - tanning under the orders of others has served him-, to set up an account that articulates everyday elementsnarrated from the simplicity of approach and without the pretensions of many who believe they were born knowing.It is only necessary to flee the pretension and treat the Viewer as an equal, and not as a mere consumer to forget quickly, to enter the elite club to which already belong the brothers Ulloa, Sánchez-Arévalo and certainly veterans as Icíar Bollain, Manuel Poirier, Nanni Moretti and Gracia Querejeta – by reducing it to the Mediterranean area. Líbero is another example of how film-making on the basis of a concise idea not to miss in emotional subterfuges that cost out or reload footage with unnecessary embellishments.Here it is important the well that word at the right time, the hypnotic power of a look, the value of silence. The film avoids rapid tear, melancholy component usually sweetening unnecessarily. We would appreciate that the father of the creature does not have recourse to how easy and on the other hand to play with us putting us always on the cutting edge, on the edge of the precipice, with little evidence and challenges.Returning to our theory on what comes or not to trade screens, the problem is not that there little permeability in our face to the Italian film industry, but that the owners of the roost ever were interested in less a close, simple and well told story. Unfortunately and, with exceptions, it is something inherent to all cinemas of the old continent.</body>
</review>
