<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Disturbia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a kid who spies on his neighbors and in addition to discover solid which is the neighboring believes discover a murderer. Bread seeds and tostadito freshly brewed honey with a filling of lettuce without salt. The beginning and end, the rest roll.</summary>
	<body>Disturbia, disturbia, of what sounds like this movie? Course of Hitchcock's rear window, although the resemblance is just plot. Given that as said the master, can not make movies (or go, what is I?) or with animals or with children. That is why did not know that in a future late adolescents taken screens to tell us stories of jumping pheromones with binoculars.The film is about a boy who loses his father and past a year not has succeeded in overcoming it. For reasons that are beside the point, put an AB such that is the futuristic movies explode and kill the prisoner, but that in this case no more than tell the police. Given that his mother forbids him any fun (the non zambomba have no news), is engaged in spying on the neighbors, and discover things "distubiantes" (like rebuena which is nearby).This is like when you take an ice cream with hot chocolate above, or rather, as when you put it a few green beans with potatoes. That is, we have a mixture of rhythms that kill me. It begins explosive, then he sleeps to wake us up at the end with a good ending. But of course, you've eaten the hot chocolate, and the stock of ice cream that is already is not the same. For not to mention that apart from beans to only eat the potatoes. The intrigue is not bad, but we have that teenage roll did not finish like me (except that is despeloten, of course).In short, film about a kid who spies on neighbors and, in addition to discover solid which is the neighboring believes discover a murderer. Bread seeds and tostadito freshly brewed honey with a filling of lettuce without salt. The beginning and end, the rest roll.I was going to put it better, but the girl told me that it was a roll. I have less personality than a sweet potato.Besitos.P.D: I have more hunger dog of the Sharpener, who ate the Sparks to eat something hot.</body>
</review>
