<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La gran estafa" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The great scam is a film that makes true honor to its title, already that anyone who goes to see her will feel cheated</summary>
	<body>There are titles which deeply marked the evolution of the work which give name, either positively or negatively. In the film, the art of holder has subverted altogether, becoming one mere element of the marketing of the film. Many of these titles are misleading, designed with the sole purpose of attracting an audience different from which is intended for the film. And it is always the incomparable work of translation of the distributors. An example of a couple of years ago is to change eternal shine of an immaculate mind by forget of my!Despite everything, put a title as the great scam is dangerous, because it can generate scathing comments from the respectable, especially at the end of the projection. Lasse Hallström takes revived interest in the figure of magnate Howard Hughes to tell us the story of a man who misled the world at the expense of the eccentric millionaire. At first glance, one minor issue for a filmmaker who has made works as memorable as the rules of House of the cider or Atando Cabos. It is a pity to see how Hollywood fagocita a majority of directors who come to their doors, making them mere comparsas. Turning to the great scam, the film has a boot more than decent, interesting to the viewer with a good pace and good be Hallström. However, as this modern Rascal is immersing in his own lying, the tape is becoming increasingly heavy and slow. All this coupled with the fact of knowing the outcome from the outset (there is even a scene that telegraphy own final) the plot to lose interest. Richard Gere for his part is not very convincing, despite being a role tailor-made.The great scam is a film that makes true honor to its title, already that anyone who goes to see her will feel cheated. Worst of all is that the film follows the descending line of Hallström started with A life ahead and Casanova.</body>
</review>
