<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Ultravioleta" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lots of action, many dead, but leaves the feeling of existential vacuum before so much violence without coming to story. In other words, that a milestone kilo I've swallowed without eating or drinking.</summary>
	<body>According to legend in the inscriptions on the sword of the Miss Violet (ultra not be that comes) the formula to create gold, the secret of who killed Kenedy, as a simple waiter in Spain can happen in a few years to be one of the largest fortunes in the country and things are written. But no one who has come far enough to the edge has managed to remain a piece and then tell. They imagined what will the movie.The film is a future world in which a virús created by man to soldiers that kill more and better, has become a part of the society hemófagos (who eat blood). As often happens in these cases, a Union between military and doctors has resulted a dictatorship that handles very strictly the designs of humanity. For a change, those who want to exterminate been nail and engaged in slaughtering human. Do hodgepodge comes ultraviolet which kills throughout the film to not less than a thousand beings humanos.¿Que can say that not you supongais already? Let's start with the positive side. I liked much small details, like the mobile phones of the future, and generally of little things which we premiered when the virus that extends. The action of the principle is pretty well, although it finishes running, giving step by an absolute soplapollez, in which the cruel and ruthless killer gets out her feelings for a child. All this giving meneos sword to all who arrima. And finally it ends in a few sudden jumps between fast-paced action and the noñeces that do not come to mind. And the script no mata, no. Moreover, it is too predictable.In short, lots of action, many dead, but the feeling of existential vacuum before so much violence without coming to story that leaves you, has made my inner peace see cracked. Or in other words, that a milestone kilo I've swallowed without eating or drinking.</body>
</review>
