<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Mala noche" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Imperfect, as almost all Opera prima, Mala noche principiaba already the relevant issues in the aesthetic ideas of the author: marginality, the abyss, gays as tortured object of a world apart from the differences...</summary>
	<body>The paths of the cinematography of an author are inscrutable. Gus Van Sant, that director among the indie and the majors, this kind of poet of the suburban, able to excite My Idaho private or Elephant and let us stunned by the surprise with psychosis (2.0) type pestiños, has removed the trunk of memories and found bad night, his directorial debut, a visceral journey to the dark of human relations background, the story of a gay white man in love with a heterosexual and Mexican illegal immigrant, pure love fou, but firmly hold to swings scoundrels of the reality and lyrical. Cruise lovers morale allows the author investigate the roots of hatred and digging without prejudice and without emitting valuations in the grey and fragmented beauty of marginal beings. Passolini, in its own way, also made a similar film. In fact the way that Van Sant scrutinises male eroticism not incomodaría to the Italian master. Bad night has come here 22 years later, but even in the United States was released shortly after becoming: had to wait for Drugstore cowboy will carry the applause and the unanimous seal of quality of the critics. Gus Van Sant is an irregular, a type used to hocicar his talent in the margins and compose a captivating portrait of disenchantment with the harshness of human happiness, but his films do not speak of engolado love, set to the melody of a song. The music that suits this filmmaker is not sweet: your pulse is forbidding, his breath is poetic, i.e. devoid of meaning, Subscriber to ask questions and to do so with beauty. What is poetry, if not? Van Sant not predicts better worlds, although the end of this film joins the goodness of pure feelings.Etiquedado New Queer Cinema can that even not convenient: they are bonds, encorsetados artifacts of domestic manufacturing that domeñan the instinct and turns art into a bound object of consumption. In this sense, Van Sant is not a director of the gay, thus bounded the term, but an author aware due to the homosexual Guild (he isn't), but without going into artistic militancias as the displayed by Gregg Akari, Fassbinder, Pedro Almodóvar - in good part of his always open filmography - and Passolini, previously cited. What lacks bad night to be a recommended work, it is not an absolute mode, is a most tack script, a less experimental setup. It shows rookie pulse, warn the seams of a too new and checked suit with the haste of beginners. Taking office in the world of cinema adult, commercial, easily exploitable, Mala noche gives added value. You can't impostado minimalism of Elephant. You don't have the burden of cynicism and nasty Drugstore Cowboy. Nor is an apotheosis, uppercase and tough as Last days, the film about Kurt Cobain. Mala noche is incorrect film, but why like, somehow. For his invaluable smell to newly named intelligence.</body>
</review>
