<review author="Taliesin" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the jungle 4.0 we again see Willis in shirt and covered with blood, but does not transmit the sensation of can lose the game with bad turn, something that turns into a classic the first film in the series.</summary>
	<body>The 4.0 that have added you to the title of this fourth installment of the Crystal jungle (a very curious "translation" of Die Hard, by the way) says openly that this time the bad guys who will have to face el bueno de John McClane are most dangerous hackers. Or, worse still, most dangerous terrorist hackers. Scares, truth? Because the truth is that in the end are not, be a most dangerous terrorist hackers morons. And of course, if the bad guys are idiots, because we will have to put the batteries if we want to see Bruce Willis staining blood shirt. Thus have McClane against the bad guys in car, McClane against the bad guys in a helicopter and the classic (thanks to Cameron and their risky lies) against the bad guys in hunting McClane. Excess is such that the half an hour easy feel saturated of action and disconnect the ability to surprise, with what the movie passes through the screen without too convey to the Viewer. The first time that McClane tells her asshole to the super maloso is tronchante. The second, esbozas a half smile. From the third you start thinking that the bad is called second name asshole and why is mosquea or anything. That happens for choosing Timothy Olyphant for the role of villain of the piece, making it clear that the absolute protagonist is Willis and that neither his alter ego do you shade in the film.I already imagine the writers at the time in which thought that a fight to cakes in a car that hangs dangerously in an elevator shaft would be the bomb (although we have seen Jurassic Park. in the first two deliveries, in fact). The only problem is explained as demons just a car into an elevator shaft that is next to a gas station control room. At that time was called the writers of lost, which explained them that they simply don't explain anything and it works. And this has been the thing.Ultimately, this fourth installment of the saga is completely dispensable and there is very little that can be saved. If anything, it must be acknowledged that the question of the hackers not led wrong at all and though they do must be entirely impossible, it seems feasible and that if that scares a little. Moreover, the film is tedious, with little pace and excessive in all aspects. That it return me the money.</body>
</review>
