<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Chapter 27" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In Chapter 27 of rookie J.P. Schaefer, gaze focuses on the figure of a cursed character for every devotee of American culture for decades: Mark David Chapman, the murderer of John Lennon.</summary>
	<body>The North American cinema has the virtue of looking for reflection about the interstices surrounding his luminous style of life. And on numerous occasions so choosing his most undesirable characters, for through them purge social sins or simply stress that the basis on which it sits their culture has nothing to do with the golden dream of who has made himself. Freud said that we can only be healthy if we look at our diseases. And this maxim has been the tendency of the film made in USA since that this generation of Directors formed by Scorsese, Coppola or Malick focused his eyes on the basement of the American life, portraying the life of beings everyday but marked by violence or uprooting.In Chapter 27 of rookie J.P. Schaefer, gaze focuses on the figure of a cursed character for every devotee of American culture for decades: Mark David Chapman, the murderer of John Lennon. The mere idea of portraying the life of this cursed character has led to some fans of musician associations to try to boycott the film. The truth is that the very idea of trying to focus a film on an anti-icono of pop culture is in the hands of a true adept a pernicious and malevolent transgression that you need to attack. But in the hands of a skeptic of any fan-atismo (such as which subscribe to this article) this idea becomes a priori attractive and if I dare even necessary.But what at first seemed to be an attempt to subvert and thereby reflect on American (pop) culture and its perverse effects, to view Chapter 27 my illusions be dampened. Not even think the thriller aficionado with psychopath that here you will find elements to enjoy. And it is that despite its excellent technical and artistic invoice, Chapter 27 is a byproduct of aesthetic new age that chokes to penetrate without escape routes in the mind of an autistic Chapman which becomes pervasive across a monochrome voiceover. The Cadence and rhythm slow tape (with the constant presence of the rye rocking by the wind) little help find in it something more than a three-day trip through the streets of a (that Yes) beautiful Manhattan, or see how a discretita Lindsay Lohan gives us a decent piece of paper (but nothing more). Everything stays in spectral air, as inhabiting the ghosts of pena Chapman.Una, above all for the enthusiasm and dietary efforts of Mr Jared Leto (best film, everything is said), lost thirty pounds to interpret to Chapman and give it a life of its own. There seems to be a common trend in Hollywood to identify quality with transformism. Things in the industry.Until today that signature stays with Taxi driver and its violence bitter, without redemption. Or the nihilism of Colonel Kurtz. Or even, if I put power, febrile incontinence of Tony Montana. But Chapman Schaefer languishes in my eyes losing all nasty as expected so potentially juicy story. Perhaps another try. Hopefully. Moment may or Chapter 27 appear on our billboards. If it had been a John Lennon biopic another gallo had sung. Things in the industry.</body>
</review>
