<review author="José A. Peig" title="La gran estafa" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The greatest merit of the film is the creation of a dual image represented in the parallelism or symbiosis between Clifford and Howard Hughes. Here, it was time, the first big movie of the season. Do not miss.</summary>
	<body>The ambition and success are in the new film by Lasse Hallström an exponent concise and devoid of moral judgments, which is conducive to proper tackling an issue that goes beyond the appearance of nostalgic biopic to be the raw representation of humán victim of his own self-worshiping dream and a society that feeds the dream based on interest ratesthen cut, relentless, with the hope of reaching heaven of the gods from the ashes of the failed.Between satire and the bittersweet comedy, the story immerses us in the Genesis, development and conclusion of a process that begins with the ideal of success driven by the outpouring iconic of a character unique at the time - the extraordinary and sinister Howard Hughes - thereafter describes the adventures of Clifford Irving (excellent Richard Gere) in his obsession with writing and earn credibility with a book of great social at a time of great upheavals impact in the social and political order.Very effectively, the film sets the narrative alternating scenes of fiction with real documents that illustrate the popular in North America in the early 1970s agitation. Let's say that the character of Clifford Irving in a neutral position with respect to the Zeitgeist of its time (their motivations are pure ego kept), but the use of montage sequences - through rhythm and dynamic pulse that is linking situations - integrates to the character in the Maremagnum of society which aims to influence based on manipulationsIt handles alleged confidential data and plays to be powerful.The greatest merit of the film is the creation of an additional - and dual - image represented in parallelism, the existential correlation or simply arising symbiosis between Clifford (symbol of the vulgar man who dreams of heaven of the gods) and the same Howard Hughes, whose presence in the film is circumscribed to the mythical image of the icon, image, the tortured imagination of Cliffordtakes the evanescent character that is itself all the myths of all ages. There is a map that summarizes the essence and the message of the film, forceful expression of the power of Fame and the myth of (vulnerable) minds of those who only aspire to become; in the sequence of Clifford presenting his book, his face, malfunctioned, displayed next to Howard Hughes in the background, enormous, a majestic face covering the degeneration of his puppet. The two faces occupy all the level and the film to the end and all, it has a same story of ambition, but since two positions and two different symbols.If to this we add nothing Mannerist of the characters and the story treatment, an exhibition of feelings, paranoia and desires within the framework of an era represented with strong visual and narrative, without making value judgements about the actions of the characters and its inherent meaning, i.e. showing the life as it is to which the own Viewer can participate in the complexity of the represented lifeHere, it was time, the first big movie of the season. Do not miss.</body>
</review>
