<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Odette" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie of those that are usually described as "beautiful" but which is quite far from the brilliance and that it is unfair to compare with "Amelie" because it lacks the magic and the atmosphere.</summary>
	<body>Preceded by the echoes of his blockbuster in France and compared with clear commercial interests, with "Amelie", premiered ago time in Spain "Odette, a comedy about happiness" (Odette Toulemonde).My ever-increasing allergy to dubbing, coupled with the fact spend nearly all summer in Coruña, prevented that he saw the film until his pass in original version subtitled in theaters Yelmo Cineplex Los Rosales of the city.The film is the debut in the direction of feature films by Eric-Emmanuel Schmitt, known writer "Monsieur Ibrahim and the flowers of the Koran".Trying to the directorial debut of a writer, one might think that the script would be the strong point of the film. However, curiously it isn't so. Or at least not the whole as the best and worst of the film is precisely in your script. Anyway, I think that we can consider the debut, in general, as quite satisfactory.Its main virtue has been the creation of a wonderful character (Odette), a woman that anyone would like to know and let it iluminase his life. Therefore, the Viewer is identified without problems with the writer protagonist (do perhaps an alter ego of the director?) and leaves Odette to fill life sense during the time that lasts the projection.He is no stranger to this success of the character, the good interpretation of Catherine Frot or the good overall role of all children.However the script, and therefore the film, promises more than what offers maybe by a lack of courage to take risks that causes history avails itself in excess to the topics and solutions easier and more predictable.In summary, we have a movie of those that are usually described as "beautiful" but which is quite far from the brilliance and that it is unfair to compare with "Amelie" because it lacks the magic and the atmosphere.Despite this, the viewer will forgive these shortcomings in exchange for having a good time and out of the film with the smile on the face.Final assessment of moonfleet: 6 out of 10.</body>
</review>
