<review author="Yul B." title="Guardianes del día" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Piece of suckling pig, friends. A crappy by the four costa I. Unbearable sequel of a franchise that has had an international impact through its trumpeted visual similarity to a trilogy that devised the Wachowski brothers whose original name you know very well.</summary>
	<body>Piece of suckling pig, friends. A crappy by the four costa I. Unbearable sequel of a franchise that has had an international impact through its trumpeted visual similarity to a trilogy that devised the Wachowski brothers whose original name you know very well. However, this is still resemble 'Matrix'. And at this rate will remain without it looking like I'm afraid (already in production is the third installment of 'Twilight Watch'). And I speak of 'Matrix' as a whole.It is true that 'Guardians of the day' imitate with effectiveness in several minutes of his footage the technique hermanísimos which has both influenced the action movie of this decade that is still unfinished. But very few for February as a China advantaged student of this phenomenon, not even to see her as a worthy successor.The success of the copieteo visual also benefited 'Guardians of the night', who also drank of that influence giving the film pitch inside and outside the USSR to surprise the audience with some effects of the very Hollywood. Timur Bekmambetov has been perhaps the more profitability has brought to this duología, getting to Universal Pictures him the direction of adaptation of 'Wanted' responsible.But neither has what has 'Matrix': plot coherence within the fiction.The film not only can live images, very spectacular to be. You can count things exclusively with images, that Yes, but must make sense. And it seems that it has not fallen Bekmambetov, either before the original film, nor now with this continued. 'Guardians of the day' is a montage of images with missed artistic pretensions, that even Squeak repeatedly falling indeseablemente for the viewer in shameful moments of series B, and between which is totally lost the plot. The ida pot of Timur is such that during many times is difficult to understand what we are seeing and for others it is pathetic to watch mounted chaos.That the paper seemed a fairly interesting story, with a strip and tug of war between peace and conflict of the forces of light and darkness, where the protagonist character, Anton struggles to regain the love of his son, Egor, who has joined the ranks of the darkness, and Svetlana, who represents the hope of light, on screen is an amalgamation of scenes, completely unstable, awkwardly continuing and quite soporific times.Four scenes, literally counted are that have surprised me (briefly) by their occasional good done. Three hundred scenes, badly told by their large number, made me think seriously about how it is possible that this film has had such a quantity of rooms in our country (249) at your disposal.Only sorry to have lost almost two hours of my time to see this film. Especially because I have shamefully fallen into the trap of the triumphalist promotions, feeling like a real fool. And unfortunately it will not be the last time to fall (involuntarily).</body>
</review>
