<review author="Cristina Ãlvarez" title="The host" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film could include in a very specific area of fantasy which uses the figure of the monster as a paradigm of the challenge to natural and social laws, to explore the cracks in our everyday world and the fragility of everything that we call normality.</summary>
	<body>One of the greatest virtues of The Host is as a hybrid experiment. The film could include in a very specific area of fantasy which uses the figure of the monster as a paradigm of the challenge to natural and social laws, to explore the cracks in our everyday world and the fragility of everything that we call normality. However, on many occasions, Bong Joon-hoo get that his film is penetrated by generic digression paths very well resolved, denoting enviable narrative pulse and a sense of rhythm.Without losing sight of the motivation his characters The Host principal sandwiched scenes of thrilling action and brilliant special effects with moments that pivoting between tragedy and comedy, and thanks to a few actors always at the height, these trancisiones are extremely emotional and revealing.Bong Joon-hoo assumed the challenge of engaging in a smart and successful game with the expectations of the viewer and so displays a renewed and original treatment of many cinematographic resources while it is a juicy challenge the conventions of the genre.Director confidence in the possibilities of their material is left to note, for example, in the decision to show the monster little after the beginning of the film (in a spectacular sequence of nearly ten minutes which leaves the bar very high). It is precisely this domain of the situation allowing the director to place also at the other end, to work on some topics (the deployment of skills to be found in the sequence of the liquidation of the monster) without that they are too forced or strident.The staging of The Host emphasizes the expressive qualities of the different scenarios creating a very disturbing contrast between the aseptic and aggressive target of the interiors of the hospital and the dirty and rainy, cold atmosphere of blue and grey tones that will preside over the rest of the film.Another of the successes of the film consists of slow to moderate but very effective use, away from emphasis exhibitionist that usually is used, in The Host accentuates the disorientation and confusion of the characters. Through distortion and echoes the alienating treatment of sound power dilation of the suspense and the isolation of the characters while it helps to suggest the features of the Monster (result of a design that oscillates between the extreme heaviness of his body and the reptile sinuosity of their movements).The choice of a very tight Assembly and nothing dramatic will allow the director a very dynamic use of camera movements that stresses the lines of action that they take place within the table and provide high doses of truthfulness and realism.Bong Joon-ho puts abuses of power in its sights since the first scene of the film. The constant presence of newscasts on television screens exhorts us to question the role of the media while the progressive dismemberment of the family serves the director to articulate a fierce criticism against the harmful action of all sectors involved in the case that it will culminate with a very bleak ending where it is revealed the loneliness and the vulnerability of the individual in a terribly hostile and threatening world.</body>
</review>
