<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Grandes esperanzas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sensitivity without sentimentality, a waste of good taste superbly captured on a tape to remember</summary>
	<body>The book of tastes is blank and the valuation of something can vary dramatically according to the criterion that applies, is something that I am not going to discover now. I say this because I have just returned to great hopes, now see that approached the ten years of its filming. Some will recall that many pan called this film "crappy", "mamarracho" and similar things, while it was also rated "masterpiece" and "boast of good taste" by other critics. We know that you as with all the arts, there are certain creations in which there can be no middle ground: he loves or hates, no grey.In particular, I remember that it caused me deep impression the force with which narrated the story, based on the famous story of Dickens. Contributes to this, in my opinion, a good adaptation and one magnificent interpretation of Gwyneth Paltrow as, above all, Ethan Hawke, with a not inconsiderable contribution of secondary Anne Bancroft and Hank Azaria, without forgetting the specific appearances of the superb Robert de Niro. perhaps it is not a wonder from the technical point of view, and the script could be better structured; but nevertheless, I cannot appreciate above all the ability to transmit sensations which owns, the intensity of the same and the exquisite taste that is an argument so hard.To all this we must add a subtle and perfectly docked soundtrack that helps strengthen the above sensations.All this is to me closer to the first group of people before, cité worshippers of this film that ultimately passed without penalty or glory by cinemas and which enjoyed a similar on the shelves of video fate clubs. Interestingly, this phenomenon is repeated throughout Europe, while in South America, the ratings were extremely positive. On the contrary, in United States was battered by public and critics.What was said. For taste, colors.</body>
</review>
