<review author="José A. Peig" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In conclusion, therefore, The Fountain, no longer a curiosity with its sporadic successes, even a certain beauty with good intentions. But, finally, making an effort we can imagine the same story with the same nuances and mystical references without resorting to a &#8220; hard &#8221; of their postcards.</summary>
	<body>If we look at the strict meaning of the metaphor and allegory, we can see that the use that may be made of these two forms of figuration depends on the intention and the means of expression used to create them. In literature, the metaphor served to establish a comparison using words, to represent an abstraction or idealization of the real and concrete object.The metaphor not only beautifies the language of the word, it adds a dimension of meaning, a way of looking at the world. Recalling that cinema and literature are two different languages, different resources to be used to create the Idea of the artist, The Fountain raises doubt as to whether the set of representations that we see on the screen is the work of a poet or a demiurge dramatic and vacuous. The difference between being creative and wanting to move from ready.The central theme of the work is the anguish against disease and the proximity of death, with hackneyed collateral issues that reinforce the dramatic impulse in a story about a doctor whose beloved suffers from a tumor, which pushes him to the desperate search for a cure to the disease. The story is simple and, in addition, simple, for the simple reason that it narrated - already by itself nothing original - concludes with a very trite moral at this stage. When you narras a very schematic and stereotypical story, what matters is not the story itself, but how to tell the story. From there, Darren Aronofsky decided to expand the number of representations from the base of a referent (the story of the doctor and the sick beloved) real, creates a metaphor (the history of the conquerors sent by Queen Elizabeth of Spain) and an allegory (the history of which is found in the "cosmic egg" along with the tree of life), according to the adánico myth. (Her Eva is the disturbing image of the beloved in the real world, and the same tree of life symbolizes the life of the beloved and the hope of defeating death).There are - as it can not be otherwise - correspondence between the reference real and the two figures. The story of the conquistadors is the "metaphorization" (too obvious and explicit, fix the reader that the same "Eva" stresses the need for complete the writing of the book to make the eternal love) conflict between the doctor and your co-workers in their fight to find a cure to diseases. The representation of the man in the cosmos and next to the tree of life is the allegory that expresses love and fear losing the beloved. If the loved person dies and want to overcome the fear and suffering for such loss, the only way is the transcendence, a State of being that it is expressed in Mannerist and topical way in the image of the "Buddha" which rises beyond the "cosmic egg" (transcendence of the self), which gives rise to a new life in which there is no fear of death and love eternalizes the memory.The metaphor of the conquerors concludes with the discovery of the same tree of life, the motif common to the three representations. The hero drinks its juice and dies when his own body has grown plant life. It is the representation (image) explicit of a sentence (Word) also explicitly said earlier: death may be a creative act, dying to be born to a new life. Triple redundancy, the capacity for synthesis is conspicuous by its absence. That a film is divided into three levels of representation relating to a different meaning order does not imply any complexity. What is more, and the current case of Aronofsky is the best example, redundancy produces simplification. That, in any case, serves to create beautiful postcards that are nothing more than a copy of artwork already seen in any Tome "New age", which is a scam for unwary spectators. Density of concepts and structures does not imply complexity, we insist. However, we do not dare to say that it is a pretentious film, with risk to mistake. No Vemos in the work of Aronofsky a point of honesty, a point of simplicity, to put it in some way. Tells the story of the doctor and creates stories parallel (metaphors) to add a touch of depth to its history, although the "depth" is misleading, vale as free experiment. But there is no depth because it is pure schematic redundant, as we have already explained.Following on from the start, the history of the cinema has shown that his way of creating metaphors or allegories not consists of introducing segments adjacent to result in a same fundamental meaning (is a blunder that cries out to heaven) and create unnecessary Parallels. In film, the image of the real reference is worth by itself and the metaphorical idea can be created from it. See the case of 2001, Space Odyssey, by Stanley Kubrick, masterful allegory based on a formulation on the human destiny on a cosmic scale. Or Dogville, Lars Von Trier, who manages to represent different levels and States of social life and the whole of humanity with minimum resources. SYNTHESIS, gentlemen, synthesis.In conclusion, therefore, The Fountain, no longer a curiosity with its sporadic successes, even a certain beauty with good intentions. But, finally, making an effort we can imagine the same story with the same nuances and mystical references without resorting to a "hard" of their postcards. It was enough to boost psychological States and the development of the story of love and fear of death in the benchmark real without resorting to unnecessary and explicit metaphorical images. But, of course, is much more difficult to do, and less comfortable. That is the capacity for synthesis, trait inherent to the true artist of the image.</body>
</review>
