<review author="Bruji" title="La extraña que hay en tí" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do dangerous argument, by his manipulator development, only ending convincing to those who did not understand that? in an eye for an eye, the world would be blind?. We are facing a new kind of cinema, which, frankly, terrifies.</summary>
	<body>The stellar vehicle that guarantees the showcasing of one of the best actresses in recent times and the peculiar style of an irregular and unpredictable director, converge in a dangerous argument that, by its manipulative development, only ends up convincing to those who did not understand that "an eye for an eye, the world would be blind". Pining the universe conciliator who forge the roswelliano Frank Capra, would be wonderful to think that the reasons that lead to Jodie Foster to embark on dangerous argument, prior review, becomes a star vehicle that guarantees its showcasing are purely professional. Even so, can that the ambitious producer again wrong, almost as much as in the review to do the King and I in 1999. In any case, it seems that the four oscars of Katherine Hepburn would continue without tremble, as many believed to observe the meteoric career of the agent of the FBI in the thriller of Jonathan Demme.Persiguiendo, perhaps, the spirit of Taxi Driver and a finish so surprising as infiltrators, the strange in Ti - benevolent translation of "the brave" -nothing has to do with the film by Martin Scorsese. While this is a "violent director", the violence of his filmography is only understood from the point of view of those who reject. So therefore indicated the difference, the theme of the production that we discussed today, nor us closer to the subgenre of the 1980s in which the streets were filled out of thugs against those who fought a Charles Bronson in full possession of his physical faculties. Titles as I am justice or El Justiciero de la Noche, branded of fascist ideology, mere action shows, lacked manipulative elements which incite to develop empathy in the Viewer. It is there where the dangerousness of the argument created by the Taylor, aimed at justifying the unjustifiable.The veteran writers, moreover, forget the wise words by Joseph l. Mankiewicz, according to which. "The difference between real life and the movies is that a script should be sense and life not". When less is unlikely that, in a city that statistically it is among the safest in the world, one person comes to be in danger of death in three consecutive times during a span of fifteen days. From there, the banalities occur between the sway of shaking cameras, games of lights and a brutally tedious pace, to reach a unexpected resolution against the pillars of democracy. Once again, American society continues to divide the world in "good" and "bad", with more brazenness ever, including the evil in the honest.After a "crash course on New York", Neil Jordan, unpredictable director, must feel like a fish in the water to receive the order. Expert on risky arguments in efectistas deception, never had problems to devise a dignified exit to the acts of violence, nor to show, behind a murderer, there is always one person, any of us as indicated on this occasion. So disappointing filmmaker, also counts with the aggravating circumstance of believing a genius, a kind of Stanley Kubrick in the eternal filming of Clockwork Orange. And, although it is always appreciated personality that some managers show after the cameras; the marked technical influence of "angry youth" and the abundance of flat media English realism of Free Cinema, end up dizzy. All this, of course, emphasizing the physical attributes of the Executive producer, now with a few tired blue eyes frightened, now with talking lips on the radio, now with the evocative touch of a hand. While the secure world we knew is transformed and agoraphobia wins the game to the flashbacks, voice-overs and the acrobatics of the Assembly.It is possible that this unfortunate product is only remembered by the shooting of the aggression suffered by the protagonists, improper lack of elegance of Jordan, more given to the filming of absolutely emetics levels. Again, everything suggests the results of box office, that we are facing a new kind of cinema, which, frankly, terrifies.</body>
</review>
