<review author="Calaf" title="Extraños en un tren" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You can not miss this round history where there are many of the virtues that led to the categóría of genius to the prolific British Alfred Hitchcock</summary>
	<body>Although I saw many years ago, I'm back to review and enjoy one of the masterpieces of Alfred Hitchcock, although I promise to start little by little comment to genius, not all his filmography (directed 53 films) but more than 30 titles available, helped of the magnificent book that gave me a friend (thanks!) on the British filmmaker.I find it difficult to talk about this film without comment or support me in some of his scenes, so if they have not seen, I recommend you to see (is a real wonder of intrigue and narrative perfection, with a multitude of memorable levels), and then read what comes next.Although Hitchcock was known as the master of suspense, it is more than the narrative technique. In this film is not extra or a plane, which is executed and filmed with brilliance and perfect calculation. The beginning is already promising. A long travelling focusing the shoes of the two protagonists, (already describing in more detail of the imaginable to them) that they lie and face on a train (after this setback shows us their faces).After this encounter, Hitchcock already attracts our attention with the histrionic tie of the Bruno character in a poetic interpretation (thus labelled Truffaut in his famous book interview with the filmmaker it) by Robert Walker, diseñana by the own Hitch. most memorable scenes. The murder of the wife of the character Guy Haines (in a loose interpretation in my view of the actor Farley Granger, that virtually repeats character of La Soga) seen through the reflection of glasses fall from the murdered.Or how the director does to look almost in the only way possible in Bruno in the middle of a crowd of people watching a tennis match: all will turn right head left him less.Or how Bruno strangles virtually with the look to the character played by the daughter of the director: Patricia Hitchcock (see photo with the father), in a prominent role secondary, not necessary for the story, but that brings so much, as another daughter with glasses of Senator Morton. In this film we see once more how Hitchcock raises questions that the viewer would be faced with a certain situation, and then gives you an answer, more or less convincing, but that leaves you satisfied. An example: when the bride of Guy begins to sense that something is happening asks him how he convinced Bruno to kill his wife. After clarifying Guy that was not the case, that Bruno is an unbalanced that is making him blackmail, she asks the question that the Viewer may have had in mind: why did not turn to the police, or why not entrusted in it from the beginning? Response that offers Guy: why, have to think like you you thinking in a principle? Which was unbeknownst in crime?Another feature of the filmmaker. The game with the Viewer. There is a certain point in that Guy calls Bruno and tells her that he has changed of opinion and that wants to put an end to all this, assassinating Bruno wants to the father. He then goes to the House of the father of Bruno. Hitchcock does not give a single track of if it has really decided this and has taken this option, so playing with the public. Finally we am relieved to see that just wanted to notify the parent of the grave danger that runs with his son, unbalanced.Another admirable virtue: the coherence of vision of the camera. If Hitchcock presents a scene with two characters talking about and one of them is sitting and the other standing, the usual plane - contraplano in the dialogue of the two makes it with a plane crushed (from above) and with another contrapicado (from below). These flat contrapicados are special taste in director, as used up to focus from below his characters when down a staircase for example.Again mentioning the book of Truffaut, he said this Alfred filming scenes of killings as if they were scenes of love, and vice versa. It is perhaps somewhat exaggerated, but in this case clearly prefers to the villain of the piece, treated with benevolence and exquisiteness, as when burning the balloon of an annoying child in the amusement park. It makes us identify with Bruno in this ugly action.More memorable scenes: the recovery of the fallen lighter to a culvert by Bruno. How is it able to create suspense in such action? Get well.Or the magnificent final sequence of the runaway guy alive, with that fight between the hooves of the horses of the same (great). Apparently, he acknowledged it was played with the type that should crawl under it to stop it. He said that if had reared its head. is it would have not forgiven him.It can be ridiculous to criticize something, that the va radiating the game of tennis to do so for all the public presence (including players) meeting with comments as such or which is playing well or poorly, or is risking. in the end. do I had to put some sticks not?That who not been seen, not to be missed this round history where there are many of the virtues that led to the categóría of genius to the prolific British Alfred Hitchcock.</body>
</review>
