<review author="Plissken" title="Supersalidos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Judd Apatow, the winner of the summer in the USA, noted another both with this ultragamberra, hilarious and very solid comedy. Over time it will be a classic of the hooligan mood.</summary>
	<body>If, in his day, 'American Pie' was sunset on the day of the 'Porky´s', 'Superbad' formula ('Supersalidos' will be called here) could be perfectly, the Disney review of a cross between 'All in a day' and ' Jo, what a night '. And I am not exaggerating. The Greg Mottola film sobran le virtues to be considered as something more than a "teen" comedy.The argument, the truth, does not promise much: Seth (memorable Jason Hill) and Evan (another lesson of great pardillismo of Michael Cera) are two kids about to end the Institute, putting course at different universities. But of course, can go more Virgin olive oil, so they DO'URDEN a plan to get drunk to their "girls" at the latest College party and thus to brand new. And to get drunk them, they will need to drink. And in the USA, the country in which you can drive before drink, his goal becomes an odyssey that will test their friendship.One of the great virtues of the indent of Seth Green and Evan Goldberg (Yes, the protagonists are the "alter ego" of the writers) is where to put the focus, diverting the sexual themes that have almost exhausted the famous saga of the pie and the resulting by-products. The search for alcohol occupies more than half of the film, and provides an almost inexhaustible source of gags and surprising characters (that McLovin deserves a nomination for an Oscar). The erótico-festiva plot is in the background, allowing shines the fauna puebla Clark County. If outside, the devilish pace of the film from the first minute just it gives rise to a time-out (Mottola directed several chapters of the brilliant series 'Arrested Development'), and the dialogues very, very tarantinianos add a density and an unusual power in a "youth" film.And there's more: secondary (especially the own Seth Green and Bill Hader as the couple of polis) give more body to the whole, and the direction, music, photography and montage are a far cry from the standard finishing of the genus. 'Superbad' is a product made with great intention, malicious intent, if you press me, but it is always healthy to see something nasty in the meantime sugar. the downside? Leaving aside the dubbing, rather depressing, gives the impression that Seth and Evan (writers) have wanted to lengthen the adventures of Seth and Evan (characters) too, and there is a slump of rhythm in the last third of the film. But without those bugs, 'Superbad' would be a classic of the hooligan mood. In fact, I think that it will be eventually, despite them.Judd Apatow, the winner of the summer in the USA, noted another both with this ultragamberra, hilarious and very solid comedy. an 8.5.</body>
</review>
