<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Sicko" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Essential documentary about the health system of the most powerful country on the planet. I am sure that the President of the Government displays it the next time that being told that social security is wrong with Spain.</summary>
	<body>This Michael Moore that appears in the poster I guess he is the twin brother of which we know. Either the "fotochó" Lord had overtime in the Office, not what is. Watch I like work to me of this type. And looks that I liked the documentary, Gee. Although they have shocked me things as fat as Americans (I still impressed), that trip to Cuba (which in other times would have burned you their compatriots at the stake) that distills Castro propaganda, and this distorted view of countries that us shows. But hey, nothing serious.The documentary is about the U.S. health care system. Starts giving a vision of people who don't have insurance to go to what if they do. Gives an overview of the entire system, and compares it to other countries, such as France. Great Britain, Canada or Cuba, leaving a terrible reality in the most powerful country in the world. You can die at the door of the hospital, and you can even get to die outside one of these, as you do not have money. Terrible.estoy overwhelmed after these two hours with the increasingly orondo Moore. Overwhelmed and outraged by the images I've seen. It is true that Michael played much with the feelings of the Viewer, getting in the skin of cases, perhaps ends, of people with limit situations. So what? If you want to make a documentary that cale in the people, have to do what they see, feel involved, touch them the fiber and boil with rage (maybe I've gone, but remained very Braveheart). As was done here with traffic campaigns. In the same way.In short, essential documentary about the health system of the most powerful country on the planet. I am sure that the President of the Government displays it the next time that being told that social security is wrong with Spain. Addresses a few issues that makes you scream with chest enchido of pride, Viva Spain and all their national entities (eye)!!Uff, by empathy, about the 18-month-old baby has made me cry like a Magdalene.Besitos.P.D: I have to stop writing criticism in the half hour after seeing the films, I glow. Not so much as Michael Moore, which would seem Hulk ruining clothes, lol.Pd2: The last pie has a commentary on a type of a website that worth the documentary only by seeing it. In my view.</body>
</review>
