<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Promesas del Este" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film maja, as I say estimable, possessing very positive elements, as already pointed and some dialogue, but also in a way, if not disappointing itself somewhat unsatisfactory.</summary>
	<body>Estimable last film of Canadian David Cronenberg, that it felt right to release on this Renciente International Festival of cinema of Donostia 2007.Me'm glad that did so personally you think a creator, lately more classical in the sense of his narrative film, but still with the nasty that you caractiza.After his glorious "A history of violence", for my taste, the best film of the year, Cronenberg us again to show the duality muerte-vida, along with the love-hate, love and respeto-odio, and revenge.And makes it very well from the point of view eminently practical, as they see the tape without breathing easily, always be very entertaining and passing the minutes with incredible ease. And, no, it is not to be very showy in rhythm, because storytelling is quiet, but inexorable towards a do determinant? end, which is in my opinion, the worst thing about the film. A little plausible, little credible end, in addition to ambigüo, which, of itself, you can't be anything bad, but as events happen I can't find you much explanation to the epilogue. Perhaps, it is just that I did not understand, but I believe that it is unconvincing.The performances are good, although Viggo Mortensen, while it gives the role very well, is not that it is very ductile. Always shows the same face (because his character is so stoic) and the same poses. The best are the "minor" characters, but immensely important as the uncle of the protagonist, played by the excellent Polish director Jerzy Skolimovsky.Excelente Howard Shore's soundtrack and the photography of Peter Suschitzky.En summary, a nice film, as I say estimable, possessing very positive elements, as already pointed and some dialogue, but also in a way, if not disappointing, itself somewhat unsatisfactory. Perhaps it is unfair because that, albeit unconsciously, I wanted that outside, at least, as "A history of violence", but the sediment that leaves is a good film, but still room for improvement.At the end of the projection in San Sebastian the public applauded, but without any passion. Ah!, with regard to the violent scenes, will be very commented out the fight in the bathrooms. There do some applauded warmly, above all for the way end (not suitable for sensitive stomachs, notice).</body>
</review>
