<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Promesas del este" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In Eastern promises, David Cronemberg demonstrates that it is in full form, portraying violence in a raw and stark way</summary>
	<body>Since its early years, the cinema has always felt a great fascination towards organized crime and everything that revolves to its around. There is nothing like banning something that a person or group of people begin to provide such property or these services illegally. And these are the stories that interest you to the movies, but all are eclipsed by the more famous Chicago boss. But, why when speaking of the mafia in the film always it is related to the italo-American Mafia?David Cronemberg premiered two years ago A story of violence, film in which analysed the psychological causes of violent outbursts. It was history, forgive the repetition, of a mobster attempting to lead a life of crime, among ordinary people. However, in Eastern promises is the way opposite, is a normal person, Anna (Naomi Watts) which is involved unwittingly in the goings of a powerful family of the Russian mafia. On this occasion, Cronemberg made a portrait of the hierarchy, power struggles and personal conflicts that occur in the interior of a Mafia family. It also shows a stark and stark, violence as already announced the brutal initial scene, that will leave impressed the spectator by its hardness and savagery. With a great visual power, Cronemberg you enter with pulse firm in the bowels of the history, and once arrived at that point, only you can limit yourself to observe the mastery of a filmmaker as David Cronemberg. Viggo Mortensen made which is probably their best performance on the big screen, that it consists of brilliantly disturbing and enigmatic Nikolai.En promises of the East, David Cronemberg demonstrates that it is in full form, depicting the violence of a raw and stark way. It is a fascinating story, and certainly one of the best films so far 2007.</body>
</review>
