<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Señal" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The signal is first and foremost a Ricardo Darín tribute to the memory of Eduardo Mignogna, and also is a good example that you can nowadays also make film noir</summary>
	<body>On 6 October (coincidentally a day after the commercial release of the signal in Spain) will comply with a year of the death of the Argentine filmmaker Eduardo Mignogna. She kept the script adapted his own novel, film that was to star in his friend Ricardo Darín as posthumous legacy. And as homage to Mignogna, Darín accepted the challenge to co-direct it with Martin Hodara.Se is rare to see a film noir plot set in the 1950s that it comes not from United States, or at least will be set there. Kid Corbalán (Ricardo Darín) is a mediocre detective that one day receives a Commission from a mysterious woman named Gloria (Julieta Díaz). Without realizing it has, Corbalán is in the midst of a settling of accounts between mafias and personal vendettas. From the first scenes the viewer checks that Ricardo Darín has learned from great filmmakers with which he has worked, and incurs the typical faults of the beginner. Very is achieved the setting of the film (notably his photograph almost in black and white), with an aroma to classic film noir that intoxicated the senses of any good lover of the seventh art self-respecting. However, and despite Darín and Hodara manage print to film the power and intensity needed, the story itself has slight ups and downs. And how not, Ricardo Darín actor returns to give us another interpretation simply master, and is easy to imagine him as a companion of misadventures of greats like Humphrey Bogart. The work of Diego Peretti, coming out of a risky way rather than airy record change is also very good.The signal is first and foremost a Ricardo Darín tribute to the memory of Eduardo Mignogna, and also is a good example that you can nowadays also make film noir (see the good German), and that this is not exclusive heritage of Hollywood.</body>
</review>
