<review author="Red Stovall" title="Terror en la niebla" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A huge hodgepodge full of nonsense</summary>
	<body>Another American remake which premiered between us, to oh surprise! It is not an Eastern horror film. This time have they got an excellent director John Carpenter film?The fog?, made in 1980, and that in spite of a couple of good ideas, consider it one of his worst films. I think it was a very untapped film, so when I found out that a new up to date of the film was underway, I thought that perhaps they best exploit the excellent material between hands, work of the same Carpenter, and his eternal partner, recently deceased, Debra Hill. Do however, when came the news that the director would be Rupert Wainwright, I lost all hope, and I started to tremble, because still I wake up sweaty, at night, remembering that awful called crappy?Stigmata?. ?It can not you do it worse?, I repeated over and over again. Well Yes. Yes it can, and after seeing the movie, I can only say that it turns the Carpenter into a masterpiece.In a very cute, coastal village that yet more mona Island, a bunch of monkeys characters roam their cute, when suddenly lives, a cute and dense fog, starts to load some, because it is the island hides a terrifying past. And no, it is not because there is a monkey.Trying to renew the previous version, they have wanted to do it in all possible aspects. Even rejuvenating to some of its main characters. So have gone hand in hand with two of the most famous actors in the current TV landscape. On the one hand, Tom Welling, interpreter of?Smallville? (serie_de_la_que_no_he_visto_ni_un_sólo_episodio,_¿qué_tal_está?), and by another, Maggie Grace, one of the protagonists of the? waiting, waiting, that there goes your favorite word, s or b r e v a l o r a d to?Does Lost?, although that itself, very entertaining. The two are? is that aren't, because their characters are not nothing, do not exist; Archetypes of archetypes of the topic. The third in discord is my beloved Selma Blair, an actress with a special curiosity, but that here nor is, does not exist, is not nothing, because there is nothing? You are welcome? Dios míoooo!!! the nieblaaaaaa? do!?!!I have chosen a bad day to quit smelling glue. What do not is you know what movie that phrase? What's going on? do not you understand what you are reading? It is that the film does not make sense. Because criticism either. And I prefer to talk about other things? How it is the fifth season of? 24? Do not assume anything, which I have not yet begun to see her, and I'm a fan of Jack Bauer, good for the first three, because the churro of the fourth was not worth or pa dipping in chocolate? I am thinking of the meme about strange habits that have happened to me, but that I leave for my blog, where I do a bit of trap and move them to the world of cinema?Well, come, I'm going to concentrate. Do already, I'm focused, pasámela, pasámela? In the director Chair, and painting the mona, Rupert Wainwright, which some personal enemy recommended that he go to the world of cinema. The realization of this film is not only extremely flat, if that isn't full of bumbling, and raises the clichés to the nth, causing sometime, specifically two, laughter. Elsewhere, suffers, and not just horror. Wainwright believes that with shooting close-ups, and then alternate them with a dramatic montage, more absurd sound effects, will cause some kind of suspense or tension, or intranqulidad, or knows what. What??The film is full of ridiculous moments, and suffers from the damn mania of wanting to explain it all, so some things are simply shameful, by incredible. If something had good Carpenter film, was that the most interesting aspects of the story were suggested, and left to the imagination of the Viewer. There's nothing of that, which is why, trying to not leave any loose, occur a number of illogical situations, and the result is worse. And if not, how bad explained and shown that it is, how is it possible that in the past (and not any spoiler) these four people could do what they did? It is that it is not possible.Anyway, a huge hodgepodge full of nonsense. I am surprised that it is produced by Carpenter; I hope that it has not been to put money, and has gained a substantial check. By the way, there are two remakes of films of Carpenter, underway; and are those of the magnificent?Halloween? and?The thing? (it was this in turn a remake of a masterpiece entitled?)The Enigma of another world? (by Christian i. Nyby). S or S, which will not make them Wainwright. S or S, which will not make them Wainwright. Uff.</body>
</review>
