<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Zona libre" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One thing is to ensure that the evolution of the characters is well perceived by the viewer through conversations, gestures and glances of the protagonists. Quite another to recreate causing a certain boredom</summary>
	<body>The film begins in Jerusalem, continues towards Jordan to finish entering Palestine. It is the wonderful Natalie Portman, which continues to grow and evolve miraculously, starring and directed by Amos Gitai, one of these managers with its own voice, who works outside the usual commercial circuits and likes to write their own scripts.We have a road movie of book, manual, which passes through landscapes very unusual on a cinema screen and, unfortunately, too common in television screens, news reports and news. A road movie in which women are absolute protagonists, but not wild style of Thelma and Louise, but their friendship and their relationship is more possibilist, more leisurely, more creative. And also contradictory, about the generational question.We have, therefore a few twigs of the most attractive, which should bring a great movie. However. There is something wrong. The narrative rhythm of Gitai, for my taste, is too slow, slow and premioso. One thing is to ensure that the evolution of the characters is well perceived by the viewer through conversations, gestures and glances of the protagonists. Quite another to recreate in the thoughts and the silences, causing a certain boredom and excessive distance.The film has very intense moments, as the talk between the American and the Portman. It has powerful images, such as the village in flames. It has very intimate sequences, as the three women in the car, vibrating with music. But lacks it continuity in the emotion. It sometimes is too discursive, too obvious.In any case, it is necessary that, besides design supermen and Scaries Movies summer, becomes another such film looking for emotion, the look and the floor. A teller and intimate cinema, a film committed with the characters, that pays more attention to the content to the continent. A film risky and minority, but those that do evolve and grow the seventh art. Pity that, however, this "free zone" more promise of what will finally end up giving.</body>
</review>
