<review author="José A. Peig" title="Esplendor en la hierba" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do has written of Splendor in the Grass which is? pure romanticism?, but their development and conclusion they imply a deep and desperate tragedy about how dreams and the purity of the young soul can be destroyed by the misunderstanding and the unconsciousness of society as a whole.</summary>
	<body>Bud Steamper and his girlfriend Deanie enjoy love, begins the film and provided the genesis of a life experience. The teenage years are that make fire the fate and life, and on this central theme Elia Kazan articulates a dramatic epic that touches various topics through different characters and the relationships between them, defining a social context which is a unavoidable key to understand the argument. In the latest images we see the reunion and last goodbye between Bud and Deanie. Their fates diverge, but converges the story to use the symbolic characters that open the narration to tell us, in the images that close narration, from the unpredictable flow of time and the sentimientosBud and Denie are the central axis around which revolve the dramatic movements of the remaining cast in a story that integrates and contrasts ideologies and attitudes, with particular emphasis on the generational conflict, which ultimately becomes a critique to the Puritanism of the American families in the roaring twenties. It should be noted the importance of communication between parents and children, not because of absence of words and phrases swapped, but by the inability of parents when it comes to interpreting the adolescent world and, above all, change or translate the cultural codes inherited by tradition in order to illuminate the conflict and know the real meaning behind each gesture.It has been written of Splendor in the Grass which is "pure romance", but their development and conclusion they imply a deep and desperate tragedy about how dreams and the purity of the young soul can be destroyed by the misunderstanding and the unconsciousness of society as a whole. While the final images express reconciliation and restoration of emotional balance as well as the fulfillment of the true vocation, underlying bitterness of a distorted destination and a frustrated dream. Nostalgia, melancholy and bitterness in harmony into perspective and avoid the cloying saturation, colour and light predominate in a consistent picture with the landscapes and vital records represented in the narrative.When you look back at the past, you acknowledge the life which could be yours, happiness and spontaneous desire as a splendor in the grass that disappears with old age. We are not talking about biological aging, but which imposed by society when already these prisoner of dogmas and social prejudices. What is left is the memory of what we were and we were able to become, as the light of the glory has faded with the passage of time, and each new step involves a bend of darkness.</body>
</review>
