<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="El abominable doctor Phibes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie that combines elements of several different film genres, ranging from suspense and horror to comedy, through on tiptoe for drama and a little bit of terror.</summary>
	<body>Reading about one of my favorite actors, the enormous Joseph Cotten, I found by chance with a 1971 film the abominable Dr. Phibes, who had only seen once, many years ago, at the festival of cinema scope of Cádiz, during a monograph of Vincent Price.Con an aesthetic halfway between the film and the comic book heroes and villainsThis film, directed by Robert Fuese, combines a variety of styles and trends, that although it is basically a thriller film, we find it several comic winks and a setting that at certain times may seem somewhat grotesque, though it must be taken into account in those years was played a lot with figurative shantytowns, and the overloaded was more or less usual.An aspect that draws attention is the characterization of Vincent Price, who plays the role of a doctor terribly disfigured by a traffic accident, and who can only talk through loudspeakers that connects to the neck through a connector (as if a walkman). Everything about this character is to put it in some way, the part Surrealist film, that it's an insane eccentric made help by a woman that always goes dressed in costumes of feathers with layer, and who lives surrounded by dolls that make up a ghostly Orchestra.Joseph Cotten, conversely, is a doctor that helps the police to solve a series of murders without apparent relation, and as always, it exudes elegance and acting ability, even without this being one of the papers lucky shell of the third man, among other many masterpieces.From the technical point of view, the film is not much, but it is curious to see the gadgets used doctor Phibes for their wickedness. The same applies to the script, which has stoppages play too heavy at times, with some scenes that extend well over the due.In any case, is an entertaining film impregnated with the nostalgia that causes see great performers already disappeared, and with the added attraction of viewing the presence of elements of comedy, suspense and the drama within a same story.</body>
</review>
