<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Doble agente" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film of spies that reminds them that proliferated during the cold war, with all the ingredients of the classics of the genre, only that transferred to the enigmatic East.</summary>
	<body>It is not that I have nothing against Asians, or a lot less. In fact, I have always felt interest for that part of the world so full of secrets and ancient traditions. Obviously, this does not mean that I like its current artistic manifestations, and I ask for the reason that the anime and the manga, many disciplines have so many followers around the world. Obviously, something must have water when they bless, but honestly I can tell you that I do not I see no interest.With Asian film I think something different, that although many times I find extremely interesting approaches, it occurs to me, and I promise you is not joke, that I am not capable of differentiating characters of others, by its huge similarity in features. It is what has happened with double agent, a Korean film which tells the story of an agent of the Korea of the North that is passed to the South as agent that defector, and facing a complex story in which it is not always clear what their loyalties.The film is interesting, deals with a complex subject and that area is very sensitive, and does so without the typical exaltation of the motherland that characterizes this type of movies when they come from Hollywood, making it clear, to put it in some way, that "everywhere boiled beans".It is present at all times, that Yes, transmitting the good movies of spies, and tension that resemble those on the cold war were shot in the 60s and 70, with arguments based on the excellent Forsyth and Le Carré novels. A good production and a tempo midway between Asia and the European complete one more than acceptable tape, which has all the necessary ingredients to spend a good time the viewer &hellip; which is capable of differentiating characters of others.</body>
</review>
