<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Payasos Asesinos Del Espacio Exterior" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film series (b) where a few clowns assassins from outer space made a stop on Earth to take a snack. Frankly I recommend it see, unpretentious, just eager to take a beer and a laugh. Insured.</summary>
	<body>Currently, the names of the films are enigmatic and strange, as trying to delude ourselves to disguise that films are hiding behind them empty and based on special effects without ton or they are. Yore, had names such as "Killer clowns from outer space" which is not if not a summary of the film. If you ask what is the movie, you will rapidly repeat the title and ready. Certainly the name can take back, but friends, they know not what they are lost.The film is a village type of U.S., where couples are engaged in a brickpit fornication, police believe to be judge Dred and the word hooligan hear without that nobody look at you as a contemporary of Methuselah. Suddenly, a meteorite falls from the sky (if it falls from the ground to outer space would be the host) and a circus tent, off which stand a few clowns that appears in the place of impact is lian to put people into a ball of cotton of giant sugar to go comiendoselos with a straw coiled. Tempting, isn't it?See that the film not attracted me almost nothing, beyond of to bring it to give birth with taste and cruelty. But ete here that we have 100% of those that will surprise you by the strange thing, but that you like by well prepared is an original screenplay. Well, it is not art and essay, but I direis than a few clowns that comes from space, that their weapons are of toy, pulling popcorn that move and become bugs of those emerging from the boxes with a dock that you wrapped in cotton of sugar that their spaceship is a tent, etc, is not to give him a chance. The make-up and decorated seems great, beating many of those made today with computer. And is that they are more human, more believable, and even tangible. I was delighted.In short, film series B where clowns assassins from outer space makes a stop on Earth to take a snack. Frankly I recommend it see, unpretentious, just eager to take a beer and a laugh. Aseguradas.genial, no more.kisses.</body>
</review>
