<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Hairspray" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lacquer, dandruff, lice and music. Musical show sixties suitable and highly recommended for all ages.</summary>
	<body>I am a geek of the musicals. It seems to me they are the essence of entertainment without worries. Well, in honor of the truth some musicals Yes dare with themes that should think like racial integration, discrimination or bad taste in hairstyles.It had long been wanting to write about Hairspray but I dared not until having seen the theatrical musical to know exactly the part of credit that should be granted to the film and its "predecessors". So come with the antecedente:1.-John Waters, famous director rude, scatological and absolute owner of the bad taste created Hairspray in 1988. Then the film wasn't music if not with music and essentially was him rebellion of fat and black against the world. As absolute detractora of Waters (admit that only stand the murders of breast) seems to me that his film was boring, with its tonic general jokes bandir them. In fact appears fleetingly as cameo in this latest version of the movie 2.-Theatre. Apparently John gave the Welcome to represent his work on Broadway. Tracy took the great leap to the stage and became a musical of success. Apollo Victoria was as follows in hosting in London and thus began his journey for the tables. For my fortune and given the success of the film a group of amateur theatre it is representing in Madrid by what I have seen has nasty Walter with the dose of innocence just then exaggerated in the film. Those who have the opportunity to compare both will notice that the play is more faithful to the history of Waters but her descafeinó it to make it suitable for all ages. I.e. nothing kisses of screw or impossible to cockroaches suits, a most accommodating end and much more light and humor.3-the 2007 version of Hairspray comes to cinema as a safe bet. (Part of an impressive in the U.S. box office and the always disturbing "summer movie" title thanks to five factor:a) regalia Travolta. There are many criticisms of that mass of latex which is in Hairspray but &hellip; after wild pigs and others is appreciated to be able to fit the petticoats and again put in a musical though it is far time which marked the passage by the Saturday night fever Broadway. Some have compared with the Mrs Doubtfire. Is that an insult? Because in my innocence I thought it was the best movie Robin Williams that make the mistake that is repairing Travolta has done in his life: takes himself too enserio.b) Zac Efron. He has become an idol of masses by High School Musical. A television success has surprised up to Disney's own and whose sole peculiarity is that the boy sings well, moves better and girls love. Adults suffer from total ignorance towards Link. No mistake, the blame is not the poor kid, is that Link is the stereotype of the "women vase" but with pants. (If we give such importance in the plot the truth is that it survives with quite dignidad.c) Queen Latifah. I admit, I I remove the hat that is fun, charming and sympathetic over not being able to. After bland and stereotypical comedies is fortunate to have the role ideal in the musicals that is so fashionable adapted to the big screen (already sneaks in Chicago) .d) Michelle Pfeiffer. An impressive return to the screens with Hairspray and Stardust. To me deserves the honorary card of bad irritant of the year. (Chapeau.e) not remove merit to newcomer Nikki Blonsky has managed nobody steal a scene in her role as obese without complexes.Tracy, endearing gordita which seeks to demonstrate that their physical appearance did not prevent him to become a star of the dance in a TV show. On his way the struggle for the rights of blacks, find love and impossible hairstyles. Something that could be extrapolated to 2007 without much lacquer and carded but possibly with less grace and fun which offers this suitable and advisable sixties musical spectacle for all ages.</body>
</review>
