<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Siete Mesas de Billar Francés" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The universe of Gracia Querejeta is extended with a new sample of intimate, simple and comforting movies and that Maribel Verdú and Blanca Portillo face two of his roles harder and better built.</summary>
	<body>Few filmmakers bet give a slap in the face so accurate, disrupting everything and, at the time, return to deal with the little things, of the details of the emotions. Insert everyday situations with moments of great intensity gives a particular richness to the story.If you don't have a strong pulse, so many ups and downs can confuse, making a path with curves very impassable. Properly managed the issue Gracia Querejeta and missing miles. So momentum is risky but carries a reward and which receives Querejeta - though the gift she does to us - is the honor of having one of the most heartfelt films of recent years. The fifth emotional journey of the screenwriter and Director is easy, is narrated without large shock, penetrates gently and that the sediment that leaves us, but with touches of humor, is not easy to swallow.Plays with a value of close and deconstructs it: the characters outlines are people like you, like me, are people who gather around a project and you delude. They wear out and recovered forces, progress and then they fall, but they raise. This struggle to move forward, sometimes alone, best in the company, mark the work of this woman who has much to tell and that times relies on an external observer, as David Planell (who signed Hector), before serving us the final result in tray.Blanca Portillo and Maribel Verdú beat in duel, the Viewer is who should judge their performances. From here we think that leaving unscathed, the two occur as survivors. It is the general tone in the cinema of Madrid, remember the confrontation between Mercedes Sampietro and Adriana Ozores in when back to my side, of which we highlight everything: Marta Belaustegui, intensity, Julieta Serrano... Like that, this tape that conveys reality is not one more: is highly recommended for all those who ever we have felt a bit abandoned and thanks to a helping hand, or to the cinema of Gracia Querejeta, have come forward.</body>
</review>
