<review author="J-rules" title="La extraña que hay en tí" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Efectivista, determined to stockings and empty in content. This is how it can be generally summarized this movie, that if not for some excellent performances of Foster i Howard, would water everywhere.</summary>
	<body>The basis of the argument is quite good: "A couple who is walking in the Park at night, they receive a beating, i the woman carried out a personal transformation to try to overcome the loss of her boyfriend". Up here, everything is correct, but at the time we enter into this process, Jordan fails miserably.Let me explain: shows a change almost Flash, where Foster supplies its trauma i their fear made the society with a coldness i a skill when it comes to killing, brutal, who would be at the height of the own Hitman. All this, connects it with a history secundária, which leads Howard i his team of police, which adds nothing to the film, and to produce very sharp way, just with all the interpretative merit of Foster. (Let's see, if that is important to porqyé in one or another way history have meet Foster i Howard, but equally, Jordan, less subtle, all)Halfway, the film sufré important, rate cuts but solve them quite well with a few dead by Foster, i some excellent intercanvios between Foster i Howard. Finally, after waiting for an hour and half, Foster begins a brief, quick revenge and whole product just closing justita foma, and with a hasty end, more or less as criticism, and where there are four reflections cheap.After this, you say, and why I have to go see this movie do?. Therefore, why not everything is bad. We must stress the great performances of the protagonists and the chemistry that is created to its os is around, above all, with the scene of coffee; the simplicity of the script, which is currently appreciated seeing so many spins empty and unnecessary, justita one-way, and a despanante Foster. (More than one already would like to encejecer as well).</body>
</review>
