<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La vida en rosa" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Irregular biopic about the diva of the French song, melodrama on the sins and the glory of a human being abrupt intoxicated by the always inevitably jodidas circumstances.</summary>
	<body>The road of excess leads to the Palace of wisdom, but then you die young and leave an exquisite corpse. The excess in tone or breath biographical films are highly flammable. Entraen possible that narrative collapses, infected of these excessive, and display a misleading visual appeal-the curiosity always attracts, we are all voyeurs but with formal shortcomings so evident that they inevitably drag the set.Serve this Introit theoretical for La Vie en Rose place, painful hagiography of the diva of the French song Edith Piaf, a lady hooked to the disaster, histrionic, stubborn, brilliant, convulsively addicted to everything as he intoxicara his talent. Or that is what Oliver Dahan proposes: a caramelized deconstruction, a catalogue of public access to the vices of a character of the artistic celebrity. Not just understand what internal motivation that encourages the product, what devious revenge justified the crucifixion. Here the commitment is to provide the panegyric, normally fed loa and biographical compliments of a self-destruction mechanism. It seems (perhaps it is) a vendetta, a frontal attack on the intimate sins of a lady that has contributed to enlarge the music of 20th century heritage, even though I don't have I by Lady fan or have one copy of their albums in my collection of discs. Anyway, the film contains traces of excellent film and is not possible (in honesty) to stick only with this ominous backroom portrayed. Film is fiction or reality, always has given us the same. We cannot remain with the figure of the diva escalafonada to success and collapsed in failure. The antipathy of Edith Piaf, an actress in State of grace called Marion Cotillard, her emotional collapse, its still personality of dark passions and infinite hatred, is the visible hook of a franco-checa production - British, in the panorama of the biopics, jutting. And not to be a display of virtuosity or by cause insobornables adhesions but because moves away from the sweet tone that permeates other tapes in the industry and does not offer easy solutions and old roads. Sins, however, of simplicity: the desire to get out of the norm has hindered a generic and bright vision of the life of the artist and will have privileged, instead, flashes too spectacular (say), scattered sweets - unfortunately - flowing into an imperfect vehicle of endiosamiento of a monument of French culture.The inventory of misfortunes that perlan footage help that I understand the chaotic and unhealthy nature of the singer, but they tarnished a biography over adjusted, less overload to the spectacle of the morbid. In addition, the footage is excessive and repetitive, causing the patient spectator contradictory sensations. It writes felt, at times, disappointed, thrilled, sentimental, violent, bored. It is not possible to then give absolute blessings to this, basically forgettable melodramatic artifact. Not turning it to oblivion or the cold shelf of the films of balance. Only for the inconsumerable lead actress deserves this chronicler of his vices tempered any hint of dissatisfaction and openly recommend this display of moral toxins.</body>
</review>
