<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Disturbia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>All faults are minimal compared to the surprise that has been found in this film one of the most enjoyable premieres of the season, one that is worth recommending.</summary>
	<body>As happened last year when a stranger (2006) calls, those responsible for Disturbia (2007) have created with his film an update key teenager of a famous thriller of yesteryear. While never explicitly mentioned that this film is a remake of rear window (1954), the influence of the Alfred Hitchcock classic is more than evident, the extent to which certain specific scenes reproduced quite faithful way the adventures that had to pass James Stewart as a result of being fisgoneando there where it should not. The obsession of the character by expose all the evil that lurks in the figure of its neighbour is also an ode to night of fear (1985), and although this time the threat does not hide a supernatural origin, not so we leave find winks more obvious to the tape by Tom Holland, which curiously almost nobody mentioned when speaking of film we are discussing today.What makes Disturbia, however, more than a simple bastardization of a masterpiece is that he has taken advantage of the chronological distance that separates it from its predecessor to introduce some new elements. It is no coincidence the fact to show us that its young protagonist, isolated from the world because of the six months of house arrest that you have fallen over, has achieved a window to the outside not only through binoculars, but also thanks to technological gadgets of our time. IPods, camcorders, mobile phones and Internet connection are there (in addition to outright examples of product-placement) as essential elements for the development and staging of very specific moments. Even the small Locator subject to the leg of the protagonist, and that communicates their movements to the police is used as a catalyst for the conflict. And it is precisely this technology that delves into the paranoia that will gradually seizing the character; the moment in which Disturbia reproduces one of the most agonizing sequences of rear window is an even more disturbing Philo precisely thanks to technology and our obsession for image.At the climax, however, is when the film achieves divorced of its main references and reach its own value. The moment in which the audacity of the protagonist gives off and began digging in the horror that has sensed is, without a doubt, the best and most outstanding. Then when the film leaves virtually all adolescent subtlety and converts the calm surface of the outskirts of class middle/high into a real nightmare that is displayed as a game of Chinese boxes, one horror after another showing to anyone you want to scratch a little more glamorous cover of the bourgeois Idyll. It is then when we really understand the title and then is when the tape takes flight and largely compensates its previous shortcomings. These shortcomings are latent, of course, in the superficiality with which play some seemingly important plot aspects, such as e.g. alleged despair of the protagonist product be locked and that, ultimately, is what leads him to become obsessed with the life of its neighbors. Perhaps also we can accuse him a fairly slow start and an excessive recreation in long comic moments that seem to be there for abultar time footage to an hour and a half. But all these defects are minimal compared to the surprise that has been found in Disturbia one of the most enjoyable premieres of the season. Even in the case alleged that the teenage versions of old classics are not pleased that read this, just for the ingenious update of the reckless voyeurism and this angusioso climax, this is a movie that is worth recommending.</body>
</review>
