<review author="José A. Peig" title="Perversidad" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We apply the maxim that, in cinema, there are films that look good and are really bad, and vice versa. Or films which are an exponent of good cinema, but without being as much as it suggests the appearance.</summary>
	<body>In line with the title given in the Spanish translation, this classic by Fritz Lang (1945) offers a brilliant exhibition of the perverse nature of the lie, perversion covering different orders of social life, as illustrated by the film: conjugal love (fake love, fake vulnerability, need or selfishness), the idyllic love, friendship and professional work. On the one hand, Christopher Cross, cowardly unhappy that aspires to win the love of a sensual beauty based on lies. On the other hand, the cruel intelligence of Kitty and Johnny, lie by material interests. Finally, all these characters will become victims of the same manipulations network created by themselves. The bonhomie of Chris (Edward g. Robinson) is the starting point used by Lang to narrate a descent into the personal hell of a man who is a victim of his own stupidity. In any case, the best trump card of the film is its consistency and plot solidity, since get express development from absolute benevolence to the final crime without stop being credible. to a certain extent. In addition, the splendid black and white photography transmits suffocation and the sordidness of an oppressive, consistent atmosphere with the psychological stifling of the central character.Every time we there is less doubt that "classic" is not a synonym for "masterpiece". The "classic" implies a tradition against which nothing can do and, certainly, this film has virtues rather than sufficient so that justified his status as model (a classic, after all, is a model from which work towards an optimal film creation). Say that it is a masterpiece, or it reaches the required state of perfection, it is an error.The central character of the story does not stop being a cliché of bonhomie and exaggerated ease to be carried away by the rubber-stamp Sham acts or unfair manipulation. And although it can be argued that such bonhomie corresponds to a profile real (i.e. within its fundamental features containing nuances that give multidimensional nature of genuine humanity) in a film in which the author tries to explain us the emotional and moral decline of a human being still a way too trite to place excessive emphasis on the stereotype of "good person victim of the cruelty of their fellows".On the other side, Joan Bennett and his spouse, also follow a pattern of evil topical and predictable. In fact, precisely because of the excess of clichés, the plot and conclusion of this film are very predictable because it shows that Lang uses the antagonisms to lead to dramatic resolution; who perpetrated the crime are not "bad", but the representative of a caricature of bonhomie (stress about "cartoon"). This, interestingly, could be understood as a virtue, but what it does is put in evidence the pursued theatrical, the simplistic and topical character of a speech that isn't at the height of the depth to which aims, or is it supposed to work. We apply the maxim that, in cinema, there are films that look good and are really bad, and vice versa. Or films which are an exponent of good cinema, but without being as much as it suggests the appearance.</body>
</review>
