<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="La Joven Jane Austen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I must admit that the young Jane Austen I liked very much. And I'm going to mark a single person responsible for this unusual fact: James McAvoy. Otherwise it is romantic and irregular portrait designed for fans of the genre who worship era dresses.</summary>
	<body>The title in English, the young Jane Austen, is fairly explanatory on what we find in this film although it is redundant since the famed writer of romance novels died aged just 42. I confess that I have experienced some reluctance when watching this film because there are several factors that play against him. The biopics of writers, and more INRI firstly the Victorian or English of time in general tend to be quite boring and extremely long. Secondly the disappointing Miss Potter still retumbaba in my head with an echo which saw possibly veiled my perspective. Also look at Anne Hathaway, is American and despite having demonstrated that the American actresses are cannon fodder to demonstrate his interpretative spirit posing as English (really the Julia Roberts in Notting Hill) is something that always gives me a bit of respect above all coming from the hands of a Princess by surprise. Then is the factor that although I do not consider myself a faithful follower of the work it of Jane Austen if me I have read five of the six works he wrote so the mixture of his fiction with his life could be me highly repetitive. And finally the fact to turn Jane Austen in an own characters out of a cocktail of pride and prejudice and sense and sensibility (as it is) might be too much for my fragile mind bearing in mind both the novels and the film and television adaptations.After all these "buts" I sing a Mea Culpa and recognize that the young Jane Austen I liked very much. And I'm going to mark a single person responsible for this unusual fact: James McAvoy. I've been watching from his two latest films this Scottish actor still unknown to the general public is one of the strengths of any genre cinema names. An all-terrain that the same is a satyr repented in Narnia as it is confronted with a dictatorial regime in South Africa. It is risky to accept after several committed roles of "infamous galán" seed of Mr Darcy and out not just unscathed but conquer any female who is in the room. And well, it's nice to not see Hugh Grant, Colin Firth and Rupert Everest sausages back in the pants of the time.Unquestionably, I advocate that the young Jane Austen is a film made for women. I not contempt to the masculine gender whose passion for Georgian arranged marriages can be as wide as my own but both the rhythm of the narration and point of view of the same is eminently feminine which sometimes can become terribly extensive (such that two hours duration) or sticky because in reality it is not a biopic in the strict sense but a love story in times where women did not have a position ample in order to allow a little paid marriage and say that he could earn a living with his pen where was almost blasphemous. The story does not stop in the role of worker and made women and focuses more on the life of a woman who seems taken from the stories of the era with their marital intrigue and leaving the irony for fiction. In short, romantic and irregular portrait designed for fans of the genre who worship era dresses.</body>
</review>
