<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Un Corazón Invencible" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film, in short, absolutely spectacular, without pyrotechnical fanfare, showing the world as it is today: absolutely confusing, complicated, chaotic and inaprensible to reality.</summary>
	<body>The last and superb film by Michael Winterbottom, the only thing I don't like is the title. And not because it does not have its logic, which well reflects the content of the story, but because it fails to convey all the grandeur of an exemplary film and, for who subscribes to this, shows the immediate future that should pass the film. If "Road to Guantanamo" was already a piece of masterpiece which demonstrates that the commercial cinema need not be incompatible with the quality and a committed speech and cutting current, "A Mighty Heart" abounds in this path, using an actress of the candelabra to tell a story, exciting, modern and counterflow, absolutely Manichean and being presented with a wealth of nuances that make it a masterpiece that still will get long, model and reference of future filmmakers who consider that a camera can be a weapon through which tell the truth of things.Let us in history. The Middle East is a powder keg after 11-S. EE.UU. He invaded the Afghanistan of the Taliban and the entire area became more unstable yet, with Pakistan as a complex scenario in which command officers, journalists and analysts from around the world, not in vain, Pakistan is halfway between the most explosive Middle East and the far East more unknown, with the India as uneasy neighbor.And that scenario in Karachi, one of the largest cities and chaotic in the world, two journalists, Daniel Pearl and his pregnant wife before returning to Europe, are finalizing an interview with different people, as a famous Sheikh who is credited with much of the violence jihadist in the area. Daniel leaves his home in taxi in the morning. And it does not return.A from there, doing a rigorous follow-up of research police, journalistic and diplomatic which gets underway to recover Daniel Pearl, Winterbottom shoots a model thriller drinking sources more diverse, since "All the President's men the" and other classics of 1970s to the series "24", but all of this with the greatest respect and the realisms, without gruesomeness, without feeding any morbid.The film, which had the theoretical ballast viewers most was aware of the tragedy of Pearl and that, therefore, the surprise effect of knowing what happens at the end of the story was disabled from the beginning; It is absolutely fascinating, maintains interest in all times, suffering with anxiety and, at times, until recently reborn hope, of course, it is as false as impossible."Untamed heart" I like (almost) everything. Performances, spídico style of filming of Winterbottom, with those close-ups, fractioned talks, that camera in hand, those enhanced shots of meetings in various bands and, later, the street images. A few foreign which are capable of transmitting the chaos, the noise, the mess and complex Karachi. Also mounted as short as short and accurate levels, all sequences of foreign, with buses, jams, agglomerations, fumes, the music, the faces. a shooting cuasidocumental that integrates seamlessly into the development of the story and contributes greatly to contextualize it in the best possible way.Special chapter for the raids and the police investigation developed by police in Pakistan. A model exercise in globalized noir in which Google, IP, mobile, those connections telephone and cyber have the leading role.A film, in short, absolutely spectacular, without pyrotechnical fanfare, showing the world as it is today: absolutely confusing, complicated, chaotic and inaprensible to reality. Why, who and with what objective kidnaps Pearl? After seeing the movie, someone is he clear? Because this is the scenario in which we operate. And Winterbottom has counted it, once again, in a masterful way. Chapeau.</body>
</review>
