<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Brokeback mountain" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Laudable intentions of its authors are not backed by the power of a solid and solvent film</summary>
	<body>How to go to "Brokeback mountain" free of prejudices, with everything what has rained since the latest Ang Lee film, even before submit (and triumph) at the Venice Festival?If the Cowboys gay, that if gay western, that if the affectionate cowboys, that if Queer West, etc. Before going through the box office, the truth, I was biased in favour of this film. First because the western is my favorite film genre (with the series noir, that Yes) and, secondly, because in a world full of rude maromos passed the life in the middle of the mountains, alone or with companies of cows and sheep, it is reasonable to think that affects the inclinations are escalating, confirmed and consumed in the heat of the fireAfter taking a cup of steaming coffee under a clear and starry sky.The most acute and ingenious commentators have been wondering all these weeks on what I would have said John Wayne before the first western gay in the history of the cinema. But, well thought, what lacked them in relations between the great Wayne and, for example, Robert Mitchum and James Caan in "El Dorado" to be considered gay? Except the carnal consummation, rather little.But let's leave psychosexual issues and begin to talk about cinema. And the truth, cinematically speaking, "Brokeback mountain" far from being a great movie, even if it is politically incorrect to say so.It starts well. Presentation of characters and character, approach the situation, beautiful images, a spectacular photography, landscapes of dream, the emergence of desire, the consummation. Not bad. It is not that the actors are a prodigy of naturalness precisely, but the film can be seen.After the return to civilization, the thing still progressing properly. A society intolerant and repressive, doubts, cowardice to accept with the head and acts that send the heart and gonads, marriage as a way of escape and normalization, etc. However, from that point, Ang Lee starts giving so many laps to the same matter that the audience ends up dizzy and somewhat boring.As happens in so many movies these past ten to fifteen years, to "Brokeback mountain" it is extra footage. In ninety minutes, the classical hour and a half, the film could have been round. Approach, knot and outcome, especially when the original narrative material that part of the script is a short story and not a novelón of eight hundred pages. But not. Ang Lee has decided to recreate the (bad) luck of the players and no ends to finish the story, which is twisted on itself until the boredom.Therefore, "Brokeback mountain" leads to more fatigue than scandal in the Viewer. The first hour of footage, notable, is declining to stay in a quite scraping enough. Laudable intentions of its authors, his committed, necessary and admirable speech in favor of a standardization and public acceptance of homosexual relations, unfortunately, is not supported by the strength of a solid and solvent film. Critics and members of the Academy of Hollywood, that Yes, they seem willing to continue playing its Chairman lousy morale, rewarding the history of the gay Cowboys, but it not approaching, not even close, the depth and Majesty of the just born "M$ B" last year. The truth, having been premiered a prodigy as a "Crash" (precisely directed by screenwriter of the film by Clint Eastwood), showered with prizes of "Brokeback Mountain" seems excessive and unjustified. Hopefully the time put each in its place.</body>
</review>
