<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="Rec" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film works more as a comedy than as a horror film, although before viewing announced trumpeted that those who suffer from heart problems or have epilepsy refrain see it...</summary>
	<body>You've been ever in any passage of terror? Probably yes. Reactions tend to be very many-colored. There are people who you say: Damn, I never go into a site, still trembling me legs. And other: psé, because it was not bad, it's always, blood, monsters, already expected me. As well, do case to the reactions of your body against this type of attractions to predict what you expect out of the pasaje del terror is Rec, whose premiere was in Sitges the past October 5. Another clear reference to talk about the new film of the director of fragile or Darkness is The Blair Witch Project. It is inevitable to think about her when you see the film, there are practically modelled scenes. However, in this new version there are more joke and nasty, much more Picardy and above all, laughter. Because let us not forget that Rec is a film of old-style zombies though clothed digitally and as a reality show televised (gentlemen, the mockumentary is fashion, we're going to do), and that gives much but to much laughter. The argument is simple, as it should be in such proposals. Occurs an emergency in a block of flats since before adorable snowing alarm to the neighborhood with horrible screams. Nobody even knows that an evil virus and that of course it becomes bloody zombies to the holiest has flooded throughout the community, and a reporter and his camera, which are making a reportage about the firefighters nocturnal life, head over there hoping to clarify the matter. Once there are locked at the mercy of the virus, since police forces have sealed the building. Ta ta cháan!!! With this premise, it begins the dance, the blood and the bad ostia. It is important little more. I think that the film works more as a comedy as horror film, although before viewing announced to trumpeting those who suffer heart problems or have epilepsy refrain see it (we may notify because the heart accelerates with laughter), although I have no doubt that the most sensitive can be more than one good scare and have wanted to do pee. If you are thinking of visiting a park of attractions for Halloween, think twice. Go see Rec in the cinema you can get much cheaper.</body>
</review>
