<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="Héros" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Video art and caught the hand SOAP. It is worth approaching Héros forgiving defects and applauding the audacity and the balls to say: this is what there is.</summary>
	<body>The film Bruno Merle is like a marathon. The initial moments correspond to the illusion and the initial nerves of the athlete by the breakneck race that awaits you. After those frantic moments of euphoria, followed others quite predictable, even bland, sprinkled with sudden accelerations in tracing length as kilograms legs fan. You have wanted to reach the goal. And without realizing one has, arrives the final Fireworks, the glorious arrival to the goal, and the race has finished. Promising approach and the absurd and surreal final are not wasted. Only for this reason worth watching this movie. It is a film risky, full of "innovations" in style, even with changes in the format of the film, from digital to 35 mm. The protagonist (Michaël Youn, well-known French and former showman of the Pataki, that great actress) is an animator of audience in sets of television three to the fourth, which I would prefer to be handsome and famous funny, totally alienated and devoid of defense mechanisms to avoid going crazy. Loss of love and the death of the father are the straw that fills the vessel, and not think otherwise kidnap singer fashion, to establish with him (and even with the film's director, with talks on several occasions) a peculiar relationship. Bruno Merle get equal parts that we feel sorrow and disgust by the character, which we odiemos and veneremos it by his audacity. But curious and really interesting of Héros is that the plastic of the film, their stylistic twists, his experimentation, that history itself is so important. Let's say they share protagonism, van completely while in the race to come up with something decent to the public, so, if history does not convince us, we can also imagine that we are in an exhibition of video art in a museum. These proposals are unlikely to materialize, but this time the cake wore enough yeast to not sink completely. Beyond of critique veiled to the mass media and the successful perverse innocence that distills the protagonist, perhaps it its better quality. On the other hand, say, if you're not a fan of Michaël Youn (highly unlikely in these parts), it may be you somewhat histrionic and sobreactuado, but in this film could afford it. Anyway, it is worth approaching Héros forgiving defects and applauding the audacity and the balls to say: this is what there is.</body>
</review>
