<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Oceans 13" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Already burned, the franchise of the thief Danny Ocean cannot be more than itself: wreak, boredom, absolute narrative collapse. In addition, notable moments, entertainment at times.</summary>
	<body>The Clooney feast &amp; friends has already hit bottom: the artistic city of some of the icons of the current film is not enough. While Ocean's eleven was a pleasant entertainment, an updated version of a 70s hit where the Rat Pack of Sinatra and Dean Martin consisted them to casinos with a chic, glamorous and bored air burst. Soderbergh slips in this digital gadget because their characters are analog. Not write I: is part of a dialogue of the film itself. Go and intelligent suspense of the first delivery now becomes a simulacrum of suspense, in a kind of aesthetic and narrative orgasm that never comes. This dissatisfaction lastra the good intentions of the tape, which exhibits the hooks of the above mathematical skillfully and improves (not difficult) the results of the second. Internal speech: Soderbergh WINS $ to finance the film indie, their whims, the daydreams does not sponsor anyone. Schizopolis or Bubble, which I have not seen, are (in their words) film that likes to do. It does not bother him, but is left to pollute by apathy and ultimately exhibits its mediocrity. As it progresses the footage, we think that there will not be climax, theft will be a bluff, which characters are tired and that the actors seem to be a bunch of friends that have been placed in half of the glitz of casinos and bright lights for pocketing some bitches at the time how much you want to enjoy. The simplistic tone of this divertimento no obvious some brilliant moments (Matt Damon in the role of proboscis Secretary of a Chinese owner of an airspace or Clooney and Pitt touched before a programme of Ophra on television), although unfortunately stored in memory moments are the bad guys: an Al Pacino without motivation, a plan of theft without grace or objectan Andy Garcia mechanical and elusive.External speech: Soderbergh loses nombradía. The food film Clint Eastwood or Steven Spielberg and Francis Ford Coppola have always done can also be here represented. Soderbergh can afford these industrial rants, but his serious film, which you like, is not to throw rockets.</body>
</review>
