<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="Derecho de familia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Burman repeated film, telling us a new story that is always the same. The director transits in the dangerous territory of the routine. Adopt the same structure that has given him success.</summary>
	<body>In the words of its director, Daniel Burman, family law is the film that closes its particular trilogy, started with waiting for the Messiah (2000) and continued with the well-known El arm party (2003).Well, what is the common thread of these three films? The search for identity of its protagonist, always played by the Uruguayan actor Daniel Hendler. The definition of the identity through the paternal figure and as a result, the paterno-filial relationship. In all three films, the father represents the greatest obstacle for the protagonist. And inevitably, the relationship with his father marks his present. In the new film by Burman, the process goes by "wanting to be a father". So, how to escape to the model of parenting adopted? Through a process of maturity, described in family law.In this way, the latest film by Burman is the more adult. With a tone of daily comedy, director us into the world of Dr. Ariel Perelman (Hendler), a young lawyer who works in the Office of poor and absent. His father (played by Arturo Gotetz), also a lawyer, it is also called Dr. Perelman. Unlike his son, were mimicking their environment without engaging with customers. And Ariel the more tries to be another, most resembles his father. There is a fact which will mark the life of Ariel. He meets Sandra (played by Julieta Díaz) and they have a son.Then opens a process of maturity. That which is far from the confusion of becoming father even without knowing be son. The inherited road and the chosen merge in a same fate: the construction of parenthood. Ariel wants to distance itself from the model of parenting he inherited from his father, but how? There is a moment in which Dr. Perelman, father of Ariel, will change its attitude, will show more caring, more involved with their affective relationships. A misterio.todo an earthquake for Ariel.Burman repeated film, telling us a new story that is always the same. The director transits in the dangerous territory of the routine. Adopt the same structure that has given him success. He walks away brave directors of his generation, such as Lisandro Alonso, Lucrecia Martel or, indeed, Martín Rejtman. FAMILY law is not surprising. More of the same: paterno-filiales relations as a problem to the personal fulfillment of the son (insurmountable the invasions of barbarians by Denys Arcand). They are rescued Hendler and Julieta Díaz's performances, and we are still waiting for a step forward in its Director, as that surprising TODAS LAS AZAFATAS VAN to Heaven (2001), his best movie to date.</body>
</review>
