<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El asesino" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mafia light, popcorn with gunpowder. For at the very least, and that is very welcome in these times of ramblings and semiotics of flea market, the tape is not meant to send any message, do not have any intention to sobering.</summary>
	<body>This is the trouble that has to film: how easy it is to make box with products of an insulting mediocrity. The murderer is nonsense that does not reach negligible levels of quality of films ametralladas under their same budgets, but is empty, repetitive, devoid of any sense of aesthetics and, more importantly, cleanly nerve orphan. As if the director hired to finish the nuisance, a such Philip g. Atwell, had abandoned all interest in amaze your audience with premeditation, nocturnal and treachery film and had opted (with how easy it is) for photocopying hundreds of stories of vengeance and redemptions, camouflaged under the title of action movie and projected as portentous showcases for the loving viewer of call and other pirotecnica of pure and simple violence. Atwell, without trampling us, recreates that world with correction: Archetypes are perfect, the pranced in the script (with the unexpected end, how not) declared incompetent to follow certain reasonable narrative line and everything is in a pitiful, vacuum, exercise of palomitero film. One more. Does not fit this chronicler of their vices in which is the worst movie of the year, it is not, not even close, but it is important to notify certain demanding public about the inconvenience of engolosinar with the very attractive trailer. Having seen this, you could say simply that we have seen the full movie.The good that has the film is that we are many films to be seen. The murderer does not blur our dossier. Understand that, occasionally, we want to see taureans, japonaiserie, unarmed movies of transcendence. Then there is the commercial gimmick, for whom thus see, together with two experts in skip with falsely kicks in the last few years, Jet Li and Jason Statham. Beyond them to heal band-aid. I saw not the only, but a friend told me a summary which could serve for this nonsense new-age, Pimp and estragante. This excess of bullets (kicks, in honor of the truth, there are not too many, luckily) enfanga a noble genus that is caramelizando, becoming a watered-down pastiche of adrenaline cheap. For at the very least, and that is very welcome in these times of ramblings and semiotics of flea market, the tape is not meant to send any message, do not have any intention to sobering. Covers only the respectable sector of tapes of dissipation mental, as said a friend of mine, but the laudable purpose is drowning in the heavy game of false identities, mentidos honor codes and (go preparing) the infumable closure.</body>
</review>
