<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="The invasion" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film has no pace, nor grace is not entertaining. Hirschbiegel has decided to throw towards intellectual film but has become a child and rather clumsy attempt to RIP on the surface.</summary>
	<body>I'm from the theory that if you don't have anything interesting to say is better to shut up. This increases depending on if also someone has already has bothered to say so should fall in the repetition and boredom.The invasion is the fourth version of the Jack Finney novel "La invasion de los thieves of bodies" that gave rise to the self-titled by Don Siegel is a myth of the fantasy film mixing politics with science fiction (who if not in cold war Communists could be the protagonists?). After this Philip Kaufman shot 78 the invasion of the ultracuerpos (and only the title gives a bit of laughter) and Abel Ferrara with hijackers of the 93 bodies. The degeneracy of these adaptations was witness to his original writer but for his fortune he will not witness this theft of ideas that he died in 1995, although I know that you stir uneasy in the Tomb.Carol is a psychiatrist who begins noticing disturbing changes in behaviour in all who surround him it. Soon discovers that an alien species of virus is invading the bodies by depriving them of human feelings undertakes the way to recover his son who is with his farcical helped, of course, by the doctor handsome on duty. The film has no pace, nor grace is not entertaining. Hirschbiegel has decided to throw towards intellectual film but has become a child and rather clumsy attempt to RIP on the surface. Known for the sinking, the truth is that it was difficult to keep the bar in this industry but its decision to choose this psudothriller of terror as the first film in the Americas has been a grim choice. It has not only been his fault, Nicole Kidman seems a zombie from the foreground which makes it difficult to create an empathy of doped heroine of caffeine and what our dear Daniel Craig has the rictus more serious than a latex doll. That said, if there is nothing intelligent to say keep all silence.</body>
</review>
