<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Shootem up" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The tape said it is the vehicle for the personal showcasing for walk and Clive Owen is the only player with enough straight face eating carrots and continue hitting shots even in full sexual intercourse and not seem ridiculous.</summary>
	<body>You know that feeling in the stomach boa when sales of the film? That gives you want to take a bazoca and kill half the world? The euphoria when you finished to see for the first time Matrix? The extreme satisfaction after 300? More or less is the impression which reveals Shoot'em Up!. After hour and peak that only you see shots and deaths of fancy shapes and impossible choreographies you realize that although the pieces do not jibe at all you do not mind that you've released so much adrenaline as if you had struggled to win back Troy. That's why you takes a while to realize that there is no script. I do not mean that it is bad, if not non-existent. At least a dozen pages can complete the lines uttered on screen (and if we remove the blocks and curses are in no more than five). And then you realize that it is normal because the argument is childish and Basic. Mr. Smith suffering from perpetual anger meddles in alien Crossfire to save a pregnant woman. Just "inheriting" the baby and pursued by thugs without knowing the reason. The funny thing is that I think that any viewer cares the reason for persecution and violence towards the child while they continue dying in the screen average of thirty men at least for shooting. On his way the "eventual nanny" and bad very bad. The characters are nothing more than archetypes exaggerated and therefore its simplicity makes them understandable and bright without the need to get you into their motivations. The tape said it is the vehicle for the personal showcasing for walk and Clive Owen is the only player with enough straight face eating carrots and continue hitting shots even in full sexual intercourse and not seem ridiculous. I can't imagine another actor seriously rictus and British accent doing what makes Clive. On the side of the bad Paul Giamatti that is labeled as a great actor though at the moment I regard effective and reliable: If you need to make laugh get you and if it has to be bad seems it. And as not the note "sexual" (non sensual) in the hands of the universal Italian: Monica Bellucci. It only takes 86 minutes so it is impossible that it becomes long because there are no breaks between a scene of action and the next, very much in the style of John Woo.</body>
</review>
