<review author="Txapulin" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Atonement literally means Atonement, is the Catholic concept whereby one is purified, cleansed of their sins. Under the guise of a confession explains a very meticulous story in a film with several touches of originality and an impeccable invoice.</summary>
	<body>I there are things that still do not understand in this of the distribution of the films. Ratatouille takes more than three months premiered in United States and more than two in Spain, when here in England we her only hope for this Friday. On the other hand Atonement will debut in Spain already in January of next year. I imagine that it is presented as one of the favourites for the upcoming oscars and you know that the more close to March is the premiere, will have more success. Atonement literally means Atonement, is the Catholic concept whereby one is purified, cleansed of their sins. Psychologically it is also the release that one feels to confess something that torments him. Because that is the film of a confession which the Narrator, a writer, makes us a few facts of dire consequences that occurred in his childhood and of which she is guilty. Contrary to what may seem at first, the film is not at all classical, in the way of telling the facts (which we see them first from the point of view of one of the characters and later more omniscient manner, with temporary jumps) or the story itself. A party that a film is extremely careful in many details and very well done (music, photography, the decorations and the interpretations are fabulous, especially some of the secondary, as the red-haired girl and her two twin brothers), these points of narrative originality and the treatment of certain scenes, as the destruction after the warthey significantly improve the value of this film.Keyra Knightley looking here for the interpretation of his life, but I think just it does not get, I can not get her to take off her image in Pirates of the Caribbean. James McAvoy is pretty well, but those that are great are the three actresses that give life to the character of sister Vanessa Redgrave, Romola Garai, Saoirse Ronan and writer, and I already predicted the supporting oscar for the small Saoirse.</body>
</review>
