<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Resident Evil Extincion" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Resident Evil does not convince. It is more of the same or even worse. Try to twist to surprise even Viewer accustomed to more elaborate spins and a little less hackneyed scripts.</summary>
	<body>Alice is now a kind of genetic experiment as his peculiar blood can serve to the Umbrella Corporation to include the T virus when it has already infected half a world. While Jesiqkyytacyyti City survivors flee to Alaska is the only corner without infecting the not dead they will attack your caravan as well as the interests of Umbrella. I took the first separate as innocent entertainment. The second began to tire me but is with the third installment when I I planto.Resident Evil does not convince. It is more of the same or even worse. Try to twist to surprise even Viewer accustomed to more elaborate spins and a little less hackneyed scripts. Its main virtue is that at least misleading not because that essentially gives what is supposed to be that it should be: a lot of surrealist fights hand-to-hand. Disappointing is the new Umbrella monstrosity both computer graphics and charisma. Next to Milla Jovovich (so haughty and little actress as always) are two heavyweights best-known for his television roles for his unfortunate performances on the big screen: Oded Fehr (Sleeper Cell or the Mummy) and Ali Larter (Heroes or Final destination) between all of them trying to navigate this tape that is doomed to collapse.This Film directed by Russell Mulcahy (producer of the three installments), and produced by Paul Anderson (director of laprimera and screenwriter of all deliveries). With this background we could not expect major changes in content and approach.It seems that this installment is based on one of the most popular games in the series "Code Veronica" that takes place in the desert and where infected crows appear for the first time but the originality for me end there. In any case we should expect to see that they think fans of video games that are you been attending rooms comes to a third party and that it has been confirmed that there will be a fourth.</body>
</review>
