<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Huella" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The footprint is a film clearly unnecessary, which seeks to update a masterpiece of Mankiewickz, but that gives us an extraordinary interpretation of Michael Caine.</summary>
	<body>After his presentation at the last Venice Festival, finally reaches the Spanish screens one of the most anticipated films of the year by fans of the film, the footprint. Strictly, one can speak of remake, that this new version as Joseph l. Mankiewicz (jewel film) adapted the play by Anthony Shaffer.Sin however, to speak of the modern version of the footprint without having in mind the formidable work of Mankiewicz is virtually impossible. Andrew Wyke (Michael Caine) is a successful novelist which invites you to spend a weekend in his mansion to Milo Tindle (Jude Law), an actor in unemployment that has escaped with his wife. Between the two develops a game twisted and dangerous consequences for the unsuccessful. Kenneth Branagh made a commendable effort to modernize the story, but sometimes gets the raya and crosses the threshold into the pretentiousness. In several key scenes of the first Act, the action is told of a hastily so that it does not give time to the Viewer to assimilate what you see. However, the worst mistake of the film is the screenplay by Harold Pinter. It is incredible that an author as Pinter is responsible for a text as the footprint. In its effort to endorse the work of Shaffer converts it in such a way that gives back to their own intentions and its meaning. The best of the film are no doubt Michael Caine and Jude Law, face in a magnificent although unequal interpretative duel. And it is that Michael Caine does a performance so memorable as of 1972.La mark is a film clearly unnecessary that seeks to update a masterpiece of Mankiewickz, but that gives us an extraordinary interpretation of Michael Caine. The rest, with the exception of Jude Law, raya in the most absolute mediocrity.</body>
</review>
