<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El Orfanato" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a mixture of some of the best horror films made in Spain, and alone, is itself a story tasteless and bland. Most staunch lovers of horror will love the orphanage, while the rest it will cause them a great indifference.</summary>
	<body>Two weeks ago, the Academy of film made public that the orphanage would be the film that would compete for the Academy Award for best film in English does not. Juan Antonio Bayona's debut could not have been better, with international critics love to her feet, with an extraordinary international distribution, and it endorsed the support of the Spanish Academy.If Spanish Cinema is in crisis, since then it does not affect to terror, that is the genre that most international successful harvest, both critics and public. The orphanage is the most recent example of this, although it can influence somehow the presence of Guillermo del Toro as producer. The first thing to be said of the directorial debut of Juan Antonio Bayona is that it is made in the classic style, which is very welcome. However, and perhaps in the search for the classic aroma, the film recalls, to a greater or lesser extent, many previous films, such as La Residencia, Los Otros, El Espinazo del Diablo or fragile. It shows clearly the hands of Guillermo del Toro in the final result, and they say evil tongues that Assembly which will finally see the public is building yours. Rather than be scary, the orphanage provokes boredom among the respectable, and some other dramatic startle achieved by the ability of Bayonne. The tape, the interest at the beginning nor manages to keep the suspense, it is very predictable and incurs many clichés of the genre. It is technically very well done, but this does not hide the flaws and inconsistencies of his screenplay. For its part, Belén Rueda is not able to carry the entire weight of the film on his shoulders, and performs a correct but something forced interpretation.The orphanage is a mixture of some of the best horror films made in Spain, and alone, is itself a story tasteless and bland. Most staunch lovers of horror will love the orphanage, while the rest it will cause them a great indifference.</body>
</review>
