<review author="Andrés Pons" title="Death Sentence" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The first minutes in the presentation of characters all very nice. Wonderful woman, very clever children, a perfect home, work of luxury that it looks like a cross between little house on the Prairie and feeling of living then become I am justice.</summary>
	<body>The creator of SAW again sank despite substantially improve the results of the very mediocre SILENCE DEATH. Apparently at last became convinced of the need to hire actors truth. The great KEVIN BACON "The lumberjack, MISTIC RIVER", KELLY PRESTON "SKY HIGH" or always solvent JOHN GOODMAN "Still as God" among others, get a greater packaging to the proposal. You can not say that about a script that we see in his female version in the failed the odd which is in me. What shows that justicieros or Avengers films never go out of fashion.The action scenes are resolved in a dignified manner without great flourishes, music and photography are really impressive giving a flawless technical aspect. Only a small point fails, the script so amazing that anyone with two fingers of forehead you can believe what you are telling.That an Executive faced with shots and call with some gangsters out winner at all times because I think it is science fiction. We see in the movies of CHARLES BRONSON for putting an example is a type of street, a hard police used to carry weapons.That gives certain verisimilitud to situations, which is a bit strange is that a clerk of the lot is suddenly an expert on weapons, fight melee that leave them in diapers to the fucking RAMBO.Type rapa to zero, change the suit and tie by chupa leather and more scary than TERMINATOR.Only missing a couple of PIERCINGS accompanied by leather boots, that if the first minutes in the presentation of characters all very nice.Wonderful woman, very clever children, a perfect home, work of luxury that it looks like a cross between little house on the Prairie and feeling of living then become I am justice.Despite this incredible fair argument, it is at least entertaining and save us the typical surprises tucked with shoehorn of the director.</body>
</review>
