<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="La antena" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I can not deny that the invoice is amazing and the work behind this proposal is worthy of praise, and why her qualify as good and I recommend it, but in my view have not chosen the appropriate means</summary>
	<body>Perhaps once have known to a chic @ of the @ which pensárais: go, has a beautiful respingona nose, large eyes that speak alone, a nice mouth &hellip; but why is that not l @ see guap @? I met yesterday to one of those people: was the film antenna, Esteban Sapir, a clock precision of arduous and detailed post-production that needed two long years that he saw the light. A silent film in black and white, with a hypervideo expressionist style drinking directly from the sources of Mèlies or Fritz Lang (in fact, references to journey to the Moon or metropolis are fully explicit, not cut a hair. tribute and nod or easy plagiarism?). The action is situated in an imaginary city controlled and submitted by Mr TV, which has mesmerized the entire population in order to force them to buy their products and thus monopolize all commercial and social activity. In this city the world has lost the gift of speech, except the woman who uses Mr. TV to spread its message through songs and televised messages, leaving absorbed throughout the world. One of the workers of the villain realizes that everything can change if the son of this woman has inherited the gift of speech, since that could counter the Machiavellian plan of the evil Mr. TV to subjugate forever never to his people. The fable is replete with references, symbols and drawings that resemble other so many classics neonata cinema era, and this Esteban Sapir and his team make it with mastery. Some sequences have nothing to envy to others of Murnau or Vartov. The use of subtitles by way of comic but coated products movement which explains more than the action of the characters with light Dim and worn that offers black and white and the general aesthetics of silent film of the dawn of cinematography is his achievement Summit. Really are the film and not the story. The problem is that you needed something more to save all, or perhaps slightly less. A cut in its length of at least 20 minutes had sitting you wonderfully, and that the film lasts 90. In my opinion, the treatment of the image, the semantic symbolism and strongly expressive ideas that go flailing rapidly, gooey and saturate the Viewer, we are asked concentrating very much and there is no choice but to disconnect at times. The simplicity and roundness of the silent film no sight in the antenna, only its format, its wrapping. I can not deny that the invoice is amazing and the work behind this proposal is worthy of praise, and why her qualify as good and I recommend it, but in my view have not chosen the appropriate means. The short, or a series of shorts dose would have been better choice, even the comic I had done the antenna a reference work. When I cross again with the antenna down the street, most likely is that pass long and set me in the girl who buys vegetables that you may seem more feota, I will not deny, but is infinitely more attractive. EA.</body>
</review>
