<review author="Plissken" title="El Orfanato" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Juan Antonio Bayona, aided by a godfather of exception, Guillermo del Toro, has conducted a very effective horror film, based on an exquisite production and a bit overused, but solid, script by Sergio G. Sánchez.</summary>
	<body>It is the "hype" Spanish of the year. Before opening in our country already has achieved the favor of the criticism and American industry (guaranteed distribution and remake), and also will be in the fight for the Oscars. And we are also talking about a film of terror, which, moreover, is an opera prima. Is it really for both 'the orphanage'?Therefore, in my view, Yes. Juan Antonio Bayona, aided by a godfather of exception, Guillermo del Toro, has conducted a very effective horror film, based on an exquisite production and a bit overused, but solid, dash of Sergio g. Sánchez. What account refers to stories already told, of course: Laura (very convincing Belén Rueda) returns to the orphanage where he spent his childhood along with Carlos (Fernando Cayo sober) and his son Simon (touching Roger Prince), with the intention of opening a residence for disabled. Laura will very soon discover the past of the orphanage stalks, and even threatens her own family.As the film progresses, it is not difficult to remember 'the changeling', 'Thriller', 'The others', 'Poltergeist' or 'Amityville', and even some other variant of the subgenre "haunted house". The great merit of Bayonne and Sánchez is that they do not deny the common places of all these titles, but they used to enhance an atmosphere which gradually becomes dark and terrible. Laura fight for his family is told with taste, and a brilliant technical Bill in every way. If little, outside Bayonne manages to succeed in the difficult task of frighten the Viewer without resorting to the viscera or the girls-in-Nightgown-with-hair-rowdy-matted. In 'The orphanage' ghosts are shocking for what they do and what they have done to them, and a success is the way in which we introduced in his little world.The rest of the ingredients is to rise to the occasion: magnificent picture of Óscar Faura (a veteran in this terror), excellent music Fernando Velázquez and spectacular art direction and the sound carried out by Iñigo Navarro and Xavier Mas. And it is sometimes pleasing to the viewer about money, Yes, but also attention to detail. 'The orphanage' occurs as one of the best Spanish proposals (and horror) of the season. Genre cinema, Yes, but why not bad film. Or much less. 8.</body>
</review>
