<review author="Bruji" title="Promesas del Este" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Don't like the sweetened noveleta of Russian mafias hundred in London, that, regardless of all kinds of truthful documentation thereon, is limited to collect topics for rave in a story unable to cause the slightest interest.</summary>
	<body>Powerful management and brilliant staging for a noveleta sweetened mafia, which, after an intensive course of Russian language with simultaneous translation, little - or nothing - has to offer. Especially recommended for people excited with David Cronenberg succumbing to the seduction of the conventional cinema, with Viggo Mortensen's nudes and the ass of Naomi Watts on bike. David Cronenberg, Canadian film that with so many and such good scares entertained children of the lovers of the fear of an entire generation. Probably, the director made worst film adaptation of a novel by Stephen King, the dead zone, - the old things - we both liked. And that, after a remake - not better - the fly, classic terrifying favorite of the undersigned, he returned to frighten the patient Viewer with those foul things than Vinieron De within. It is not known where, to vomit. Just when the geek universe relamía taste with prestigious titles such as Scanners, Videodrome, Existenz, or Spider, the creator of anger decides - well thought out - there is no best terror to which comes from the inside of the man himself, so it should promote psychological transformations, exploit the double morality of his flat characters and shoot a "normal movie"A history of violence, which reaches a considerable size which increases - if possible - its valuation. On the present occasion, Cronenberg is wrong of history and, what is worse, screenwriter. To the even a plot of mafias, covenants and families, the histórico-cinéfila memory back flight towards reliable havens of better times and enviable productions, landing in the dangerous Harbor in which filmic odious comparisons are unavoidable. In this exercise, is easy to observe that Mortensen, nude in a similar scene of sexual violence, transmitted much less the Viewer to which Robert De Niro, really creepy, with all his clothes back (once upon a time in America, Sergio Leone); that the unsustainable situation that leads to the infatuation of the bad with the good girl boy, aborted by his folly, front to which Martin Scorsese built for one of ours; or that peace between families shot by Coppola, that it will be running rivers of blood, raises more tension necks cutting bleeding GLUGs. It must be because violence always suggested was more disturbing than explicitly, albeit Cronenberg who represents. It must be because "the filmmakers are not alchemists, and excrement of chicken (scripts as Eastern promises) can never transform into chocolate". Over one hundred minutes that make up your footage (which will seem thousand six hundred), the slowness and the solemnity (which, most citing the Wilder God, never were once synonymous with depth) they come to despair. The inadequate use of the excellent soundtrack and non-existent intrigue, suffocates the surprise factor ahead of the events, which is why the three secrets that preserves the story will be unveiled with predictable sharpness, without recourse to the translation of the newspaper, nor to the ridiculous question of "Need to know who you are" with which culminates the morbid roll with irresistible Hitman. And, if it does not convince the sweetened noveleta of Russian mafias hundred in London that, regardless of all kinds of truthful documentation thereon, confined to collect topics for rave in a story unable to cause the slightest interest; Neither does the laughable plot parallel adoption, closer to an impossible of Magi that gift to what dictates the Hague Convention in this area. We were, therefore, with the technical aspects of an impeccable production, among his sober photography; with the always pleasing stage presence of Naomi Watss, with interesting interpretations of the secondary actors; and with a director who, at times, it reminds us genuine ingenious wild Peckinpah brutality.</body>
</review>
