<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Asalto a la comisaría del distrito 13" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Masterpiece, of worship, sublime recreation of the dramatic tension of extreme characters.</summary>
	<body>In a time where are privileged the rewriting of the classic patterns and is censored or limits any novel onslaught and, risky, therefore it is easy to develop film, such as cash register, advances, progresses satisfactorily, but the cinema as art, not. There are writers that boast having grasped the spirit or the essence or the pattern of other authors to call (sincerely) teachers and are installed in this placid and accommodative gallery where the excesses and the adventure did not encourage his artistic pulse. In this regard, assault on the precinct 13, the capital work by the great John Carpenter, is Howard Hawks, Rio Grande and we see in the final climax to John Wayne, Walter Brennan and Dean Martin zafar as you can of the horde of gunmen trying to impose his sense of things with the primary language of the western (violence).Carpenter reformulates the landscape, dramatic pulse accelerates and where Hawks, the master, saw the grandiose and monumentalizado landscape of the western, he understands a desiccated and Nicotinic props, the Commissioner besieged by other hordes, but they adapted to the times and turned into thugs criminals. Also moves away from the writing of the original when it holds the terror in an intimate space and feeds its crescendo with the existential anguish (well-reasoned during all the footage) of characters always on the verge of death. The review apora hue that western omitted: some fantastic or supernatural element, the possibility (opened by the George a. Romero zombie universe) that the escalation of violence evident Street comes from the disquieting certainty that the world is falling apart, guilty of any recognizable apocalyptic disease. Carpenter, already master, filmed his siege with sobriety, without delaying in these notes, becoming plausible, enjoyable and exciting up the short argument, its rather than discrete narrative premise, the assault itself. The subject, the fantastic contours of the author-crazy is resumed in ghosts of Mars.(The film acquired a justified nombradía by the scene in which a girl dies of a shot as he nears a caminón distributor of ice cream: brutal)Jean-François Richet in 2005 recorded a very decent remake of John Carpenter's work, with identical title, which does not depend on, but who pays admired tribute.</body>
</review>
