<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Un plan brillante" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is worth looking at her carefully for the so solid structure that is built.</summary>
	<body>Demi Moore is an Executive of a distributor of diamonds amounting not as it deserves for the mere fact that it is a woman. Michael Caine is working in the service of cleaning the company and has a plan to steal some diamonds and retire with some comfort. The problem is that she is not sure of wanting to collaborate in a robbery. We are at the beginning of the 1960s in a sad London and bored. "A brilliant plan" won't the history by his characters acartonados and horrifyingly ideal, perhaps her slip program required in a double session of some paulista school, but it is worth looking at her carefully for the so solid structure that is built.Aristotle says that to tell good a story must be split into three chunks. We must begin her, go into flour and must be finish. SYD Field, one of the best-known script theorists, warned that if he wanted to justify their hefty fees of Professor of screenwriting I had to add something that had not said Aristóteles. So I came up with the idea of the two "plot points". Two turns, one to serve as a hinge between the first act and the second are needed to tell a story (plot point 1, "pp") and the other between the third and the second Act (plot point 2, "pp2"). He later made another idea which makes it more noteworthy than the first; came up that a climax right in the center of the second act which he called "midpoint" needed. Thus, the ideal structure of a script would not be the ternary, would be Quaternary, with the second Act divided in two. Some define the midpoint as the catastrophe, the protagonist loses everything. Others call it the point of no return, the protagonist can not turn back. Demi Moore may not already report to the employee of the cleaning, can not get off even if you want to.The Quaternary structure with a central climax is interesting because it allows the unexpected surprise, this tireless vice of the contemporary writers, is tolerable. When the surprise occurs at the midpoint, the film works. If you don't believe me, go to see "A brilliant plan" and compare it with the surprise of "Fight Club", "Prestige", "Identity" etc..Freud said that the pleasure of a joke is of an economic nature. For the price of listening to a story we understand two, which tell us and which left between the lines. Something similar occurs with a good twist like this movie. During the first half we speculate about a protagonist who does not know whether to participate or not participate in a robbery. During the second half of the film, after the monumental surprise, we discovered that all the details of the principle that seemed unnecessary charge sense from a second reading: the sick wife, stuck cloaca, the histrionic representative of the insurance company.The films name is dodgy await the end, (a plot point 2) to give back to the plot. Thus they fail to create a second reading. The Viewer does not have time to do a second reading. The viewer has only time to see wrong and ready is the director manipulating information and taking his hat bunnies. But it is not the same, one is not left with the feeling of having seen two stories for the price of one, and, if looks it coldly, discovers that he has not even grace.</body>
</review>
