<review author="Yojimbo" title="¿Y tú Quién Eres?" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a new genre in which a script, a director and actors intend to make a film that aware to the viewer but ignoring carry out everything that a film would need.</summary>
	<body>A decent director, a real and painful subject for many people and a few talented actors were the perfect formula to make the film a small oasis. However "are you who you are?" becomes another example of "movie-story" on which I intend to warn for those who feel the impulse to spend money on going to see it.Peli-report is a new genre in which a script, a director and actors intend to make a film that aware to the viewer but ignoring carrying out all that a film would need, i.e., a script with a well crafted story, minimally real dialogue, sober a direction and fulfillment that you not stale, and actors leading with his talent and on their shoulders a story.Mercero does not want to leave room for misunderstandings and trusts Cristina Brondo to represent the protagonist of the movie-story from the beginning. She is an outstanding student who prepares their oppositions to notary. Summer arrives and his family decides to go on vacation and leave the grandfather, already major and with his ailments of Alzheimer's disease in a serviced residence. First encounter. What is wrong in a nursing home? Then a stronghold in which tiran elders who bother to holiday (the only vision offered by the film) that can be either a place in which they are better treated at home (neither of CONAE, clear).The film, like Mar Adentro, imposes a sensitivity and an overwhelming logic. The rest is of ogres. But &hellip; explains, with film logic, that a methodical student, in that summer, decides to change his life to devote himself to caring for elders with Alzheimer's disease? How can we explain that each phrase of the character is a tirade of a brochure? And more questions, which do not have to do with the loss of my memory, much less. Do and these planes of the prota driving (a convertible Audi of course) and recalling, which film of terror, phrases of the sick? And that a carer and that doctor who are 24 hours always serving the elderly? Is it that there is no shift? And the hipermegasuperchachi residence of the death that loses ill Alzheimer's as soon as they open the door? And these jokes that do not have any grace? And the relationship between doctor and patient granddaughter Sung? And that non-existent friendship between Alexandre and López Vázquez who inexplicably ends in tears? And these grips brothers of the protagonist who speak as if they had Down's syndrome?And the final: after that final phrase (title) of the character of Alexandre are will thinking the protagonist that is disheartening to take Grampa, that unrecognized, to a residence?Finally, a cluster of cinematographic absurdities that make to convince the viewer that has seen an interview La 2 fiction rather than a film dealing with Alzheimer's. All outstanding and tasteful is the beautiful head of animation in the initial credit titles.</body>
</review>
