<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="1408" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The first part, about the first 40 minutes, has an impeccable invoice with the dose just that portends that we will see a great film of suspense and tension that melts the air staying in a bunch of clichés of the horror film.</summary>
	<body>It has just presented at the Sitges 2007 festival with a sense of "neither cold nor heat" and will be in charge of closing the event with his second pass screening. The story is based on a short story by Stephen King, and could well have stayed at a short interesting fiction. But unfortunately 1408 account only with the names of the protagonists to attract the public to the room. The story sounds like known. A mediocre writer (Cusack) after having published a brilliant novel specialises in guides for tourists of the esoteric and travels throughout the United States to find hotels with Ghost more terrifying. A postcard invites you to visit the Dolphin Hotel where a room, the 1408, has a mortality rate among its guests so high that they have decided to close it. With the intention of checking which terrifying is it person in the hotel where his officer (Samuel l. Jackson) tries to convince that it is not a good idea but John Cusack, our "fearless" writer, gets fully into the room that will slowly playing her tricks. The penalty is that we are already a bit tired of hearing the same story from the mouth of the famous and valued above writer about tormented characters who dedicate their life to bury under the books themselves write. Especially the recent secret window La is a ghost hanging over this tape.Carefully reading this synopsis does anyone come you to mind "The shining"? And to so many others? It is this the main weak point of the film, one has the feeling leaves vu from the first moment that the character of Cusack crosses the door of the enchanted room. And anecdotal because I must admit that the first part about the first 40 minutes, has an impeccable invoice with the dose just that portends that we will see a great film of suspense and tension that melts the air staying in a bunch of clichés of the horror film. The solution of the director is trying to surprise with several unexpected twists that are a bit forced and childish and being discovered even disappoint the Viewer. The penalty is that I have no very clear until that point I must blame the Director, the screenwriter or the King himself. If I had to risk it would say that producers should look for ideas in other writers and take a deep breath.PostScript. For lovers and detractors of Samuel l. Jackson (that I am aware that there are many) is actually a secondary but because you know that it is very beautiful in the poster.</body>
</review>
