<review author="José A. Peig" title="El Orfanato" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Synthesizing, failed movie, scares and suspense to go-go, imitating but plagiarizing earlier works. Beauty at the end, but somewhat forced and disjointed with the tone of most of his previous development. Nevertheless, it is an interesting and recommendable experiment of Mr Bayona.</summary>
	<body>Drinking from classics of the genre as the shining, Poltergeist, the changeling, or the more recent and popular the others of Alejandro Amenabar, Juan Antonio Bayona returns about the same topics to create a product, once again, that aims to justify in the giro plot (rather, it is a turning-point in the meanings) given in the last minutes of a film thatuntil that time, he was dying in his absolute puerility. The story opens with images that refer to the kindergarten, in a sense literally, including the idealization of the image of the past, with that group of children play involved in flower petals swept away by the wind. Photography emphasizes the ensoñador landscape, trees, haunted house, the sea and the lighthouse on a horizon that defines the boundaries of the space of the dream, children and friends (children) lost. This initial segment already hints that the narrative revolves around the lost childhood and the recovery of the past. The final segment becomes on the same grounds, then when the story discovers all their cards, as we shall see.The film progresses as if it were the typical comic about a haunted house that holds the memory of macabre events. We are witnessing a succession of passages and Mannerist tics of the genre in question, with levels, contraplanos, frames, scares, changes of pace, reasons and dialogues, an overwhelmingly puerile platitudes set by little originality that prevails at all levels: both the history and the way to tell the tale. Some dialogues can brand of emetics, and Visual tricks used by j. Bayonne, besides the fact that we have already seen them in a multitude of products similar (and better than this), appear at times unwelcome if we attend to the rhythms, and the proper dramatic progression. In other cases, they are too sudden for violating the same structure used tempo. This, finally, is quite logical if what is intended is kept in suspense to the viewer and capture their attention so not to lose those final minutes, the true raison d ' être of the product. Let us say it already. The orphanage is not a film about Paranormal and ghosts, although that the stratum of Mythology movie fan (and cinéfaga, might add) that uses as a base from which to create an intimate story, an introspective immersion in the tormented minds of Laura (Belén Rueda), the only true protagonist of the represented story. Motivated by the fantasies of Simon, the son adopted, and especially after the disappearance of this, begins a search for his past childhood. It is not trivial that Simon mentions Wendy as figuration of the own Laura. Therein lies the secret of the film. It is the spirit of Sr James Barrie which inspires the ultimate meaning, not that of H. P Lovecraft.Laura regained his childhood from the ashes of their dead friends. Interestingly, images of ash dust and bones found in a sinister corner of home meet the purpose of expressing the revival from the horror of death, according to the meanings game that presents us with the story in his Odyssey to the length and width of the corridors and loopholes of the orphanage. The search and reconstruction of the self and the memory of son lost - along with his imaginary friends, which are none other than the childhood of Laura friends - is, at the same time, search and retrieval of the lost childhood. Believe to see, another common place that in this case reminds us the recent work of M. Night Shyamalan. Note the reader Laura sequence in the basement with the body of Simon, newly found. Laura evokes the oblivion and the denial of the ghosts of the past (through a long circular travelling).The result is the discovery of the pútrido corpse of Simon. Forget the past is bury children, which means the child Simon's death. There is a sort of symbiosis between the life of Simon and the psychological state of Laura in a later sequence, when Laura comes into the children's bedroom, the old bed bathed by the light that enters through the window in the Center, then, sitting in the rocking chair, wished to return to the life of Simon. Then the friends of his childhood reappear, the light of the lighthouse returns to shine and textual words of Simon (the lost boys) children gather around themselves, as Wendy in j. Barrie classic and night profile of the external landscape, embellished with the light of the lighthouse, evokes the magic of the country never never. when the spouse of Laura returns to the orphanageIt has already died for the present and living in the past, in the dimension of the ghosts of indelible memories, in another time.The key scene (Laura-Wendy recovering "lost children" with an act of faith), and can be cheesy, this resolved with some dignity, and is the point towards which walk the entire structure and previous development. But although the worthy end strengthens considerably as a whole, ninety minutes of vulgarity with five minutes of a quite relative beauty they cannot justify. In any case, the claim of combining a horror story with a process of return and recovery of children, that mixture between a dramatic base text and a subtext of metaphorical nature does not have sufficient packaging, not to mention many elements of storytelling that are involved with shoehorn, most any other place that is loose.Synthesizing, failed movie, scares and suspense to go-go, imitating but plagiarizing earlier works. Beauty at the end, but somewhat forced and disjointed with the tone of most of his previous development. Nevertheless, it is an interesting and recommendable experiment of Mr Bayona. We risk even, say, slightly more suggestive and deep than the pretentious and overrated the laberinto del fauno, directed by who here produces, Guillermo del Toro.</body>
</review>
