<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El Orfanato" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A masterpiece from beginning to end, a dazzling debut full of imagination and intelligence. Moving at all times, terrifying several sequences and a grandiose Belén Rueda.</summary>
	<body>There, in this debut, a disturbing, bleak, acechadora atmosphere and, at the same time, some children also pursued, but in this case, the protagonist. There is no doubt that we have the best film of what it far this year, and that is much. The orphanage, presented at a thousand festivals and acclaimed by all living that we have seen, is the film which, in my humble opinion, takes the cake. It is true that it has been sold as a ghost story; and it is. But goes far, far beyond. Moreover, orphans who persecute Laura are, simply, the symbolic complement of this so powerfully dramatic story. This is a trip to the faith, the pain and reality. Without doubt, a cinematographic poetry finally come true.And it is that the direction of Juan Antonio Bayona rookie deserves no less than a strong applause. Perhaps at the beginning of the footage seems somewhat flat and overly formal (which not bad), but as the film goes into his own entrails, charged not only more pace, but also more life. No, the work of the director is not perfect, and that, precisely, makes that the orphanage is a sublime film at the same time that very personal. Although it shows a clear tribute to the cinema by Spielberg (especially to close encounters of the third stage, a favorite of Bayonne), or classic horror, the film manages to get away with its showing a glorious scene, very risky levels and an incredibly terrifying suspense. Highlight the infinite good moments in the movie, this travelling around terrified Laura, the visit of the medium told in very risky way and traffic accidents (monitor not break the seat of the leap that pegarán.) (I warn them). But do not want to forget key scenes and all that happen at the end of the film (I also suggest buying scarves before officers in the room). This is undoubtedly one of the most heart wrenching and terrible decades úlitmas endings, and I am not exaggerating, because he is cheating or is as unreal as the of the sixth sense, for instance. A poetic and metaphorical conclusion about the power of pain. And not to forget the last two levels, just round off this masterpiece in any way.While the Directorate presents some other esguinze or even important, the screenplay for Sergio Sánchez is simply perfect. Probably with a start somewhat precipitated, but certainly essential to understand the end, begins to be carried away by the tragedy of the protagonist and a few strange very well-written. And it is that you are not fissures, especially in its conclusive, absolutely round part. Lack is not anything, no extra anything. He flees from the topical structure and skips several steps that are really, absolutely redundant. The characters, especially the central, are portrayed in a realistic way and nothing sentimental. A prodigious writing done with intelligence (perhaps too much) and with a perfectionism rarely seen in a screenplay.Another of the strong points of this poignant story is that Belén Rueda, not in State of grace, but at the Summit of the interpretation. Its superb recreation us delves inside, its past and its present terrible without barely put faces of easy scare even make grimaces. Their eyes say it all. And that is what is most valued in a performance. It does not exageraría if say that the nomination for the statuette Golden that Pe finally Almodóvar deserves thousand times. Although everything remains to be seen. For the moment, we can taste his, repeat, magnificent, shocking and realistic performance. If it continues, this woman will become the quintessential Spanish film actress (for my could be perfectly already). Although not fall short side, offer us a great example of how to act without view that lie behind the story. All of them, to be well-written, pate will be showing different facets throughout the film. Fernando Cayo shows courage and a very expressive facets (attentive, very attentive to his final face), Geraldine Chaplin shows us once again that he can convince us with only appearing few minutes (remember a phrase telling you to Bethlehem and which is essential to understand, once again, the end), Roger Prince (for the moment, the first child of a film that is not heavy)(, or tiresome) and Montserrat Carulla, in a very risky though quite brief role (prepare, prepare &hellip;).The intelligence of the orphanage is due especially to the fact that manages to create fear and tension with scenes where nothing appears and everything you imagine. Terrible sequences, that Yes, that say it all just looks and reactions (mostly thanks to the excellent Belén). But the most important element of the film is drama, achieved in such a way that moves us and shakes with claustrophobic and tense scenes as Laura recreating the old orphanage (terrible and sublime game from the wall or the meal). Bayonne and Sánchez offer us a perfect lesson in how to combine two very difficult as the horror and drama genres. This is called pure cinema. There are moments in which the viewer will jump of tension, others that will cry (and much) and some that will not know if what you are seeing is exactly a film or a simple dream. And there is the magnificent trick of the film, this foray that undergoes the viewer in the history, which in the end you end up believing you her at all.Finally, say that the technical section of the film is excellent. Telling that there are many beginners in the orphanage (musician, director of photography, montadora &hellip;), barely noticeable difference between a film made by veterans and one by novices. Moreover, all technical in this film is maintained so that you wrapped it in magic and dazzling way. And this, without any doubt, is a huge achievement. Both the beautiful and poignant score by Fernando Velázquez (unforgettable the song that sounds at the end), as the incredible picture (there are some levels truly prodigious, as her husband is for example the protagonist's running across the sea approximately going to rescue, or all levels in the dark), and not to mention a wonderful Edition (grandiose main credit titles).A masterpiece from beginning to end, a dazzling debut full of imagination and intelligence. Moving at all times, terrifying several sequences and a grandiose Belén Rueda. If they finally nominated her for an Oscar, I will not to think that the Academy of Hollywood is doing something really good, very good. And, finally, to mention the producer Guillermo del Toro, which has been able to rely on a type as ready as it is Juan Antonio Bayona, a director to be much, much into account. Congratulations!</body>
</review>
