<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good Spanish film genre that is impeccably made from the formal point of view.</summary>
	<body>Good movie genre Spanish, which has recently been chosen as a representative to the Oscars in Hollywood. And, although we do not know how are the other two who were on the list that have not released them yet, yes we can say that, at least, is made flawlessly from the formal point of view.It has a very attractive staging, excellent music and photography and a superb montage that gives a considerable dramatic force. To all this we must add, how not, good very worthy performances, highlighting a breathtaking Rueda.Sin Bethlehem not any embargo is positive because the interest declines somewhat towards the middle of the tape, at the very moment in which the character of the enigmatic snowing disappears.Hitherto the film keeps growing tension the Viewer, with moments frankly notables as when the mother note that her son has disappeared from the House in the middle of the party. But as soon as it does an appearance the team that will try to help them come up with the child, begins to decrease, not the interest in knowing how to end all, but the unit completely internal cohexionada that existed until then.Thus we come to an end of the totally credible story and, luckily, closed round in shape, with a beautiful and moving epilogue. It is a success that, through an excellent Assembly which is flailing us the steps that give the characters in the past, can guess and understand what really happened. This makes the apparent ñoño end, its total sense, provided that we admit the spirit of the film.In short, which is frankly fine, although obviously it has been overrated.The seven minutes of applause in the last Cannes International Film Festival gave a huge popularity to the tape, but the have given a category of sublime that it does not deserve. But it is worth the trouble.</body>
</review>
