<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>At times it becomes predictable, namely, the good, the bad, a sheet of spikes that will happen? You don't have to wait long, for guess what, the "bad" vehicle is a truck where eventually the tape then?</summary>
	<body>At the time, when I saw "Casino Royale", the new adventures of the new 007 said and I quote "could go through any other tape action, if it were not for the endless 007 franchise", change the 007 franchise by the of "Die Hard" (his name in V.O.) and we have cleared the equation, and it is that, we have one tape of action thatstarred, again by Bruce Willis, who after his success in this saga hartó to make movies of this nature, and accompanied by Justin Long, a kid who has left less more in this join stars on screen, and to that end up seeing up in the soup.The plot briefly inspired by an article in a magazine (Hey or novels are needed in this film.), we should go with the times, revolves around a group of terrorists computer (French, has bad sitting them at the States France has not its French arm in the subject of Iraq), which are intended to make the chaos theory already made by Jeff Goldbum in "Jurassic Park" child's playcompared with which want to rolling these in Washington also true that computer is "a tad ghost" and is that, for a server that passes much of their working day surrounded by "idems" is not believed many of the things that covered in the broader computing, appears on the screen, very conception of unreality that one is trying to, and intends to put in situation.It is impossible to see this scene and not drop!AMOS COME YAAAA! , and it is that, in this type of film you have to be with mind ready to receive all kinds of FANTASIES animated of yesterday and today.By Bruce Willis not only if they spend the years, but also the kilos, and is already more and breaking in some scenes with face of "can not with my life", on the other hand, and seeing the good make the character who plays Mary Elizabeth Winstead (onscreen daughter) one thinks a good Spin Off starring Baby Mclanegive ideas to this world of Hollywood, lacking in them.Once more the music returns to be, once again, what wrong accompanies the films of recent, blasting action, and descordinada, okay, I understand that teenagers are who paid their entry to see so great show, but it is that one just with earache of so much noise that he intends to be music.Many times we complain that in the American cinema, treat the Viewer as if it were foolish, explaining again and again things, however, in this film is just the opposite, that that is 10 min. already there is a shootout, and we have got ourselves into "into flour", but had not been better to explain the deaths of the first minutes? Especially funny are 2 references to the latest action film aficionado will find on screen, a terminator (his figure detonates the bomb the home of Justin) and another to Spawn, (a failure at the box office, contained in which Mclane starts "accidentally" an arm).Timothy Olyphant fails at any time to be a villain of entity, does not reach or the height of bitumen to its predecessors, Maggie Q does not pass to the typical villain vase and Kevin Smith (lately in any tape self-respecting) here makes a brief, almost fleeting appearance, which just adds nothing in the plot, as well as the excellent product placement of "Microsoft" and Xbox, with this covert advertising of the Gears of Wars, who appears in scene 2 times and almost without coming to story.At times it becomes predictable, namely, the good, the bad, a sheet of spikes that will happen? You don't have to wait long, for guess what, the "bad" vehicle is a truck where eventually the tape then? A LITTLE OF ORIGINALITY, BY TOUTATIS!Anyway, in short, DISAPPOINTING, DISAPPOINTING, very DISAPPOINTING.</body>
</review>
