<review author="Andrés Pons" title="El Orfanato" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A mixture of Poltergueist, the end of the ladder, suspense or the recent the other, terror of classical which is technically overwhelming in all its aspects, but the script is known memory.</summary>
	<body>A debutante whose limited experience is some video clips for artists of middling type camela, not dream never have so many means for a debut.Thanks to Guillermo del toro who lives his best time after the overwhelming success of the laberinto del fauno young Bayonne was a unique opportunity.Began to advertise the film as if it were the panacea of contemporary horror, it was said that in dogs I boot no less than ten minutes of applause. It starts to comment on possible nominations for the Academy Awards. Even is already chosen by the Spanish Academy to compete for them for the award for best foreign language film.With so much criticism over overwhelmed one must be aimed at the film hungry discover a monumental work or a new genius of the genus.What particularly just discovered is that Marketing managers are the real geniuses because the orphanage is only one film of haunted houses.A mixture of POLSTERGUEIST, the end of the ladder, suspense or the recent the other, terror of classical which is technically overwhelming in all its aspects, but the script is known memory. The beats of music to announce the known shock is not an invention of this film the truth. Bethlehem wheel demonstrates once again after offshore which is good actress and the once magnificent GERALDINE CHAPLIN "Unforgettable in doctor zhivago" returns to perform a role that clears the grotesque ridicule.Ultimately the orphanage is a horror film classic Bayonne where shows have expertise to create certain moments of tension and is technically quite laudable. Though of course it is not the masterpiece that we sell and I think even less as a whole to other works of similar characteristics.</body>
</review>
