<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="El Orfanato" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is true that the film used some topics of best horror movies, and drink of many films of the genre of reference, but 'The orphanage' works. And it does it very well.</summary>
	<body>Is true that I wanted to taste it, but did not expect much from the film debut of Juan Antonio Bayona, the orphanage. Nor is it that I had spoken very well from it, and I already feared me a disappointment. But it has been just the opposite.It is true that the film used some topics of best horror movies, and drink of many films of the genre of reference (the other, Poltergeist), but the orphanage works. And it does it very well.The script has seemed pretty good and be robust enough to withstand the envestidas of which tilden it of beans. The story is good and very well told, and in addition to the miedín that gives, is quite exciting and poignant. Bayonne shows us what is able to make one of the best works of Spanish completion of the year, maintaining tense the viewer into the more grisly moments, and making him jump seat when less it expected, in an effective and reassuringly terrifying manner (that long a horror film failed it really)kill them without having to resort to old tricks easy to raise the volume of the music with one blow to leave without timpanos viewers and, incidentally, of a heart attack. Three hundred souls who were in the room tonight with me, will attest.The soundtrack of Fernando Velázquez, by the way, quite pretty, and fulfill its role perfectly: accompany images, history, and strengthen his soul.The orphanage also has a very interesting cast is excellent: going through the child protagonist, Roger Prince; by a few anecdotal, but correctísimos Montserrat Carulla and Fernando Cayo, until a Geraldine Chaplin to gustísimo in a role that comes as the ring finger, and a Belén Rueda that surprises us with a wonderful interpretation, that you could well have its first Goya for best main actress of the year (remember that the Goya has already won for best actress by - that picture is not for both-Mar adentro).Some Cape loose plot (although unimportant), and the fact that many elements of the film are the result of a cocktail of best horror movies, make the orphanage does not take a score of honours.And before concluding, I would like to comment on the outstanding advertising campaign that has had the movie. Being Spanish, surprise me very much, and I am glad that finally a patriotic film product is publicized as it deserves, and the results are only look out the nearest cinema and see people coming to see the movie. That Spanish producers learn from the orphanage. I foresee a considerable international success for this film. In addition, I am not surprised nothing to take a corner at the next ceremony of the Oscar.Que, by the way, the Yankee who have already purchased the film rights to his own remake are so original. No comment.</body>
</review>
