<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Promesas del Este" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Wonderful sample of good doing, one further step in the complete Filmography of the Canadian. A quasi perfect, crude and wildly concienciador film.</summary>
	<body>Violence has always been a fairly useful subject in this of the seventh art. One of the clearest examples has been the Canadian David Cronenberg, capable of surprise, may trouble and stalk the viewer with acclaimed as inseparable or fly, or rather raise with his penultimate and masterful A history of violence. Eastern promises one could expect less. It might be the second part of the latter, but the truth is that you for me, this time has exceeded even further, giving us a film perfect quasi, crude oil and wildly concienciador. There are two scenes of violence extreme (and so extreme) that appear in the film. Two samples that leave us enough clear that violence is not something free, nor something that benefits no one. But Cronenberg falls not only short with this subject, but explores the depths of its protagonists (particularly those of a superb Viggo Mortensen) and consciousness as something hard to pay. And is that the character of Nikolai is a cold, calculating and finally amazing. With Mortensen, highlight the presence of Armin Mueller-Stahl, whose character sadistic and unpleasant, but with his apparent peaceful face, makes create us even more fear and tension. This is a film, moreover, perfectionist and calculated from beginning to end, which has a script by Steven Knight truly incredible with some really fascinating dialogues with a poetic air. It contains already mythical scenes such as the search for the baby by the hospital or the barber shop, without letting me the best of all, that in a warm and bloody sauna.It could condemn the film have an end somewhat far-fetched, but think, believe and agree that could not be less successful. This is a drama criminal, realistic, and hard, very hard, which deals with the subject of violence with pulse and stark way. If that conclusion not League too with the outline of the film is because the surprise factor is as it should be, surprise, not because Cronenberg decide aparar of its principal subject (very attentive to the bright flat end).Eastern promises is a wonderful sample of the good to make, one further step in the complete Filmography of the Canadian and, finally, the real demonstration by Mortensen is an actor first.</body>
</review>
