<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los burdeles de Paprika" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Movie tits and ass. The argument is easily among the teetering of majestic breasts, beautiful ass and populated pubis. A joy to the eye in these times of anorexias and other hueseces. Viva wine, say, viva Tinto Brass.</summary>
	<body>Tinto Brass, are what give me? Jur jur, which rhyme more subtle. Well Yes, friends, before the visual another film of the famous Tinto Brass, who did not know who was until the other day. But hey, that most good director there with their wives in leather and its desparrame sexual. Fine cinnamon. By the way, I read the other day a colleague as he titled his critique of this movie and do not understand as he was able to say tits three or four times. If I I had to take drops seven times to remove them from the retina.The film deals with Paprika, a Italian girl who decides to devote his life to encourage banana (as I have the rhyme!). Total, that what starts as a reason to make money, is becoming a working hobby that gives good yields, as well as joy to the Netherlands. We could summarize with the title, given that the movie is about the brothels in which works Paprika, but hey, we don't need much argument.Tits and more tits. Beautiful ass, those that you hold for not falling off of the bed. Well dense mats that you have to do scans to investigate the origin of life. And the film has something more? The truth is that not. But what happiness gives bone happy see these Brunettes meats, that as the saying, what are going to eat the worms that eat before them Christians. Making a special section, the actress who embodies Paprika, has tits for sleeping the big sleep between them. Cinnamon thin, I reiterate.In short, movie tits and ass. The argument is easily among the teetering of majestic breasts, beautiful ass and populated pubis. A joy to the eye in these times of anorexias and other hueseces. Viva wine, say, viva Tinto Brass.Como movie is very bad, but that joy and desparrame.kisses.</body>
</review>
