<review author="Kiko de España" title="Los Cronocrímenes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a very risky Pirouette as effective, so terrifying as fun. Trapped in time, Memento, Twilight zone, Phillip k. Dick, Prime, Mad doctors, black comedy, eroticism and dry hosts. Everything you need.</summary>
	<body>Talent: set of faculties or both artistic and intellectual capacities. Person very intelligent or remarkable in any science or activity. Synonyms: reason, intellect, wit-Talentoso: has talent and ingenuity. Synonym: Nacho Vigalondo. Cronocrimenes (I put the tilde) is as effective, so terrifying as risky Pirouette as fun and the proposal more fresh and less "Spanish" in a long time seeking something that contestant or The Birthday also sought, a little refresh the patriotic picture.A man who accidentally travels to the past and meets itself. A naked girl in the middle of a forest. A strange indivuduo with the face covered by a pink bandage. A disturbing mansion on the slope of a hill. Pieces of an unpredictable puzzle that lead to an unusual form of crime. Who is the murderer? Who the victim?Sounds like a topicazo, but it is really difficult to talk about the film without gutting her, so I will just say that Karra Elejalde convinces me, amuses me and I moved (although this to a lesser extent, of course) as Hector and that loads without problem with the movie to their backs, despite take a long time according to his own words, to understand the story. No wonder!Could not win the jackpot, but best screenplay in the official section that it is up to this twisted story that could take place in a hypothetical Memento almost lands in Springfield and he is supported by the Fantastic Fest of Austin.Me seems that crush her would be a mistake because it plays in the same league as the piropeada Prime and with the same precarious means "the mathematicians" manages to a much more pleasant and honest workingand above all thanks to a fascinating, twisted approach with adequate doses of humor azabache marks the House to not enjoy.Perhaps at last I third loose throttle a bit, but I think that it is necessary.We hope that the expectation which has been created in Sitges open the doors to the national, more complicated than the international distribution. and that the remake. And these touches of giallo.</body>
</review>
