<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="Cars" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>From Toy Story I keep wonder at the level and quality that have reached the animations. The details, the scenery, everything is so real and so perfect. It is simply magical...</summary>
	<body>Lovers of animated films long ago were waiting for Cars (2006), because in theory was the last film that Disney and Pixar would produce boards. The companies had been divorced for great sadness of many and this was going to be his last son, therefore, the expectations were great. However, months before the release of Cars, Disney and Pixar returned to marry and I think that we are going to be very happy, for always? Meanwhile. Disfrutemos.para start, before the movie went a short film by Pixar called the man Orchestra, which was terrific and if someone wishes to find on the internet, you will be eternally grateful. I am very bad surfer, so far do not know to search for videos on the network. Sorry for you. Without more introductions, let's see what is Cars. Here the "actors" are cars with distinct personalities. I never thought that a few machines as "square" as the cars could humanize, but do.The protagonist is Lightning McQueen, a rookie very talented race car, but self-worshiping up over not being able to. His dream is to get the Pixon Cup, as it would happen in history for being the first rookie in get this achievement. I Lightning McQueen surrounded by mass media. It is the car of the moment.Lightning McQueen has it all, except the most important thing. friends. In his world all it's him, despises his technical team who considered unimportant to his triumphs, doesn't even know their names. Also to his little chic sponsor, a brand of antioxidant, belittled because rusty cars are the worst.The race for Pixon is a triple tie which must be solved in a great final race in California.Rayo McQueen and his two experienced rivals.On the way to California, while Lightning McQueen is transported in his trailer, faithful Mack, an accident occurs that makes our protagonist get out of interstate and go to fall to a people lost in the middle of the desert, Radiator Springs, where it will be trapped serving a sentence and learning much more than expected. Not more or I will become in a spoiler story. But do not believe that I'm not dying of desire. The film is so, so, so pretty.Well, go to see it and discover that and much more. A security that there is no lost with this movie is that the team Director is the same of the also fabulous The Incredibles and Finding Nemo. What more guarantee?From Toy Story I keep wonder at the level and quality that have reached the animations. The details, the scenery, everything is so real and so perfect. It is simply. Magical. And laborious, because for this film drew 43,000 sketches, nothing less.Fact: If they see in English, the voice of Ferrari Michael Shumacher is the real Michael Shumacher.Toy Cars Story: do not lift from their seats before the end credits. As always the Pixar guys want to recognise the work of the entire team and give us some surprises. In this case, a funny version of Toy Story with actors cars.Tires: another tribute to Toy Story can appreciate this brand of tires of career: Ligthyear.Y one more: the number that holds the protagonist McQueen on his side is 95, this is on purpose that Toy Story was released in 1995.Otros tributes: named after the hero was released in memory of Glenn McQueen, an animator from Pixar who died in 2002. The genial character Mater plaque, reads "A113", which is a reference to the Salon of animation from the California Institute of the arts, where many Pixar animators studied.Eye with flies: until the bugs are car shaped!</body>
</review>
