<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El Orfanato" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Go to the cinema as quickly as possible to see already that's some blowout, sure, funny that goes and tells them something about the story. Or, for that matter, the end. Do or make comparisons to other films with that?The orphanage? It can be related.</summary>
	<body>Heard out of the film: "I thought it was going to be another españolada, but the Jimmy came to see her on Friday and told me that she was p. mother." what a pity having to continue listening to things as well, but the youth of this country still thinks that Spanish Cinema is, in general, sucks. Good, youth, maturity and senescence: with few exceptions (Amenábar), the Spanish renegamos our film until it was necessary that Almodóvar triumph first in France and then in Hollywood before being recognized in Spain. sad Lo of the matter is that when you leave a "The orphanage", rather than speak well of the Spanish film, the thing is shipped with that gloomy "does not seem a Spanish film"Perhaps the phrase that has most contributed to that this long weekend the rooms of cinema that projected the film of Bayonne have been packed and that, at the end of it, to be heard some and shy aplausos.¿Por what, suddenly, the Spanish spectators come en masse and in droves (seems that "The orphanage" figures will be record after their first weekend of exhibition) to see According to what Spanish films?We could start by saying that the genre of horror and suspense is a trump card in favour, but does not guarantee success, as Jaume Balagueró could testify. In this case, that Yes, we are before an exemplary horror film, a film of book, with its scares, repullos, stress, anxiety, fear and several surprises. The fact that the protagonist does not undress, is also an asset in favour of complicity with an audience, especially the women, being tired of our actresses have to leave in full refocile, at least a couple of times for film. In this case, a Belén Rueda at all erotic, in addition to not teach nor Frida of meat, is extraordinary.In addition, actors are understood when speaking. They vocalize instead of mumble phrases loose and disjointed, as if they had a sock inside the mouth or walked half drugged and drunken. And sound effects, impressive. A film, as well as seen, heard, with what that going to the cinema was converted back to a good experience. In addition, see a movie of fear with the full House, cool more.We have a film that seems a film and not a stretched version of the soap opera fashion. A careful design of production, an extraordinary staging and, above all, a solid history of. well, we will not say what. That Yes, advice of friend, go to the cinema as quickly as possible to see already that's some blowout, sure, funny that goes and tells them something about the history. Or, for that matter, the end. Or will they make comparisons to other films with which "The orphanage" can be related.Therefore, go as quickly as possible the film to enjoy terrorizing a great film which, however, not do I know if it will ultimately convince the Academy more elderly hollywodiense sector, whose hearts not pass it very well with this orphanage full of surprises.</body>
</review>
