<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Lío embarazoso" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tape that judging by its title you can reject, and that however, and removing a good handful of absurdities may become like some and terrify others, specially dedicated to all those who intend to become pregnant in the near future.</summary>
	<body>For some time this part one is starting: Park the animosity I feel towards the romantic comedy (and just seeing the force thanks / because of my wife), and I try to appreciate, measure if it is worth or not, sometimes I come to value only by the actors involved in it, others for the title; This film that brings us today has all the ballots to be completely rejected for a movie buff Pro, but, as I am not I've willing to see it.I think that who is behind the film Judd Apatow, and the large group formed by Paul Rudd, Seth Rogen and Jonah Hill (excellent in "supersalidos"), if Adam Sadler and Santiago segura put his friends, that Seth Rogen and Apatow not can do the same? Accompanied by the famous Katherine Heigl ("Grey Anatomy") I loved the multitude of current references that appear on screen, from "Lost" to "Munich", through "Spiderman", "Monk", "Brokeback Mountain" or "Transmerica" and "Desperate housewives" series.In one of the journals of cinema that I often read monthly they referred to this film as tied in a new series of "Catholic tendencies" which demonstrate that, practise unprotected sex brings dire consequences, as well as the controversy over abortion and some thing rather than the movie, plays; If seen in this film that allegation is "beyond" look and if there were critics who saw in "300" a critique of Bush and the war in Iraq, or in the most recent "the strange that there are in my" an invitation to free will, here the only thing I see is a very Disney comedy (below invoice "Virgin at 40") and little else, ah! not I forget her excellent website.Excellent appearances in lightweight cameos of director Harold Ramis, and actress Joanna Kerns (famous in Spain for being the mother of "the problems grow", Maggie Seaver).On the negative plot, say the film lasts too (two hour and peak long reach tire), the party that takes place in Las Vegas Needless perhaps does not City casinos quite promotion with the myriad of Teleseryes taking place there? Its too feminist language in some moments, especially a phrase that says the sister of the main character related to the great self tender offer and which has in its context criticize = lose = change is perhaps my ex - was the same writer?Aside, once again, and this happy ending, is an attempt to moralize, and educate viewers on how great the experience of being parents (soon to my I have become to remove the desire).</body>
</review>
