<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El Orfanato" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entertaining, recommended, almost a masterpiece. The debut of Bayonne has the stamp of the bull, but contains enough charms (however) to understand it as a speech separate...</summary>
	<body>There is a reasonable rule which prescribes that Gothic breath Spanish film died with Narciso Ibáñez Serrador, but Alejandro Amenábar turned the pattern and invoiced an outstanding exercise in aureolado ghosts film melodrama and pure fantastique. Juan Antonio Bayona, the director of the orphanage, weapon another solid exception and without reaching the classicism of Amenábar or the re-birth of Ibáñez Serrador, recover - from cara patria gallery - the genre in a way we hope that final.Everything can argue to overturn the general tone of magnificence awarded the tape no longer excess critic committed to impartiality - or we all unequivocally partial and that, ultimately, this is - an outburst of intransigence. Because the orphanage is a very interesting film and their successes shine above shortcomings (natural). Also the film as an industry requires orphanages such as this, which they acceptation our noticeboard and seek abroad, an image which until now had only manchega signature or specific products already installed in the memory of the time (Bardem, Saura, Erice, Neville, Berlanga).More than a movie (or the time) than a movie the orphanage is a path where should develop the film industry to own and strange rejoicing and consolidation of a market and profit expectations reasonable and worthy.Bayonne, which comes from the video clip, relaxes the dynamism of concise writing three-minute song to shoot a horror story that never attends the predictable inventory of syncopated scares, the American cinema of identical pulse picks up perfectly, but that gathers handmade perhaps, voices, bells, echoes, landscapes and views already sounds. It seems that the film has already been seen, and that perception late during any part of the footage. Not so in the end, poetic, exalted, chivado a producer as Guillermo del Toro to print the film air that you like, that mixture special where the dreams, reality, tales and the greed of life embrace to create a narrative frame only, important, worthy to be included in our memory time after having attended his staging.The orphanage is an irregular piece, that is sure. Lasts too: it could not incurring the resource of the filling, but stimulates even those pieces hollow, possibly difficult to baste with the main subject of the film. There are lost, even missing characters. This unquestionable evidence has its justification: the tape rests on the bony shoulders of Belén Rueda, is sublime. It is a film absolutely overturned on the sentimentality of a character thrown on the brink of the abyss and buffeted by forces that do not know and that you must pay due respect in this threshold. The prodigious script by Sergio g. Sánchez, which took to write ten years, as he has in a press interview, enables the fantastic artifice, the mist of the Gothic tale which referred to start this review. The impeccable technical invoice dazzles over the certainty of knowing that we are witnessing a scramble of scenes seen throughout life in a multitude of tapes. Excuse: Bayonne reformulates the clichés, narrow them in a very precise drawing of characters, in a lavish display of knowledge of classic cinema. I thought that Hitchcock would have enjoyed it, but there will be who deny me this whim. Mine is.Outside sensiblerías, Bayonne has built a sensitive filmic space. It is not the same. That no one expected a melodrama, a tour of interpretative force supported by outstanding dialogues. They are not needed. The (I insist) intelligent script pespunta ideas that do not require subsequent seams. Or semantic fanfare. Everything you said is very well said, and could not be said otherwise.If the Viewer is no friend of childhood as an engine of a story and they are loaded landscapes idealized around the mist and mystery, then this is not his film. The orphanage abuses of this intriguing atmosphere of classical easements and murky visual style. The intimate story of the girl Laura (Belén Rueda) and his adopted son is a modern extension of the tale to the Poe or the Lovecraft, but without the competition of evil entities. The horror that we are witnessing is poetic in nature: disturbed, but not saturated; It shocked, but it not shocked. Everything is bathed by the investment of the myth of Peter Pan and his offspring of lost boys who want to at the bottom of the tunnel of metaphors, return to life or, in any case, life to do something so your lethargy (his placid dream, its games and silent cosmos) looks as much as possible to it. This deconstruction is the unmatched bet of Bayonne: an update of the power of faith and how beliefs can open doors to new worlds and consent that we go into them. The Poltergeist effect could have been omitted. It is the weaker, despite being one of the most showy and mounted. Geraldine Chaplin does not credible a merely casual, barely relevant character in the narrative journey of the film.This chronicler of his vices not enjoyed, although it seems, so much as I would like to: was left to carry by an excess of love for the genre and did not respond with the proper delivery. Only he felt relieved, rewarded, when he attended the final Vertigo, that content and prodigious episode of pure poetry. Laura/Wendy is the heroine of this risky (and healthy, and achieved) ghost story. It is not terrified of others heroin because it discovered the truth in fear and this, here are the outstanding turn, seeks the truth in it and, ultimately, to Miss Miss also.</body>
</review>
