<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Tre metri sopra il cielo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Friendship, racing motorcycles, clashes of classes, a species of umpteenth Romeo and Juliet with a freshness that makes it delicious.</summary>
	<body>Tre Metri Sopra Il Cielo is based on the eponymous book by the Italian writer Federico Moccia that enjoyed great popularity in his country among the new youth. Precisely this same public is directed the film who consumed the tape with a voracious desire because it's an exquisite exercise of reflection on the transition to adulthood and because the healthy habit of down to Earth to raise current social issues outside the comedy had been lost in Italy. Its content is not very original and we raked nauseam: good girl meets bad boy, they fall in love and happen events in the middle that seek to break away from his love. Friendship, racing motorcycles, clashes of classes, a species of umpteenth Romeo and Juliet with a freshness that makes it delicious. Wouldn't be interesting if it were not because unlike our American in Europe friends no we are concerned both the end and the means so the interpretation of a handful of kids talent and a dash more worried about being faithful to the spirit of their own characters to the culture of the happy end get that, all that we enjoy with this film of transition to adulthoodWe can taste this tape. I.e. between the bunch of confusing people there are some who, albeit only slightly, can represent every type of public facilities including more adults.The beauty lies in the rapport with their characters. Rather than fall mere stereotypes are an evolution of themselves and have nothing to do with what was at the beginning of the film when they reach its denouement. Original is the link that guides us through the tape with a voice-over from of an invented Italian radio, 107.3 FM Radio chaos, which is a reflection for each event and we are always left with a thought like "live from the future", "Turning on the contrary" or quotes from movies and mythical songs.Finally don't forget to quote the discovery in this movie which has proved to be one of the most sought after actors in the current Italian cinema, Riccardo Scamarcio, which is simply brilliant in the role of Step "teenage boyfriend that all have wanted to have" and the father of Babi as counterpoint and glorious moments of companionship and inter-generational understanding.DATA on the película:fecha of Italy release: 12 March 2004No has been dubbed into Spanish or released in our country.They made a musical due to the success of the book and the film</body>
</review>
