<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Las 13 Rosas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Touching story of 13 women executed unjustly. These women whose memory has not erased the history were as "Las 13 Rosas", Martinez-Lazaro recovers these facts becoming one of the films of the year.</summary>
	<body>This is the touching story of 13 women who you had to live a harsh reality after the Spanish Civil War. Almost all minors, were unjustly executed on 5 August 1939 in the walls of the cemetery of the Almudena. These women whose memory has not deleted the history, they were remembered as "Las 13 Rosas" and Martinez-Lazaro retrieves these facts into what certainly will be one of the films of the year.Las 13 Rosas, from my point of view is the peak of Emilio Martinez-Lazaro, the definitive work. Directed with a taste of exquisite and accompanied by Original Soundtrack (by Roque Baños) that perfectly complements the satellite and you moved to a world full of textures, colors and even smells.These girls had not committed any crime or offence except be affiliated to the Socialistaslo youth which seems that you served as an excuse for generating unrealistic reasons and be carried to a Council of war that would judge them unfairly accusing them of events which had not carried out without testing and depuñes have been subjected to imprisonment and harsh police interrogations. The end of all this was to give a lesson to the whole society to persuade that not revelera against the established regime.Account director, who at any time has tried to be faithful to the fact real taking as point of view for the film turn their characters more in heroines, victims. For this reason and that would have been unbearable on screen, has not wanted to show the details of the horror suffered by these girls. So then proceeded to make a synthesis that would allow the story to fit with the footage.It is a drama film which you gets into the soul deeply. The art direction is outstanding, but I still like I Veronica Sanchez, overshadowed by a unstoppable and majestic Pilar López de Ayala and Marta Etura. It is absolutely transducer, everything plays it like, except certain nuances, is as saw the same character forever but in different situations of a life itself. And to make matters worse accompanied by Fran Perea which not paste or glue and reminds us how not to "Los Serrano", a total prick in an artistic piece that if it were not for these two, we could describe as perfect.Special mentions for that fabulous actor, magno and regio Asier Etxeandía starred a stellar moment when he plays the main theme of the film in French. Also for the rightly rescued Goya Toledo that brings the most out of your character and demonstrating an important interpretative maturity.On this occasion I will let the issue of the ages of some actresses because the result is really so good it deserves the penalty sacríficar the credibility of youth.To watch movies as Las 13 Rosas, you can breathe with some relief thinking that "at last something decent in the middle of the precarious and pathetic picture of the Spanish film" we are starting to make good movies and shows, this film.As I said at the beginning we are dealing with a very meticulous film, locations and costumes I've loved, I've tried to remove all possible faults and only I found Verónica Sánchez skirt was crooked in a sequence, but it is otherwise a totally successful and well documented costume. (Congratulations Lena Mossum).Absolutely recommended film, I think that it is the very best you are going to see this year in the Spanish scene.</body>
</review>
