<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="La gran estafa" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Themes throughout almost two-hour film endless escape in the great scam. The overall result is very disappointing.</summary>
	<body>A film called the price of truth was released in 2003. It chronicled the experiences of a young journalist working for The New Republic that had the ability to get the best stories. Unfortunately none of those brilliant articles were real and he had invented them even to falsify the documentation that had been provided as evidence. Sthephen Glass, which was his real name was fired and somewhat later published a book about the history that led to the scandal.I love movies about writers and journalists. Perhaps because they often have interesting to say things and quite committed reflections on any topical issue self-respecting. If this one to the fascination that awaken characters as Howard Hughes (for those who have a tendency to forget already took a biography film recently in the hands of Scorsese with the Aviator) the truth is that the combination promises to be explosive.In this case is Clifford Irving who deceives in full decade of I 70 to the American publishing industry promising an authorized biography of the most sought-after character of the time. From the moment in which accepts the custom is forced to distort and lie to save face in authentic and grotesque attempts to not be discovered.The film directed by Lasse Hallström and starring Richard Gere. I never liked much this actor from the eighties is weak (in the most literal sense of the word) and that lacks charisma inside and outside of the screen that remains much effectiveness to a character that should be able to deceive with their words to Middle America. Comparison with the previous aforementioned tape is perhaps very negative for the great scam for while one opts for an effective and concise footage in this escape themes throughout almost two hours on end. The overall result is very disappointing.</body>
</review>
