<review author="J-rules" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What have you done to John McLane? My face of outrage out of the room was Championship to see how it can be to destroy a mythical character in 2 hours of film.</summary>
	<body>At least, that have done so perfectly, and but watch as the adventure can be described to great stretches more grossing inversomilmente in the series.McLane is a victim of a new digital era, in which there is must ensure at all costs that the movie is naif and chic (with the damn blue and green filters of Wiseman), where you have to have a script superfluous, technological and unnecessary to fill footage; where the bad have to be plain and totally deadpan; and where McLane has to spend half movie going from one place to another, and where be denied at all times the function for which was invented, i.e. to fight, getting dirty and say many tacos. Of the Nakatomi McLane is well little in this delivery is only a mirage of what one day became, in which he succumbs to Hollywood and clear, can no longer be a hero that smoke and insults all living being, but that it must be thin and delicate, and by every damn we have to hear four silly little girlanything characteristic of the McLane's lifetime. In addition, with so many shades of green and blue, disappeared us the greasy and dirty McLane, which makes load throughout the film of a tontaina such as Tim Long, making freaki for pc's, although it seems that it has escaped the your American Pie or Transformers seeing humor that spends.Above, McLane is no longer human, only is a super-polícia de plastic, which comes out unscathed incredible situations (this was normal), and which is not even a scratch!, only small scratches, nothing of blood and more blood.In addition, no scene of action is already quite credible, why if one is dedicated to bring each scene shown at the end, at the end the viewer becomes insensitive to such explosion and left really believe in the film. Clear, example the versus between the F-30 and the truck. (Much ado about nothing)But worst of all, is that Willis must face the evil more deadpan, dull, and least credible of all the series, Timothy Olyohant a.k.a. Soso-man. Which it causes the same effect that kill his girlfriend, to earn the Alarcón de la Torre of penalty in the last minute. The rest is also highly worthy of criticism, but in the meantime nonsense, passes very well unnoticed. Script loose and absurd, incredible situations, slow pace for a movie of action, Wiseman only succeeds in putting the camera, why the rest is wrong, it only saves Maggie Q and halfway, and so an endless number of things more &hellip; but above all, what you have missed more than less in the movie has been the tensionsomeone can tell me that they have made with her, why I have not seen anywhere.Finally, only say that if he is called, for example, Super-polícia, would have a pass as a movie action and entertainment, but as they are called La jungle &hellip;, this pass disappears, and therefore becomes a zero on the left.And as I read in a blog: "the difference between (I) the jungle 4.0 BOURNE ULTIMATUM., is that BOURNE BOURNE, and MCLANE is A poly lost in the midst of so much nonsense VIDEOCLIPERA"</body>
</review>
