<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Shootem up" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Everything happens in frenetic way, out of breath from which swallow his grateful footage. It happens fast and forget even better. Again the man.</summary>
	<body>Ago because while political correctness are inoculated in the bowels of the contemporary cinema, strengthening the enthronement of standardised characters which, without calling into question any social prototype, our evenings of film make more enjoyable. But authors like Tarantino and Rodriguez managed to attract the attention of the specialized public and producing skeptics, making it possible to unite political incorrectness and artistic quality (of course, ensuring success in box office without pools or sibyls). Thus the naïve macarrismo, announcement of colony macho-ismo and wild virtual hemoglobin choreography sold with relative ease in products like this that touches us.The figure of the hero honored in the films of yesteryear, the eighties sensitive cynic, the elegant and ligón 007 (with pardon of the Campbell Bond) that runs without disheveled, all leave step Clive Owen, the male that like all (and all). Lancôme has seen Reef that supposed to put this face (carved with mud) on his signature. You know that times ahead duplicated his wise cynicism, leaving everything as it is, but allowing aesthetic macho-ismo and defense of the trigger helpings licenses. How take one Miss Harry, although it does not wash! How much!Shoot ' Em Up is an effective metallic cosmetic product, around the figure of Mr Smith (all can be Smith, in a first-person game), an impersonal intelligent and hyperactive assassin to kill dozens of undesirable thugs under the command of his antagonist, a Paul Giamatti funny (which not graceful) in his role as bad, overwhelmed family guy, and custom pistolón. Everything happens in frenetic way, out of breath from which swallow his grateful footage (86 minutes). Characters, cartoons in the service of such action: the hard lanky (to the McClane), sensitive devorahombres (a pneumatic Bellucci, which puts to the service of who wants her breasts of Circe), the sympathetic villain, the props of corpses sown shamelessly beyond where treads do hero?, omnipresent, loud music in the moments of orgy testosterónica, choreographed to the John Woo.En endgo and see. It happens fast and forget even better.</body>
</review>
