<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Poseidon" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is as if we now put to make semiotics with the song of the summer and find three feet to a simple cat. Poseidon is the cat of the summer. The fat cat going to box.</summary>
	<body>There are some strict mood and severe step that cinephiles not transije with products like this because they abound in deception and perhaps are they escoran in excess, and very deliberately, of artistic values. The subgenre of naval disaster has not given remarkable titles in the history of the cinema and Wolfgang Petersen has not done much for bending the rule. Poseidon water lost in the script, and not in the wave of I don't know how many meters that tomb. Little matter that there are actors as nor is it relevant that these actors have given a few phrases. There are currently twenty-minute verbal film and seventy (Luckily the footage is reasonable) special effects. And not bad, exactly. We have heard many times that the film lacks media caters ingenuity. The film is art and, occasionally, business. Or even business and few times, art. Lacking in artistic ambition, Poseidón sinks because you don't need to float to make box office. Requires a vitamin gruesomeness trailer several manifests where pasta producer him/her and not going more in effects. In this case, Poseidón reaches the acceptable average of artifice digital films without stridency. The deception is consented and far from being warning not to repeat such an experience again becomes seed generous future approaches to movies of the same kind, as scandalously commercial (and misaligned of strictly cinematic quality) products which are even excluded from the usual meat of some critics of current press viciously. It is as if we now put to make semiotics with the song of the summer and find three feet to a simple cat. Poseidon is the cat of the summer. The fat cat going to box. Film education, that there is also, like the book or the musical happens to see these clunkers when one has, what was I, acne, or large eyes that open more to the Prodigy of studies and all those gadgets in the service of entertainment pure and simple. Then this friendly, undemanding membership should allow the pleasure of seeing other things. Adolescence, with their dizziness and its líbidos, like last seen one day the diligence of John Ford. Or M, the vampire of Dusseldorf, Fritz Lang. In end, film, art, knowledge, beauty. Evasion also, of course. Having said that, we perhaps allowing see Poseidón in a summer cinema, eating popcorn with one hand and pouring a liter of coke in the other. A good ambigú would give the ideal metaphysical counterpoint. Oh, except for the first two minutes of the film where a comprehensive and perfect camera sweeps the boat. The only thing real is the character that makes running for cover. In fact, we already knew, is merit infographic.</body>
</review>
