<review author="José A. Peig" title="En la ciudad" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The splendid script allows you to dive into the world of feelings with great versatility, real characters as life itself who at all times follow a development tailored to the millimeter.</summary>
	<body>Cesc Gay (2003) movie immerses us in a collective soul affected by atomization produced because of internal isolation, self-deception, and fear to reveal the intimate needs of relationship and affection in emotional circumstances. It represents the way of life of the middle class in Barcelona with a group of men and women whose sentimental becoming draws parallel to the time lines occurring differences in the reasons that affect the decisions and viewpoints that enrich the pulse of the narration. A film in which the silences and the thought of the hidden heart behind them has his choral vocals inspired by the everyday reality of today's society. The words lie or say really.The society of the middle classes. The story and the concise display of each scenario puts the emphasis on the uses and customs of a specific social stratum, characterized by the extent and dynamics of social relations held in a conventional and accommodative life mode; work (liberal professions, mainly), sofa, bed, cafes, restaurants and parties. Over all the footage we see characters that, apparently, cannot avoid being prisoners of that flow of conventions which leads them to judge lecturing about the intimate life of others, while continuing to hide own deficiencies. Thus, is a human set wrapped by stability and wealth in the material order, but dysfunctional and vacuum in the aspects of spiritual and personal development. The emotional life is the agonizing palpitation calling loudly for an examination of conscience. Film, therefore, markedly sociological, so frequent in the Spanish cinema, whose thesis does not go beyond a budget of common knowledge nowadays.Well, the splendid script lets dive into this world of feelings with great versatility, real characters as life itself who at all times follow a development tailored to the millimetre, according to a pattern defined from the beginning until the end of the narrative.It is effective to structure the progression of the collective drama based on a succession of sequences showing - of a segmented way - the life of each one of the characters, state until the final scene in which all converge around a round table, moment in which palpitation (tears) of a key character, turn on the feeling that, up to this sceneHe remained disguised. The last shared silence expresses and synthesizes altogether which in the previous development was atomized. A bitter end but also hopeful. Tears are a sign they all recognize, regardless of the specific and idiosyncratic reasons.</body>
</review>
