<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Ho Voglia Di Te" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It renounced the spirit of the Step of the first film to close a story that promised to be interesting and more mature than its predecessor, which achieved with a certain dignity until you reach the last quarter of an hour of footage.</summary>
	<body>They say that second parts were never good. Be a continuation does not have to necessarily mean that it is bad, but in this case is to implement less. Ho Voglia Di Te takes place a couple of years after the events narrated in Tre Metri Sopra Il Cielo when Step returns from United States and is reunited with his friends, enemies, and ghosts of the past by those who fled the country. It also has as origin the Maccio literary writing while in this case is more evil than an asset. He soon meets a mysterious girl that starts a relationship while he tries to fix his life putting your goals in order, found a job and starts an adult life that has been postponed for years. The misfortune of Ho Voglia Di Te is undoubtedly its forced, forced and abrupt more complacent than satisfactory outcome. He renounced the spirit of the Step of the first film and fits in an aburguesada fairly mediocre solution to close a story that promised to be interesting and more mature than its predecessor and which get some dignity until you reach the last quarter of an hour of footage with this "taken from the manga twist" that could have been saved with a.With the new director disappears the voiceover of the radio replacing with a perfect soundtrack with the names of the Italian song today and also resigns to the crazed of motorbike racing to put in place proper camera and levels little risky. Indeed if something peca is little ambitious already that with his characters players that had already captivated to the public could have put more meat in the grill. DATA on the película:fecha of Italy premiere: 9 March 2007No has been dubbed into Spanish or released in our country.It is the continuation of Tre Metri Sopra Il Cielo</body>
</review>
