<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="The Fall" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It reflects here on the creation of a fiction and its effect in reality, about the power of imagination and innocence as the best of medicines. Fair winner in Sitges 2007.</summary>
	<body>If the cell, película-promoción - video clip of Jennifer Lopez (that great actress) the good of Tarsem Singh stuck bump, its new and colorful The Fall not followed the steps and succeeds in stopping at the end of the cliff to observe in his Majesty and contemplate the remains of his previous film with derision, and in addition, win the award for best film at the Sitges Festival Fantàstic section 2007.Es certain that The fall is somewhat pompous and over-elaborate, but Singh this time has bundled the backpack and be self-financed the joke to give luster to a bittersweet story, booting a performance to the two main characters that win you the megalomaniac aspirations of the director. Fundamentally, the film features two bullets of gold into the Chamber, and other silver completing the charger. Namely, the gold are, on the one hand, the exceptional photography and the explosion of textures and colours that give off every one of their planes, starting with the moment initial black-and-white a crisp, frozen in time, and all of the Visual subtleties that lie ahead, following the translation of natural landscapes full of life and almost co-stars, and ending with the dazzling composition of each of the frames, almost carefully sculpted to chisel to the delight of the spectators. The other bullet of gold, the emotional interpretation of Romanian girls Catinca Untaru, who seems to not know that it is being filmed and is delivered in body and soul to the history and forms an anthological interpretive Duet with Lee Pace. Silver are perhaps the fable that is us told, rich in details and profuse in content and the idea of connectivity between cultures that transpires from it. The action takes place in a Los Angeles hospital in the 1920s. In it, an Indian girl recovering from a broken arm meets a depressed and vengeful specialist of film that just having an accident in one of his movies. Then develops between them a special relationship, a Covenant whereby the specialist the girl tells a story to change that morphine from the clinic, this brings to put an end to his life. It is then when we witness the story of six heroes through the children's eyes of Catinca Untaru (an African slave, the own Lee Pace as a kind of warrior of the mask, an anarchist bombs and pyrotechnics specialist, a shaman rastafari with special skills for war, a picturesque Charles Darwin and an Indian Prince), seeking revenge for grievances Mr hatred has caused them. The desperation of the Narrator makes the tale to acquire defeatists dyes, but the girl not shall be expired and will enter into a dialectic battle with Lee Pace to snatch the end of the story and at the same time to save her life. Here reflects on the creation of a fiction and its effect in reality, about the power of imagination and innocence as the best of medicines, of how all deserve us a second chance when they leave us lying in the ditch. Perhaps it sounds like watered-down and pastiche of easy emotions but sometimes it's good to be carried away by the look of a girl and for his kindness, although those attending the press room where announced that the Fall was the winning film of the festival silbaran timidly to see that the award-winning did not meet the classic canons of the fantasy or horror. I thought very good choice. That did not seem so good was to award for best actress was take him Manuela Velasco for his portrayal in Rec. Catinca Untaru with five year old gives thousand turns. And if none of this convinces you, raise you viewing of The fall as a virtual tour of almost half the world (filmed in 23 countries) with images that has happened never filmed nor the best makers of National Geographic, or as an object lesson of which feel Chair in the difficult art of build a storygood or not, but emotional in the best sense of the word. All a finding this The Fall. Let us hope that Tarsem Singh not recruited for his new film to Enrique Iglesias, and is limit to produce video clips. Mr Singh, every thing on your site.</body>
</review>
