<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="The Last Kiss" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Complicated is that as good as L'Ultimo Bacio raw can get both losing the essence, the grace and the balance of a brilliant story about fear of maturity.</summary>
	<body>Complicated is that with a subject takes precedence as good as L &#39; Ultimo Bacio can get both losing the essence, the grace and the balance of a brilliant story about fear of maturity.Tony Goldwyn simply uses the usual system used by United States to make the perfect remake of foreign films: copy and paste. But in The Last Kiss happens something very funny in this process, get that in exactly the same duration of footage have 40% of the story rather less gracefully. Analyzing coldly that footage which is subtracted to the history of friendship and principles of each pair will be directly gag comedians irrelevant based on the essence of drama who in reality were trying to tell. (Note, though that Filmax puts on its tab (which is a comedy is a lie)Michael, the protagonist who is trapped to find out that he is going to have a baby, the flight can come from the hand of a young woman who knows at the wedding of a friend. While he gets fully into their new relationship and problems of ocultár his girlfriend friends are tucked into the same necessities trying to deal with their own fears to grow with more or less dignity.Zach Braff is quite unsatisfactory and even his relationship with a University (eliminating the tension of what they means for your relationship and even shortening the original age difference) just know seems taken from a Sitcom. In fact the quality of the young American actors that seem to come from American Pie is very disappointing. The script has been fairly cut and they have even dared to change the magnificent outcome of the original tape that somehow was the magic of the original film. It was Paul Haggis, writer of "Million Dollar Baby" which has perpetrated this blasphemy of the tijeretazo.In summary, neither fu fa.</body>
</review>
