<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="El último beso" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Prejudices to see Italian cinema and the fact become popular after the remake can do you some damage although it may be a good time to give you the opportunity to also.</summary>
	<body>We are older. Carlo does not want to assume it, and is a shame because his girlfriend that he hoped a child has quite clear, also it seems to see the light of his mother who decides to finally take the step of leaving her husband. But Carlo still decide with their increasingly large Peter Pan complex. Just have to see to his friends: a fairly bitter married by his wife and his son, an addict to the casual encounters and the last is obsessed with his ex who hates his job and whose father is on the deathbed. At the wedding of another friend realize their problems and some events just detonating their need for change in the form of a lovely Lolita teen love, choosing a trip into the unknown together with the friends of a lifetime or make decisions that can affect an entire family. Some discover that they want to remain kids, others decide that they were not ready to stop being so although they thought and any that will always remain so. I could not tell which of the characters that populate L'Ultimo Bacio is that has come over me. Perhaps for that share the age and the spirit of these friends there is a seamless connection with most of the feelings and fears reflected in the tape. The script is simply brilliant talks, even the most dramatic, rozan perfection. What is normal in a movie with such choral claim makes one of the cores of the story more boring or simply less interesting but this stone is saved to perfection. When it seems that we sobreponemos the visual impact of a scene (there really are dramatic) or a decision of a character that is waiting around the corner.The actors reach a State of absolute grace. The scenes with discussions (believe me there are a few) they deserve to see and would probably not work so effectively if not thanks to them. The youngster Martina Stella and Stefano Accorsi emit a chemical that is appreciated on the screen. Do not fool you, this is a drama film with a romantic touch, there is no rest for the humor because we all know that in some ways love is a drama or would not be realistic or interesting.Impressive the end, an outcome that will delight any lover of good cinema with a magnificent reflections that obviously were not respected in its American remake so if you've seen the latter forget everything and view this jewel of contemporary cinema without prejudice and I assure you that there will be two hours well invested.DATA of the película:Estrenada in Spain (therefore you can find easily in Spanish) Spain release: 2 July later 2004Remake of the American The Last Kiss</body>
</review>
