<review author="Juan Manuel" title="Cariño, estoy hecho un perro" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Highly recommended choice for going to the cinema and join the smile of children. Don't worry if this is not the movie you have chosen, leave that their children are that carry you.</summary>
	<body>Based on a success of real factory 1959 live action Disney comes to our screens a remake of this family comedy. Love'm made a dog, starring Tim Allen, Kristin Davis, Danny Glover and Robert Downey Jr. The film tells the story of a lawyer that absorbed by his work away each time that she wants to and that feels every day abandoned family. This story also is involved a dog of great longevity that accidentally transferred you to the character of Tim Allen, the ability to take his canine form. This is the starting point of a hilarious comedy highly recommended to do with children. The film has all the elements of the family comedy Disney. A father who is no longer in the family wave, and that each day that passes is more and more absent from the small events of the day to day of their family, a mother that is not the way of doing her husband back to the man who fell in love with, and a couple of teenage rebels who arealong with the shift, the trigger for a 180º turn animal have as a result the expected happy ending to which we are accustomed the films of this genre. As it could not be otherwise, a movie Disney self-respecting must have some "bad" they are to rise to the occasion, very evil, nor very edulcorados that if they are to have that Nice and tontorrón touch have the evil Disney characters, therefore a great Robert Downey Jr. assumes the role of the scientist evil itself which is a great actor fluently. The film gives a succession of gags, most of them concerning the film from the first minutes of footage from the film starring Tim Allen, who start out loud, way continued and sustained to an audience that is delivering over its 99 minutes of footage.It is a film designed to stop children imagination with the adventures of a dog friendly, understanding and great parents to find the solution to their difficulties and wool personal during the 99 minute film has us subject to the big screen. Disney characters have a personal approach that make children feel identified with them and which in turn succeed us, adults, connect with a relative ease with children internalized and slept once we went and that during the session he returned to us in contemplation of the smile of the nieces that we filmfor one, or the children of her own to others. A smile that we add almost with neglect because, while these characters are closest to those of the series of "honey, I shrunk the kids", that in the of "Mary Poppins", in addition have a special charm that makes we see the movie with pleasure.Tim Allen as an engine of the great películaEl actor, producer, and writer delivers your best festival of grimaces, gestures and expressions in a sympathetic interpretation direct heiress of best gestural humor of the silent film era. He bears much of the weight of a film that has one of its best moments in the appearances of the great actor. Especially noted are the scenes in court. There is where Allen offers a recital of gestures and expressions with which large and small break out laughing during the viewing of the film. Let us not lose sight a nice Chase in which the actor, literally running on all fours, stars in a persecution of the purest Disney style, with gardens full of people watering their plants, people always through impeding the persecution and a final auction that does not disappoint.In short and as a whole; "I love am made a dog" is a highly recommended choice for going to the cinema and join the smile of children. Don't worry if this is not the movie you have chosen, leave that their children are that carry you. The film will win you and you will see its rictus is relaxed and in a few minutes you are dominated by the smile and laughter enjoying almost equal to the smallest room.Word of one which already went through that.Until the next.</body>
</review>
