<review author="Jose Contreras" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The orphanage deserves to become one of those clichés that everyone agrees with only mention the title.</summary>
	<body>On one occasion, I screened "The sixth sense" in class and a student asked me why the psychologist could see others and them you did not see him. I realized that Shyamalan had shot for "Ghost" after spectators who accepted as natural a world of invisible dead is only seen by mediums as Whoopy Goldberg. So I told him to see "Ghost". There are films that mark a before and an after. And I think "The orphanage" deserves to go on that list. I believe that it deserves to become one of those clichés that everyone agrees with only mention the title. Shyamalan introduced the idea of the complexity in the genre of ghosts. Ghosts are not there only to terrorize us, have a history, want to let us listen, are, in short, one character. What "The orphanage" adds to this imaginary is the world of the ghosts is as a game in which we can only enter as we entered a game, noting the rules with absolute seriousness and olividando the rules of the real world while we are inside. Huizinga observed that the rules of the game, the space, the observation of laws which do not have to be the moral, the inviolability of those rules, the creation of a new order and costumes, were applicable to other things, as, for example, to religious ceremonies. Bayonne has realized that those rules are valid for children's superstitions, to the spirit world, and at the same time, to the threads that bind to the viewer with what happens inside a fiction. The son of the protagonist has an invisible friend that plays at all hours. Mother listens patiently to the fantasy of his son, but the father is concerned. A game to which the boy plays with his invisible friends is the hide things. When the child disappears the mother did not find anyone who can help you find it. You will need to search within itself. You will have to learn how to play if you want to see his son.</body>
</review>
