<review author="Cp" title="Promesas del Este" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It doesn't have a history of gangsters, but it is actually a good story, where there are gangsters.</summary>
	<body>It could start this comment with a question: does Te gusto A history of violence? If the answer is yes then do not hesitate to go see the new movie by Cronenberg. It is not just that the style is the same, including installation, photography and pace but we also have the same actor as the main character, Viggo Mortensen, and we return to enter into the criminal underworld.With another simple story, but by no means boring, Cronenberg allows continue the characters discover their motivations, looking for their way or trying to flee the same. Unlike in the previous film by the director, in this case there is no a main character that we continue constantly, but we are going jumping between two main lines. On the one hand, the driver Russian portrayed by Mortensen, and on the other, the London nurse, but also of Russian origin, played by Naomi Watts. We are participating in the important moments, which make progress the story or are important for the characters. Both actors are great in his role, but above all Mortensen is the weight of the film, with a role worthy of an Oscar, with scenes that we will remember long time, but above all with the impression that carried out of the room, that has filled the screen completely, even when simply this sitting reading a book (actually)(, a newspaper) with its vodka and its tobacco. This is not a politically correct film. There are tobacco, there is vodka, there are prostitutes, and in general you do what you want, what you want, but you have something good will and makeup your performances.There are great performances also secondary, although always hidden after Viggo Mortensen. Highlight for my taste to Armin Mueller-Stahl as the crime boss, who is able to view a grandfather likeable and good-natured when need you to, but it can also give a sense of danger, which makes his own son, played by Vincent Cassel back frightened and not be able to raise their voices. Everytime Mortensen and Mueller are together, everything revolves around the two, as the other characters a second plane that loses importance. I have read since some criticisms, that Cassell plays a somewhat ridiculous, but I disagree. For me, it is merit of the actor so clearly reflect the weak son of the great Chief, constantly falling into the ridiculous. It is not a bad performance, but precisely which does not distinguish the interpretation of the role that he has played. For me, the merit is the Director, having successful totally in the cast, putting last example, Naomi Watts, which may seem something sosa even, but for my plays perfectly to his nurse, which passes through a bad time in your life, as we learn from grounds in their family meals phrases and looking for desperate an objective, or that police specializing in Russian mafia that barely appears twice, counterpoint of the mafia Barber who also appears shortly, but that in both cases are vital to the story.Finally, we return to find the brand of manufactures a Cronenberg accustomed in his life prior to the blood and the toughest scenes, which is violence. As in his previous film, arises suddenly, is fast, is mortal and is very, very bloody. Nothing beautiful fighting and precise choreography. Here bout as you can, dirty and little effectively. The wounds are not a stain of blood under the shirt, but damage causing displeasure in all those who did not follow Cronenberg when horror films.Summary: It seems not a gangster story, but it is actually a good story, where there are gangster. Well directed, paused, but not slow, well chosen actors, notably Viggo Mortensen and his new brand of manufactures, realistic and bloody violence, not suitable for type hollywood fights fans.</body>
</review>
