<review author="JLO" title="Matanza" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do a hard but necessary, project done with dignity, showing the most painful sides of this country with erratic path to backtrack to the President and his failed phrase:?We are condemned... to success?.</summary>
	<body>Documentary film Argentine relates the follow-up during four years of several marginal families, in their struggle to achieve health, work, education and that was the germ of the piquetero social movement coinciding with the weak Government of NATO (and its visible head the President De La Rua), movement which took in check to the Government releasing the unfortunate events of December 2001. Divided into two distinct halves, a social and more attractive, and a second with a more political tinge and opens their eyes to those who look at things happen only by the newspapers and tv channels, usual Chronicle of our social situation in the province of Buenos Aires. Already from the titles (and with the right choice of the anthem by Charly García as Fund) in its first half, the four members of the documentary group Primero de Mayo (all brandishing the camera, almost always in hand) us excited with the testimonies of villagers stripped bare its faults of all kinds, both health and education materials showing solidarity between the small neighborhoods of the partido of La Matanza (more than 40) and to a lesser extent, his own mistakes without low blows, but perhaps (being the only thing questionable) a too complacent look toward them. The end (less attractive) focuses on the workers struggle and more than twenty days of roadblocks that kept in suspense so this people like Minister Bullrich and Governor Felipe Solá. Filmed entirely in video should be noted that there is no use of voice-over (common in a documentary resource), being residents who tell their stories making them so real pleasant and nearby, and also more queribles, focusing the story in only three or four people which improves both the narration to feel more closeness and empathy towards them, as for not dispersarce in the story. The approach and the stories of the protagonists between sad and melancholic, make us to know his love for the place, its projects to pure lung, his Union despite everything and overwhelming force that now up to politicians they know and fear. The duality of the title marks both the physical location of the facts narrated of the feeling that lets us the film about the future of all these people, excluded from a decent life both their own limitations and usual inaction of the politicians of the day. A hard but necessary, project done with dignity, showing the most painful sides of this country with erratic path to backtrack to the President and his failed phrase: "We're doomed". "a success". KILLING direction: Nicholas Batlle, Ruben Delgado, Fernando Menéndez, Emiliano Penelas duration: 73 minutes (Betacam SP, colour)</body>
</review>
