<review author="José A. Peig" title="Blade runner" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A whole risked that Ridley Scott managed to combine with harmony and great visual sense, reflecting a world from which emanate the loneliness and melancholy, moments close to the dreams and the expressionist stroke.</summary>
	<body>They were few critics that have failed to appreciate the difficulty Scott to tell a simple story with simplicity. On the basis of the appraisal on their day made by Diego Galán (diario El País, February 2, 1983), we again noted the imperative claims of the role of film critic as someone that, first and foremost, must have the capacity of understanding required more beyond appearances and judgments made lightly. Despite this, and curiously, consider that the statement of Galán is not entirely misguided, and partly explains why spent several years before Blade Runner took the plaudits.Firstly, he noted a feature of the film which, in the view of many critics, is the main defect and the most obvious. Blade Runner, indeed, tells a simple story, but at no time is that there are difficulties in a fluid narrative and a structured script so confined to expose what is essential. The dialogues are scarce, often the gesture, the look and the framing that draws the position of a character in solitude to live in a decadent world, have greater narrative relevance that the words, and this indicates that we we have a mainly visual film. Put another way, the continent is dominated on the content. It seems that Ridley Scott is more concerned with creating atmospheres and beauticians images than to develop the psychology of the characters, the relationship between them, and the background of the story. There where, apparently, there is an imbalance between form and substance, in fact, there is a perfect synchrony between scenario and staging, between the (concise despite his extravagance) visual space, with its cadences and rhythms, and the history of the main characters, which runs also rhythmic and pace slow, as a tear which is slowly falling, until the end.Broadly speaking, therefore the visual imagery executed by this filmmaker at the service of the poetics of the story, with the sadness and the loneliness that are themselves. It is at this point where can better understand the comment of Diego Galán, for whom the self-absorption of Scott would lead to excessive use of the flat long, visual density, the repetitive Word, the sluggishness that often manifest the development of sequences. All this hinders a story that - a suppose - could dispense with both contemplative shantytowns. Simplicity is always a couple virtue with the complexity. Why, despite their "flaws" film triumphs by the comprehensive existing conjunction between all parties. No embargo. why we think that dialogs are somewhat tasteless?. Indeed, except specific cases, and if the shortage of dialogues outside little, the words spoken by the characters (even the voiceover) not reveal much more than what the image expresses itself, especially in the scenes that describe the relationship between Deckard and Rachael. Do the test, remove the volume to the device and you will see that the expression of the eyes and gestures are sufficient to know what is brewing in the scene. This is called cinema in its purest form. The dialogues, in short, follow a concise scheme to the millimetre, an adjacent reinforcing - when the situation requires - the meaning of the image.Even the most celebrated statement, and that to a greater extent it has risen to the film to the category of myth and paradigm, we can serve to exemplify this trait: I have seen things that you could not even imagine. . The focus of the expressions of Rutger Hauer and Harrison Ford, the first sitting in a manner similar to the "Lotus posture" and the second defeated and surprised by the unexpected attitude of the rival, in the context of what has happened previously, more the symbolic element of the Dove flying free after the death of Nexus six, constitute the essential meaning of the passage: the exaltation of life through death accepted by the replicant. The Nexus six words are an ornament, an addition that embellishes an image already on its beautiful and narrative validity. We insist, remove the voice and check yourselves (but do not forget, if they can, to open the channel of the soundtrack, masterful musical composition by Vangelis that expresses all the tragic lyricism in each sequence). After Kubrick, Ridley Scott renewed the genre of science fiction to elevate it to a State worthy of Shakespeare and Nietzsche. Images from the start, refinery fires and a confusion of lights and sounds that are covered by an eye, look, see consciousness (and flow of feelings and emotions that that implies), fundamental leitmotif in the course of the film, along with the significance of remembrance. Life is memory, we are our memories. Memory, in this case, generated with the image of the photographs.We have already discussed the importance of the expressiveness of eyes over any dialogue. And it is that, in this film, the eyes are the heart of the characters and the universe represented. If consider six Nexus as the personification of the spirit of the work, the gaze of the whole remaining is at odds to the Messianic look and mystic quasi of Nexus, the eye that contains everything and which, in the end, said the merit and the sense of its existence on the fact of seeing: I have seen things that you... Therefore, the eye as a symbolic element (see also the OWL of Tyrell), life and personal wealth is built with the variety of sensations and Visual perceptions, idea very coherent with the richness of textures that Scott immerses us in a fascinating world full of contrasts, between the reverie and decay, synthesis of futurism, antiquity and tradition. Let's see: I've seen attack ships on fire more than Orion. I've seen shine rays (c) in the dark near the Tanhauser gate. . Here we see Nexus as the conscious look that has internalized his experience of the world to become soul, his way of loving the world and, hence, to life. If the love of Nexus for life exceeds the undefined and Deckard vacuum it is precisely, because the conscience of Nexus covers more extensions and depths.No one better that he knows that the fear of death is a powerful instrument of slavery, as no one in the film cries, in the way that he does, for his dead friends.This leads us to the Nexus rebellion against the creator, metaphor of the human condition. I've equipped with eyes to see the world, the ability to generate feelings to love him, but the time is insufficient. Give me eternal life. But the creator imposes its laws, and the rebel Angel decides to kill the creator destroying his undeserved ability to see. You are not worthy of your creation. After the huge lenses of glass eyes. The expression on the face of Nexus reveals his pain by the fact of life.As we see, there is much symbolism and many references to the Judeo-Christian mythology (not to mention nor those hands punched by "nails of Christ"). Perhaps in this aspect is where most deteriorates the work, by the excessive mysticism in a tale of science fiction that did not need to refer to the religious symbols so explicitly. And in another order of things, and related to an earlier comment, excess footage because of the renascence in the purely aesthetic intention represents a setback to the smooth and concise narrative. In any case, this aspect is not Resolutive by numerous variables hermeneutics which they influence their assessment, and, accordingly, we do not consider that you harm to all parties that, synthesized into a coherent whole, they have created a perfect work. The debate, without more is open. The sentimental relationship between Deckard and Rachael can also be a critical point in the story, it seems an element forced with the mere purpose of stress the psychological crossroads of Deckard. And that is the necessary role played by Rachael: the element that embodies or motivating to a greater extent the moral and emotional dilemma of the Hunter of droids.Blade Runner, also, as a synthesis of universes and cross-genres. Film Noir, science fiction, the western, the almost medieval Gothic in the fortress of Tyrell, a risky set but that Ridley Scott managed to combine with harmony and great visual sense, reflecting a world from which emanate the loneliness and melancholy, moments close to the dreams and the expressionist stroke. Too bad that she cannot live. But who lives?. Where find the line that separates the human of the cybernetic? If what matters is the conscience of see, love and remember, some sense of the world and the rules of the game that Deckard has been forced to play? Isn't he a replicant?. We are Replicants until we have shown that we are human.All those moments will be lost in time, like tears in the rain. It is time to die.</body>
</review>
