<review author="Silvia" title="En la tiniebla" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The overall impression that leaves the movie is like a coffee decaffeinated, not very satisfactory, but not entirely unpleasant.</summary>
	<body>The darkness is, despite what the title might suggest, a thriller tinged dramatic (or sensibleros if you want to) film, a tale of ghosts with a dramatic tone, rather than a horror film. The new film by Craig Rosenberg brings us again, after some time without appearing on screen, Demi Moore, who was in a not too distant past, one of the highest paid actresses of the film industry.The successful life of the character of Demmi Moore writer is truncated after the death of his son. From the rugged death of the child - which the mother feels deeply guilty - the marriage of Rachel is broken and his creativity as a writer disappears, so it is forced to move to a solo spot to try to regain his inspiration and his emotional stability. The writer is going to live in a lonely House in the farther from Wales, in the island of Ynys Landwynn tip. A place of wild beauty, with long beaches and a lighthouse that is particularly important. There Rachel begins to experience chilling visions of his son, and begins a romance with its nearest neighbour, Angus McCulloch (Jamie Edgell), a lighthouse keeper who lives on a small island in front of the House. The visions appear more frequently and there are all kinds of events that no one else can see (apart from the Madwoman of the people).The argument is fraught with topics as the the man/woman/family that moved to an abandoned house and begins to perceive signals of ghosts. The film is unoriginal, but manages to stay in tension with some scares. Constant plot turns that manage to disassemble the hypotheses or theories that can make the viewer with regard to the course of events occur along the script. Especially, to half of the tape, the argument changes radically in a way that can be considered something forced but also him away a little of the typical outcomes of this genre of movies. Thus the overall impression that leaves the movie is like a coffee decaffeinated, not very satisfactory, but not entirely unpleasant.Recommended for those who would like to receive signals from the more beyond. And is that you as says in one scene the lover of the writer: "Can that the dead lend more than less than us to them".</body>
</review>
