<review author="Bruji" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The directorial debut of Jota Bayonne, alternating sequences achieved absolute master of film with those of an expert filmmaker videoclipero. A clear example in which a virtually perfect script aspires to masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>So far, there is much what we learned in the field of terror. Final destination, for example, was in charge of claiming that the plans outlined by the death are difficult to Dodge. House on Haunted Hill noted how the status of one of the protagonists, maintained secret, knew to influence the course of events. Mythical titles as the entity or Poltergeist showed that, in his day, thought us of science fiction: the possibility not only to detect, but also to measure with sophisticated instruments the alleged presence of other dimensions. The Lair, for its part, made understand that the facts that produce fear in adults come often from child's play. And while thirteen ghosts pursues the piece that is missing; The others, the last step or Amityville recall that the great mysteries remain always hidden in attics, basements and sheds... or at the end of corridors endless, as it warned Kubrick on the shining. On the basis of these premises, between the friends of fear, an obvious question arises. Would the creation of a new story that, fleeing from the evils of contemporary cinema, regardless of material of offal and the abuse of sound effects to scare, was able to shake the viewer be possible?. Yes-- is in the script selected by the Sundance Institute, in origin, giving rise to a short called I know that you're there, and ended by calling the attention of producer Guillermo del Toro. Shot on sets of Pharaonic dimensions in the purest style of the classic Hollywood, the orphanage draws on a multitude of predetermined concepts of gender to give shape to an intense drama. All of this is treated with an extreme meticulousness that away her of plagiarism and the attractive temptation of the tribute. Don't talk about a typical horror film, although small hands that the role of the walls start to step to the initial credit titles already produced concern. The script by Sergio g. Sánchez, as it has come to the screen, presents two fissures unforgivable, if we take into account that this was revised and perfected for a year and a half. The first of them kicks off the agonising dramatic load of the plot, ignores the basic recommendations of the Spanish Ministry of Social Welfare and contradicts both the present and the past of the protagonist with his partner. The second should be sought in the police files created on own account. However, his greatness lies in that both go unnoticed in a hypnotic and enveloping, history that deprived of the Faculty of thinking and banishes the sense of deception. The central axis of the argument, by itself alone, is so powerful and impressive, as capable of feeding real fears that calan in the mood and remain in the memory of the Viewer; leaving the film, difficult it will be repair in its shortcomings, and liberating exhale a sigh of relief, because it was not even a nightmare, just a good movie that disrupts the soul. Now good to repair in the execution of the script-after praise the meticulous production design and the exquisite art direction of Joseph Rosell - the set ends not convincing; still, perhaps attributable this unpleasant impression to the address of a novel technical team. While the soundtrack remains in a flat second discrete; the Assembly, undoubtedly correct, not you appreciated or a single virguería that makes it worthy of mention, reaching a photograph that, at no time, reaches the height of the product. The director, for his part, alternates achieved sequences of absolute master of film with those of a video-clip, the latter corresponding to the filming taking place in open spaces. It won't be easy to forget the sway of the camera in the English hideaway with adult Laura, nor the creation of contaminated passages of a rarefied atmosphere from the best classic horror, nor memorable frames that show close-ups of a brilliant performance, nor the tenderness of two looks intersect with a piano. Unfortunately, they are not easy to forget the shots to the ground, desencuadrados frames nor you retimes them beach. This irregularity reaches to the heart of the orphanage, Belén Rueda, who fails to establish any chemical with Fernando Cayo nor with the young Prince Roger, brilliant in all interventions. A character who, as the woman that gives life, knows traced from nothing all of the mock actress with the face of panic after the cry of action!, to the aspect that should have the fortitude if it decided to personify it. To configure the rest of the cast, the direction of strong bet casting by the secondary actors, with the priceless stage presence of Geraldine Chaplin and the invaluable collaboration of a great Lady of Catalan Theatre, Montserrat Carulla. In all cases, the orphanage is a major success of the Spanish film, insofar as it provides a clear and concise about the type of film response that the public wants to see and why pay (an important fact) in the halls of projection (those who might be closed). The kind of film which reconciles to critique and masses, perhaps to contain an undeniable American touch that both like the viewer and so little patriotic filmmakers. And is the first still believe that you to get lost in "the most personal film of..""there will always be time, or not." Acclaimed by European critics, acquired by the American industry, unbeatable springboard of a rookie team; for the obsessive fixation of this servant by the "flashbacks", it will always be the essential reference that leads to the magisterial resolution of a plot with only three flashes. Fast. Decisive. Sharp. One, two, three, touches the wall!.</body>
</review>
