<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Joven Jane Austen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The young Jane Austen is an elegant film, with a great taste, which does not fall into the romantic drama or biopic conventions.</summary>
	<body>One of the authors whose novels have been adapted to the big screen on more occasions is the British Jane Austen. For many, the best author in the English language from William Shakespeare, and for others, a simple writer of early 19th century romantic serials. So it is not surprising that a film that portrayed his life is controversial by nature, and even if the lead actress is American.But with the young Jane Austen, his director Julian Jarrold does not sign a current biopic nor made up the type of argument that might be expected. Jarrold flees from the conventions, and only focuses on the years in which Jane Austen was just a girl who dreamed of becoming a writer. It is counting its fight against established social standards and the romance with a young Irish man, relationship that marked the literary work of Austen. As a result, Jarrold may show how the author's own experiences influenced his later work, introducing the tape some passages of his most popular novels. This narrated with great elegance, without losing the good taste or a true classic aftertaste of more intoxicating. Despite their almost two-hour, history is not heavy or dull, rather than flying with a pace that allows to enjoy each scene with calm, without slowness or haste. Technically, the tape has an impeccable invoice, since late 18th century environment is recreated to perfection. But all this would have lost if not for the fabulous interpretive staff of the film. Anne Hathaway outboard his interpretation of an insecure and inexperienced Jane Austen, giving it a great humanity and tenderness through a sober and content work. James McAvoy also performs a brilliant interpretation of a rogue Hustler with, Yes, a Fund of goodness and nobility. And what about actors such as James Cromwell and Maggie Smith.La young Jane Austen is an elegant film, with a great taste, which does not fall into the romantic drama or biopic conventions. In addition, it allows to enjoy the work of Anne Hathaway and James McAvoy, two young performers will give much to talk about in the future.</body>
</review>
