<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Barcelona (Un Mapa)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Barcelona (A map) is a dissertation failed on modern life in a big city, but that allows to enjoy the performances of actors of the stature of Josep Maria Pou, Núria Espert, Rosa María Sardà and María Botto</summary>
	<body>There are few filmmakers around the world that are able to offer a new movie every year, and no doubt the clearest example and known is that of Woody Allen. But in the Spanish film we also have a filmmaker capable of carrying out a feat worthy of the Hercules himself. It's the Barcelona director Ventura Pons, which in 2007 was already premiered La life abysmal, and now offers us his new work, Barcelona (A map).Six characters, contemporary Archetypes of urban solitude, are found in an old flat in Barcelona's Eixample. An old couple, her brother and three realquilados, a woman who teaches French, a guard and a pregnant Argentine girl. All of this is divided into five big scenes, each of them being a conversation between two characters. Barcelona (A map), is a film whose only asset is their characters, their feelings and emotions, which, although it has great appeal, is also equally dangerous if you don't have a solid and occasionally brilliant screenplay as a backup. And unfortunately, this happens to new work by Ventura Pons, which is based on a script sometimes something flimsy that enters nonsensical ramblings and nonsense about life in a big city problems. In justice, it must be said that there are some great scenes that outperforms the rest, and is the star Josep Maria Pou and María Botto. The weaker of all is that has as protagonists to Núria Espert and Paul Derqui.Barcelona (A map) is a dissertation failed on modern life in a big city, but that allows to enjoy the performances of actors of the stature of Josep Maria Pou, Núria Espert, Rosa María Sardà and María Botto. Only to see the duel between Pou and the Sardà it is worth going to see the new film by Ventura Pons.</body>
</review>
