<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Secretos cantados" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film of characters in those that the French do frequently and which have reached a skill that makes them quite reliable.</summary>
	<body>This summer came to our screens a new recent success of French cinema. It's "Secrets Sung" (Les Héros de la famille) Thierry Klifa. I can not avoid mentioning that the allegedly ingenious translation of the original title of the film does not only give me one more argument, if needed me, in my defense of the original version.Leaving aside that detail, we are dealing with a film of characters in those that the French do frequently and which have reached a skill that makes them quite reliable when deciding to go to the cinema.The story revolves around a heritage whose most prized asset is a place called "The Blue Parrot". To its around it will link the characters in the film.The truth is that the initial situation could have given more, although the characters are interesting and well interpreted by a set of actors and actresses good of presence and charisma. They walk across the screen, and it is a pleasure to see them, Catherine Deneuve, Emmanuelle Béart, Gérard Lanvin and Miou-Miou, to mention the most important.By the way, say that I find it difficult to see Emmanuelle Béart as a successful singer with future ahead as he whispers rather than sings. A detail that was intended to blur with the fascination that follows the actress and achieved, although partially.The screenplay, written by Christopher Thompson is and quite right, you want to build a intrigue non-existent and meaningless, thus creating a confusion in the relationships of the characters.Still, glad see a film based on an interesting script despite their defectillos, with attractive characters and performed with correction. If the average film which premieres (or becomes) in Spain so, could give us with a song in the teeth.Final assessment of moonfleet: 6 out of 10.</body>
</review>
