<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="El Orfanato" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do not know if?The orphanage? You'll end up representing us in the final phase of the Oscars, but already you are booting applause by half the world, and making national viewers prefer for a movie Spanish, and that is an achievement.</summary>
	<body>Juan Antonio Bayona made his debut in the feature film in the best possible way, with success among critics and public. Seconded and supported by Guillermo del Toro, "The orphanage" presents a story which is known to us: mother in a gigantic House of field, where there are strange and with children of medium. Yes, it may seem very typical, but the success of Bayonne and yours, is that they make us believe what we are seeing and identifying us with its protagonist, Bethlehem Rueda.La actress Gets the weight of the film on his shoulders and get, not only not fall, but lift with her arms, that performs an interpretation that already sounds like one of the best of the year.The story has been written by Sergio g. Sánchez, and Bayonne has been transformed into images, leaves us wonderful prints at the same time as terrifying, that while not abuse of scares and shocks, there is more than one that will make viewers to vibrate in their seats.All aspects deserve to stand out, the set of the film has an impeccable invoice, but where to get win the public is with feelings that follow those actors. It should be special attention Roger Princep, Simon, who with little age manages to give freshness and naturalness to situations, and even more, to make us believe that the character of Belén Rueda has really lost his son and will strive to recover it.I don't know if "The orphanage" will end up representing us in the final phase of the Oscars, but either way, you are already booting applause by half the world, making national viewers prefer a film by Spanish, and that is something that as it stands the landscape, is an achievement.</body>
</review>
