<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Las 13 Rosas" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Las 13 Rosas is an extraordinary film, is a fact of the Civil war without complexes, and surely will help eradicate the fear to address similar stories in the film.</summary>
	<body>There is no more than read the newspapers or turn on the radio to check that sadly, in 2007 Spain talk about the Civil War, the dictatorship and the Francoist repression, is controversial. There is who is of the opinion that it is best not to mention the subject and forget, but who leaves aside the history is doomed to make the same mistakes of the past. And cinema, with few exceptions (Ay, Carmela!, the bicycles are for the summertime), barely spoke about the Civil War, of course excluding the pamphlets made during the dictatorship.Why a movie like Las 13 Rosas, who will be heavily attacked by political issues, is very necessary, and that it has a fact specific, unjust and atrocious, but do a great normally and without any kind of revanchism. Emilio Martínez-Lázaro offers a clean an act cruel, barbaric and tremendously unjust portrait: the execution of a group of young girls by their political ideas or have helped people with the same ideology. But the Madrid filmmaker is not only limited to make a prison and judicial Chronicle, but also reflects fear of the population of Madrid before the triumphal entry of the national troops. Between all this fear, moreover, are the old grudges, opportunists and profiteers seeking only their own benefit. All this reflects a Martínez-Lázaro which, demonstrating a great tact and delicacy, does not load the inks on the repression during the first hour of the film. The tone of the film goes up to approaching the arrests of the protagonists and his subsequent incarceration, until you reach a final filled with a great emotion and intensity. The effort to recreate that time has been Titanic, from the costumes to the digital effects all the technical aspects of Las 13 Rosas pass the examination with note. The cast of the film is simply spectacular, and even partly unfair, it is impossible to not overemphasize its trio protagonist, three of the Spanish stars of greater talent of his generation: Pilar López de Ayala, Marta Etura and Verónica Sánchez. Las 13 Rosas is an extraordinary film, is a fact of the Civil war without complexes, and surely will help eradicate the fear to address similar stories in the film. It is a film that claims of course and serves as a tribute to the memory of these young women who were victims of a brutal and unjust repression. And the day that a phrase as the previous stops be controversy in this country, we may say with Justice finally society has overcome the trauma of the Civil war and the dictatorship.</body>
</review>
