<review author="Kiko de España" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>From 100 to 0 in 50 minutes. Zombie does not dare from ecuador. A pity because the first half of the film (until that concentrated the original fifty eternal final minutes) made us hope for the best. But not.</summary>
	<body>It desencanta me the retromake of the Carpenter classic Zombie. Let's start with the beginning. The night of Halloween was a picture of gender which lasted for 90 minutes and Halloween is a product Dimension that lasts 20 minutes more. Up there, except for the product Dimension, more or less well.The problem that I find in the movie, always from my point of view (worship extreme Carpenter, Yes, but also much respect to Zombie and his two previous films) is so brutal partition to which it is subject.The first of the two parties focuses on the childhood White trash of Michael Myers, where is güarra to the picture. Zombie demystifies the spectrum approaching her every day between mascots about to be executed, abuse, ill-treatment and absolute absence of love and touch, only some MIME of a mother who tries to be him as best as possible but who works at a night club, who lives with a drunk son of a bitch and that is mocked by fellow school of his son. Already I say, regular characters (and actors) film of Zombie which appears will give the nail on the head with the invention. The director allowed the luxury of show us the origin of the mask and show us what is sensed in the prologue to the original movie: a crude and violent, killing cold, in charge of a demon that is nothing more than a child with many problems, both physical and psychological. Very well. Furthermore, the child with the adult mask gives a bad feeling that you cagas.Now is the turn of the second part of the movie, which is as the 90-minute Halloween Carpenter, but in 50 minutes and with that touch "as Dimension" as deja vu and so disappointing.If you bother to do more real evil for fifty minutes later is that it was not necessary, because the psychopath returns to be a supernatural being by magic, and as an example of the worst film shot by Zombie so far put the scene of the escape, poorly filmed, poorly raised and resolved in a way that can believe meI fail to see in no time. You even start to bother the use above the director gives his usual frozen and slow motions. Here Zombie not moved the original to zombilandia, is the head which fits the old story and I think that this is a problem if you are looking for give something personal to an alien history. To my still giving me more fear the Forsaken that Myers Zombie.Otro crime is the third Act, where spend most of the footage of wall on wall, wardrobe closet and scares to one hundred, coming to think that the "tributes" to the original (death nailing pardillo kid and the shroud)(, for example) are even forced and stuck with shoehorn.And also I am convinced the use of original film music because it is cold.Like the recent Sleuth, while in that Branagh you risk much more than Zombie here, it's an unnecessary and quite decaffeinated remake. Even so the movie is not a disaster thanks to the fifty minutes of "prologue" and despite this fashion so terrible and unnecessary to have three finals in the same film.</body>
</review>
