<review author="Kiko de España" title="Stuck" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Here, as in Dogville, the crappy is to understand that it might have you happened to you or what is worse, it can be that according to which circumstances you reactions in the same way. It is called amorality.</summary>
	<body>Despite having a career that defines the irregular term always keep in mind to a guy like Stuart Gordon. The director of re-animator and Dolls brings us the best of his films recent, superior King of the ants and Edmond, two interesting but much more unsuccessful than his penultimate proposal titles, the brutal and inspired by real events Stuck.Para to start highlight the casting, which is perfect and all the characters in the film are recognizable: young people with aspirations and bad head, malas compañías, painful labor reality, selfishness, hijoputismo &hellip; life itself.How to shoot does not vary too much from their jobs, with the camera on his shoulder, the best way to tell this story and put the viewer in the historiaTom (formidable, Stephen Rea) loses his job, his home and his dignity has no choice but to sleep on a bench in the Park because life, despite the fact that one always has the option of choosingIt is a shit that almost always gives more kicks than hugs. While trying to fall asleep the police advised that you get closer to a lodging for homeless people, which have no other way that access.Brandi (Mena Suvari, producer of the film) is a young nurse who works in a clinic and which probably, according to his boss, ends up in a short time as head of nurses. Brandi is romantically linked to Rashid, a dealer of three to the fourth that keeps her happy and her friend Tanya based on all kinds of drugs.To celebrate the possible rise they decide partying, although there has not been the news probably the plan would have been the same, and get into the pub on fashion to get pastis and take copazos.And as this is the real life (again, the film reads a real based on real events) the girl, all borrachuza and placed it, runs over Tom, leaving it embedded in the glass of the car. What makes the girl? Since throwing for House cagando centellas with poor Tom, alive and kicking almost there stuck.Since then the life of Brandi becomes a nightmare as raw as unnecessary (in turn) to avoid helping a poor Devil who only wants to go to the hospital.Here, as in Dogville, the crappy is to understand that it might have you happened to you or what is worse, it can be that according to which circumstances you reactions in the same way. It is called amorality. I guess that it is why get us loose laughter when the events are triggered and everything becomes, if possible, even worse and the only thing you have to do is take the car and go to your House.</body>
</review>
