<review author="J-rules" title="El Orfanato" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The orphanage is not anything that you have not seen already 50 times, and is not more than a rehash of many different movies. But as always, there are ways and ways to make the remake, and this is the outstanding!</summary>
	<body>Having jeto must be a degree, and Bayonne has done to perfection. But as explains that the best Spanish film of 2007, and one of the best of the last decade of the Spanish film, is a remix of as unforgettable as Poltergeist films or others, which is crowned with the end of Peter Pan i constantly lies in the excellent Belén Rueda.Bayona has done what only great managers or the ready can doi.e., take the best of other films, coordinate everything to perfection, and add some performances to get the hat.As the script only has to adapt to the situation, Bayonne can focus on the actions, which make that the basis is more solid than it already was good principle. And then it is when, after some very credible performances, appears the absolute protagonist of the film, Belén Rueda, which enrolls likewise that of the newsprint, which shows that the pressure is not a thing that goes with it. Although the weight of the film rests him fully, it is able to exit the screen and overshadow anyone who shares a flat with her. The rest of performances have remark, although Bethlehem leave shortly for the rest.The argument you know from memory, and there is no need say so, why at the end and all, and as I said earlier, lives of all the references of the genre, and therefore without knowing anything about it already know how it will pan out. Even with that, we have some saved surprises, and they are given with cuenta-gotas. The camera is always on your site and Bayonne is efficient and effective. The pace is appropriate and is very well accompanied by a voltage which can be cut with knife.I have little more to highlight of a film that you you know memory i that supplies the lack of originality, with some performances and a Belén Rueda of hangovers. Bayonne promises and we are sure that we will feel his name several times. Everything for end consolidated, undoubtedly the best film ESPANYOLA of 2007.</body>
</review>
