<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Los Cronocrímenes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>My first feeling at the end of the movie was the of seeing something good but that certainly still could have been much better.</summary>
	<body>My first feeling at the end of the movie was the of seeing something good but that certainly still could have been much better. Let me explain: is that a little sweet and sour taste after seeing a kind of version somewhat troubled and contained too much of the actual capacity and imagery of the always playful and talented director of the shortfilms "7: 35 in the morning" and "Clash". The Cronocrimenes could have been even more subversive, more exciting, more spectacular, bloodiest, more Disney, more fun, more frightening, and which already offers, at the same time, actually is a real blow to the Bureau and a notice that there is true intentions to change the direction of the Spanish film, expand the current boundaries of genres, influences, themes and intentions and making a film more interesting, entertaining and attractive. Vigalondo tells rightly a history of travel in time with one made daring, original and intelligent and with a good script as best weapon. Bet bravely by a dose of science fiction away from conventions, risking the most with a minimalist staging and different and very authentic in its purposes. But it is also true that it overlooks some important aspects that had been able to significantly enrich the result. We have a picture right, but obsessively focused on realism, in the naturalness in a mise en scene perhaps too spectacular, and supported in a direction of art which seems to try to find a look that touches even the ugliness and chaotic. The address is not particularly striking and the camera is not at any time draw attention to so the visual language this subject rather to the service of the action. Not a plot is constructed with sufficient space for the attainment of some particularly noteworthy performances. Some insurance will discuss if it has been good or not the decision to grant is likewise one of the important roles of the film. My personal view is that the decision was good if the intention was to get work as a professional actor, but I also wonder if no could be found in Spain to some other actor even better and more experienced than himself for that role. Even with this, Vigalondo complies as an actor and his character, no doubt, manages to create empathy. The character of Barbara Goenaga, I would have liked to know something more to be able to accompany a little better in their adventure throughout history. About Karra Alejalde is now in tastes, because it is a very peculiar actor which leads to love and hate in equal parts. To me, particularly, I think is right for the role because it gives a turbid and unhealthy depth to the character and enough realism to their most extreme actions.The theme of conflict, development and emotional developments of the characters and motivations of these are usually somewhat schematic in the movie, when all this, however, is in my opinion always needed to help maintain regularly enough interest and sustain the pace, even despite being a genre film.The characters are also very few and the temporary puzzle proposed in the plot is therefore limited to the few pieces with which the author is obliged has play, and this results in the ability to surprise view diminished and many of the actions that occur, sometimes happen merely to comply with the turns and the temporary trouble, causing previously. This makes the argument it something predictable at times. However, Vigalondo manages to create an intelligent network temporary who shoots and nimbly accelerates the pulse and the dramatic tension, especially in the final part and get control at all times the twists and the plot pirouettes closing in addition everything with admirable ingenuity. In addition, add that enigmatic Eugenio Mira music accompanies and rightly extols the atmosphere of mystery and tension the film proposes.The debut of Nacho Vigalondo is one bet authenticates, surprising, anárquica and a both kamikaze seen preferences and the General tastes of the public and also seen the current scene of the fatherland national industry. It is certainly a very special and highly recommended movie and I encourage you all to you try to enjoy it in the film and if this is possible, I hope that very soon. A different a different author's proposal and this already it is of itself always a pleasant news.</body>
</review>
