<review author="José A. Peig" title="Cuando el destino nos alcance" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If science fiction is a genre that allows exploring the concerns of mankind on a global scale, Soylent Green is an immortal piece directed by Richard Fleischer with sobriety.</summary>
	<body>Science fiction in the service of an apocalyptic thriller that plays with three basic ideas of great current relevance: climate change, overpopulation, and the monopoly of resources by a minority business. The permanence of his subjects, in reference to sociology and our present globalized consumption, is one of its core values, despite being a film designed on the basis of the emerging early 1970s environmentalism. If science fiction is a genre that allows exploring the concerns of mankind on a global scale, Soylent Green is an immortal piece directed by Richard Fleischer with sobriety. A solvent story that exposes a detective plot in an apocalyptic environment, thus comes to be a clear precedent of masterpieces such as Blade Runner, though, that Yes, the work of Fleischer not advantage the theme and setting of form so suggestive, as happens in the film by Ridley Scott. more than exploration and socio-economic reflectionthe film is his soul in the described relationship around the characters played by two icons of the cinema Hollywood and Charlton Heston, Edward g. Robinson, each of them representative of two times separated by a gap of destruction and imbalances on a planetary scale, which gives rise to an effective drama of opposites. Drama which is a sensible resolution at the time in which the central character shares the beauty of the old world with the old Sun, the last fraternal bond between two generations separated by time and cultural decline, being the old man the true driver of the great final revelation, a macabre idea that comes to be a picture of the situation in our days: even metaphorically, we are cattle of corporations that use our lives and our consciences for the benefit of the few. According to the heartbreaking final cry of a dying Charlton Heston, we also can say that our current state is maintained with the death of human beings living in the areas related to what we call "third world", since the death of ones - in a context of overpopulation and knowing that the planet has limited resources - allows that the minority of the rich world can continue to enjoy their privileges.As a result, the film hides a macabre allegory of the current situation. Replace "human corpses" by the benefit won by every human being condemned to die of starvation. Perhaps we need a voice to show us clearly that our system feeds on death. But it is also true, we tend to think that the planet has sufficient resources to supply the entire population, which is not true, or at least, not everyone could enjoy the standard of living in the so-called "welfare society". The film also focuses on this aspect to show how food quality and the only luxury are within reach of a few.</body>
</review>
