<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Killing America" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Disturbed vision of America deep, not overly inspired, but sincere. PECA of predictable, gets carried away by reasoning already learned in lots of similar tapes. Video store resource for afternoon rain at home. This is already something.</summary>
	<body>A desastrada children can mark a whole life. Said it Sigmund Freud and tried it in own meat Maculey Culkin and Drew Barrymore, Joselito and a friend of mine that still, to its thirty and peak years has not seen the light of wisdom and the sparkling of the sanity bombillitas. Killing America rests his disturbed breath on this evidence of manual of psychology. The story of the two brothers that fatigue secondary roads with the perseverance of the greedy psychopath of corpses is contaminated in a history of one nihilistic sediment more than evident, but we are not dealing with any Treaty of human behavior or Douglas Sirk is behind the camera. These times of relative and moral distress consent revisions of classic patterns atufadas by simple, obvious and legitimate way of doing box while shocked staff. I doubt very much that Killing America is a profitable experiment. It is a temperamental movie road, a telefilm of programmable quality at night, safe from mojigatas minds or spirits of weak Constitution, and not because the guts of their content offends or enroll with effrontery Al Gore so in fashion but because they are taken for granted by known for accepted, ways of living and behaviour are not sufficiently justified. The violence that the brothers protagonists not argues with enough weight. The flood of dead that are entailed footage unsettles at a point in which already not us affects another body or the way the murderers get rid of evidence and the feeling of guilt. There. Lasts, to their benefit, little: seventy minutes well taken. Tires against the stubborn collection of disasters that perlan those (few) minutes. The pilgrimage towards the nirvana of redemption has, in the final stretch, an ethereal descent, a foray into the epidermis of love, but until love acquires macabre letters and we are witnessing between the shock and the indifference, equally, the spectacle made in USA of the decline of their empire. Or is not what the title alludes? Them have not very clear: seems to me that stays one always halfway. With desire of seeing more and eager of not that this hint of deliberately avant-garde film ends, stop the player (Yes, has been already taken domestic meeting of video store) and go into the street to walk.</body>
</review>
