<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entertaining tape of adventures that he possesses the same virtues and suffers from the same defects than its predecessor.</summary>
	<body>I have been able to attend a special pass which will be, in all likelihood, the highest grossing film of the year worldwide: "Pirates of the Caribbean: the chest of the dead man" (do Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man? s Chest) of Gore Verbinsky.En the film continue attending, almost at the same point where we left them, the adventures featuring Captain Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp)Will Turner (Orlando Bloom) and Elisabeth Swann (Keira Knightley).I have to admit that during the first hour of projection I thought that we could be one of the jewels of the year. Because the film starts very well, with a lot of pace and a very fun; but unfortunately later things only get worse and the pace drops a bit. Sobran whole passages were not necessary at all, and once again, we have another case of confusion between the spectacular and the spectacular. To achieve an exciting duel to swords it is not necessary to place it at the top of a Ferris wheel, that is spectacular, what we need to do is roll it so it is exciting. But of course, it is much more difficult and would possibly make the film a product much more than "for all ages" intended by its managers, who do not seek anything else, no mistake, that raise the most money possible.Why is sometimes lost time in telling the story branches that do not contribute anything except a divertidilla fight or a comic situation (almost always something child), to the detriment of others who explained us better the motivations of the characters, and that would be more exciting some of its decisions. There are moments, dialogues and situations calling out more emotion but that they may not have either because some actors not can give it either because for that moment was exciting should have prepared for him beforehand. And as I said, that erode you commercial potential to the tape.I would also do some "slight" changes in the cast. First Keira Knightley is not the ideal actress to play an indomitable woman of adventurous spirit; It does not simply type. But even accepting that, it is unbelievable that a woman with that character was fell in love with a type with the cowardly aspect of Orlando Bloom (and that original version improves). Luckily to compensate for the acting balance we have people such as Stellan Skarsgård and Bill Nighy that despite working almost in anonymity due to makeup or special effects applied to his face, made interpretations over the appointed two protagonists.Now that I mention it I would say that the film is technically impeccable and very impressive would have to see here at end of season so we disagree to the oscar for best visual effects over the next year.Johnny Depp, a great interpretation capable of dramatic, comedic performances, it deserves special mention contained or exaggerated. An actor who works happy on a tightrope and carried out here again a great interpretation of one of its most popular characters. Without it everything else no sense. He is the comedy, he is the drama, he is the adventure. Jack Sparrow is the film.In short, for me, the film has the same virtues and suffers from the same defects than its predecessor. It's an entertaining tape of adventures that will make the delights of all kinds of audiences and to provide two and a half hours fun viewers, especially to the less demanding, that is no bad. However to those able to enjoy large tapes of adventures of all times it is possible pyrotechnics know you little.</body>
</review>
