<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Promesas del Este" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tremendous and extraordinary film by David Cronenberg. Film noir of the best invoice, tough, direct and uncompromising. And in only ninety-six minutes, which, for the times, is quite an achievement.</summary>
	<body>It had been but very well received on the festival circuit, so the expectation was high, not in vain, the previous RAID by David Cronenberg in the black genre, "A history of violence", turned out to be an undisputed masterpiece.With "Eastern promises", the veteran filmmaker repeated with the chameleonic Viggo Mortensen, referring in this noir which, personally, I love so much. But in this case, instead of traveling to the United States.UU. It does so to a theoretically multicultural London in that, however, as many and as varied cultures coexist, but without mixing or integrate with those around them. As the Russians, for example, in this film comprising a separate group, a mafia exclusive and inclusive, a family full of rituals, symbols, keys, and relationships of the most complex, dense and variegated. And therefore the subtitled VO of the Russian dialogues gives importance to one film postmodern, faithful reflection of the complicated globalized world in that live. "Promises of the East" in a masterly film which, on the basis of the discovery of an intimate diary, escarba in the miseries of a society corrupted to the bone marrow. And it does so without moralina, without be discursive, without being giving. Through a black as tar and rough like sandpaper paper history, Cronenberg film makes a shocking denunciation of trafficking of white and the hell that awaits so many Slavic youth who come to Western Europe convinced that will find paradise. And makes it more difficult to Cronenberg: denounce these facts through the simple tell one story, narrating events that make illuminate a truth that is shows crudely in the eyes, frame to frame, without speeches or proclamations, telar sentimentality or maniqueístas dulcificaciones.We have a story with many protagonists, represented by actors in State of grace. Starting with Viggo Mortensen, who a few days ago they were expelled from a London restaurant by the earmarks of Russian mafioso who had. That had gotten into the role, we will. A Naomi Watts radiant, but obscured by rain in London and in the darkness of the locations which the director has chosen to tell a story certainly grim and gloomy.It is Vincent Cassel, enfant terrible of French cinema, which outboard to the hysterical character of homosexual locked in a closet with doors of oak and steel, but, above all, is the sober, unsettling and terribly wonderful Armin Müller-Stahl, playing the godfather of the Zakone V Vory, the Russian Mafia. Perhaps the best of the film is the sequence in which the Watts is known for the first time. On the one hand, Bewitched. On the other hand. Note that something strange there's. And even so, he falls under the influence of the friendly old man who runs an ethnic restaurant cuisine delicious Russian dishes, that cares for his son and defends their cultural roots. Atracción-repulsión. Admiración-ASCO. As in the also impressive "The music box", that the subsidiary paternal dialectic that develops between the character played by Müller-Stahl and his daughter, a sensational Jessica Lange reached unusual levels of interest and excitement.And it is, of course, the sequence of the sauna, clear. We give the word to the Canadian director: "violence is violence..." It is always bloody. "When we are talking about violence, talk of human bodies, the destruction of human bodies and then what you have to show is that they are bodies against bodies." should be more explicit? Sensitive souls, rotate the face, with noticeable grimaces of repulsion. Garantizado.Tremenda and extraordinary film by David Cronenberg. Film noir of the best invoice, tough, direct and uncompromising. And in only ninety-six minutes, which, for the times, is quite an achievement.</body>
</review>
