<review author="Jack Torrance" title="El Orfanato" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A bet that from the outset it is little genuine, very deliberate and calculated and as an orphan of soul that should be sought in another type of orphanage. The films with absolutely nothing to say.</summary>
	<body>Enveloped by the now untouchable and immaculate signing of the irregular Guillermo del Toro, the orphanage has been receiving applause and praise for any festival where has been released. The tape is finally available to the public in any Center of the country. Bravo, that money that could go to the twelfth from stupidity of America finishes in national boxes. Nobody any hits to the new film to be the candidate to go to the Oscars by our country. It is assumed that the producers for and creators of the film all is wonderful and unexpected, a surprise. In addition the film was an opera prima. "It seems that we once again have another Laberinto del Fauno" claim critics and exhibitors. Everything seems perfect. But it is not. Orphanage J.A.Bayona is nothing more than the unfortunate product of a cheat and commercial operation, a pre-cooked appetizer which has the insolence to Pat on the back if same as if its creation had been fruit of prodigious creativity of a new genius.Sure, the budget invested in the film is left notice on your impeccable Bill. Photography is wonderful although occasionally, everything becomes too perfect and calculated, all frames have been carefully crafted, but sometimes such composition is so perfect that we just do not believe us that true this object in the House by if. A feeling that could be applied to most aspects of the film. The plans of the House from the outside, the beautiful pictures of the Asturian Coast and some that another little something more here and there are if it doubts the best of this film of "ghost". In the notable it seems irrefutable to include interesting acting of Belén Rueda that while credible makes his character, continues to be the umpteenth representation of strong woman faced with the loss of a child we have seen so many times in the film made in Hollywood. Wheel well composed their interpretation although his constant face of amargamiento (anyone would say that it was the filming of hangover) and their moments of "cool MOM" are in crunch times. The film, a new approach to the theme of Haunted House, this shot with craft and it shows the director handles the camera with conviction, but this full of moments that supposedly has been developed thinking to create moments of emotivividad, terror, breathtaking, magic or drama. Commitment to check a film of commercial significance, is so evident in playing the chord to what Spielberg than most moments of purported enchantment are vaguely successful and only leave in evidence a script without personality and an address inexperienced to not know how to operate that should be unexpected moments that arise from the depths of the characters and not an empty lesson planning in a film class an expensive University. From the first moments of the film, with some another stolen plane of "Save private Ryan", the intimate moments are corny and recargados(esa_secuencia_de_Laura_y_su_marido_tocando_el_piano_a_la_limón) and is a long collection of enforced situations to be "similar." who do nothing more than increase the constant feeling of dejavù which oozes this orphanage. As if it were the new subgenre to cultivate in our country from El laberinto del fauno (2006), the film seems to want to avoid being too fantastic to focus on the drama to at last give a blow to the sixth sense that it justifies (or desjustifique) throughout the film. Certainly surprising, its end reveals some of the many traps that used the movie and at the end one believes to have been attending a selection of great moments of cinema of haunted houses whose purpose is to create a suitable breeding ground for Bayonne explore the big clichés of the genre and without a hair cut, take what most interested in films to which tries to pay tribute. Since then the central argument has more of Polstergeist than of anything else, that the only significant difference is the substitution of the actress that of medium, long ago also of others and not just good, that pompous soundtrack helps increase the constant feeling of having seen and heard before each scene of the screen. There is no shortage other fundamental details seen already many times, dolls that give Juju, bumps, crunch child games in the Park. even deprive the inevitable drawing made by the child to see the ghosts, the inevitable phrases "do want to play with us?" etc.etc.. Worst of all is the solemn tone that carries throughout the film, completely lacking in humour, that gives rise to a handful of situations that border the ridiculous. The character of benign, an elderly woman with glasses ass of glass seems to be written to be performed by the moreno of cruz y raya and his outrage when reminds the most glorious moments of the film by Javier Fesser. The laughter of the staff do not stop when we are shown the history of benign and his son a deformed child to what Jason Voorhes who died (uh, ho! surprise! drowned in the cliffs) in a home video recorded some time ago. But the most glorious time of this festival of involuntary humour is when the police inspector tells Laura with a very solemn tone: "we have asked all attendees of the opening, nobody remembers having seen a child with a sack over his head".Simply glorious. Laughter is separate, even more funny to see this famed Director of video clips of camela applied to his opera prima tactics of many of his pieces for the caló group, were not others that emulate other films. Thus, we find a similar to the right The Dark (2005) whiff, in which one Maria Bello suspiciously reminiscent to this Belén rueda, he lost his daughter in the cliffs, kidnapped by the spirits, and ran along the beach looking for his missing daughter, to the disbelief of everyone, clear. There are levels to confirm ties with John Fawcett film and we can see diving teams tracking the area to find the body women finding the remains of the murdered girl after digging a little bit in the shed. Not missing the level "girl - falls-inside-of-the-shower" of dawn of the muertos(Dawn_of_the_dead,2004) taken from the same angle and all. Ultimately, the orphanage is the horror film to grandmothers of the season. Horror for all ages planned and designed for the enjoyment of the Moms who want to see "one of those scares". A formally impeccable job that of released with American signature would be absolutely slaughtered by the crítica(o_lo_que_es_peor,_completamente_ignorado) and that contains many of the most common hobbies of the big Hollywood Blockbusters. A bet that from the outset it is little genuine, very deliberate and calculated and as an orphan of soul that should be sought in another type of orphanage. The films with absolutely nothing to say.</body>
</review>
