<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Operación Mata-Hari" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about swindlers which are caught in a Web of international espionage. It is not too advisable, since it is quite loose and humor remain distant. Only the pair of main actors gives you a speck of interest.</summary>
	<body>Lovers anonymous meeting, 9 am. "Good morning, my name is Tito Chinchan and recognize that." "I like Gracita Morales." This woman's voice makes me laugh a lot, also reminds me my sister-in-law, her it imitates to perfection and I rio twice. Bad thing is that I had never seen a whole film, and I certainly finished dizzy. Although everything is allowed to women that said "the señoooorito" with that rintintín never matched.The film is about a black man that has a microalgo and kill you anything else start the film. Another black takes the witness until he meets a pair of con artists of middling (José Sazatornil and Gracita Morales). Since that time, we have a comedy of persecutions and shot with hundreds of young girls in bí-kí-ní (that would say the great Saza) in the agony of the Franco regime. It smacks of moral relaxation on all four sides.I have the toddler so accustomed to see these gems of films on Sunday morning that accommodates up already to see with one hand below the diaper. Pity that in this the censors of the caudillo still not allowed the joy felpudiana years later. The story is pretty bad, with a sobreactuado Saza and a Gracita without payload fairing that save from the wreck to the footage. It becomes quite heavy, despite being very it cortita, although it has nice moments. I only stay with the phrase tontez "your kisses must know chocolate" of an actor of great similar to Martinez the facade while trying to kiss the exotic actress. Well, and explains when not drugs.In short, film about swindlers which are caught in a Web of international espionage. It is not too advisable, given that it is quite loose and humorous points remain distant. Only the pair of main actors gives you a speck of interest. It would be better to have called "operation Bí-kí-ní".kisses.</body>
</review>
