<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Guardianes del día" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Second part of the trilogy about guys who want to maintain the level of forces between good and evil. There is no action and has a script too convoluted for what is expected of these films. That need further explanation.</summary>
	<body>Here a reference should be guardians of the night, which is the first part of which we have between hands, but paraphrasing a buddy mine, very memorable should not, by that I do not remember anything from it. From what I've heard is that it this Russian production (this is clear by the posters are in Cyrillic) is a trilogy and they want to equip Matrix. I think that most well the director is believed that he is doing a remake of the Neo and the mother that bore it, but not, or much less.The film is a guy named Anton (Anton, pirulero, everyone, everyone, learn your game, and which do not learn, will pay a garment, Anton) I think that it is a guardian of the day and have to patrol with a partner which is a kind of chosen. In these fighting against a guardian of the night which is being the son of Anton (pirulero) with what is lia there a roll on parents and children. All this sprinkled by the pursuit of the chalk of fate, that I think that go cutrez find a chalk, but good.Certainly, for a change, I have to say that I have not heard of the story. On the one hand, the aesthetic is very successful, with soundtrack type music video, but do not you get to find out what noses are talking about. I.e. they suddenly change to a sort of parallel world, but you don't understand or how they arrived, nor exactly what paint there nor that meaning has. The subject of the action has seemed very mediocre three fights at all, some even cutronas and nothing more. I was expecting I something full of unnecessary struggles for showcasing special effects, which always like, but nothing. What is more, nor the car building scene ends be spectacular.In short, second part of the trilogy about guys who want to maintain the level of forces between good and evil. There is no action and has a script too convoluted for what is expected of these films. That need further explanation.Besitos.P.D: The lesbian scene is so rare that neither excites staff.Pd2: The ball if cool, look at your where.</body>
</review>
