<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Supersalidos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about the search for alcohol "open pussies" three mindless American teenagers. Very good start, very good final lyrics, a heavy result that leaves one rather than bitter aftertaste.</summary>
	<body>I told to my medium Zucchini that if came to the cinema to see "Superbad". Stayed you a face so wanting to send me to hell, but as if everything he wanted to leave at the same time. Come on, a jam in the larynx, which when it desatascó already was on his way in the film only to Xuxa (which says the girl is not with men that do not use condoms). And is that wanting to lead a mother to a film where one of the first words that say "chocholechelandia" is complicated. Very complicated.The film is about two pre-university friends who see as ends his life of the Institute and want to wet the churro before. They are not precisely the archetype student player of the football team, if not rather the prototype of follower of Onan or pajillero, as they prefer to say so. Even with these falls them from the sky the opportunity of a lifetime, one of the girls more buenorras of the "AUL" which wants to go to his party. And now incidentally, who get alcohol. Thus have no choice but to resort to another friend, with more expensive panoli even if it should be, which has a false card.Had not read more than good reviews of this film, it may well be about as bestial promotion, but the thing well painted. And Yes, the first time wasn't bad, with million words profanity, extreme lumpiness, and even a moment in the history of the cinema, which is when extracts the notebook of drawings of Phalluses. But from there, you get bored of having the "cock" in the ear, "pussy" in the nose, and the "blowjob" in the mouth, and already do not know nor as sit in the cinema. Luckily he had the room for me. And it is a film of humor so long becomes desperate. Especially when this American teenage humor is not that what is more grace makes me. Luckily I could detoxify at home with one of Mariano Ozores, than if not.In short, film about the search for alcohol "open pussies" three mindless American teenagers. Very good start, very good final lyrics, a heavy result that leaves one rather than bitter aftertaste.To me me bored.kisses.</body>
</review>
