<review author="Estesoyo" title="El Orfanato" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am even the eggs of films that just wrong because there is no talent to come up with a final in conditions. And I am even the eggs of the critics of bogus, that in your fucking life have been a horror film, and exalt this mierdecilla as if it were to be a new classic.</summary>
	<body>The orphanage is a Spanish film of terror haunted house. That Yes, despite having a virtually Hispanic cast in its entirety, the story he tells is very American, imitating the style of scares based on raising the volume of the special effects as needed. As a friend of mine would say: the same shit with different packaging.Said the director, Juan Antonio Bayona, who alucinaba with the response media that he had had with his first job. And it is that it is not for less. To my also seems to me amazing exaggerated support which has had in the media. Newspapers and televisions that treated as junk (recognize that often well-deserved form) to the genre of horror and fantasy, have drooled exalted from this minor story, that will not go to the history of the cinema, or in general nor the Spanish.And it is that we are facing a haunted house story. that I have already seen a million times. Damn, is not even particularly well shot. It works well as a low-budget experiment, or it would work better in short format, but her she shits as feature film. The story is 100% predictable and scares us is giving are classics of the monster series-b: covered by a mask and don't stop tell us how horrible that is and above all, raise the volume of the music at the moment Summit. And this not already strained. I put zeros to films with more tradition than this (and were well well-deserved eh?).In the end. Once again, cheated, I went to cinema hoping to find the classic breath of fresh air, a low budget but sincere and original work, an attractive history and absorbent. well not. The same shit. 'The sixth sense' is certainly the film has done more damage to the horror genre. I am even the eggs of ghost stories mixed with human and that in the end everyone is dead. I am even the eggs of films that just wrong because there is no talent to come up with a final in conditions. And I am even the eggs of the critics of bogus, that in your fucking life have been a horror film, and exalt this mierdecilla as if it were to be a new classic. Damn, if only a classic every 5 years, and that if we are lucky.People go out of the film saying, ' damn, that fear have spent '. And I say: do fear? when? When get you hit an aunt with the shattered face, when they close the doors at once or when the aunt gives back, raise the volume and sees a child?. But Uncle, that this I've seen already thousand times. At the end of the movie I thought. they have not yet released the basement. and indeed, they draw. Just need a bit of country music to have it all.The story goes an orphanage (obviously) who is going to take a couple. The girl (Belen Rueda, another drama more behind him) lived there small and wants to return to care for children with problems. Then we know that there are ghosts, the son of the couple can see them and as always (bufff) parents do not believe you and think they are the typical invisible friends. Parents seeking disappears right away the child and empienza. The mother investigates and learns that he had a deformed child who died in a joke of other children. The mother of the deformed child poisoned the rest and was mounted so the curse of the House. All die in the end, the child of Belen Rueda is that it was in the basement dead (it had fallen without further) and mother commits suicide to be with the fantasmitas. Therefore all this counted with large ups and downs in the volume of the music and with fairly little skill by the director, which skips several narrative stages of history, doing that in the end it does not end curdling the truño. There is an obsession with constant to the spectator, which ends with the respectable sending shit to the aforementioned director scares. Then, the roll of. that ugly I am. I'll teach my face. well not her I teach you. Damn, already worth, we've seen all uncle. There are two good moments throughout the film only: when the medium tells us what has happened with the children and when is playing the mother to chocolate English with the ghosts and everytime it turns there is one more. that is achieved, but two hours of film cannot be based on a continuous shock.Actors: Belén Rueda is the personified desolation. Come on that is all fucking day desolate, sad, destroyed. the joy of the orchard. Difficult to judge the work of someone who only shows a record throughout the film. I think that it is poorly directed and that in most expert hands could have given more than Yes. To see if it stops flowing dramas a little bored, is he dies around the world.The rest simply pass through there. I have read about Geraldine Chaplin, that makes a very funny role. Hell, funny compared to the Belen Rueda, and compared with her anything does grace. Get 5 minutes and is limited to walking zombie by the House. But advantage to tell us what has happened with the children and it does is original, very well solve the scarcity of effects with an agile narrative and exciting. But go, endure the two hours just for this scene is going to be that not.As his first film, we could think to be condescending and put a good note, but not. It is now when you can and must risk. It will later be subject by a budget, producers, need a good box office, etc. But now you can be original and groundbreaking. If you don't want to or you can be the best you not spend this genus, and go to romantic movies that tend to have better criticism and acceptance. For my part: zero.</body>
</review>
