<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="La extraña que hay en tí" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A failed immersion in the world of guilt and revenge. Don't know if this is a tribute to Charles Bronson, but it would certainly be dissatisfied.</summary>
	<body>Some are already somewhat tired of both post 11-S. Greengrass and Lee (Spike) already made grandiose and entertaining films, respectively, about the tragedy, although they were totally different and incomparable. Now comes Neil Jordan from Ireland to, secretly, a reflection on the consequences of that horrific day, although I say secretly because cover it with the history of an urban justicira who wants to take revenge on those who killed her boyfriend. Sounds like a topicazo, and it is, but Jordan unfolds, fortunately, regularly leaving a maja, although equally unsuccessful commercial film. And one of the good things that has is a Jodie Foster great, with a couple of truly appalling scaean, and a great Terrence Howard who can handle as NY police. A final clumsy (go a plagiarism to this wonder of Fincher!) makes the odd in you is to dismantle and cease to be what it was as a whole (more or less like the character of Erica).The plot is simple, although the Irish the wraps in such a way that it seems, more or less deep, with reflections on revenge and that as common sense of guilt. Yes, the character of Foster repeated thousand and one times the same, I don't know if so it is clear to us, or because it just always feels the same once he has Avenged. The film is repetitive, predictable and on several occasions extremely unrealistic or makes no logical sense, but is at the same time shot realistically, with a pulse by Jordan truly staff and some bright flat sequence as Erica escaping through the streets of the city (similar to the initial, ESA Yes, magnificent and previous film director)(Breakfast on Pluto). He has successes, although it has more bugs. It is risky, topical, predictable, strange (never better said). First and foremost, a failed immersion in the world of guilt and revenge. Don't know if this is a tribute to Charles Bronson, but it would certainly be dissatisfied.</body>
</review>
