<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="El Orfanato" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great debut by J.A. Bayona, returning to the top Spanish horror movies. Correct in all respects, entertaining, disturbing.</summary>
	<body>Average film, once in the House closed coup the umpteenth door (and all now the corresponding hop), a friend told me to sottovoce: "pa' me that the House falls on ramp". It is true. and perhaps if the architect had done his work well, or the Carpenter had been revised to fund these hinges, or if simply anyone bothered to close Windows from time to time, perhaps then we we avoid some another scare in this kind of movies. Now however, do can imagine someone a film of terror, with gloomy House included, without any other door? And what I say the noise of these noises that do not come from any particular site and can not awarded to anyone nor to anything in particular? Too late to be the gardener, too sharp to be the caldera, too serious to be air. The children can not miss. Children are always scary. I was thinking of having one, but I'm back to rule out that option.Jokes apart, in the orphanage work the old tricks (that there are, and pairs) and new (to there them). Newcomer Jota has shown a great talent for carrying out (because knew it who had been following his career) and skillfully directs a film very disturbing and distressing. The script is very correct. and though bebe from many sources, one has to assume that nothing new there is under the Sun since the time of Aristophanes. The plot hooks, moving between the thriller and the terror, and in the end surprises us as they already did the others or the sixth sense (among many others, clear).It stands out, for my taste, the interpretation of Belén Rueda. So much that it overshadows the correct interpretation of Fernando Cayo and the rest of the side. Wheel convinces in the desperate search for his son and the spectator suffers at their own pace. Add to all this a picture excellent, very appropriate to the tone of the film, and will be one of the most interesting horror films of recent years. Confirms that we master the genre.</body>
</review>
