<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Brujas mágicas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Genius Ozores alleged trial film a few witches by covens. Neither the best nor the worst. You can make grace, but nor is it to save in memory.</summary>
	<body>Since that I discovered that viewers of all the films screened at Spain, my life appear on the website of the Ministry of culture to taken a new direction. I hope that I go fast this, which I am all day seeing receipts. What've noticed me, that with all that gets people with my dear Ozores, Pajares and company, had revenues ridiculing the majority of current Spanish productions. Something will be.The film is about a Miller - pregonero (Pajares) which has much success among the young girls of the village. He wants to be chaste and pure, but it is them who want their member of 40 centimeters (no less). Only rejects women from his master, so this in retaliation, accused of holding festivals to the devil and called nothing more and nothing less than to the Holy Inquisition. He casually passes through there a Pilgrim (Ozores) that takes advantage of the situation as a critique of this movie do? Easy, it gives to the key and until that fill lines, heh, heh. With this production I laughed enough not to make the approach to situations especially humorous, if not make me grace continuous anachronisms. In the case of a film set in the middle ages, they speak with peace of mind of the European Community, of CDS and other. That is nice. Then in the section "jumping breasts and hairy mats" is not the most appropriate, with a single repeated scene of "rebozus in harinus" it's okay. In bad, see the Pajares face when it simulates that you have a dedicated to work took Miss destrempa up to Nacho Vidal.Resumiendo, genius Ozores alleged trial film a few witches by covens. Neither the best nor the worst. You can make grace, but nor is it to save in memory. To get some good laughs with friends.Besitos.P.D: The Jock that leads Pajares has more padding than the Berrocal tits.</body>
</review>
