<review author="José A. Peig" title="El pasaje" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Forgotten and unknown to a large part of the public of today, The Passage remains a strong exercise of film halfway between the "JohnFordiano" Classicism and decadent aestheticism of the early 1970s.</summary>
	<body>Forgotten and unknown to a large part of the public of today, The Passage remains a strong exercise of film halfway between the "JohnFordiano" Classicism and decadent aestheticism of the early 1970s, sporadically, showing similarities to the cinema verité style. It was a time of transition and the road to reformulations remained open on hold while this type of product on such somewhat coarse grounds, marked the charts waiting for the new craft.To highlight the conciseness and simplicity of their structures, is a film of action and adventure in a framework of war film, but not the work within this genre inspired by the spirit of the introspective epic rather than the collectivism of the honor and the strategy can frame. In the first images we see home to the Basque Shepherd between the Pyrenean nieves, receives two American officers requesting his service to save and hide a scientist persecuted by the nazis. The idea of the renegade hero, the archetype of humanity hidden behind the gesture of roughness (paper which as well has been given to Anthony Quinn) of its initial negative. In the images that close the story, we see the same pastor wrapped between the snows of his home, seeing leaving, with gesture of satisfaction, the doctor and his family. The adventure road and process towards redemption or self-knowledge, topic presented here with more lukewarm on John Ford, but the absence of claims and the millimeter disposition of each element at stake compensated, to some extent, the simplicity of the story.J lee-Thompson leads effectively and makes a quite remarkable use of the mountainous landscape, it would seem that claustrophobic while he recreates with good taste in the Majesty of the geographic reliefs, creating the sense dramatic with a theme as eternal and always agonizing as the persecution, the atosigante shadow of the pursuer and the hopelessness of the persecutedin this case, a family whose mother, in one of the most emotional scenes, flees to his doom to save loved ones, with the silent accomplice of the observer, Basque Shepherd whose look impartial and comprehensive embodies the objective sensitivity of who knows where arrive the limits and the pain of a mother. On the other hand, and in exchange for a certain bucolic lyricism, passages starring Malcolm Mcdowell (in a stereotyped and something sobreactuada a nazi soldier, but extremely sharp in all his gestures and glances representation) reinforce a tone of sordidness and fascist megalomania, counterpoint to the down-to-Earth rudeness of the Basque Shepherd.</body>
</review>
