<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="An American Crime" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a necessary film in times in which torture and the harassment are justified for political ends and is taken for granted that ethically correctness always dwells in the West, but seeing it we stir the stomach and we sacrifiquemos dinner.</summary>
	<body>One of the precepts of the fundamentalist Baptist Church is as follows: practical loyalty to the Christian faith in everyday life, at work, family and society, and commitment to preach to every creature of Word and by example. Mrs Gertrude Baniszewsky, a widow, ill and with seven children behind him, decided to preaching, with the complicity of all his children, his good news an innocent girl of 16 years-based harassment, torture, mutilation and sexual abuse of the most diverse, involucandro it to the neighborhood of a lost people of Indianapolis, back in the 1960s. The girl in question was Sylvia Likens, who had been in the care of Gertrude with his younger sister, that her parents had to leave for work during a season. Big mistake. They were leaving their daughters in the hands of the evil personified evil of a society which justified their facts arguing that such punishments were necessary to put right a lost soul. It could be the plot of a horror film, but it happened in United States. A ruthless and authentic American crime. Under the skin of the horror of the final result emit rotten vapors sexual repression, the lessons imbibed with sticks and humiliation, the railway imposition of Christian ideas travestidas precepts fundamentalists and above all, the injustice of being human when violence it seizes him, and can't stop. In the room were heard sighs attempting to relieve the sensation of nausea while the body was looking for accommodation in the armchair of the cinema, we were forced to watch how nearly an entire people can to agree to torture an innocent girl. The list of abuses is endless, but although Tommy O'Haver shows much of what happened, we are just at the tip of the iceberg. If one investigates a little, it notes that the inhabitants of Indianapolis considered this crime as the Dantesque perpetrated against a person throughout its history and what he suffered the child exceeds the tolerable limits. Why Tommy O'Haver prevents us we revolvamos more than enough and shows us just so we realize what we can be able to do in our supposedly democratic and civilized worlds. It is hard to talk about anything else other than the history, but it is worth noting the excellent work of Catherine Keener as Gertrude Baniszewsky (Capote, Being John Malkovich) and Ellen Page (Hard Candy) as Sylvia. The clash is Titanic, although winning is Keener. His eyes cold and loss is overwhelming, and achieves the desired effect. In summary, An American Crime is a necessary movie in times in which torture and the harassment are justified for political ends and is taken for granted that ethically correctness always dwells in the West, but seeing it we stir the stomach and we sacrifiquemos dinner.</body>
</review>
