<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="It's fine! Everything is fine!" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is as if a screenwriter with cerebral palsy and David Lynch lobotomizado join forces to make one of the more bizarre, refreshing and absurd films that have seen in my life.</summary>
	<body>This &hellip; start. Well the first thing I will say is &hellip; unclassifiable. But if I strive a little, let's see &hellip; could say that it is as if a lobotomizado David Lynch and a screenwriter with cerebral palsy (the latter is not no joke, it is reality) join forces to make one of the more bizarre, refreshing and absurd films that have seen in my life. Then say that porn is not projected in commercial theaters. It's fine, everything is fine has porn hardcore, as if it were not enough history to put the cry in the sky to certain sectors of society or to test our idea of where just the imagination and risk and where bad taste (probably most will decline by bad taste). I still do not know, and probably do not know. Perhaps it will take a few years, and after reviewing, you can say something. Which Yes, is that Crispin Glover is not a normal guy. I was fortunate to see the premiere of the film in 35 mm in Sitges, presented by the own Glover, and only with that had given me satisfied. Crispin, dressed in a suit type "I'm elegant with a mafia twist", hair planchadita and atusada which included a sharp face and sweaty fruit of nerves, we began to talk about the film without really saying anything. His model girlfriend, provided him with a smile on the lips. This guy knows something we don't know, and gives me laughs at us. His proposal is totally geek, Geek in uppercase. The movie us into the perverse and overheated mind of a troubled cincuentón of cerebral palsy (the screenwriter for the film, Steven C. Stewart, who died within a month of completing the film, and I can assure that veery happy for having done), makes us dive into his obsession for long-haired women and presents a world in which all when understand you speaks (although you can barely mumble nonsense words) and you they want sexually. Dialogs are, therefore, endless, and never fail to understand what it says, only through the responses of their lovers. Once the above is passed through the stone to all kinds of women (a bitter widow, a daughter of the first lolita, a prostitute &hellip;) strangles them with its powerful forearm and back to start. Crispin Glover for his film get a look between eighties and amazing timeless, and the use of colors is formidable. The movie holds final surprise for us and makes us understand what appeared to be a derision to persons with problems of mobility and speech is really a tribute. The director presents a world in which it is not absurd as a stunning woman fervently want almost inanimate body of a patient. Without giving has, the film is set and slowly let the absurd to flood our heads until hardly feel puzzled about the situation. I believe that Crispin Glover is aware of that passes through an inner world is not the most, and this is the ultimate test. Well, actually no, because this film accompanies a prequel (What is it?) and a sequel, still to shoot (It is mine). The trouble with Charlie's Angels and the friend of rats in Willard is in form. It is becoming the film underground cult figure, and he knows. Hopefully you have mecha for awhile. We will enjoy it (we are a minority, clear).</body>
</review>
