<review author="Kiko de España" title="Supersalidos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Superbad is a Superbonita movie disguised as a movie Supergamberra and a beautiful and bitter (at the bottom) singing to the friendship. Pity the Castilian dubbing, Superbad of truth. A peliculón which will be even more when you understand what kids are saying.</summary>
	<body>First test of maturity.Superbad is a bitter hymn to friendship in form of wild comedy. Superbad is a movie about friends that will soon no longer be despite the affection felt between them. Superbad is a superbonita movie supergamberra movie dressed up as. The good that has is that it is also, as said the great Noel, Superbuena.Tres so charismatic and endearing actors that it is difficult to stay with one, good intentions and perhaps the weakest of all, the usual unwillingness in the composition and the absence of brilliantly filmed moments. But that's brand of the House and the key, as in Virgin at 40 or Knocked up is in the script.Say the own writers that the movie was conceived at the same time that live the protagonists of the film, perhaps that is why there are quite honesty in the movie and we have no nude girls retozando by bedding: nobody here eats a tail.Way wrong but inevitable is compares it with American Pie, which was honest and sincere that she had John McTiernan.Superbad 2002 Rollerball "goes" some kids who have to drink for the holidays "cole" and how difficult it is to achieve in this country according to which things. This simple anecdote serves to ensure that the three guys (wax will be the great Dominator of the future together with Shia, Hill is meat of coarse comedy and Mintz-Plasse do not say anything &hellip;) discover that maybe is not that what they really want the progress despite inevitably go in a new direction.The police bring a "new comedy within comedy" thank God, and have one of the best quotes from the movie, which explains that once they stopped at a rate that was called.The other great sentence is McLovin (!) with a drunk.Seth Rogen is one of the writers of the movie, the COP with moustache, the prota of Knocked up and the great revelation of Virgin at 40. All these movies have grossed more than $ 100,000,000 and shows that sometimes the general public isn't stupid.Pity the Castilian dubbing: crappy, pseudoamateur and ultraridículo.A peliculón that will become even bigger when you understand what the players are saying.</body>
</review>
