<review author="Antonio" title="Silent Hill" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie respects throughout the atmosphere, aesthetics and the characters, essential elements that have achieved the "Silent Hill" series is one of the most respected and plays.</summary>
	<body>When a veteran videoadicto as I have to see the adaptation of a game to the big screen, it goes through a sense of pleasure resembling that invades you when you hold the command and switch on the console with your latest acquisition videojueguil. Unfortunately this sensation diminishes and transforming into disappointment according to the film are goes away more and more not only of the original idea of the game but also its aesthetic of his characters, his "charm", in short everything what did a great video game. And it is that adapting is never easy. A video game has been designed very differently to a film, although increasingly both genders give the impression of converge slowly.For all these reasons I didn't much hope with "Silent Hill". Well, at least not was directed by Uwe Boll, profanador of jewels like "Alone in the dark", which encouraged me a little more.The beginning, quite typical, shows us a sleepwalking girl nearing death. In these times of sleepwalking, the girl (from The Ring, all girls scary movies are equal, when a blonde short hair girl?) believes that he is in "Silent Hill", so his mother, in an attempt to cure his daughter will take the people abandoned under mysterious circumstances. It would have been much more intelligent by the girl say "Disneeeey Woooorld" instead of "Siiiilent Hiiiill" in these bouts of sleepwalking, but clear, rather than a horror movie we would have otherwise.From here, start to happen strange phenomena in Silent Hill, where exciting moments of action occur when darkness seizes the town where constantly raining down ash and more relaxed moments where we know something more about Silent Hill, without never bother us that overlap between stories. The characters are well made and characterized by their peers (those who have) video game, emphasizing Cybil, the police, appearing as curious note at 18 of the 20 characters more gay video games (http://gaygamer.net/index.php?s=gayest), what nonsense list.The movie respects throughout the atmosphere, aesthetics and the characters, essential elements that have achieved the "Silent Hill" series is one of the most respected and plays. Disconcerting at first, until that we fail to half do not know very well what goes the plot, very characteristic also the game. Finally! a worthy adaptation of a video game.PS: the zombie nurses could have given more game, apart from the "1, 2, 3" English hide and seek.PD2: Buff, illusion out Tito Chinchán blog. I hope not to disappoint, even if not at the height of this experienced critic.</body>
</review>
