<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El espía" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A correct spy film that adds nothing new to the genre cinema, but which nevertheless unfolds successfully, especially with the incredible performance of Chris Cooper, an actor who always must be taken into account.</summary>
	<body>During the history of the American cinema we have seen real wonders about espionage, either the master or frenetismos as the own Bourne, of a more modern era. Seeing the spy I noticed that there is a justified reason why has to do this film. It is our incunvencia process of the Robert Hanssen espionage? Lol As well, with that phrase so loved and hated by some as the "based on a true story", the film of Bill Ray is sold as such, a story that happened, and that unfortunately a few we are interested in. However, the film, leisurely pace and without just action, able to keep as footage of dialogue (which rather than deep thinking) and finds a (slow) point not just disturb the Viewer.It is topical in much of the content, but does not intend to show it. Several of his scenes are enviably original, but apparent senzillez. It is not so much what you see but those looks and intimate conversations that make the spy film, rather than espionage, intellectual. It is not, nor much less, what was this wonderful second film of Robert de Niro. Fails, not even, the level of the Jason Bourne trilogy, but it has something that others do not have, something difficult to describiri, quiet, cosy cold and dry. This, also, is a clear portrait to that life so boring and dangerous spies, who play their lives as overlooking weapons. Your script is senzillo (which not bad). Does not bring anything new and interesting film spies, but that Yes, account events paused and intelligent way.The cast looks very satisfactorily, mainly the great (far side) Chris Cooper, that cooprotagoniza the film with the young Ryan Phillippe, who saw that he was already a good actor in the great Crash. Both are harmonized in a great way, form a duo interesting and very well written dialogues. Probably a little recurrence of talks between them, but this would be a minor problem. And, above all, do not forget the final moment, where both show his charisma with just looks. A true success. Although the secondary Laura Linney must not detract from, because its interpretation is, as usual, excellent.A correct spy film that adds nothing new to the genre cinema, but which nevertheless unfolds successfully, especially with the incredible performance of Chris Cooper, an actor who always must be taken into account.</body>
</review>
