<review author="Kiko de España" title="Stardust" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The best movie of magical adventures I've seen in my life. Not hate me for such an assertion, but Stardust seems almost perfect and a wise choice for a first date bar movie. Endearing.</summary>
	<body>I do not like the Princess Bride, Willow, Legend, Conan, Conan Returns (kidding), Hook, dark glass, inside the labyrinth or the anillera trilogy I swallowed in film because she had to see it.Let's say I have a problem with the swords and the magical worlds. Let's say that they touch me the eggs almost as much as the movies of time with the wonderful exception of Marie Antoinette. Let's say that now pass by your head a host of insults towards myself and especially my ability to analyze a movie as Stardust.No is so hard: Stardust feel me great.I enjoyed as a child in the pass in Sitges this tale full of bad English host and more balanced than any of the films that I quote above and Pirates of the Caribbean (which I've only seen the first chapter, forgive me Ironcita) Stardust is the total, resounding, definitive, confirmation of Matthew Vaughn, who had already left in Layer Cake enough samples of criterion as to trust in this adaptation of a Gaiman little serious, which is the to my I like.Bruges, brothers who do not hesitate to kill between them for a Kingdom, Knights, star shaped girl with fake British accent and above all, humour in abundance during cent thirty minutes.But there will be controversy. There will be who argumentará De Niro is a caricature of himself and that only try to imitate another recent film pirata-payaso.Believe me, De Niro passes better gatewayed at its last, let me tell &hellip; eleven latest movies playing captain Shakespeare, a rude piratón with a secret &hellip; Charlie Cox convinces me (and how!) as Tristan, the prologue with the guardian of the wall (and its evolution) is hilarious and nothing, I repeat, nothing, makes screeching perfectly oiled from a grandiose epic that hinge, as almost all the large offending movies (see Grindhouse) of recent years, fails at the box office in a precipitous manner in favour of "pure cinema" titles such as wild pigs or hour Tip 3. I shit in the mother that gave birth.</body>
</review>
