<review author="Jack Torrance" title="Hatchet" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is sad that in only the two and a half minutes of the false "Thanksgiving" trailer for Eli Roth has more sarcasm, affection and knowledge of the Slasher that throughout the film by Adam Green.</summary>
	<body>Considered by many specialist sites such as one of the films to take into account in this 2007, the independent Hatchet has been released in the United States in small distribution circuits. An exhibition limited for a film of relative under budget, which has sold very well as a tribute to the Slashers of the eighties, with the series Friday the 13th as a standard. Hatchet tries to impersonate a return to forms and spirit of tapes as the killer of Rosemary, burning, or The Prom Night, but any connoisseur of the subgenre quickly realizes that there is no link with them except the stubbornness of their creators for attempting to present your product in this way.A tribute with irony and true love to the genus seek, first, a stylistic approach appropriate, using their lack of budget as an element in their favor. It is sad that in only the two and a half minutes of the false "Thanksgiving" trailer for Eli Roth has more sarcasm, affection and knowledge of the Slasher that throughout the film by Adam Green. Hatchet is raised as a psycho-splatter the old-fashioned, but their characters, situations, script or formal aspect seem taken from any film created for the American video market. There is no spark in potentially funny situations and those who have (very) occasionally, are repeated until exhaustion. Once seen the grace, film stops working and they start endless tedious situations. In a film of this kind, deliberately bad?, various incompetences in exchange for a bit of fun world can forgive. What happens is that when a 80 minute film should expect 50 so that something begins to happen, it fails something important.There is no character development, any especially funny situation. anything. When it comes to the time of the appearance of Victor Crowley, supernatural killer function, one is too boring as that it cares to see to be deformed destroying the odious characters of forms more wild than one can imagine. But even al gore is well shot. The effects are very good, old-style, but shooting them is flat, without passion and so amateur as the rest of the film. In conclusion. Hatchet is a tedious journey of 80 minutes shot without style or profession. For more irritation, short its end abruptly, in a feint to try to leave the Viewer without knowing which will happen. Get only the sensation of thymus reaches dangerous levels. Very laudable in its attempt to parody films bloody and bad, taking the path of irony and pitorreo, but when you do not offer a product that will improve in any aspect to the movies that you want to emulate, it is better to stay at home.Of course, not rely on the many and effusive criticism that will receive pages websites, Blogs and other specialized media.Hatchet is not the Slither of films of serial killers, not even this at the height of the worst sequels in the series of the Hockey mask. Well was maybe yes of the Octava.¿o the ninth?</body>
</review>
