<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Supersalidos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The adventures living in a night the protagonists are really fun. But nor let the laughter we cheat, the film is not no wonder and has serious problems of rhythm.</summary>
	<body>"Supersalidos", very bad and somewhat perverse translation of the original title "Superbad", is a film that didn't go to see. The comedies of the type "American pie" or I am not interested in "Porky's" (in fact have not seen any of the two) and the lack of time, endemic evil of our time, forces me to choose what I see or public. Finally, thanks to the gentle invitation of Sony Pictures Spain and via muchocine.net had the opportunity to attend a press pass at the superb facilities of the aforementioned company in Madrid.Y there, I took a surprise &hellip; on surprise, but surprise. Relative because those who hate this genre are going to hate this movie and those who worship going to an idol. Surprise because we are between these two positions are those who can leave surprised the film. And this for several reasons.First because the title is somewhat misleading. The story focuses on three hatched teenagers, Yes, on the other hand almost all adolescents (for what cheat us?). But is the search for the alcohol for a party, in a country in which children under 21 years of age can not buy it, which focuses much of the film.The other major topic of the tape is the friendship between Seth (Jonah Hill) and Evan (Michael Cera), alter egos of the writers Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg, which will be put to the test to the admission in different universities which, in turn, will lead to some point's unexpected good cinema. Attention, by the way, to the possible connotations gay history.The adventures living in a night the protagonists are really fun (advise going to the cinema in gang because this is the typical movie that can be enjoyed more so). Especially good are the scenes planned on situations before the purely verbal, simplistic and based on the alleged grace of the swearing words of the protagonists (although some have his joke in general are repetitive).But what I think it will be especially remembered, out of the film, is the scene of the liquor store (say no more) and everything about the funniest movie character: McLovin (Christopher Mintz-Plasse). To his around the most hilarious scenes take place to the extent that, without being the main character, becomes the real owner of the role. It is difficult to end up not being a fan of McLovin.Pero neither let the laughter we fooled, the film is not no wonder and has serious problems of rhythm. Both at the global level, the movie takes enough to boot, is too long and has slippages worrying level internal rate of some of the scenes that make long and either take in arise either in resolved.These defects cause the whole is somewhat irregular and alternate the laughter with a slight boredom. If we add this to the film's low claims, we will reach the conclusion that the movie is simply correct. What, on the other hand, is much more than I expected.Final assessment in moonfleet: 5.5 out of 10</body>
</review>
