<review author="Andrés Pons" title="La Huella" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Halfway through footage at least always excellent in this role Jude Law gives el baile de san pito mutating without warning in a cheap copy of Jim Carrey exceeding even their faces.</summary>
	<body>Let's fuck the classics with the greater possible boldly, we will carry out the ridiculous by copying one of the greatest cinematic masterpieces and her plunge into the mire of the filth.Go is that not the purpose of this Remake? Because I am surprised but it is what found me. KENNETH BRANAGH is a director and competent actor when it adapts to the great playwright SHAKESPEARE "HAMLET, much ado about nothing" what happens is that when it comes out of these adaptations his film deteriorates quite.CAINE returned to acting in one of his best films in his excellent career embodying the opposite character, ends it his doing his natural heir "JUDE LAW" that apparently because I interpret another character of the great actor in the also mediocre Remake of ALFIE.The screenplay by HAROLD PINTER written for the occasion is an ode to the incompetence or a crash course in how to destroy a good story.The film makes no sense in all its footage without never to know which balls are playing this pair of clowns.We do not know that her pussy intended to but gives as well to half of footage at least always excellent in this role JUDE LAW gives el baile de san pito mutating without warning in a cheap copy of JIM CARREY exceeding even their faces. I guess that to be at the level of his prodigious partner that is the only thing salvageable in the disaster got a crab in the ass leaving carried away by such wonderful experience. I guess that BRANAGH that cared a pepper because you don't understand the because no control to that actor who suddenly became insane, although to see his collection of drawings without sense nor anyone controlled you to the.The music is similar to the picture is grim, but the best is to come in the final Fireworks. Suddenly we have a tape that could be involved in a GAY film festival and just change you the title by the of "Te voy a meter footprint behind with my tranca gonna freak out and to my wife slut is going to find out".</body>
</review>
