<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Disturbia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Disturbia is a teenager thriller, a disturbing picture of the solitude of an individual Justice has been confined to his home. Hitchcock thought for adolescents in the 21st century.</summary>
	<body>The model.Or you're analog or digital are. The lofty and sensitive suspense by the great Alfred Hitchcock basculaba between Cartesian, unproblematically, sistematizable and computable evidence and the uncertainty of the amazement that not let Assualt by predictable patterns or consents to the routine or neutral aesthetics. Hitchcock was driving his talent for ambiguous territories and refuting the pre-eminence of the well with sordid battering of pure evil, with pertubadas conclusions on the human condition. But it was Hitchcock who was a being analog, arguing its prodigious cinematic pulse on noble handles almost all literary. The Empire of imagination planned, free.If it is true that the Jesuits invented the suspense, according to some anecdote about his life in an English boarding school and how the noble cloister Regent left the punished to run severísimas physical assaults which it was subject, Hitchcock invented the dramatized suspense, suspense as single ingredient of the plot. Everything else is incidental. The Viewer is also an actor of this plot. James Stewart is the invalid who escruta their backyard neighbors in search of strong emotions and encounters what he believes is a murder, but James Stewart, in a formidable game of mirrors, is also the spectator placidly installed in the armchair, in a subtle exercise of duplicate voyeurism. We do not criticize what we're blessing with our viewing. The copy. D. j. Caruso has filmed an attractive update to the voyeur of Hitchcock in this Disturbia, but times they dictate their laws and it is not possible to minimize the filmic space and give the young plays Shia Lebouf in the adult that once made James Stewart. One is proverbially equipped with a sophisticated digital mentality and the other is an analog dreamer possessing only binoculars and a horse boredom. In this sense, Disturbia is the logical film for the times in which we live. IPod, Windows Live, broadband, X-box, as portable Mac. All this technological paraphernalia is the flag of coupling a solid argument, led with care and very skillfully assembled to satisfy a diverse record of public. Disturbia is a teenager thriller, a disturbing picture of the solitude of an individual Justice has been confined to his home through an AB e with GPS so that it expíe the aggression towards a teacher. It is also a pleasant vehicle for mixing suspense in the purest style Hitchcock with bobalicón romanticism of adolescents with hormones bursting them all seams of the soul. In its essence, Disturbia is an intelligent proposal barely recordable, but becomes pleasant in his not very extensive footage. It is not worth making the game of contrasts. Each time it has its references and it, balcony to the Vertigo of the gadgets, delusional in his Machiavellian demolition of the responsibility and the noble chapter of the personal effort, produces subjects as the portrayed in the film, individuals without stridency, which can be heroes or villains and not require excessive script to be carried away by an option or the other. And the bad, the hazy murderer in the House opposite, a flat, David Morse, is a vaguely acceptable anonymous citizen, without the charm of a Hannibal Lecter or morbidity of the Boston strangler (a formidable Tony Curtis, by the way). Here is a meaningless subject of history, one that we can not find reasons which justify its anomaly because (simply) no matter. The hodgepodge of topics they are assembled with ex officio and the malice of the voyeur is lowered with sugary landscapes of juvenile comedy that everything conforms to the moral dictates that will allow to make a larger box.The only requirement of the plot is that it has killed much and that his house has an infernal basement where all the worms in the world celebrate their good luck. We would have liked a more rugged tone, a more sordid aftertaste, but D.J. Caruso - a guy ready - has chosen not to miss in sadismos, on outputs of tone, more or less gore from the original story variations. Theirs is more caramel: there is no factor surprise, but the game created by its writers leads to well planned scenes and moments of entertaining films over not being able to. And therefore contaminated readers, it is much and appreciated much more. 1954 is very far away. Disturbia is a gum light, acceptable, but perhaps want a steak of beef of Kobe and then friend reader ay, what saves us is the magic of our shelves of DVDs and the lust out of his sleeve the original and deposit it with exquisite care and absolute Rapture in the player. Darkness. The film exists. And it is one of the most essential pleasures that we have. Although it is not a bad film, what will happen to it, none of this.</body>
</review>
