<review author="Estesoyo" title="El número 23" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The curse of the 23. By the time that he heard anything so stupid. Because of course, if you take your date of birth, her divides by 23, he sums multiplied by x 23 and subtractions you 23,000 and get you 4 more so it fits... you get 23! Uncle, is for shit is.</summary>
	<body>It is a strange film, this gimmick, as it is marked by the presence of the known and histrionic actor Jim Carrey. This tipejo has won the life (well since then, won because he has made a Fortune) doing all kinds of grimaces and antics, with greater or lesser grace. It is one of these actors makes humor by exhaustion. As these kids who do not stop do you grimaces and cuddle until exhausted you spend them a smile to make you stop in peace the fuck up. This type is the same. All the while putting faces, until it achieves that by pure weakness you escape a smile. Never occurred to me to see one of his movies again.Well, because the weary of Carrey, as it is already lined, now insists on that he wants to be an actor. There is who has been compared with Jerry Lewis, also made deplorable comedies in its infancy but then gave us a masterful interpretation. Found only in its beginnings: regrettable and a shame for the history of cinema. Carrey later insists in dramatic roles, with more penalty than glory.Here is a psychological thriller, or it seems at first. The story goes a guy who reads a novel that narrates his own life, that Yes, from a point of view fantastic and full of action in which is seen as a great success of private detective (in reality is dedicated to hunting animals loose around the city, go shit work by Jove!). In the book it is trapped by a curse related to the number 23 which begins to affect him in his real life. Here he painted well, and already was I thinking. is it possible that this clown has done something interesting? Well not. The story follows.The story follows. but the ideas were exhausted. Immediately sees that the book or his wife has written to try to return it crazy or has written the because it was mad. All comes down to the research of the author, which is in fact himself, by the family (including teen crio). That Yes, all well watered with a delusional surrealist: the curse of the numbers is no not lying women hiding corpses in the Park, the protagonist turns out to be amnesiac and nobody knows his past. Amazing uncle. This reminds me of the novels of Agatha Christie, in which at the end came a distant relative that had not appeared at this time and was the murderer. Shit decent of living with the rest of this website. The thing is that the guy is loaded to a girl at the University and was amnesiac of the scare. As his father was accounting, stay marked by numbers, in particular the 23, you see your. Then redo his life and married the first girl that is, it is also a goat as it seems. The thing has its charms, see for parties: 1) the curse of 23. By the time that he heard anything so stupid. Because obviously, if you choose your date of birth, her you divides by 23, add you multiplied by 2 23 subtractions le 23,000 and get you 4 more so it fits. you get 23! Uncle, is for shit is!(2) The mysterious amnesia. But as a pussy you can be married to a guy 17 years without knowing it is a crazy murderer? Damn, and with a son and everything. Above to protect him (sends eggs) is to unearth the victim of her husband so that they are not included. (I guess that being one with little knowledge of American culture did not know these ancestrales.3 costrumbres) search. Meet a former psychologist who treated him and see him. the neck was slit to not talk to him. ?¿. I hallucinate. I can not think anything to comment on, I was super-pasmado. It should be in the dictionary section for explanation of 'without rhyme or reason'. (4) The end: the guy comes and goes to jail. I tell you if you even thought to go see her. Do not uncle, is very bad.Joel Schumacher did, among others: last call, hidden young, Uun day of fury, a pair of Batman, anyway. especially action and pretty mediocre. But this now takes the award lifetime truño: mega-truño. After a career filled with movies, at least now we have clear which is the worst of all that they lapped.About the actors, the thing is funny. The son of the chalao they practically or focus, comes all the time in the background, and women take out especially when you are telling the story of the detective. and the truth is that it gains enough in picardias or Nightgown. But nothing, everything revolves around the Carrey, not just do neither well nor badly. Taking the pasta has the uncle the first thing that should be done is to select a good story and not trash like this. The truth is that you neither being more optimistic that I can save is shit of film. Total, other truño, another zero.</body>
</review>
