<review author="Naty Buqué" title="Rapado" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A small, almost amateur film but with a very strong itself, intelligent consciousness and, if it is too simple, is interesting as a preamble to what Rejtman did brilliantly then, with 'Silvia Prieto' and 'The magical gloves'.</summary>
	<body>Shaved, the first feature film of the Argentine Martín Rejtman, based on a self-titled story of his namesake book, is largely the genesis of his style unique, intelligent and extremely interesting, but quite amateur version without the humor that would mark his following films.The feature perhaps Rejtman film main is the creation of a diegesis not realistic (but not so far from the realism), with a code of action itself, for framing small stories with empty characters (not merely empty: there is an emptying as a result of a social context that crumbling social relations). This, in turn, with a sense of humor excruciating, built with sadly funny characters and dialogs (sort of shared monologues, where we talk about but it is not heard) underpinning.The humor does not appear in shaved. The characters have nothing to say or do, but this is not resolved, in his later films, with the humor that this pathos generated by stupid dialogues and that do not allow communication between those who argue. The film is much more explicitly sad, although never assume the code of the drama.The plot of the film moves not by the characters but by objects ranging, worthless, hand in hand, by all of them. Obviously eloquent about the pathetic consumer society in decadence that was the Argentina of the 1990s (moving objects are a clock, stolen motorcycles, counterfeits, pieces of video games that function as money), the film also speaks of a lost generation - not in the sense that no longer but that is not a heading.With a very good photography and camera moves, framing some desolate environments (houses of families of class average goings unless, desolate Buenos Aires streets), the film is aesthetically simple but careful. The same happens with the plot.In short, a small, almost amateur film but with a very strong itself, intelligent consciousness and, if it is too simple, is interesting as a preamble to what Rejtman did brilliantly then, in the same vein, with Silvia Prieto and the magical gloves.</body>
</review>
