<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="Gerry" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I think that the film is more valuable if we have that sometimes need stripping content images, to slow down the action to see beyond the Vortex and the microscopic details to pass to the fore.</summary>
	<body>We can go on tour and among the Brambles, find us with a Boulder. From here we have two options. Either hitting a kick to depart from the path, without stopping to think about the consequences, either bend us, hold it between the hands, feel the sharp edges and roughness of the surface, go home and open books of geology to categorize her. We can even save it in a shop window and make it our hobby and treasure, our perfect and wonderful Boulder. For approaching Gerry, first film of the trilogy about death (along with Elephant and Last Days), there is to know in advance of what foot limp, knowing if we are of them walking through the jungle with the machete ahead rebanando bamboo or have in mind to become entomologists, zoologists and observers of the behavior of primates. If we are the first, see Gerry will mean not see anything at all, or see the least. If we are the seconds, Gerry will become more than a vision, I would say in contemplation. The argument could not be simpler: two friends (Matt Damon just before losing the memory in "The case Bourne" and Casey Affleck) decide to take an excursion through the desert. As the road is going to be crowded of weekenders and they decide that it is offroad trekking, they deviate from the fixed path looking for solitude and wild nature. The problem is that they do not carry compass or maps of the area, not even "camperas" boots or provisions. When they realize that they are lost and they cannot give back because they have not taken precautions already is too late for them. And here ends the script. What illustrates perfectly what level can develop one idea, showing infinite edges which has a Boulder is that original drafts of the script for Van Sant was just a line to describe one of the somewhat rocambolescas situations that occur in the film, made on 20 pages in the review made by Casey Affleck. It is true that there is endless levels, could be considered soporíferos or bored, shot Gus Van Sant-style, but in austerity and simplicity of the images and the vision of a mocking and perverse desert that shows its teeth in exponential progression, hides all a collection of gestures, interactions, mood swings, assumptions of reality and dances of glances and madness between the two protagonists thatpossibly for being friends in real life, they are fully committed. The dialogue is minimal, but why not basic or insubstantial, though we do not always understand. Moreover, I think that you one of the purposes of the film is that we do not always understand why act like they do, or why they say what they say. There isn't any spark. I think that the film is more valuable if we realize that sometimes we need bare content images, need to slow down the action to see beyond the Vortex and that the microscopic details go to the fore. At the end of the desert you don't expect anything other than death, and it is no hurry to nail us the claws. Everything in time, saith the Lord of the scythe.</body>
</review>
