<review author="Naty Buqué" title="Inland empire" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Inland Empire is a visual, sound and intellectual experience.</summary>
	<body>Finally, when he only remained in Buenos Aires a single (and horrible, and distant) room to see Inland Empire, attended the function.I won't get the silly as often happens with criticisms of Lynch's movies. Talk about the camera, actions of the super flash to avoid the 'I did not understand anything, but is good'.I did not understand anything, but it is good.The film follows the typical structure lyncheana, where two or more diegetic levels come into play and mingle without prior notice. Another film that the viewer desentrañe with elements that are repeated in different 'levels' (which speaks of chaos or Association free or chamuyo in lynch does not understand anything: his films have more structure than the more typical dramón yankee). This time, however, believe it plays a little more and exits at the realism of the earlier films of this line (say lost Highway and Mulholland Drive), and already not we ourselves to the biplane realidad-sueño but that we are moving into something much more complex that could be defined as a triad (realidad-sueño - fiction) Although it may be more correct to think of two biplanes: realidad-sueño, realidad-ficción. If this is added the fact that fiction is that of a film, then adds the complexity involved in the film within the film.What I think is that finally the film is not resolved in the realism of a schizophrenic having nightmares, but history is more open towards a fantastic paranoid or something. To ensure this, however, her he would twice more.On the other hand, experimentation with digital camera opens many doors to Lynch, and if you lose the tidiness of Mulholland Drive, left the greater variety of movements of camera, image quality, lens and even picture, contributing to the distinction of the levels that are playing. This holds also largely in the codes of the characters acting, trait very interesting to analyze (which, of course, I will not do).Another thing I would like to highlight of the film is the brilliant use of rather violent images. I'm the first ethical voice against free of violence in film and main antagonist of the Hostel type rubbish found in this film an empirical test for arguing that it is not violence per is that bothers me on the screen. Lynch uses visual violence: the film has even a bit of masturbatorio enjoy the physical suffering of the other, the blood, the imminent death. And it works. I, at least, as a spectator, suffered such scenes (and not.) by disgust but by anxiety (The destroyed meat became, in the lynch House, shattered meat of a subject).There are several things to mention. The self reference, even the autoparodia; the excellent performances; the photography of puta madre. And safer than other things that I was forgetting.Best of all, however, is to see this film is an experience in itself, and an individual experience. You can see 4 times and understand the plot, that is not the crux of the matter. The best is entering the film without the plot import, let perceive the imágenes-tópico he spoke Deleuze to find pure images, enjoy this, think of things in relation to the image and not necessarily in relation to the meaning of the actions that take place in that image and related to (the rest of the actions that take place in) the entire film.Exactly that. Inland Empire is a visual, sound and intellectual experience.</body>
</review>
