<review author="Plissken" title="Las 13 Rosas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Correct adaptation of Emilio Martínez-Lázaro in which parties shine more than the whole, and that at least shakes almost pamphleteering tone of any similar production.</summary>
	<body>Emilio Martínez-Lázaro is one of my weaknesses. As director is probably not the most incendiary, but certainly has an innate talent for urban comedy. 'Amo tu cama rica', 'The worst years of our lives' or 'The other side of the bed' you are backed up in this field. Now just change log for returning to drama with 'Las 13 Rosas', which tells the tragic story of thirteen women shot in 1939 by the simple fact of being related to the Socialist Youth and the SGP.The sensation that leaves 'Las 13 Rosas' ends, is ambiguous: feel pity for the historical fact that counts, that goes far beyond any ideology: the execution of 56 persons (43 men were sentenced to die like them) as a response to the murder of three others is hardly justifiable today, but speaks clear of how were the spirits then, and how much that worked the grudge as the main engine of the civil war and post-war.But you also alegras that the point of view that has chosen Martínez-Lázaro is not the topic of "the heroic defenders of freedom crushed by Franco hordes": the Madrid director is concerned, more than militancias relations and human reactions. And Socialists or Communists or fascists who are the characters that run by the Madrid of the postwar, Martínez-Lázaro and Ignacio Martínez de Pisón, its screenwriter, have been able to speak to us about normal people in extreme circumstances, and no icons of resistance or personifications of evil. This is the great success of 'Las 13 Rosas'. Others call it warmth, I think it's balance.So much interest for having "normal" life of the young protagonists has its pros and cons. On the one hand, the manners and alien narration largely due to the drama that is its outcome allows a very meritorious reconstruction of a Madrid fresh out of a war, and José Luis Alcaine makes magic on the picture (sometimes too much), with a very good art direction and a few digital effects above our national average. The downside is that the events prior to the capture of the Roses end up being something already seen, with a feeling of watching an episode of luxury 'Amar en tiempos revueltos' which is not shaken until the last half hour, much more interesting. This point is precisely the weakest of the film, feeling that all this already have seen you before.Apart from the great work in the technical section, highlight the interpretive effort of the protagonists. Verónica Sánchez and Pilar López de Ayala maintain a good tone, without exaggeration, but for me that really shine are Marta Etura (somo always), Bárbara Lennie (idem), Nadia De Santiago and Gabriella Pession.En summary, correct adaptation of Emilio Martínez-Lázaro, in which parties shine more than all, and unless is shaken almost pamphleteering tone of any similar production. A 6.</body>
</review>
