<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="The invasion" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Invasion is practically a disguised, free and totally unnecessary remake. And as a thriller, fails miserably in its first precept, the scheming and keep in suspense to the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>There are literary works for which the film feels a special weakness, and they are transferred to the big screen on a regular basis by the various cinemas worldwide. But it is striking how the case of the novel by Jack Finney La invasion of the thieves of bodies, which in just fifty years has seen four adaptations to each person more distinct.For anyone to devote his life to the film, whether technical, directors or actors, it seems that one of your goals is the reach Hollywood, the Mecca of the seventh art. It is not surprising that after this masterpiece which is the sinking, Hollywood tentara to Olivier Hirschbiegel. And the result is invasion, a science fiction thriller starring Nicole Kidman and Daniel Craig in which a strange alien virus is slowly seizing of human beings. After seeing invasion, one to heist a terrible doubt, and is if the alien virus is also transmitted through the film projected on a screen, that the film not only not thrilled but leaves you totally frozen. More after a short time of anguish which our brain is being debated in this dilemma, came to the conclusion: the affected is the own Hirschbiegel, who has lost the ability to convey emotions to the audience. Leaving aside the usual bugs and inconsistencies of the script, the development of the story is how much less strange, and the character development is simply non-existent. Hirschbiegel has not lost what good do behind the camera, giving the movie a good packaging, although occasionally chaotic Assembly can play tricks. Unlike the characters of invasion, cannot sleep, viewers are victims of a deep torpor. Between yawn and yawn, halfway through the suffering comes the best of the tape, the purported hug between George Bush and Hugo Chávez, which will cause a flood of laughter among the respectable. Nicole Kidman for its part remains in the descending line in which embarked after the hours, while Daniel Craig, Jeremy Northam and Jeffrey Wright dedicated his effort to defend something virtually indefensible.Invasion is practically a disguised, free and totally unnecessary remake. And as a thriller, fails miserably in its first precept, the scheming and keep in suspense to the Viewer. Perhaps the virus made its nest in Hollywood, annulling the capacity of their films to convey emotions.</body>
</review>
