<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Stardust" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Stardust is a fun, and exciting film that will enjoy as nice to anyone who wants to enter without prejudice in a story not taken seriously if same.</summary>
	<body>Fantasy cinema experienced a boom since Peter Jackson broke the box office around the world with the adaptation of the Lord of the rings. In Hollywood they interpreted it as a sign of the potential of the genre, and if there are not, the Chronicles of Narnia, Eragon, the six signs of light, all of them, with strong influences from the films of Jackson.Ahora it is the turn to Stardust, movie that adapts the work of Neil Gaiman, tells how a small village in England in the 19th century is separated from a magical world by a wall. Tristan (Charlie Cox), crosses the magical world to pick up a fallen star and thus be able to marry Victoria (Sienna Miller). However, upon arriving, he meets that the fallen star named Yvaine (Claire Danes), which must protect from a wicked witch (Michelle Pfeiffer). One of the main virtues of Stardust is that not taken seriously if same, giving Matthew Vaugh a tone quite attractive autoparodia. Also has its good dose of humor, and pure at this point, it is impossible not to mention the character of a Robert DeNiro giving vent to his comic vis. But taken seriously, the story is interesting and has all the ingredients for a good tape of entertainment. Stardust captures the viewer's attention from the first moment, and the intensity and pace of the film not decay at any time despite its long duration. At the technical level, it is very successful, and interpretive level, all actors perform to a high level.Stardust is a fun, and exciting film that will enjoy as nice to anyone who wants to enter without prejudice in a story not taken seriously if same. It is far from the levels of the Lord of the rings, but it clearly improves the rest of fantastic films made in its wake.</body>
</review>
