<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El sueño de Cassandra" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cassandra´s Dream is one of the more loose of all films of Woody Allen, who uses themes already exploited in Match Point, Scoop, or offences and misdemeanours.</summary>
	<body>True to its autumnal appointment, comes the new Woody Allen film in a year in which precisely the figure of New York filmmaker has been one of the most giving that talk. And it is that without doubt the filming of the project Spanish of Allen (who will take title Vicky Cristina Barcelona) has created a great expectation, that will significantly benefit the commercial Cassandra´s Dream.En race this new work, Allen returns to play some of the themes already played in his previous works, Match Point and Scoop (although this was a comedy)(it still very much in mind the murder and its consequences). On this occasion, two brothers who for various reasons urgently needed a large amount of money, are facing the decision to achieve their dreams if they accept to kill a person. Woody Allen remains Woody Allen, i.e. Cassandra´s Dream is a film that possesses an excellent Bill, but however it is not at the height of the filmography from the New York filmmaker. The script uses the recurring questions (murder, ethical and moral issues, the fault, repentance) in the recent film of Allen, becoming the development of history and their own it plot something tired and repetitive. Even calls attention to one of the female characters is an actress with a desire to succeed, as Scarlett Johansson in Match Point. The interpretive level of the tape is one of their greatest virtues, with Ewan McGregor and Colin Farrell simply extraordinary, that accompanies a no less brilliant Tom Wilkinson, and Hayley Atwell, genuine revelation of the film.Cassandra´s Dream is one of the more loose of all films of Woody Allen, who uses themes already exploited in Match Point, Scoop, or offences and misdemeanours. In the film only we can recognize the usual ingenuity of Allen, lost among so much philosophical digression.</body>
</review>
