<review author="Silvia Giner" title="La Luna en Botella" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Moon in the bottle is the story of one of them, people who dreams of change lives with everyday utopias, those that are not intended to necessarily change the world, but the way it treats us.</summary>
	<body>Today I had a wonderful experience to see this movie, I have finally seen the possibility of doing something different in Spain come true. Thank God, the universe has conspired with Grojo (Director of the film) to make us the greatest gift this year. A film full of that magical surrealist makes you vibrate and believe that No, it can be a Yes and that simply believe to be.The Moon in the bottle for me as an actress is the light of hope for the film Spanish, is the hope to work with a genius, full of Bohemian románticismo. Grojo means an incentive to continue with a profession in Spain is completely undermined.The aesthetics of the film reminded me much Mouling Rouge (bridging the gap Hispanic), the soundtrack is talented, catchy and there are moments where ries of happiness and excitement, mythical times for a script with a clearer message as utopian, but that is precisely, have our own utopia cosmic (in my case would be working in a movie like this) to become brave, but tell us how mad we done things outside the norm, somo brave because we not only want to be, also want to be (Carmen Rico mythical phrase). It was time that someone look details, millimeter, whereas vital even to the cat that passes through the streets. And make no mistake, the donkey is the true protagonist.There are minor characters from life, that we are used to see and continue to be secondary but with more importance, but the interpretation of these is so brutal that they arrive to become real animals in the House, leaving the novice players (Barbara Goenaga and Edu Soto) light years. In fact the only downside that I am going to make the movie is this, Barbara and Edu are absolutely insignificant, minimal and overshadowed by so much talent: Dominique Pinon, Pep Jové, Star Zimmerman (fabulously regia and immense and for samples, the sequence with the piano to arrive at the café: spectacular), Michael Jenn, Joan Dalmau, Federico Luppi, Francisco Algora and Richard Collins-Moore. That piece of actors is that not is which is best of them.It is a shame that people with so much talent has to do the misfortune that his film has no distribution, is not fair. Sometimes I have said that there are films so wonderful that they are not suitable for all tastes, this is one of them. The average viewer is not ready for this avalanche of talent.Note by the directorHay people who loves to say no. People tired of hearing it. And there are people whose life is broken then of a not.The Moon in the bottle is the story of one of them, people who dreams of change lives with everyday utopias, those that are not intended to necessarily change the world, but the way it treats us. As the story progresses, the characters discover that not everything is impossible and that there is always a second chance; It is enough to really believe in it.Music, circus and cabaret in a choral story with Spanish actors, French, Argentines, English, Americans, Koreans, Swedes or Chilean, assembled or mixed in coffee Rossignol, a place with very special charm and personality, where the music of René Dupéré played the role of universal language. You can be in any Western capital of our days. Coffee Rossignol, everyone together around the piano, to laugh, to cry, to love. must be a party!If manage to spread the hope, the illusion. If do, forget what they think or tell others. If add a point of insanity, rebellion and transgression.We will end up putting the Moon in that bottle.GROJO</body>
</review>
