<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Death Sentence" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The only thing offered to us is an insignificant entertainment with the typical American hero whose amount of inconsistencies is endless.</summary>
	<body>They say evil tongues that everything is invented in the world of cinema. Originality is dead and we are witnessing the same movie over and over again with minor variations. The penalty is that some of these films are not only remixes of all of the above if not they don't have neither the vision nor the ambition to contribute something new or original to its predecessors.We say Death Sentece is an eye for an eye look American History X. If I'm going to a production of dubious quality and 95 to explain the reason that Kevin Bacon me bored. A family happy and perfect is destroyed because of a senseless murder, either a poor kid in a gas station or a poor girl in her own home. As we all know the American justice well has never worked so it is always better to finish the work yourself, while Sally Field is more well-behaved and leaves the justice to mess up and release the murderer for lack of evidence seems that Mr Bacon saw the previous movie and decided to boycott the trial to be executing his own revenge more bloody and sloppy hand.It is obvious that there is not much difference except that putting a man on the lead role gives the license allow more scenes of action and violence free to dress the footage.One of my multiple theories says that if a tape is not a comedy begins with recordings of home videos of a happy family often end up being an unmitigated disaster. In the case of Death Sentence only makes water, isn't totally disposable through the presence of Kevin Bacon which seems to have made a pact with the devil to not age and thus perform such diverse films (something like his colleague Nicolas Cage) so in the long run his name is no guarantee of a good product. Even more lost in this universe appears John Goodman in a role that surreal pure is even comical.The penalty is that the promotion is taken so enserio about its own product qualifying production Shakesperiana or Greek tragedy when in reality the Director of Saw the only thing offered to us is an insignificant entertainment with the typical American hero whose amount of inconsistencies is endless: how to learn to shoot a weapon a type that has never had a gun?, Why the police not stop you before?, is it necessary to shave you to look like a gang member?,.</body>
</review>
