<review author="José A. Peig" title="Stardust" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We have the happy moment of discovering a little gem that stands out from the thriving mediocrity that has prevailed in the most recent fantasy film.</summary>
	<body>Stardust proposes a fiction that develops halfway between two worlds, and plays with the viewer through the ruse of crossing genres and tones. Stardust is a libérrima joke of evasion; the mode when it starts (a decrease from the stars) and sequence with which completed the story (an upgrade to the same sidereal space), and taking into account the profiles and the variables that define the crux of the narrative, we have a sample of how the fantasy film argues in its own laws, where anything goes and everything is credible always and when the creators of the work in question have been able to form a coherent idea in what refers to the tone and meaning. Stardust is one of these pieces need not be justified nor develop an argument with hairs and signals so that the viewer can enter in the game. It is, in itself, a game of imagination in the service of the Viewer.Film in Bruges, Princes and princesses, sword, magic, strange beings, happy ending. With these ingredients, the logical thing is to come up with a bland and predictable product. If we attend a basic rule in the art of narration, it teaches us that always we dip ingredients common to a model or subgenre, but importantly recombinarlos and build profiles with the pulse of the creator, who returns to the archetypal land to raise his wand and leave there a singular impression. It may be a failed film Stardust, you notice that it could have been much more versatile in all its parts, but we have the happy moment of discovering a little gem that stands out from the thriving mediocrity that has prevailed in the most recent fantasy film.As we have already said, the story is not original, but Matthew Vaughn film has two very important virtues: the construction of characters, even being planted on a stereotype, these have their own personality and possess adequate at its end aesthetic and playful freshness. The narrative is surprisingly agile, takes full advantage of the elements of healthy comedy and irony to build relations between characters, situations and the varied elements of visual, but careful imagery, Yes, at least, quite concise, tailored to the needs of the story, regardless - in general terms - habitual abuse of special effects. This blend of fantasy, love, irony and satire, works and also manages to escape with solvency aimed towards the sentimental scenes: where it is approaching the danger of falling into "cakes" field, the script and structure save the moment with the extravagant gesture of some of his landscapes or funniest characters. To highlight the Robert de Niro and Michelle Pfeiffer, which look a histrionics that, in this case, fits perfectly with the overall tone of the work. In fact, we could define Stardust as a histrionic fantasy style with right themselves.Your main problem is excess footage, another usual ballast in productions of the style. In the background appear characters, passages and dispensable dialogues, that do that - especially in ecuador of the narration - the dominant fluidity lost in dramatic depth and then is when the story is dispersed unnecessarily. Fortunately, in the last stretch recovery pulse, with a hilarious final duel. And, finally, despite being a product quite "sui generis", is as delicious as the traditional fairy tale, while delivering his strangeness without that is heard to clench the pretentious attempt. Pure sympathy and conviviality.</body>
</review>
