<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Redacted" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not get nor much less do trace irregular career of its director or contribute anything new.</summary>
	<body>The film is shot in Jordan halfway between a mockumentary and a conventional fiction. The mixture supposed initially significantly increase the realism for even more impact on the critical message towards the conflict in Iraq, but precisely that mixture is which is not working properly. Brian de Palma is not Paul Greengrass and the first appears to believe that realism is achieved basically showing the faces of boredom of the marines in a guard post at the pace of a classical music for minutes. Palma mix video cameras, security cameras, Youtubes, style of story and film format but without much success little that the viewer controls minimally the coherence of the cinematographic language. The result is not away from a series of prepared stagings and some good performances which however fail never seem real. And we are then left alone with the history and this because it is not too original nor holds any remarkable surprise for us. It was among others, the same Brian de Palma who already told us this same story in 89 with "Hearts of iron". What was on the Viet Nam war and this now is supposedly inspired by the massacre of Mahmudiya. And I then wonder: what is the message that gives me as a spectator? that the marines get bored and unmotivated and confused rape and kill without mercy in Iraq? what war does not make sense?According to the director: "the film is an attempt to bring to the American people the reality of what is happening in Iraq" &hellip; "Are images that will stop the war." "One only expects that these images indignant to the public enough to motivate its legislators to vote against this war," staging a violation of some energúmenos for more effectively draw the attention to the American people with a bit of care is under my opinion give information biased and sensationalist, because the real killers and responsible travel with chauffeur, play golf and lie their ass in offices of luxury while taking decisions that bombed and they are left to die without any regard to thousands of people in poor countries but with natural resources plunder. Wars kill, is violated, is amputates, steals, was humiliated, tortured and this is unfortunately so obvious that it would have interested me much more observe the miserable and frivolous lives of the real culprits of the conflict and not a couple of illiterate Texans with license to kill and rape.Half the resolution of the real case, the impact of those affected on the one hand and the other is left in the movie and discovered great that in reality all this exposed in somewhat disheveled manner, without much I care or talent, only to cause in some way. That if it ends with a series of photographs of murdered Iraqi civilians, as if it were actually a video of Manos Unidas, but with that one, actually, as a viewer, do not know very well how to react after the whole.Redacted left me cold and although it is clear that whatever is done to try to espabilar consciousness apeleladas in the Western world is necessary and always well intentioned and received, as movie fails nor much less trace the irregular career of its director or contribute anything new.</body>
</review>
