<review author="Txapulin" title="Stardust" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film has been a real surprise. Expected me a child movie full of special effects and familiar faces and I found a rather youthful film with an adult and ironic humor that reminds "The Princess Bride".</summary>
	<body>This film has been a real surprise. Expected me a child movie full of special effects and familiar faces, just to hang out, and I found a rather youthful movie, Yes, full of special effects and familiar faces, but with a very successful history, good characters well interpreted, and ironic humour reminiscent of another fairy tale of humor: the Princess Bride. When seeing the letters at the end, I saw that the film is based on a novel by Neil Gaiman, for a moment crossed me wires and thought that it was the same author that the Princess Bride, but, the latter is not William Goldman, and are of different generations. The novel the Princess Bride is 1973 and the novel Stardust is 1997, and guess that the latter owes a lot to the first. It tells the story of a character born from the relationship between two different worlds. on the one hand the village of Wall, which, as its name indicates, is close to a wall which marks the boundary between England and the imaginary world of Faery, where is the Kingdom of Stormhold. You only need to mislead the guardian of the wall to enter the world where witches and the princes are fighting and killing among them to achieve immortality or the reign. Immortality comes if you get the heart of a star, and the reign will be for one of the heirs to find a flying and elusive diamond that has been lost among the stars. Both elements converge in Yvaine, the character of Claire Danes, who will be prosecuted by the ambitious throughout the film, including the protagonist, who also want a star for handing over her to his beloved, only that in this case the circumstances will change radically.The film is littered with stars (in Hollywood, in this case), although they are mostly in supporting roles. Michelle Pfeiffer is a witch in search of eternal youth. This woman you must put the same makeup when you old witch where rejuvenates, because it is equal to that in the witches of Eastwick, and that twenty years ago. Robert de Niro is an ambiguous pirate captain (mmmm for what sounds like?) of a flying boat which will collect rays of storm. Peter O'Toole (which is everywhere lately) is the dying King of Stormhold. One of his sons is Rupert Everett. Ian McKellen (who is also on all sides) is the Narrator. And the beautiful (that not so good actress) Claire Danes in the role of shooting star. The rest of performers are less known.On the film itself, the film elements not highlighted, but it is because they are at the service of the story, not to highlight, as it should be. The sets and costumes are very well. The special effects are good when they are funds or 3D models, but they sing the effects 2D (smoke, fire, refulgencias, etc.). The music is markedly epic, so much that it almost calca and mixes part of Pirates of the Caribbean and the Lord of the rings. As I have said, the brighter is the script, the story full of very good details of humor, that does not prevent adult references sex, and the definition of the characters, and a rhythm and a plot that converge in a beautiful final fairy tale so magical as original.</body>
</review>
