<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Don erre que erre" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The work peak of Paco Martínez Soria. Tremendous peliculón for evenings of boredom and torpor</summary>
	<body>Well, so you may see that a critic of posh like me (medium hair for others) lives of its readers, I decided to oiros. It could have followed with author movies that you like so much, or criticisms of Bulgarian melodramas that you dazzle, but let's take a small twist. As the week is long and the films I see you not always interested, let's return to those films that all and all you have seen. To see if you animais and discussed a little about Spanish film classics. To start and go preparing for what can this be, we have what many consider peak of Paco Martínez Soria, so to enjoy the work. By the way, the stars for these special cases system has changed, as you can see.The film is Don Rodrigo, a man going to the Bank to collect 257 pesetas. Total, that at the time of the cashier transaction - Don Rodrigo a mugger enters the Bank and gets everything inside, including its 257 pesetas. After a bit of fuss and sofocones, Don Ricardo discovers that scoundrels workers of the entity do not want him to return their 257 pesetas because is lan when removed because they were not owned by the Bank. This begins an odyssey that surprise you the classical, with Don Ricardo unleashed that shows the values of perseverance and that justice WINS always.Don Paco Martínez Soria sausager in the costume of the noble Don Ricardo gross to defend the rights of people on foot in the Spain of the skin of a bull. Fight against giants to achieve what the desires, their longed 257 pesetas. On the way he loses more than that amount, but what is fair is fair. Well, this is a tremendous peliculón for evenings of boredom and torpor. The argument hooks from the outset by its strength and forcefulness, addition to get everyone Don Ricardo and want that justice will prevail. Situations affecting this nice gentleman Spanish are more wild, including a crazy hunt. A time peak, for me, is when a guard fine you and to recognize you want to remove the fine and the flatly refuses. Surprise your scream "Libeeeeeertaaaaaad" of Braveheart. Only lacked a Spain Viva full lung.In short, we seen anachronistically, have a light film to help us take the siesta ritmillo, but outside by the honking (cries) that stuck during all of it. If you see at the time, critical tremendous society (come on, I say, that I am not so old for having lived that time). Four stronger gold, not narrowly reaching total dandruff.</body>
</review>
