<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Promesas del Este" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cronenberg deals with how the tentaculares mafia environments prevent its abandonment to who one day formed part of them or how extends to the lives of those who relate some, if you want side, with its surroundings</summary>
	<body>A history of violence as this Eastern promises demonstrate a manifest interest in David Cronenberg in the vicinity of the violent world of the mafia. Last two tapes of this director of granado in the fantasy genre last not strive to address these criminal clans with a similar to emblematic works like the Godfather depth charge. But yes choose them as a framework for more concrete stories about characters caught up in the Web of the underworld.In complicity with the splendid work of the chameleonic Viggo Mortensen, star of both films, the Canadian filmmaker discusses how these tentaculares environments prevent its abandonment to who one day formed part of them or how extends to the lives of those who relate some, if you want side, with its surroundings. The character of Naomi Watts, a midwife at a London hospital, will happen this last in Eastern promises. After bringing to the world the son of a Ukrainian teenager who died after giving birth, she, also of Russian origin, lies in the moral obligation to come up with a family who entrust the care of the newborn orphan, at the time that can communicate you the news of the death of the mother.The track of a newspaper in the hands of the young dead mother will lead to Anna Khitrova up to a family of the Russian mafia who used this girl to prostitution and then threw it as commodity disposable having her become a junkie. There will encounter with the mysterious Nikolai Luzhin (the character of Mortensen), a chófer-recadero - thug in the service of the spoiled son of the boss of the clan (a great Vincent Cassel). His father, played by Armin Mueller-Stahl, skillfully represents the iconic figure of the leader of the family clan, as well as of prominent CAPO between the various Mafia families. In this relationship as father and son remain during the film is enough film topic while isn't anything new in the film shear stress between a strict mafia leader and his wayward little exemplary son.Khitrova findings through the daily dangerously converge you to this world with own rules away altogether from the other that we agree to call normal. Only one-man parco, with neat typical aspect of Russian mobster, records of compass and protection to not interfere more than we. Nikolai, who claims to be only a driver, knows a lot more than what counts and silent as you can to survive in a community where disputes are often settled with the body of the opponent dumped into the River.Without being a film of a continuous violence, yes onscreen raw violence the House brand Cronenberg, who usually does not hurt him in clothes show more rough details. Icy photography in a modern London and a good general choice of the cast are the guarantees of this Cronenberg film with similar plot paths passing to the of his magnificent, and perhaps higher, predecessor.</body>
</review>
