<review author="Juan Fondevila" title="El viaje de Chihiro" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I'm glad that there are still people like Miyazaki without useless sensiblerías and with fair doses of love and pain dares to tell a story out of regular flows of horror and tragedy without sense of many films.</summary>
	<body>Lately it is difficult that surprised us books, film or art. It seems that the only way to innovate is to be increasingly hard in the arguments and that only you can say new things from the deep pain and stories instances of rape, concentration camps, repressive dictatorships, incest, Sexualities fustradas and other various horrors of humanity. Above all that is necessary to esribir if someone needs to do so, because literature has no limits or restrictions and provide intense looks on humans, but let us not forget that art and the lbros have been distinguished by its diversity and capacity for expression of different forms of thinking of the people and the immense tapestry of colors of the world. Apart from horror there are compassion, will, friendship and imagination. Throughout history have been created worlds like Middle-Earth and extraordinary adventures such as the of the history forever which, without being real, have taught us much more than some wonderful novels less fanciful in facing life in this complex world.For this reason, the other day when I saw spirited away happened to me two things. The first teaching is that the manga, cartoons, can bring to art and cinema treasures if they are well used. We must look out everything above topics, because perhaps it brought me more this film that certain books of brainy intellectuals. The second was the recovery of hope that there is still people who invents and makes art with its weapons, using imagination and the creation of new worlds. Seeing it reminded me of certain stages of my childhood and those nights eternal asking me was the ginger cake that took the Cinco.Me am glad that there are still people like Hayao Miyazaki without useless sensiblerías and with fair doses of love and pain dares to tell a story out of regular flows of horror and tragedy without sense of many filmsbooks and modern art. I will not tell anything about the plot of the movie. The living room of your House, overstuffed sofa, a television and a dvd you will give many more answers than I am about it. Happy holidays!</body>
</review>
