<review author="Juan Fondevila" title="Las vírgenes suicidas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unfortunately sometimes hides under beautiful faces, blonde Manes to wind and eyes of blue infinity. The misfortune is sometimes found in large houses of extensive gardens, where the leaves of autumn sheet hides the lawn. The misfortune is sometimes a shining Apple with a worm lurking inside.</summary>
	<body>Live between the intense aroma of the talent does not guarantee that art shoot your hands, eyes and mouth. The fragrance of the art is whimsical, dance through the air, sits in a few people, not passed from parents to children. But there are times that a surprise that intense perfume, which transforms the mind of him who plays, draws a small tour and just meters further, as a legacy, sets its destination. Sofia Coppola was impregnated and the Virgin suicides was his first demonstration of his intense and fragrant perfume of talent. Perhaps his first hit was take to film the great novel by Jeffrey Eugenides and transported to the screen the melancholy of the sunset that inhabit its pages. Unfortunately sometimes hides under beautiful faces, blonde Manes to wind and eyes of blue infinity. The misfortune is sometimes found in large houses of extensive gardens, where the leaves of autumn sheet hides the lawn. The misfortune is sometimes a shining Apple with a worm lurking inside.While watching the movie I wanted and not wanted to be neighbor of the Lisbon. I wanted that Lux (Kirsten Dunst) I would hammer the heart to nailing her eyes on me showing me hatred and eternal love. I wanted to be invited to the only and last party that took place in the Lisbon House and dance spinning to a sister, her golden mane, her white dress. I wanted to approach me with trembling step and knock on the door of the Office of the father (James Woods) and make an appointment with his daughter as if you request a piece of heaven. And challenge the powerful gaze of the mother (Kathleen Turner) with boldness that only has a crush on fifteen years. And, at the same time, I wanted to escape the charm of those five girls, forget them, send them away. Because I knew that it was in danger of as those neighbouring the Lisbon boys awaken me years later with a dry throat, heart throbbing and the mind full of those now unattainable infinite blue eyes. There are beautiful olmos dead inside.</body>
</review>
