<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Buenos Días, Noche" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Buongiorno, Notte is social and political cinema in its purest form. It is a tape of claustrophobic fear and anger, despair and concerns to equal doses that deals with a topic which, unfortunately, is still strong today.</summary>
	<body>"Buongiorno, Notte", takes its title from a verse by Emily Dickinson and tells one of the most black episodes of the Italian history of the setenta.16 of March 1978. The so-called Red Brigades, a group of Communist character has kidnapped Aldo Moro, a former Italian Minister of the Catholic Democratic Party just talks with parties Italian Communist Marxists of the moment. After murdering the bodyguards in public they keep held for almost two months in a rented apartment whose only Union abroad is Chiara, a young woman who works in the Ministry and begins to doubt the noble initial purposes to see the political implications and media of these acts.Buongiorno, Notte is social and political cinema in its purest form. It is a tape of claustrophobic fear and anger, despair and concerns to equal doses that deals with a topic which, unfortunately, is still strong today. Almost documentary desire of an era is reflected in images from archive of news of the time and the front pages of newspapers that shook the country creating a false sense of reality that clashes with the oniric pieces of her female protagonist and were quite dispensable part of somewhat confusing. But no doubt Buongiorno, Notte goes beyond, is a critical approach to a situation whose wounds are still open (the sons of Moro gave the go-ahead the tape and praised the treatment given to the character of his father), in fact even with a bit of historical perspective former members of the armed band have talked about the feelings that are reflected in the tape and justified their acts in the same way that make it the own characters. A film that teaches and recalls without desire to politicize, where the bad guys are so heinous, nor the good are saints, a film showing the principles, remorse and the decisions that lead to a normal person to fight for his politics to unsuspected heights and where the more innocent young may end up being a terrible terrorist and innocent boy being accused for a crime he did not commit.The story is based on real events but narrated in a way very free that, apart from the crosses of releases of the band with the Government during the "popular trial", little is known of his captivity.Real are the letters of Aldo to his family, the replies of the President Giulio Andreotti (recently convicted of the intellectual authorship of the assassination in 1979 of journalist that spread the former President with the Italian mafia links) as well as the same Pope Paul VI. Documentation for the film is quite long, fit to highlight other two tapes that narrate the same events "The Moro (Il caso Moro) case", in 1986 directed by Giuseppe Ferrara, and the recent "Piazza delle Cinque Lune" of Renzo Martinelli. "the prisoner (Il prigioniero)", written together with Paola Tavella by Anna Laura Braghetti, responsible for monitoring the hostage and the House of the Caetani StreetMarco Bellocchio is freely inspired to make the film. The rest is filled with a bit of wit and common sense to give the history of Chiara and his double life of interest needed to become an anti-hero with remorse caught by own events. It premiered dubbed on Spain.</body>
</review>
