<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Stardust" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nice film of fantastic adventures, that will not go to the history of the cinema precisely.</summary>
	<body>Pretty pretty fantastic adventure film, full of action and fantasy, appropriate for all ages, although not precisely for the smallest of the House because you have violence and assassinations, although almost always shown with a black humor, can't be violent and unpleasant (again, for the little ones).It is well told, with clarity and without stun to the respectable with abstruse scenes. Here the argument is fácilcemente and the characters quite well defined, are sharp from the start.The only thing negative can be its long, slightly more than two hours to tell a story that would have sufficed with just over an hour and a half. But there are scenes of filling half of the film, which are irregular in their interest and that bedevil the good rhythm that, in general, has the tape. An imaginative tape, with action, humor and love, full of romanticism, and also, as I said earlier, of violence.All this under the prism of fantasy, which is the Foundation which supports an argument where the good fight against evil, an evil which manifests itself in human greed, lust for power and the search for eternal youth.Arguably, it is positive because the human virtues are imposed, in unequal battle, defects, criminal acts of petty things.The best thing is its first half-hour, where they feel the bases of history, and the character played by Robert de Niro, this time something more active than in other tapes where the great actor often simply comply (and charge), without further. Here she plays an atypical character, with substance, which is in line with the new times where deeper human values are imposed on the choice which one to choose, by more politically and socially incorrect seem. Something exemplary in the background, although unfortunately there are samples of parody and some coarse salt in the representation of that character, something that makes laughter, but that would have perhaps required something more serious.But, in General, it's a very entertaining movie, where imagination overflows to each frame and contains good moments and characters, such as the goat turned into humans. Gets very well the time, although I am afraid that it leaves not much footprint in memory after a while.</body>
</review>
