<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Yo hice a Roque III" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Amazing script, great cast of actors, rustic decorated and surreal dialogues. An essential wonder in any Caspoteca self-respecting.</summary>
	<body>Damn, not is that they recorded new films, taking in the Spanish film library wonders like this. They had to Rocky and Roque with his "roquina", where you will stop.The film is two colleagues of the school that things are not going too well. One of them (Esteso) has women and children, while teammate (Pajares) lives of journal a doubtful please made him at the tender age of 6 years. Both work in a nonsense of a detergent Pilón, which causes the first joke of the film called. Roque (Pajares) was Boxer and champion of Melilla, although for many years. On the other hand, Frederick (Esteso) is a retired jockey since it has gained (and is old, that a kid is not). Total, Frederick decides to get rid of his companion tendiendole a trap that combat against the champion, to see if it wrecks. And there is Paco (Antonio Ozores) as the owner of the gym. And it is already bundled.Well, this is not going over the Spanish film. Damn, is very good, all absolutely everything. For starters, the cast of actors, which is the cream of our cinema. Then, the script is incredible, that there are no remaining. What mind has thought this? And originality of the title, which I say this? A wonder. In addition, if add you that nipples from time to time, dialogs are surreal, and the sets are "rustic" leave we face a masterpiece of the Iberian casposidad.In short, essential in any "caspoteca" self-respecting. Although to savor it well, well, it is best to have it recorded on VHS with the "fly" for Telecinco in the right bottom margin. Damn, I'm dying of laughter, that good!Mythical phrases from the movie "not be if fuck you or operating you Appendix, almost better first thing." "I have no neck, I'm poor". Only by hearing this, is worth seeing her. And to tell the truth, gives very good vibes see it. It is so silly that he is appreciated in this world so crazy that we played live.</body>
</review>
