<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="El Orfanato" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although this represents a good step for the formation of an industry of gender in the country, as a film it is pretty poor and easily forgettable.</summary>
	<body>Few things are already say about the orphanage (2007), except perhaps the surprise which has caused me tremendous glove silk with which criticism has dealt with a film that in practice nothing more or less drinking proposal. I put that I speak not of the typical tarifadas criticisms with which the distributors tend to support their products; praise to the opera prima of Juan Antonio Bayona have reached even several strata of "independent" critique. And is that if something I clear after the viewing of this film is that, in its case, seems to be two different views: those who see the tape as a contribution to the "cinema" Spanish (specifically those that hold in genre cinema and not repetitive dramones of Civil war or vulgar social proselytizing) and those that judge her only as a film. The views are unequal, but that is due to the work of Bayonne is also.And is that, purely narrative level, the failure at the orphanage are more than evident: input becomes obvious that we have a film patchwork whose most interesting sequences are because they are taken from classics like Suspense (1961), the changeling (1980) and Poltergeist (1982), or even more recent like the other works (2001) and fragile (2005)all of them (admittedly) far superior to film Bayona, that happens ultimately be another exponent of the already worn formula for children, old mansions crappy and secrets of the past, everything revolving around the already very overused archetype of "Mother courage" to face supernatural forces to recover the missing son. Difficult it has Mr Bayona to achieve something interesting from a premise which is not given any new contribution, and above all the weight lead role in an actress so limited as Belén Rueda, who jumps from the incapacitating to the hysteria of inexplicable form.Another problem is the beginning, in which the character of Belén Rueda arrives with his family to the old Asturian House stood where the orphanage of his childhood, becomes too long and uninteresting. It is only when I finally get the supernatural element Bayonne film begins to charge force, a virtue which is revealed in what to me is one of their best sequence: one involving the paranormal investigators, which included a Geraldine Chaplin making Zelda Rubinstein. Unfortunately, this interesting time (that gives way to a frantic and cash supernatural showdown between the protagonist and the inhabitants of the House) is truncated by the arrival of a disastrous end; the final twist that encloses the history is not only predictable up to say enough is enough, but it hides behind an overly sweetened and corny, outcome that is trying to be poetic and sublime but fails miserably. That is blame not only of the obvious constraints of Belén Rueda as an actress, but a script full of plot holes, inconsistencies and loose ends that don't have nothing better to do than defraud the viewer at the end.Still, not everything is bad, that film Bayona gets really good moments when he tries to recreate in its atmosphere and flee melodramatic sentimentalism. It is only when it escapes from its potential as a horror film when it falls. In addition, the mere fact of that attention be given to the film genre already made in this country (and Spanish) is a step forward, even if the benefit is this film and not others much better made previously, as for example the the Devil's backbone (2000), by Guillermo del Toro, who here acts as executive producer making the film in a couple theme of his work El laberinto del Fauno (2006). Apart from that, the amount of positive reviews that this film has received is done to me inexplicable.The orphanage, therefore, can be seen in two ways: while represents a good step for the formation of an industry of gender in the country, such as film is quite poor and easily forgettable. As as happened with 28 weeks later (2007), we have a medium-sized tape that has received a bombo disproportionate solely because his head is Spanish. That there is no who remove me the head.</body>
</review>
