<review author="Jack Torrance" title="The invasion" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The end product is a correct thriller science fiction with quite a few moments of terror and tension, although it's not absolutely I anodino, if that is quite irrelevant.</summary>
	<body>The current socio-political State in the world is a suitable breeding ground for the horror movies &amp; science fiction, always reflects the climate of his time, including images that are significant of the events globally in the time in which it was created. However the current study films have cut wings and believe that the imagery of the film has to do with the collective subconscious is something naive, because what really moves the production of such films is profitable business. So, we have before us a new Remake: the fourth version of "Invasion of the body snatchers" called simply invasion. What a priori may be little right, given the relative closeness of the new version in the 1990s, becomes suggestive thanks to the situation of dementia and paranoia in which we live submerged. Unfortunately the interesting Olver Hirschbiegel director's vision has been mutilated and overhauled to conform to more complacent parameters. The merits of the film are concentrated in scattered moments that make suspicious are isolated scenes shot by the original director. However, the final product is a correct thriller science fiction with quite a few moments of terror and tension, although it's not absolutely I anodino, if that is quite irrelevant. There are several details that resemble a good independent film, with characters and unusual performances in the big Blockbusters, and there are several things it does well they resemble the previous works of the director of "The sinking", do not have continuity during the film. In general, the moments in which the invasion is taking shape are well developed and manage to reflect the phenomenon on a global scale in an effective way. The passages in which the protagonist realizes that something has changed and how has to not be discovered are also successful. The best of this new version is how definitively accepted that invasion really mean a possible change for good, and raises the question of whether really worth that the human race continues to exist.This is exemplified very well on a subtle level ending in the eyes of Nicole Kidman to teammate when everything seems to be remitido(un_final_que_huele_a_imposición_de_hollywood).A look that uncovers their sense of possible mistake. would not have been better to have been left to carry? is perhaps the most radical idea posed by this new version, which in the Fund, despite the final Hollywood aftertaste, is much more pessimistic others, considering that humans have no salvation from ourselves. Despite its many successes, the film, as a whole it is a failed experience. A montage of abrupt, without any kind of course makes the first minutes of the tape something that doesn't seem to be what he really wants. Sequences cut by a pattern that does not correspond to what it seems they wanted to translate to shoot them, as if needed few seconds more to ensure that they function correctly. If we add to this stupid and unnecessary flashbacks, horrendous infographics plans of targeted cells and a narrative drift due to the "inserts" the Wachosky, have a fresco of what not to do in a movie, right next to scenes that are within the best of the year. A monstrosity that simply can be seen and doesn't bother too, but that leaves a sediment of bitterness for not be able to see the original version as it was conceived. Perhaps this does not improve the present and even be too bland. But n invasion there are too many signs that are sensed a good movie that someone has tried to turn into something else. The result is a light work, passion without claw, but nor is any disaster and manages to entertain enough to Miss viewing.</body>
</review>
