<review author="Adrian Bravo" title="Funny Games" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When violence comes out of the television screen.</summary>
	<body>Funny Games is a stylus, a knife for close and acute leaf waiting for the chance to nail between your ribs to slowly bleed you viciously. Look back is always welcome to review the work of one of the most committed directors politically and socially from the European scene, Michael Haneke, and thank God, equally committed to crossing the borders of the cinematographic language from a perspective completely as author. The look is, if it fits, doubly wise, because he is about to release a remake of Funny Games in United States (Yes, Michael Haneke versioning himself, we assume / hope that it does to finance transgressors upcoming projects of which we are accustomed) starring the prolific Naomi Watts and Michael Pitt. If cache, the latest film from Haneke, poses an incisive look at the wound that caused the confrontation between the Algerian community in France and own Parisians in the 1960s, conflict that it resulted in the massacre of more than 400 Algerians (many of the remains may still lie at the bottom of the Seine), Funny Games emphasis in stark violence, violence by violence, from a political point of view less, although it can not help bring to light the ghosts that appear in almost all his films (the trivialization of violence, the hibernation of the blame in Western society, the desacralization of the brutality by the media, the class struggle &hellip;) Funny Games is the story of a family of upper class that is preparing to spend a quiet holiday in a luxurious coastal village, but their plans are truncated by the appearance of a perverse young couple, as dragos Clockwork Orange (and with a curiously similar aesthetics) get sibilinamente involved in their lives, at home, to inject blood and terror in their heads and play literally with their lives. When they seem to find a way of salvation, the perverse game beyond the screen, becomes global, meta-film, and we realize that there is no any exit. It is the triumph of pessimism, the tragic end, the triumph of the wicked game and the dissolution of the boundaries between reality and fiction. The film even performs a fast rewind to remove any hint of optimism, and executioners converse with the Viewer, forcing him to position of one side or another. Opulent society generates violence and this has no intention of diluting its effect and attacks with its virulence, and also makes it because Yes. Haneke makes us reflect on the inconvenience of numb before the images that show us the pain. Haneke films and this in particular, concerned with the current slasher of contemporary French cinema, and to some degree explains the critical success of a movie so hard and ultraviolence as A l'interieur, which a similar approach, won some prizes in this 2007 Sitges. When you see as a man kills another man through a television screen and not feel almost nothing, not you llaméis a psychologist, Michael Haneke and his Funny Games you will give the diagnosis.</body>
</review>
