<review author="José A. Peig" title="Eva al desnudo" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The dialogues are an exemplary example of organization, building character and sense of narrative, irony, laughing, melancholy, humor, replicas and contrarreplicas that leave us out of breath before the overwhelming dramatic force.</summary>
	<body>All about eve is a furious look at the world of film and theatre stars. Idolatry and the ambition to occupy the center of gravity in lathe which revolve the feelings, the need to see recognized the merits and compensate for the weakness with the love of the public. And forgive this emphasis, because the set of relationships described points to the need - so common and elemental - be loved, despite being part of a game without another rule to the manipulate others with the purpose of achieving stardom or staying in an influential position.On the one hand have a contradictory and personality full of edges that have an impact on the lives of their close to Margo Channing (Bette Davis), human expression of the idol, and, at the same time, it affects the entire development of the argument. She is the pálpito-antítesis of Eva, stir consciences and develops the conflict of a plot that is entangled in a choral drama where each character's actions expand items, interact and lead the development until its conclusion. Margo resignation to their status and, somehow, it represents the antithetical to the Eva's stance, since Margo attitudes underlying the desire to break the chains of the success, flee from fame to win love, leaving behind a mock youth. Eva, on the other hand, does not fear old age and will do everything to resemble his idol. Not hesitate to sell their feelings to win fame. The well-known phrase of Margo, has been very well, Eva, but I wouldn't worry both of the heart: you can always put that trophy in his stead, replacement of humanity expresses the vanity of who puts the hit above the true appreciation to their peers.Joseph l. Mankiewizc developed a fierce Chronicle on how a loser passionate about the art world ascends through the manipulation and foul play, to achieve his goal. He manages to synthesize in the character of Eva (Anne Baxter) two psychological dimensions; the sincere bonhomie and falsehood, a complex character that moves between these two lands until, in the end, faced with Addison (George Sanders), discover all their cards and reveals their weakness on the eve of a performance that will make it worthy of winning the trophy. The look of Mankiewizc ranges from satire and pessimism, links to the interpretive set through a smart game of complicity and mistrust, dissecting various records that make up the humanity of each character with enormous versatility. The dialogues are an exemplary example of organization, building character and sense of narrative, irony, laughing, melancholy, humor, replicas and contrarreplicas that leave us out of breath before the overwhelming dramatic force.The flat end is anthological; Multiple image expressed through a game of mirrors that synthesizes the struggle of egos developed throughout the entire film. Perfect image, ultimately, unhealthy idolatry that has inspired Eva in their climb to success.</body>
</review>
