<review author="Mario" title="Saw 4" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>While not he harbored hopes of the plot I hooked, itself at least hoped to find a good serving of sophisticated torture ready to be degustadas. Unfortunately, this time neither one nor the other.</summary>
	<body>Before gutting the fourth installment of Saw IV should clarify that he hurts from this rostrum criticize a saga of this caliber. LF and devoid of any kind of claim terror sagas are, as you know, much appreciated here, and the wanderings of Jigsaw (now converted into a parody of themselves) seems confirmed that they will arrive at least until his sixth delivery.Saw movies meet many of the requirements to become a legendary franchise in the style of Friday the 13th and nightmare on Elm Street: General characteristics Subrayadísimas, as the generosity when it comes to show blood and viscera (touching the gore in the third installment and seriously attenuated in the latter) the succession of deliveries without almost time for respitethe exploitation of the moderately surprising successes of the first part and the inevitable lack of coherence and claims, are shown on each of the films without any trap or cardboard. Saw doesn't fool anyone (at least no longer) and the spectator who comes to the room should be prepared for what you are going to offer.However, despite my appreciation for the bet casquera representing these tapes, can not help feel disappointed by its fourth installment. If in Saw III had relegated almost completely the spirit close to the thriller that could guess slightly in previous deliveries (mostly the first) by placing almost 100 percent of the action in a succession of the most macabre and hilarious torture, Saw IV replicates these more or less autoparódicos channels towards an indefinable style.The film again seeks to become strong in the final surprise, with more vigor that never in fact, becoming the script an impossible to gibberish by who has not seen the previous deliveries. It gives the feeling of that Darren Lynn Bousman seeks to recover the seriousness and grant a spirit of geometric building, designed as a whole from the start to the series of films. This claim, if it is it would fall under its own weight with a script that you know, if possible, more crazy than ever: the bulk of the plot is based on a policeman following scary puzzles, step-by-step plans and without skip one comma, totally and absolutely implausible, and, as on previous occasions, the narrative jumps between parallel stories focusing, in the second instance, the outrageous and unjustified (at least not correctly) origin of the psychopath.Again a surprising and unexpected ending adorns and accelerates the closure of the movie with two surprises this time, a quite interesting related to the timeline and the other, resobada and above more stupid than ever, concerning the characters. All this sprinkled with the already famous and effective melody marks House.In the visual section the movie loses many integers with respect to its predecessors. Devised by Jigsaw traps are unavoidable on this occasion; virtually no importance is given to the torture and most of the games are not too castings and they are very confusing. With the exception of one or two macabre jokes in the rest costs know the procedure to be taken by the victim, and above all shot with a crazy camera that stands before the clarity of situations. If it were not for the initial autopsy, strong point of the movie, the disappointment would be irreconcilable.Ultimately, even seeing Saw IV with a compassionate look, counsel as I consider myself of such proposals, not finished follow the thread to the director. While not he harbored hopes of the plot I hooked, itself at least hoped to find a good serving of sophisticated torture ready to be degustadas. Unfortunately, this time neither one nor the other.</body>
</review>
