<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Los Seis Signos de la Luz" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Totally expendable if you not with a minor. That Yes, I can assure you that if you have less than 14 years or your companion is in that age range is a secure implementation that will enjoy much.</summary>
	<body>I occasionally try to take me to the movies to a good critic I know, he is my cousin of nine years and may be useful for some movies that find me unclassifiable or certainly frustrating sea. Many years ago the producers realized that seeing a movie in the environment of a film plagued with people who enjoy the tape can affect the vision of the critic and make you feel a little more generous when it comes to writing about it. Why invite press in cinemas passes with children for children's films was a common practice that got quite good result. There is no heart that resist to say that a film is bad when hundreds of kids have been enjoying and throwing popcorn each others to your around because while the reader of your criticism is his father can not ignore the fact that the child has moved it well that, for better or for worseIt was the par public which created the film and that will consume it in cinemas, DVDs and various merchandising. The Variant that exists now is that there is a new genre of adventure after the emergence of fantasy films for children and adolescents is rebounding dramatically with child actors and epic adventures in parallel as the Chronicles of Narnia, Eragon, or Harry Potter worlds. The public of these is wider and it must be quite carefully already that although infants of up to fifteen years enjoy with these desktop divertimenti possible adult viewer who has enjoyed with ribbons as the Gonnies or the Chip Prodigioso wants to relive the 1980s and just deal with a simple deployment of effects special flavouring the last success of the Juvenile literature. The six signs of light tells the story of Will, an American teenager who has just moved with his large family to England and that will discover that it is chosen to carry out a special mission to find over time of the six signs of light to help fight against the darkness that want to take over the world. On his way to the signs Will count with the help of the ancient, timeless people who help the search engines to discover their powers and use them in time to save the world. I am a great follower of fantasy films from action-adventure. I grew up with adventurers with Hat and whip and Golden boys. I can not help that a teenager gets into a magical world remind children's readings as the history forever and all this background is what makes tapes like this become me something boring and loose. Invoice impeccable but careless in the care of adult audiences get leaving little footprint and a memory between nostalgic and pretentious after viewing. Totally expendable if you not with a minor. That Yes, I can assure you that if you have less than 14 years or your companion is in that age range is a secure implementation that will enjoy much.</body>
</review>
