<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Una verdad incómoda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What I dislike A really uncomfortable, that is exclusively based on a strong name and a so well perpetrated marketing campaign.</summary>
	<body>Documentary or Video political advertising? This is the idea I had in mind during the viewing of the tape. It is not that it is a shocking or my cousin has told me that climate change is as false as the Pérez tooth but it is actually scientific data and format of an incovenient truth giving enough to think about their doctrinal and scientific bases.Al Gore record entirely one of their multiple conferences on climate change and this will be the groso of content on the ecological problems of our planet, the rest is decorated with a handful of images of his political career, his family and his children. Many graphics, diagrams and photos demonstrating what almost everyone knows, increasingly less ice at the Poles, increasingly more natural disasters are preventable?, CO2 emissions to the atmosphere and increases in temperatures around the globe. All very correct, very orchestrated and very well put in scene by an Al Gore with a point of unpayable Showman but the dilemma is whether it is a good or a bad documentary and I think that from a scientific point of view any best and most successful but that llegaríansemanas Earth, a documentary macro it took to record several years has failed the images that Al Gore only bothered to generate computer (as) (the bear swimming adrift in the Ocean) a colossal work that nobody is going to enjoy because we we obcecado to see the work of the almost American President.It is unquestionable that a politician of his stature speaks, it is easy to buy the product is selling because he is known, committed and get on the big screen. If an Oscar have given up! But from the documentary point of view I am missing things, I am missing sources, scientists, experiences in the first person, something that is not a dogma of faith to believe me this so well sold and unquestionable truth. That is what I dislike of A truth Incomoda, based exclusively on a strong name and a so well perpetrated marketing campaign.</body>
</review>
