<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Cateto a babor" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We have a comedieta, a beautiful love story, a story of overcoming human and a small final féliz drama for the same price. That more you can request?</summary>
	<body>Alfredo Landa is one of the best actors that has borne him the skin of a bull in the centuries of existence of the same. You can say that he has done films of Swedish topless and everything as you please, but in this life there is to eat. And be confronted with such mastery infamous scripts sobeteos and toqueteos, replete with topicazos, does anyone. Now I would like to see me modern actors strive in these places.The film is about Miguel Cañete, noble labrador of the deep Spain that is required call-up for military service, none other than the Navy. In his naval career he should bear a younger brother who is in his charge. To complete the misfortunes, he falls into the hands of Sergeant channels, the most ruthless of all commanders of the barracks of San Fernando. Can our hero overcome difficult tests that puts the destination on its way? Veanla and will know.Forerunner of the great war films, in which sergeants are bad with the soldiers, but hide a heart more tender than the mother's day. Viva Sergeant channels. We have great actors, such as Rafaela Aparicio in the role of maid, Florinda Chico as mother of the cieguita and wife of Sergeant Canales scathing as always, Jose Sacristán recruit or the greatest of all time, don Alfredo Landa in the role of cathetus. And the rest of the cast of actors, the cream of our cinema. When the actors were great quality each and every one of them. The film begins with a small history lesson, which does not but highlight the patriotic caspismo much-needed at all times. And the tremendous finalón, with the real hero Spanish Cañete sailor.In short, an essential film in any caspoteca self-respecting. We have a comedieta, a beautiful love story, a story of overcoming human and a small final féliz drama for the same price. That more you can request? Want to up of enlisted in the Navy as a volunteer!PS: "where must draw so much water?" This is not one phrase either, but a declaration of principles.Pd2: "Oh, the Navy!" by Rafaela Aparicio, giant sentence.P.D.3: Not to miss the face of Alfredo Landa after the phrase "where see you, with that face, us has been a seductive" Academy Award for the best performance, jua jua.P.D.4: "Quietly, round and pelon", you can define better to Alfredo Landa?</body>
</review>
