<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Supersalidos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Supersalidos offers more than a priori one can expect before a product of this kind, but this confirms that she is should not stick all films and genres in the same pot, that from time to time, one can be found small gems like this.</summary>
	<body>The Disney proposal for the season, is presented as a comedy that goes far beyond the typical teen movies wanting to link. The main success of "Superbad" are a few credible characters (and with which we identify easily) perfectly embodied by three very peculiar actors.Writers (Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg) were based on their own experiences to give realism this story of friendship, in which the University is presented as a challenge and obstacle for friends of any American Institute, that they will be separated to study many miles away. This is one of the sub-plots of the film, the main is that thanks to the false passport Fogell, aka Mclovin (a God), the guys will buy alcoholic beverages of the party which gives Jules, and which will attend Becca, the girls that are in love.As I said, Jonah Hill, Michael Cera, Christopher Mintz-Plasse, Martha McIsaac and the own Seth Rogen (the main cast of the film) make us delight us with a few gamberras interpretations, while deep, where we climbed on a roller coaster of adventures, which occurs in all, becoming an ordeal to get alcohol and later the girls.One of the best parts is that it is starring "Mclovin" and police officers. Intelligent, well built and dynamic, dialogues that make laughter are insured.To put a snag, he hoped that is somehow closed the subplot (or that they completed us) of Mclovin at the end of the film, but after the Seth and Evan, did not again appear that such mythical character, and that reminds me the starring Charlie Korsmo in "Because I can't wait," another interesting movie that many people are unaware of.In short, "Supersalidos" offers more than what a priori one can wait (or think) before a product of this kind, but this confirms that she is should not stick all films and genres in the same pot, that from time to time, one can be found small gems like this.</body>
</review>
