<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Stardust" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With a hectic pace the adventure story is able to link all its characters in an entertaining tape that blends comedy, action and romantic style of the Princess Bride.</summary>
	<body>For a time this part I I realized that the relationship between my desire to see a film and printing is just leaving me is inversely proportional. I.e. when I'm dying to see something usually turn out to be a hodgepodge of very careful. For this reason and to the expectations raised by the promotion, criticism and reception in Stardust United States I've become very cautious and I tried to hide my excitement to mislead the statistics.Seems that it has been well it is fantastic fable has fulfilled my highest hopes. Usually normal when a filmmaker decides to hide his proposal after the label of "Fable or tale" there are two possible outcomes: a boring and infantiloide firecracker anchored in the newest FX (as an unfortunate misfortune or the Chronicles of Narnia series) or on the contrary an adventure magic and entertaining (such as Big Fish, Chocolat or Charley and the Chocolate factory to name a few). I would put the object of this critique in the second group.Tristan (Cox) wants to conquer the love of victory (Miller) why promises that you bring you as a gift a star fall from the sky. So an American in love with England should enter into a magical world where you will find endearing as the pirate characters Shakespeare (DeNiro) and hides a dark secret, or terrible witches (Pfeiffer) that aware of the magical star power decided to pursue her and do with it without the sons of a King of a distant planet that are intended to kill each other to be able to inherit (and travel together with their ghosts to the) (search for the Medallion that will give them the power). When our young Heartthrob is its star it isn't exactly what I expected that to fall into the magical area has become a damsel named Yvaine (Danes) who can give you as many headaches as headaches.With a hectic pace the adventure story is able to link all its characters in an entertaining tape that blends comedy, action and romantic style of the Princess Bride. If he is also a classification for all ages and the best cast side we found on the big screen in many years the Christmas movie was clear but her they premiere in October, we'll see what happens.</body>
</review>
