<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El Asesinato de Jesse James por el Cobarde Robert Ford" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film reference in the final months of 2007, and offers the possibility of enjoying one of the best performances of the year, a Brad Pitt who deservedly won the Volpi Cup at the Venice Film Festival, and is presented as a serious candidate to the Oscar's.</summary>
	<body>There are few figures in United States that are well-known and are part of the popular culture of its society as Jesse James. For many, the Bushranger feared and reputed a disillusioned idealist who continued a losing war of the 19th century, for others. What is sure is that its about forged a legend and myth, that have survived to our days.The film has led on many occasions the life of Jesse James to the big screen, so Andrew Dominik decided to give the story a new approach, distancing themselves from the best-known facet of James and focusing on his last months of life. It does not through the eyes of the mythical Bushranger, but that you do from the perspective of the man that ended with the legend. Based on the novel by Ron Hansen, the assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford is an approach to the man that was behind the myth, showing his more human side, but also their miseries and turn dark and tormented. At a leisurely pace, without being tired or bored, Dominik goes telling the viewer a story exciting hooked from the beginning and able to maintain attention despite its more than two hours and a half of duration. But beyond the achievements of Dominik emerges the omnipresent figure of Brad Pitt, who performed an extraordinary composition full of nuances which consolidates as one of the finest actors of the time. Casey Affleck and Sam Rockwell performed at the same time very good jobs.The assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford is a film reference in the final months of 2007, and offers the possibility of enjoying one of the best performances of the year, a Brad Pitt who deservedly won the Volpi Cup at the Venice Film Festival, and is presented as a serious candidate to the Oscar's.</body>
</review>
