<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Oviedo Express" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Oviedo Express is one of the cooler movies of Spanish film of 2007, that combines a number of elements which seemed to have been lost, such as magical realism and Surrealism itself</summary>
	<body>Spanish film this year has undergone major and serious ups and downs. He began so excellent earlier this year, something unusual, but shortly afterwards however suffered a downturn in quality than not recovered until after the summer. It is in these months, with premieres of films like Mataharis, 13 roses or seven French billiard tables, when Spanish film greatly improves.Oviedo Express certainly is another title to be considered in such recovery, and is that Gonzalo Suárez signing a great movie. He is that of a film of difficult rating or description, being perhaps the right one, being also the most ambiguous of comedy-drama. The argument is simple, the arrival to Oviedo from a large theatrical company to represent La Regenta is a small revolution in the city. Oviedo Express has a certain air of manners comedy, as well as a tone of magical realism reminiscent of Manuel Gutiérrez Aragón, and even has totally surreal touches. Despite this, it is a fresh and original, proposal in which Gonzalo Suárez mixed with great skill antagonistic elements. The vision that Gonzalo Suárez moves the Viewer is a vision distorted by the retranca, sarcasm and irony in which no one is spared. Having said that, the film reaches its moments of greatest genius when it focuses on the theatrical company and its components. Tributes to Sidney Lumet and Billy Wilder, especially that of this, are master. The interpretations are all soberbias (including the Aitana Sánchez-Gijón), although it is impossible to not highlight of that great actor named Carmelo Gómez. Oviedo Express is one of the cooler movies of Spanish film of 2007, that combines a number of elements which seemed to have been lost, such as magical realism and Surrealism itself. It offers the Viewer, as well as spend a fun time, a vision steeped in irony of the theatre, culture, politics and social life of a small town.</body>
</review>
