<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="American Gangster" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story often told but few so enthusiastically and media. A great script and lots of money to afford the best players.The main drawback is it is so accurate that it is predictable and sometimes boring.</summary>
	<body>There are many films that are made with the premise of having a good time between buddy and filmmaking of step. In this two old acquaintances: Denzel Washington (changing the role of good and evil on this occasion) and Ridley Scott (Gladiator, A good year). The trouble with these old friendships is that at times the colegueo isn't enough so that everything goes smoothly.Impeccable script about two individuals that were able to be made if same. One from the illegality and the other from an honesty that is even ridiculous. American Gangster illustrates the advent of one of the biggest drug traffickers in New York and the excessive persecution of a mediocre police to do the right thing. A story often told but few so enthusiastically and media. A great script and lots of money to afford the best actors that are placed on the skin of these two characters (which may also carry some nomination) and a handful of secondary (such as Cuba Gooding Jr. that appears when you least expect in any production) but perhaps a lack of originality, risk and rhythm. The main drawback is it is so accurate that it is predictable and sometimes boring. Part Fank Lucas goes from man of confidence and a mafioso driver to fill the gap which will leave after his death thanks to a very risky drug operation. Funny thing is that this "don't nobody" doesn't call attention to itself and its great organization and thanks to them survives with a degree of immunity even within the own corruption around him. On the other hand Richie Roberts is a somewhat clunky COP that has too many principles with their profession and too few for other things. This way when his personal life goes entirely to scuttle and his best friend of the body ends in a Bureau of forensic decides to amend the errors and hunt more drug dealer off the streets. There are two things that unite these two characters and it is precisely their ferrous ethical principles. Their fidelity and loyalty to this way of life will determine their decisions that lead to the outcome, which to my taste is quite obvious and raked but is bad of based made real, that history is marked factory.</body>
</review>
