<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El erótico enmascarado" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The caspómetro low hours. More Pajares and less Estesos.</summary>
	<body>The film is about Manolo (student of mismísmo Fraga), a Professor of social sciences which will be promoted to a Ministry. It has several problems the cheerful teacher, given that is bundled with the daughter of the Minister, the youth was porn actor (tremendous tool, by the way) and currently has a problem of "virility". Therefore resorted to an eminent psychiatrist (Ozores) that will cure this lack of erections. On the one hand, the psychiatrist wants to divorce his wife while that haunts him a gay. On the other hand, they want to unseat this post Manolo, barbets details in his dark past. Come on, art and essay that they say.Juanito Navarro Senator Fernando Esteso erotic, Ozores psychiatrist, Maria Isbert, Chus Lampreade, etc, is that does not lack detail. The film itself is a tremendous firecracker, because, unlike others, it has too many gracietas. Although it has its dotted in some respects. It has nipples nipple jumping defying the laws of gravity, which faithfully reflect sexual freedom and the joy of the happy 1980s. It has subtle gracietas on the volatility of certain politicians, with their continuous changes of jacket and ideologies. It has its mess and it comedy, but it does not exceed. Well, a bit of science fiction there, and is that after watching fuck Ozores and Esteso one believes that it is possible to Dodge bullets or walk by the waters.In short, another one of the "Ozoril" genre, did not finish like me, although paraphrasing a very famous King "A naked well worth seeing the film" well, actually said Paris is well worth a mass, in relation to its passage to Christianity more recalcitrant about the Crown of France, but basically I wanted to say that, certainly.The caspómetro low hours. More Pajares and less Estesos.P.D: "is why remember me this Ayatollah Khomeini?", says Esteso before the mat of his girlfriend, so, without laughing or anything.Pd2: Fuck that grotesque of male bodies. That difference with the metrosexual being now.P.D.3: Intimate scene Ozores as a psychiatrist in his underwear to the annals of the history of the cinema.P.D.4: "Rooooojaaaaaa, when your rooooojaaaaaa you've done to you?"P.D.5: "I am less macho than Estíbaliz" large phrases for posterity.</body>
</review>
