<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El sueño de Cassandra" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do as if it were a real Greek tragedy, ' Cassandra? s Dream' is conceived as the new challenge of master Woody Allen, another confirmation that his undeniable talent beats yet.</summary>
	<body>When Match Point premiered, the public (only not European) surrendered to master Woody Allen. And I include myself in this group. That was a masterpiece that vovlía to the adventures of another of its wonders, offences and misdemeanours; that I was back to the crime and the conscience, both portrayed in a manner closer to Dostoievski and Highsmith to the own previous Allen (more focused on inteligentísimas comedies or some tributes to admired Bergman). And is that the new genius not only us has satisfied their fans on a yearly basis, also we have amazed with some indisputable masterpieces. This year, after a lighter Scoop another thing, once again (for the third time, if not calculating evil) to his favorite themes and more concienciadores, these focused guilt and human consciousness, and you pass to the crime. With Cassandra's Dream teacher shows us once again that his talent has not been exhausted, has even lost originality. And I say that because his last film is no less than the closest thing to a masterpiece, a masterful (concienciador and terrible) waste of good film, very good.Although, however, not everything went you on wheels with the third and final installment of his London trilogy. The criticism her crushed rather than caressed. They have left it on the floor! And I wonder, how can make this mistake? Honestly, this is a question without and with response. No, because I fails to fit in my stubborn head that film critics (many of them fans of the director) may not understand that Cassandra's Dream is not a surrender, a "I don't know or I'm more interested" by maestrísimo Woody. Go already! You have (and many) similarities with Match Point. So what? It is not even accurate, has several basic elements that change on his penultimate film. Here the story does not focus on a man of class low to ascend socially through crime, here the thing is much more amplified. In this dream of Cassandra come to play so sensitive as the family, fraternal relations, loyalty &hellip; in my opinion, nor is it a copy outright to Match Point, nor a director performance. Woody Allen is more in shape than ever! As he says, when I was young yes they were interested in these tragedies, but your problem is that you were only jokes. It has now aged (matured perhaps not, because it seems that it has always done), and believes that this is the precisomo time to deal with such tragedies. It is, without doubt, and will be, a controversial film. That its capacity for childbearing new stories follow you off, but also directed them Cassandra's Dream and meet forty years having directed what he has directed. Since then, outrage me there.We are focusing on the wonderful movie before us, there is no doubt that virtually contains all the elements to be another masterpiece of the director. And it is, but find, as only failure, the small similarities with Match Point. Yes, can that I contradezca, but it is not quite true. While some criticize for being original and little charisma, I criticize it for containing small (very small!) elements similar to his first foray into the English City. Whether a pair of police officers present in the outcome, a stereotype of femme-fatale a both scarletjohanssonizado and a main character with similar questions to the of the superb Jonathan Rhys Meyers. Although, despite running a quasi perfect script, there are some other elements which not me convince to come, as a presentation somewhat elongated and cutting, despite having one of the most sensational film endings of recent years, recorded. Its flat end, utterly, elected in a better way impossible, and accompanied with the splendid score again, within the lares of Allen, Philip Glass, just conmocionando, and the unísino, destroying the Viewer. Terrible, poetic, too tragic.It is also imperative to comment that his trip to the English capital has sat in fable. If the result, both box office and critical, was excellent at Match Point, of Scoop was not, although no one however mentioned that it was more than what it was, a simple but effective comedy in the style of Allen, although somewhat simplified. Cassandra's Dream is a back in the tragedy, extremely fierce, terrible conclusion in its content, powerful in its storytelling, balanced, smart and hard, very lasts. He is not the best work of the director, but one of them. Its level is higher than many of his other dramas (such as September or husbands and wives), and I am personally delighted that us has returned with such wonder.Woody Allen continues here, portraying the London City as any director has done (both foreign and English). His plans, his way of seeing social as in any other country Ascension (se) seen, cruel and interested manner, and also the use of colours grey, on the contents of his works (although these elements have only been represented in Match and Cassandra's). And I think that his vision can not be more accurate. In addition, the personalities of their characters (including the of Hugh Jackman in Scoop) are cold, calculating and mentally obsessive. Ewan McGregor in the film in question, is an ambitious uncle and triumfador, one of those being rendered, but luxury cars a selfish to any rule, however, knows well choose the girls. Canvi, in the film adds a character of equal importance, although of opposite personality, as it is his brother, a malleable and mechanical roller of cars that costs it to take the weight of a terrible fact his conscience. In short, a human either. These two misfortunes collide in Cassandra's Dream, in a perverse and manipulative game about the limit of the ambition, conscience, guilt, the temptation and sexual desire. All these elements together form this wonder. His script, does not lack tell is practically perfect, with scenes of duration needed, sublime dialogues and very allenianos (those who speak of God, common but even greater depth), a final (as much as say) nothing to hit, but as an end to a tragedy must be intelligent, brief and no less dramatic.The cast, once again, is characterized by its brilliance. The fictional brothers of Allen, his new "muses" are two commercial actors, although none of them is below the outstanding. Ewan McGregor is brilliant in its role of ambitious, and Irishman Colin Farrell, better than never as brother more stubborn, humane and sincere of the two (which I has fallen tremendously well). As a side, are a huge Tom Wilkinson, of custom, and the beautiful and rookie Hayley Atwell, a captivating paper, well remembers the Johansson in their first time with Woody. All in all the new movie, suffering from disorders, are, generally speaking, imperfect (never forget this feature), and hence the seductive moves as if it were a beautiful complement that will following the desire of the protagonist through her intelligence.As if it were a real Greek tragedy, Cassandra's Dream is conceived as the new challenge of master Woody Allen, another confirmation that his undeniable talent beats yet. While band its favourite themes, as the imperfection of the human being or the incursion of the comic in the tragic, get trapped and not release us until its beautiful and sensational conclusion. And I will continue without understanding the unnecessary and bad conception are having it. Frankly, incomprehensible.</body>
</review>
