<review author="Estesoyo" title="300" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>300 is a movie or a comic book? Difficult question by Jove. It seems a living crèche, with a lot of figurines that move from pose to pose. But what is no doubt is a truño more in this endless list...</summary>
	<body>The film is based on a comic book by Frank Miller, which neither reached me impact too. The most interesting was the presentation, in the form of book in hardcover and in landscape format, and as it is usual from his era Sin City, in glorious black and white. The most famous battle of the Greek Spartans, with certain historical mistakes that we can forgive for what licenses artistic and narrative tells us. but in the end, it isn't more than a comic book that there is a battle. It does not for more.Already from the outset depends on where they come: or you read the comic book or not. If have you read already you know what you'll find, and all you can say is whether it is true or not, and if you have not read. therefore do not uncle, because the film follows the comic book cartoon to cartoon. This reminds me of the Akira film. This film was accurate to the comic, but the good thing that I had was that two hours of film were equivalent to a hundred volumes, with what it cost then (and now I suppose) in time and money. Without any added value.And this is what happens to the movie '300'. It adds nothing to the comic. I even think that it cost me less read the comic book who see the movie. An alluring comic leave you a film of the lot. It is totally unnecessary. It is to see a boring video clip of a song: If you already liked you'll not like more and if not, then spend everything.It is incomprehensible to me as it has been able to wake up so many passions. It is nothing more than comic in movement, and with the same licenses that allow you to a comic: e.g. scene gore of the handles of the Leonidas dismemberment to the enemy left in the film, the characters are deformed in physiognomy both factions in their eagerness to resemble the comic book fighting are spectacular but unrealistic, enemies are stupid ass. The charm that might turn out to have the comic is lost to take him to the big screen.And the best are the dialogues. that if I can not kneel because it hurts the back of slaughtering your soldiers. that if we are fighting for freedom. I thought they were going to fall pro-American pamphlets of the sky. am not a historian, and not be if it really could be to say something like, but by God! they could have been otherwise! It so much that I almost have to leave the cinema with the aching ears thumping.History may impact especially to the American public accustomed to the vapid biographies of its nobel and his boring wars (that if against Indians or against themselves). But European history has many more stories and much more shocking than this. Now if you do not read anything and you think everything you said television, because you will hallucinate uncle.At least it is better than the adaptation of Sin City, I have no strength to see again. and that luckily I almost managed to forget already. But this only means that still need bad it could get worse.The director, Zack Snyde, becoming a specialist in shoot exactly as you are told. A mandate going. It has made the remake of 'The dawn of the dead', stuck to the original and now '300' nailed to the original. They can catch it for the remake of 'The orphanage', those who liked them continue liking because hara exactly the same.The actors will make me extremely boring, especially the Butler with the number of faces in the movie.So little more can tell you. initially not even her I liked to make a criticism, it was seeing her and forget her. I lost many hours watching film of shit not me inmuto.</body>
</review>
