<review author="Bruji" title="El sueño de Cassandra" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Allen is still gaining momentum even when it does not exercise of Woody Allen. The ability to jump between genres, narrative concision of the scripts and the film silverware, always highlight in a panorama which lacks such invaluable aspects.</summary>
	<body>Woody Allen is still gaining momentum even - or especially - when it does not exercise of Woody Allen. The ability to jump between genres, narrative concision of the scripts and film goldwork which characterized his work, always highlight within a panorama - current - which lacks such invaluable aspects. The latest installment of the trilogy London is no exception...And the curse of Apollo fell upon Cassandra, daughter of the King of Troy. Their dreams would prophesy misfortune than not be believed, pull the destruction. To lovers just them the mention of certain city, evocative of nostalgia, to remember the lives of the Princes Eric Bana and Orlando Bloom. Then, only it should be expected that the title of the film was put randomly, wondered if perhaps powerful Aphrodite was, and reach the conclusion that the world of coincidences was never a constant in the original universe of its director. With Woody Allen, "very improvised" is just the result of "very tested".In any case, it would be interesting to try to analyze the dream of Cassandra from two different points of view: under "the prism of psychoanalysis", which would lead us to compare it with the rest of the recent Filmography of its author; and, on the other hand, as a film which premiered at the 2007 year. The findings might surprise. It is possible that all the other was the prelude to a creative crisis that seems to be submerged the director of Annie Hall. Compared to the whole of his work, the London trilogy seems mediocre, unchecked productions that him notoriety into fame. While Scoop does not happen to be a "nice" adventure, in Match Point is limited to relocate an American tragedy to the city of the Thames. And it is the originality of this history, nominated for an Oscar, only such in its outcome, after showing an approach reasonably similar to which George Stevens develop in 1.951 from a novel by Theodore Dreiser, a film he titled A place in the Sun. However, and in the worst cases, it is not difficult to verify how the unexpected twist of the new Allen, the modern classic, the compulsive director capable of shooting at the speed of the 1940s, continues gaining momentum among the new generations of moviegoers and - very interestingly - among all those which we never support him. Perhaps for the dream of Cassandra, in the line of Match Point, the claim of Allen has been the adapt a Greek tragedy - this time with much more success - to our days. To do so, uses its vast capacity to offer the viewer the same candy always with different packaging, by resorting to the obsessive idea by sex, the injustice of el capricho male when repair in the personality of a woman below her waist, and a reflection on the deranged psychopathy of the world in which we live, so present in his work. Similarly, relies on his innate ability to describe the characters with only a sentence achieved: "I am ambitious, self-centred and difficult", both reminiscent of many descriptions of the unmatched Deconstructing Harry. Continues with an accurate portrait of family, widely discussed in Hannah and his sisters, to offer that anecdotal view of multiple lovers who seem to be so and it are not magnified with the introduction of one of these events worthy of framing: "the family is the family, but there are a few limits". And culminates with the mastery demonstrated in crimes and misdemeanours to unite two parallel plots, to a serious perspective - not without humour - refer to moral status elasticity human: the appalling fact that haunts some, is easily assimilable by others. All this with a film absolute disregard for the English capital, which Spielberg cinematographer fails to avoid, so far from the love which shows by New York City in the master Manhattan.Si the dream of Cassandra is seen as a film by unknown director which premiered at the 2007 year - necessarily - ends to draw attention. The originality of its approach, its acute dialogues, the strength in the structure of the script, excellent measurement of time, proper rhythm that unfolds the plot, the marvelous direction of actors (the performance of Collin Farell is credible!). they are not common in contemporary cinema. Such is the mastery that follows a product which is not drama, is not comedy, is not thriller. It isn't anything but convincing, sorry for forgetting to put a vehicle damaged on the right side of a British road; alarming failures of script, which makes shine the Sun after dinner and watch three different times on the clock of Ewan Mcgregor in a plano-contraplano of twenty seconds in duration; and the irony of showing the Anglo-Saxon characters always smoking in public places. You can not yet smoking in such strict city, "does that life is great?". Even for Bonnie and Clyde was, and although they do not give desire to invade Poland with this new Opera, there is no, nor the slightest doubt of his genius.</body>
</review>
