<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La noche de los muertos vivientes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Capital title of new modern horror cinema. From here has fallen pigswill and trumpets and clarínes that sound when over purely personal considerations, the film becomes a time notary have sounded...</summary>
	<body>I always had the idea that the night of the living dead was not only the film zombies in white and black that stubbornly a friend of mine wanted to he saw a Scotch tape (not I see them, no longer exist) retained as absolute jewel in the film. I saw her and it seemed not an absolute gem of a film. In any case, found me a great horror film advancing to comedy or a comedy film that forced coup of viscus, tear and several gruesomeness, entry into the territory of the terror. Twenty years ago this and last night I could see it in a more than acceptable DVD edition that exceeded despite the rough black and white, the jewel of my friend. No longer see you (circumstances are the predictable: the distance, which is forgotten, and the time, which is the bug bastard that prevents the affections and the routines in these affections) but I can't help but think of those my years of glowing love for cinema and the vision between the uncertainty and the fascination of the works of George a. Romero. I now appreciate what then not I knew: the value, the foundational aspect of a genre that Romero broke up then recompose while that artistic emergency was aimed at account of the usual ferocity of criticism. Night of the living dead is the death certificate from Gothic films to the use of the haunted houses and the ghosts of corrupt shrouds and souls in penalty with nauseating drapery and deranged look. From here, the genus British noble weight of the fantastique and embraced new roads, paths lighted by the lights of the cold war and the real fear that some obscurantist political and emparanoiado pressed the fateful button. Already know: the deadly toy of Oppenheimer Sting gracefully portrayed in the fantastic Russians. And the tape had to bother, I imagine: semidocumentary tone, its drab concept of what we consider a script and the twilight tone of the characters strengthens the idea of revolution, pregnant concern of surprise. Then (and from this brief can then write the indecent volume on the history of Terror from these apocalyptic zombies) came a flood of films sketches by the mother before us, but children, inevitably embadurnadas of a less relevant speech, just disturbing and, in almost all cases - except for the great and the land of the living dead - recent, flat in excitement and cynicism. Because the 1968 George a. Romero film is an encyclopedia of cynicism: an artifact of unforeseen side effects. --Critics of the time agreed on the social character of the film. So great: there are social. Viet Nam, nuclear fear, the dreadful war without war that lasted forty years and formed several generations in blindness and the forging of a deep, well-documented nationalism. But Romero did not want to reach both: there are circumstances surrounding certain artistic events - a book, an album, a film - working involuntarily as a myth. This are obvious and Romero only provided the props, the zombies, the expressionist whiff, the almost formal care neglect and, above all, the argument: that rumor just converted into tumult and which sows corpses the city, formerly stronghold of comfort and plácido stage of aburguesada life of an innocent population, deceived and indoctrinated in the belief that no other life could better be possible. The dead, those who have no break, come to burst that useless catechism. Even the origin of the dead, never counted, can induce the shaking: we do not know whether they return to torture the living through some toxic sortilegio or is a mere consequence of the inscrutable designs of the dark, from alien to the Cartesian solidity of the real and tangible, of the material and measurable. Voodoo, toxins, do experiments? Romero no matter the origin: he wants to display the desconhort, the impossibility of finding a grab - physical, spiritual - which defeat evil.All the dead that walk, these corpses eaten by disgust, roam without moral purpose: displaces them the primordial instinct of hunger, nor Romero explained. Or need to do. No other movie of zombies that has continued to this us supplied explanations. Mind the sharp picture of the demolition of a society may be spent, infected by the same virus that cracked skin, dismember the meat and raise the dead of their coffins. This is chaos and not the modern vision of the jungle 4.0. this link (now demonized Youtube grace) long the full tape. Yes, complete.</body>
</review>
