<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Jenaro el de los 14" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More bad than bad. Another clear example that if Alfredo Landa had been American would have eight oscars at home.</summary>
	<body>Buff, than surfeit of Iberian film, think I need a pair of Orcs and spacecraft sessions to detoxify me.The film is about Jenaro, a village of deep Spain and inveterate player of lotteries pregonero. One day, the surprise of the day football takes him to fool the people of Jenaro from 14. So with the beret surface warships threaded part to the capital to collect the money. But there he discovers bad which is society and all you want to take advantage of it. I do not understand, with the face of intellectual who has this man.Well, another clear example of our crappy film of the 1970s. And is there is no where take it. We can view it as the home version of "beauty and the beast" or "The ugly duckling", given that we have a redomado loser, that of the overnight is the most popular man in the country. Women who encamar (to use appropriate language) with him, to give the braguetazo of their lives. In the middle of the film we see something very obvious, "Pretty Woman" is nothing but a sequel to adapatada to this current times. A prostitute met millionaire to the saca of the street and fills her whims. HA, I already see Alfredo Landa asking image rights to Richard Gere. By the way, there are collaborations with renowned as Inigo "of the mustache" or Jaime de Mora y Aragón. But I am not convinced and aburridísima. Moreover, on top of evils is a chest or obliquely. This isn't scurfy film, it is the essence of dandruff.In short, more bad than bad. Another clear example that if Alfredo Landa had been American would have eight oscars at home. A caspita performance by don Alfredo.Besitos.P.D: "Rather than continuous gaze is alternating look" fine patriotic humor.Pd2: "and that's a knife?, men use this" says Jenaro by deploying the knife of Curro Jiménez p. (d). 3: "He has lost half glasses" tells Jaime de Mora y Aragon to see his Monocle. They will certainly shake and drop acorns "iiiiiieeeeeepa, dispatch!"</body>
</review>
