<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="El sueño de Cassandra" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It follows that whiff to telefilm, which you can hardly avoid smell it...</summary>
	<body>Woody Allen is a great film of all time. He is a genius, no doubt. But, citing a phrase itself, not devoid of sense, I have to say that "the genius also disprosean".In his third film shot in London, Allen returned to the line had been drawn up recently with his masterpiece, Match Point. But this time, the ambition it adds family, lies, delitos.y money. All these elements in the hands of the New York can give as a result a great movie. But, of course, this is not the case.The main problem of Cassandra's Dream is the whiff to telefilm has. Their first ten or fifteen minutes are worthy of a film of Antena 3, a Saturday after eating. I feel extremely vulgar comparison, but it is the most appropriate. The dialogues and photography are so mediocre that one cannot understand that we are really dealing with a work of Allen. Although the plot on paper has its point of interest, his approach and development is so bland that it is boring. Mediocre. Very mediocre.The unique virtues of this, no longer minor works, but bad film, are probably the performances of Colin Farrell and Ewan McGregor. They are not exceptional, but they do have good moments. But its major drawback is that they are loaded with all the weight of the film. And it is not enough to lift.But, if were not enough, the pace is too slow and the film seems to combine the drama and the comedy with a formula that does not end curdling. The way to delve into the human psyche is comic, and does not seem to be his claim that that works. The McGregor character reminds the of Rhys-Meyers in Match Point, but the depth of it is vague and comes to be almost unbelievable.Allen ends its cycle London, probably in the worst possible way, and who knows if thinking that either he put too much interest after Match Point and Scoop. His next film seems to lead an even worse way. "Vicky Cristina Barcelona" will come to our screens next year. Go name.</body>
</review>
