<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="The invasion" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is the version of the ultracuerpos that promotes less capabilities (this including the unpardonable absence of true distinctive element of the series) and its second reading is too put in evidence.</summary>
	<body>To be the fourth version of a familiar story, invasion (2007) seems to not have learned the lesson very well. What had to be the entry into the German director Oliver Hirschbiegel Hollywood stays in a medium adaptation which not only is more liberties taken in the original novel by Jack Finney, they even failed to reach the minimum of enjoyment of gender which Yes knew how to get their three previous versions. To what extent that is blame the director or producers who got the hand (which is Joe Silver, father of this creature) do not know. I can only say the result is well below that expected, and that the ultracuerpos seem to have suffered its first defeat serious in its invasion of the Tierra.Al start from ground already known to all, invasion does not need large explanatory Preludes: we know from the outset that an alien race is taking our planet by assault, and does it so in the form of a virus that spreads after the fall to the land of one of our own space artifacts. The virus spreads by our system (something that the film crush and again in unnecessary computer sequences) and makes human clones extraterrestrial. The main of the affected cities is Washington D.C., place where the Carol Benell psychiatrist (played by Nicole Kidman in the change of sex of the protagonist) discovers a strange paranoia that makes them believe that their loved ones are no longer the same in their patients. The rest already know: the Replicants aliens soon begin to increase in number and put pressure on the human, who must flee while looking for a cure.It is in their already known instances where invasion gets its best fruits. Of itself, the fact that expiration date in a big city makes clear that it is the version of Phillip Kauffman (released in 1978) which has served as a major source of inspiration, something that is noticeable in those scenes in which the invasion is taking place in front of the noses of the character, as well as the presence of Veronica Cartwright in a small role. Also, those moments in which the ultracuerpos make group presence and harass the doctor are quite good and intense, but this hardly can be considered an own merit because that is something that we have already seen three other times. Still achieved big moments, especially those concerning a murderously untapped Daniel Craig whose participation is reduced to little more than the guaperas on duty.Where Yes fails this version of the ultracuerpos in their already very guided action scenes, that on several occasions seem tucked with shoehorn and are not very short story, so note to leagues that were an imposition of the study to ease the pace of the film. Such scenes almost always confined to a Chase drive quite poor and repetitive, in which we see the aliens behave like smart Zombie (simile that is reinforced in the form as the virus spreads), something which clashes with already apparently. In addition, the typical plot of the child in danger charged too much relevance and distracts the film to delve into the subtext of conformity and egalitarianism that "seems" to be the center of the story, a subtext that addresses the perennial presence of the conflict on the human race and, in a way quite interesting initially, linking to this film with other classics as ultimatum to Earth (1951). Pity that, come to the end, the "message" of the film becomes too obvious and seems to be highlighted so that even the most palurdo of the room can give account. The outcome, because of this, is easy and outlets, a far cry from the one seen in other versions, even in its immediate predecessor, Abel Ferrara premiered in 1993. invasion, therefore, won't be a film easily forgettable, perhaps remarkable only as a vehicle of exploitation of Nicole Kidman. As regards gender, it is the version of the ultracuerpos that promotes less capabilities (this including the unpardonable absence of true distinctive element of the series) and its second reading is too put in evidence. In short, until the remake coming.</body>
</review>
