<review author="Andrés Pons" title="El Asesinato de Jesse James por el Cobarde Robert Ford" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film is dipped in directions quite different from its predecessors, initially only tells his last moments before his death at the hands of his greatest admirer. In the background is not an exaltation on the character since his portrait is not the hero that previous products we sold.</summary>
	<body>How many movies were made about Jesse James? WESTERNS who attended her figure in all kinds of productions are countless. Since most commercial that used his name to build routine shows face at the box office, young gun and sequel are clear examples.Passing by authentic wonders of celluloid where sought the truth, one of the most brilliant was bold with an impressive HENRY FONDA. Again come to his figure with a little-known director although he proved a huge talent with other biography I encumbro ERIC BANA in which you interpret the criminal CHOPPER. This film is dipped in directions quite different from its predecessors, initially only tells his last moments before his death at the hands of his greatest admirer. In the background is not an exaltation on the character since his portrait is not the hero that previous products we sold. Here we have a bandit who lives at the edge of the law without any heroism, is a ruthless killer and as such is portrayed.It is her killer that is carrying the baton in a masterful interpretation of CASSEY AFLECK "double win with goodbye small goodbye" where in a way intimate included their stormy love/hate relationship with the Bandit.Highlight the work of a BRAD PITT than when you removed the mask of commercial actor demonstrating good qualities as they tested twelve monkeys and the fight among others club.Photography, music highlights to give the story an intimate air, reflective portrait of a few men who live in the abyss with a preciosista staged.This is certainly a WESTERN in disguise, I say why disguise deceptively gender belongs to the jeans but not the forms. Shots, nor duels under the Sun, or fights in the Hall. It is the drama of two men in a relationship of friendship and hatred in equal parts, is the portrait of a murder by the disappointment.A film precuscular shot with enormous talent by its director, great performances of the cast, immaculate to be one of the most real biographies of the Bushranger technical aspects.Their excessive duration all unresolved deduct you points to what postulated as a great masterpiece of all forms a film high altitude exercise.</body>
</review>
