<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Un funeral de muerte" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The funeral is linking all the misfortunes imaginable to organize a real ordeal for their protagonists seen from outside is the sea of hilarious, horrifically delicious and humorously very black.</summary>
	<body>There is nothing sadder than the loss of a loved and luckily in our country that the funeral of this body included wake still has not been fashion. This kind of social gatherings where part of dealing with the pain you have to socialize with family, friends and acquaintances of the deceased, both those you love as those who should not be torture themselves. Why funerals take the best and worst of ourselves. In this case an average family bury a beloved and loving father, but if the family is strange the dead was even more. In this way their children are involved in a problem of huge dimensions when they discover his "shady" past and while they grapple with several side crises arising from the envy, quarrels, blackmail or accidental intake of drugs.The choral approach in which half of the members of the family are involved in the plot to hide the evidence gets, once again, a film without actors defined as it has been customary in the film Made In UK (if it worked with Love Actually will work for any comedy and precisely one of its performers appeared in both). The anecdotal is that production is not English, its technical data discovers that USA, Germany and the Netherlands have put the money for carrying out this tape where it converges the best of American cinema with European elegance that sells both (although don't have Hugh grant on the poster). The British actors when they get to make movies make it big so the esperpentos attending this burial include pieces worthy of being cattle a film themselves. A uniformity that is much appreciated as the cool breeze it is at this stage where without a great comedian at the head of the productions not come forward. A compact cast very well guided by Oz (may I call you master Yoda for old times) which is comfortable, opting instead for a right direction and little risky that fulfils the objectives.The tragicomedies flavoured English have a certain elegant charm without falling into easy laughter (although I do not share the enthusiasm for one or another eschatological joke). Admittedly, it has cost me years to understand his humor but that once given the step each time enjoy more pearls that are set on the island of bad weather and the eternal tea time. I laughed, I laughed so much when ever is them torcían more things. Is it about the wild sitcom, that once they start is quite difficult to stop them. That way the funeral will linking all the misfortunes imaginable to organize a real ordeal for their protagonists seen from outside is the sea of hilarious, horrifically delicious and humorously very black.As said one of its protagonists: "Has been exciting, to be a burial, clear."</body>
</review>
