<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Furia de Titanes" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Classic adventure on heavenly disputes of Greek mythology. It tastes like festive period, Christmas NAP with the kids running around the House and you settled the binges on the couch. Grandiose.</summary>
	<body>I like these films of rancid colors. These happen over and over again when upcoming seminars, see Christmas or Easter periods. I like that you can see them awhile, you go to make popcorn, to service, to play with your children, and come back when you still hooked. The I've been watching this late, what did more things. And not only I've heard, if not that I liked. Now don't you know do these things? Are we more magnanimous with papier-mache than with the computer? Who knows.The film is about the Celestial movements of Greek mythology. Zeus apparently had a mess with a human, becoming rain (fine mode to say, of course), and her pre침칩 of Perseus. But hete here that the father of the girl not learned that the pre침ador was the great bastard, I say haceedor, so they got into a tomb of cardboard stone (is that fleet) mother and son and threw them into the sea. Puff, put Zeus as an arm of the sea and tells na less than the God of the sea to draw the Titan that you delete the map to the city of the murderous King's daughters and grandchildren. Step gives an abracito that fuses. Cool or not cool the idea? To me makes me.Tremendous, tremendous. For starters, the touch stale old special effects with movements impossible, as if missed frames with papier-mache on all sides, with everything you need to stick to the sofa. The argument is full of gossip, which already warned me my dear mother-in-law to the mythological clamoring, where all are parents or mothers of human and among them want to kill the kids. Well, it said, were not. And the greatest thing is the flavor family who have these films, to sit on the couch to see her with a giant popcorn Bowl covered with the blanket and seeing how they killed including jellyfish, kr치kenes and the mother who gave birth.In short, classic adventure on heavenly disputes of Greek mythology. It tastes like festive period, Christmas NAP with the kids running around the House and you settled the binges on the couch. Grandiose. What special effects, what effects.Besitos.P.D: Get the teacher (I dare not write it) of Harry Potter. Which is head of his house and has a face of chard.Pd2: Ah, and ladies in porretas without coming to story. That joy found cute breasts and sober buttocks in the middle of a NAP.</body>
</review>
