<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los bingueros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A cult of Spanish scurfy cinema film. In his time, he had more than a million and a half viewers in the film, is not feat.</summary>
	<body>You never have been to bingo? I've only been once and it was very funny. To begin with, an unbelievable, given stress that kid numbers accelerated and not gave me time or to scratch me nose. Then, in what your're honing the marker Carioca, a snowing sings line. And a fat, bingo. And your with stupid face. At the end of the day, apart from the money we lost, we we have a boligrafazo someone what, he threw it as we not mention in the evening, us. Played us nothing (except the boligrafazo), but to laugh.The film is about Fermín Cejuela (Esteso) and Amadeo Savoy (Pajares). The first was dedicated to pick up eggs and know if you have chick inside or not, standing for life. The second, worker's Bank with a burning desire to fortune. For various reasons, they reach his ears the possibility to get lots of money on bingo. So, by the ups and downs of the film scurfy, nothing less falling together, Pajares, Ozores and Esteso, that more can you ask?Well, we have to Pajares, Esteso and Ozores, the Kings of patria dandruff. And then small holdings, as the Normal Duval (or so says the IMDB), Florinda Chico and a black in balls which I think is called Africa. The subject shows US the sad Spain of transition, where the opening to the game meant that españolitos lost their savings. Insane script, with impossible phrases that disarm to the painted. And clearly, the plot hooks, given that it is impossible to know where it will go. In addition, has everything what is expected of a film of these gentlemen, women in leather, game, persecutions, easy jokes and dandruff on all sides.In short, a cult of Spanish scurfy cinema film. In his time, he had more than a million and a half viewers in the film, is not feat. And I say, if there is freakis who worship films of grotesque drawings with giant heads, as there will not be freakis of Pajares and Esteso? I, the first of them. The peak of the Iberian dandruff.Besitos.P.D: "do you say to the washer?" The cheapest sell. No, that says that we must change the drum. "Yeah, man, and the trumpet" with these dialogues, that leave?Pd2: "were the Franks Germans?" "The Franks were Galician from Ferrol!" patriotic humor on all sides. After saying that, grab a urinal and is going to shit.P.D.3: Strong, had a coach which he said "have given Me a clock, but I can not put" and you wondered, "why?" and answered descojonado of laughter "that is wall!". Damn, is that he pulled him out of this film.P.D.4: "If I have the black" says Esteso a black kid on top. That very fine humor. By the way, because always leaves a black in pelotas in Pajares films? Is it to give an exotic touch? I say that because in Spain, at that time, few were.</body>
</review>
