<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="El Asesinato de Jesse James por el Cobarde Robert Ford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unusual and very unconventional Western realistic.</summary>
	<body>Good western, which however can be considered atypical, very unconventional, so it carries with it.I would like to say that it is not a film from the West to use, with lots of action, shooting and fighting, but it is a reflexive awareness of what was the life and death of the famous raided banks and trains Jesse James. And not only him but the man who killed him in the back.A nothing annoying voice, who hears only at specific times, is telling us what happens moments later, as well as explain the physical problems of the main character. Consequence to a sober address, and Dominik, filmmaker, able to maintain interest at all times, despite its obvious long. Not bored one iota, not tired, but I think Yes it shows its long footage, especially by its quiet and steady pace, which is not slow, but that it slows down when it should, which is most of the footage. There is therefore nervous movements of camera or a riotous Assembly, so that the viewer can absorb, and sometimes taste, clearly shows how much you (the appearance of the train assailed with light penetrating in the forest, the murder itself, endowed with a great tension in spite of knowing what will happen &hellip;).Unhurried but without breaks, we are seeing what felt the characters, some characters whose lives hung and depended on the figure of Jesse James, great pope, loved and feared, especially feared by all, and in whose shadow arrimaban. If not happened, if they were emancipated and betray him, let alone would be with them and end their lives "as if it were a formality", as it is in a tragic and violent time.Great performances, with a trio excellent protagonist: Brad Pitt, Sam Rockwell and Casey Affleck, younger brother of Ben, the latter getting transmit, with few gestures but determinants, their psychology, their love, respect, worship by Jesse, and later their fear and hatred or perhaps more animosity towards him.Superb photography that enhances beautiful snowy landscapes and a sunset scene elegant and supple, always at the service of history and not the interpreters and an exhibition of shocking violence, perhaps as few action scenes but full of force and drama, very realistic, far from which they used to watch in the classic westerns of the golden age of Hollywood.Una movie I do not think it lasts too in the billboards to be clear that It is not created to be a commercial success, but that seeing calmly and without haste, it can be a breath of fresh air to a genus which is you are trying to boost and place again at the forefront, not I know if with much success (think "3: 10 to Yuma" is working very well in the USA).</body>
</review>
