<review author="José A. Peig" title="El sueño de Cassandra" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tragedy marks the House, somewhat dodgier, but it has the potential to leave a bitter sediment in the sensitive spectator, complying with the essential objective of a modest product.</summary>
	<body>On Match Point, Woody Allen pondered the ambition that weakens the nobility of the human being in a universe ruled by chance. Cassandra's dream is another twist on the same object back and using very similar dramatic elements, offers us a bitter dissertation on the (so-called) American dream, without forgetting the usual comic pulse. Based on a theme, as recurring in the recent Filmography of Allen, the representation draws a pathetic smile through which the Viewer provides the life of characters desperate pessimism of the creator-driven.History of two losers who yearn to have the comfort and material goods through minimal effort. When they ask for help his wealthy uncle Howard, Providence imposes an unexpected price, an effort which in this case becomes the moral dilemma that holds all the discourse. As always, the characters are defined with millimeter accuracy and the development of chemical and conflicting attitudes has a clear plot reason, with which we have a film with a fairly solid development (contrary to what has been said since the first press passes). And it is that simplicity is a virtue here. Film apparently connotative and doomed to topics, but Allen doesn't forget the story you want to tell and gets to the end of his narration of thesis without getting his traps to produce an irreparable bias. The story works in its formal aspects, but is noticeable in excess the hand of the writer; the words of Ian and Terry are the same conscience of Allen, repeating the same dilemma already mentioned in earlier works, and thus often cease to be themselves to become the "thesis" of the film, with what the story loses in depth to rave in the megalomaniac speech, referred to in a certain superficiality very well disguised by unquestioned narrative agility in what to the scheme and the general progression. Film, in short, bright when you look at her on the basis of its scheme external until you reach a final situation resolved consistently, but failed according to the richness of nuances that tries to offer from the tragedy that beats in the background.In the speech, some issues include: Ian almost nihilist unconscious, and defends the stark reality of nature. The life feeds on death, and here the character exposes a wrong approach, since that own the natural world variables applied to the same culture of the American dream, obviating the necessary distinction between these two strata of life human. Terry is the obvious cliché of social consciousness. Each lost in their egoism, the other in the confusion of a weak soul together staged failure and frustrated dreams. The last shot, we see the boat "Cassandra's dream" rocking between the waves, the last witness to the end of an illusion. Thus, concludes with a clear reference to the first images of the film, when the two brothers go to port to buy at the best price.Finally, tragedy marks the House, somewhat dodgier, but it has the potential to leave a bitter sediment in the sensitive spectator, complying with the essential objective of a modest product.</body>
</review>
