<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="American Gangster" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Can blacks play to be gangsters?</summary>
	<body>The genre of gangsters (if it is that you can be described as well) has inherited much the Lair of the western by the nostalgia of universes that do not already belong in the modern world, but that attract our attention, either for freedom and desparpajo with which their heroes campan at ease outside the law, or cloudy coherence of their codes of honorsometimes sensible and moral which he runs with magnificence the so-called civilized world (the Godfather is the emblem of this trend of gender).Is why American gangster begins with a scene in which a tired and skeptical "Bumpy" Johnson, confesses to his driver and successor Frank Lucas (Denzel Washington) be surprised by the new world that will leave, without moral or personal relations, dominated by large international corporations. "The good old days are gone.""Bumpy" Johnson really existed (as almost all those who populate the plot of the film), and therein inspire the black Godfather in the films Shaft in the 1970s. Johnson embodies the gangster principles, with a sort of Robin Hood to the poor of Harlem. But in addition to this, "Bumpy" Johnson became an icon for the black community to dare to compete with the white mafia of Italian origin. In fact the character protagonist, Frank Lucas, though he does not possess the spirit of his predecessor and more moves by the simple motto of you eat or you eat, does serve during the tape as an emblem of black power. In any other scene of drops this thesis, and is not difficult to see how the film opts for introducing, though slightly, the racial clash in the gangster world of the 1970s.But don't think the viewer that American gangster offers a cinema to the Spike Lee. Scott, like signal of more or less unequal factory premium visual spectacle to the narrative depth (ya, know about Blade Runner); If anything is allowed to dress a superficial background of social conflict, epic flavored Serpico (in regards to the character of the COP Richie Roberts) and a true whiff to the typical American eulogy of the man himself. And if you press me, travels parallel to the recent Zodiac, playing to the dialectic between the police (of personal life disordered but moral professional flawless) and the gangster (of personal life peaceful but moral dubious) in addition, American Gangster does not add to the genus major reforms beyond a touch of paint marked by a smart pace, not decaying despite his footage, and an excellent technical invoice. They are not few virtues for a product that doesn't disappoint to who look for a time. But that any Navigator be swayed by the songs of siren song of the promotional merchandising, which proclaims American gangster as a new masterpiece of the genre, to the height of the Padrino.American gangster contains significant gaps of script, while 157 minutes give to much. No profiling with solidity character more childish doctrine of the saved who can deflate the possibilities of providing the set of an epic or a lyricism Yes possessing other great works of the genre. The main character, starring a nothing credible Denzel Washington (force Yes seen in tapes like training day), contrasts with the sharper profile of Russell Crowe in a well nuanced role and edges. Highlights some coup d ' script, such as the scene in the bar with the brothers, to surprise a viewer delivered to what waiting is in the end a juicy narrative boiling, not to the Scarface Brian de Palma, but at least.American gangster he notices not knowing very well what wants to be Mayor. It starts well, delineating the biography of an interesting character, but the script is soon diluted in Fuzzy lines that emulate other similar works, but that level it to mediocrity. And I say mediocrity because it looks the intention of Scott to offer an outstanding, classical history that says now.The final scene indicates the search of filmmaker (as also tried it unsuccessfully Scorsese with its Gangs of New York) of a discourse on the nature of the violence in their country, especially that caused by poverty which plunged to African-Americans, displacing the bleak territory of delinquency and marginalization, but in the end is silenced by White America, that which was sent their boys to die in Viet Nam. To this is added, the widespread corruption that zanganea around all Mafia order (especially the drug business), exemplified here by police.American gangster not excited. You can amaze at times, taste of fragmented scenes more or less well resolved and showy manner, but does not offer the dramatic intensity nor the internal coherence of the Yes are touched other works of the genre. Which writes suspicion that Scott is too concerned about like, and that is a task that works with products of epic light but effective as a Gladiator, but not here. American gangster Scott wants to play to be Coppola, combined with the visual mastery of a Brian de Palma, but comes a hybrid to fit best.Noteworthy is the obsession of the character by seeming to be a white which goes unnoticed among many, and how he complains to his brother his racial attire. These scenes amply outlined us more disturbing reflection of the film. If you want to be a racial gangster, at most you will get is to sweep the streets with your dirty body. If you travistes you Rico white, you can then enter the game (if whites you make clear). That is why the resolution of the plot could not be less than ironic. Judge for yourselves.</body>
</review>
