<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Arma Fatal (Hot Fuzz)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Edgar Wright, if they may make me so bold, should receive some symbolic trophy by tremendous nerve and grace and be crowned King of the Disney parody definitely.</summary>
	<body>Edgar Wright and Simon Pegg are a perfect tandem. Much has been done hope this new movie where have decided to destroy the myths of action cinema of police with the same indiscretion that did so with terror in Shaun of the Dead.En this time Nicholas "Angle" a brilliant London policeman is "rewarded" for his excellent service record and to a lost village in the hand of God. What promised to be a destination the sea of simple dislike to this police action but for his fortune Sandford notable peace is going to be trastocada by a series of "suspicious and terrible accident".I will not talk of the multiple both explicit references as implied tapes as "Called Bodhi", "Lethal weapon", "La jungle de Cristal" or "Two rebel policemen" that this time the director has chosen to show us the scenes copied with authentic shamelessness and grace throughout the film by removing a bit of bad baba movie fan since then just die for me myths such as Charles Bronson and Chuck Norris, I prefer the Angel agent without blinking to doubt.The realization highlight above all mounting, fast, very fast, extremely direct and expressive that gives it a very necessary to standardize Cadence a tape, by duration, it could have been done a little heavy. An excellent decision of the director who, if they may make me so bold, should receive some symbolic trophy by tremendous nerve and grace and be crowned as King of the Disney parody (and already passage teach something of the genus American residents) impeccable cast with Nick Frost (always hilarious), Jim Broadbent (Moulin Rouge), Timothy Dalton (attempt to Bond) and a long etcetera that puts hairs as hooks.It is nice to see that after the long wait the thing has been good, especially when a well-deserved rush in the budget with respect to its predecessor makes comedies with such a good trial like this.I can't wait to see the following prepare us.FOR more GEEKS: Atentos to the cameo because Santa is Peter Jackson himself, Jeannine is Cate Banchett and its director also appears briefly.</body>
</review>
