<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Zombies party" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Shaun of The Dead should be declared a cult Film for posterity. A slogan can be defined: making fun of everything and everyone: of the clichés of the clichés of the slow, serious movies zombies. Maquiavélicamente perfect.</summary>
	<body>I will not go to try to explain that combination of alcohol and psychotropic substances translators decided to put the incredible title of Zombies Party to Shaun of the Dead, once discarded to make the title more "Castilian" prefer to simply fantasize about crazy bet carried out to try to boycott one of the best comedies in contemporary of our time in a terrible way.This perlite will have gone unnoticed for the majority of mortals because it is English, had little or no promotion and its main strengths are that the director and actors had collaborated successfully in the series Spaced issued in Great Britain where it has many acolytes (all of them recruited to make zombies at the end of the tape of voluntarily and the symbolic 1 pound amount) but that Spain nobody knows."Shaun is an English medium: lives in a House shared in the London neighborhood of Crouch End, has a mediocre job and his main hobby is to go to your favorite Pub the"Winchester"to paint". Obviously his girlfriend is fed up with him and responsible teammate does not support his family has more and minuses that his stepfather is not exactly charming. The problem is that one tomorrow Shaun rises and its around start to happen strange things. At the beginning doesn't notice, course, the English are rare people and drunks from two in the afternoon, I also percataría me of the unusual fact that have become Zombies who want to eat it.There are several things that I love in this film. One of them is that after seeing her in 2004 the fate did to work right next to where his characters lived so I can boast of having bought milk many times in the shop that Shaun came and where he began to see their monstrous friends. This anecdote only thing that makes is feel even more sympathy for this tape forced vision to any lover of good cinema. Half of my acquaintances have been threatened with death so they see and given that 95% are agree with me that almost suffered an embolism for the attacks of laughter I think that Shaun of The Dead should be declared a cult Film for posterity.The brilliance of the script is owe to Edgar Wright and Simon Pegg (the first director of the creature and the second its protagonist). A real fan of the genre films beyond the basic jokes recocerá iconography series say mentioning: George a. Romero, Peter Jackson, Robert Rodriguez, Tarantino, phrases of the own Spaced and so long that it would be impossible to concretize list. If you are not a supporter of this type of film you can enjoy much discovering great truths of humanity to escape a zombie that is very slow pointless or any bad disc can be a good weapon if necessary.A slogan can be defined: making fun of everything and everyone: of the clichés of the clichés of the slow, serious movies zombies &hellip; Maquiavélicamente perfect.</body>
</review>
