<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="The invasion" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I was about to sleep me and swear that I was afraid that the alien bug invaded my drowsiness and end up waking me at all. I however, I have seen much worse, clear. And when there is a dream, not worth trompetería Haydn or from AC/DC live.</summary>
	<body>Perhaps (I say only maybe) science fiction cultured, intellectual depth and mythological practical need a low budget, a profile of serie B and, above all, a completely disconnected treatment of palomitero film, cars that make tops on a banana peel and aliens of posh, they invade as he does not want the thing and, in a few days, dominate the planet Earth and to hold shares in Dow-Jones and eat hamburgers with Coca-Cola out of one movie theater. The pandemic that we slip is in fact, the mirror in which man must look, once the 20th century has closed its balance of dead, his account of injustices and their inventory of wars, guerrilla, riots and varied coat and formidable propaganda cultural suicide.I say that this version of (Don Siegel, 1.956) body snatchers spare, it adds nothing. And this appreciation strictly personal (as all the expressed by this chronicler of their vices) does not report that the film is bad or mediocre. I even arriesgaré to express that, at times, it kept my attention and made me enjoy in my armchair. Everyone knows that the illusions are marked letters and there is always a cabronazo with poker face incendiary who discovers the risk and you put in evidence in front of the mob of thugs in timba. From there to the alley and the alley to the hospital or the sky. I do not think that we merezcamos hell for us, Mount head inside, a booklet different to that gives us life. Write (and write about film even more) is a tiring business, which rarely compensates, but which provides to the disturbed perpetrated it unspeakable joys, júbilos of the size of the head of Charles Laughton. Nor should go by these branches we both like. Let's go back to the thieves of bodies: invasion is a tape with pretensions. Producers (Joe Silver to the distraught head) threw by Oliver Hirschbiegel - renowned, highly reputed, after the convincing and damning the last days of Hitler called the collapse--biography. They believed it obsolete that so useful intellectual air draft to turn commercial products into products of worship. They marraron: they got too many views in a simple story in excess. It has been a hybrid between thriller without shaft and cinema arthouse with the tap open inspiration. The message: man is a wolf to man. The alien invaders bodies bring a sort of nirvana in which there is no illuminated or disturbed, heterodox or memos, or geniuses: all clustered around a univocal concept of the sentimentality, all abalconados in the unpolluted air. And hete here that heroin Kidman, immaculate in her role as mother courage, not hugs the discourse of the invading bug and runs along streets and squares, laboratories and supermarkets, to find his son, and on the way, save the world. In this case, sorry, there is no cheerleader, but that is another movie and tonight plays invasion. not going to be me giving the Conference on the benefits of science fiction when it comes to witness the fragility of a society, but it must be admitted that the film fulfils that function with honours. We have the impression that we are selling a documentary about the dangers of technology or excessive moral apathy plaguing our consciences. Mine, for now, is safe, well entrenched in my laptop, listening to the music of Bill Evans and delaying a long drink (that was said before) while outside the streets not exhibited no sign of alien threat, but let's focus. Invasion: the argument is a hack of some script hired at the last minute and, apparently, poorly paid. This is where the individual, lacking in narrative, but sobrado ingenuity of nasty business, has sprayed poison the body of the story. There is more than one inconsistency and there are more than two dramatic gaps that leave the viewer out of the picture, if ever has come to feel, really, part of the entertainment. For do not burst the possibility for the gentle reader to give him an opportunity, it is not give no stroke, albeit mild, at the end, but cost me a lot, really, keep quiet and not gloat I to argue with hairs, slime and slimy bodies of outer space the sloppy end have mounted. I swear that until that end I was reasonably happy. Did not expect much, so the disappointment would not be Symphony. Even Opera. But the end came and with it the relief of the abandonment of the room - which was, moreover, empty: I saw the movie with my wife, already - and the certainty that these people of Hollywood gets into marshy lands and then they cannot exit and end up with mud up at the same end of labor pride. It is a saying. Now can one understand that the writers of the Mecca of cinema have long since strike. Or I do not understand at all. At this point, it is better to understand little and be exclusively carried away by feelings. The mine, in this obviable remake of the great original body snatchers, deserving separate criticism, are easily hospedables into the box for the failed experiences. There are so many. Last night, without going any further, I sat in my favorite chair with legitimate claim to see a fun bit of television and spent almost an hour of my life contemplate pigswill. Another failed experience. Or the invention of DTT, which has just entered in my village, I resarce of the thrashing of abuses that involves keeping entertaining a television. Why movie theaters are shelter and warm womb to the wounded for the sweetness of the always beloved frame. I am afraid that it has left me a spirited overview, without the usual technical deployment. It will be that a foreign body has crept me laryngeal track and hopes to I sleep to become one of them. Tomorrow as my criticisms are cold and hallucinated. By the influence of galaxies and quasars blessed.The collective fears story told here malconvence: he joins the inertia of having already seen similar messages in very identical tapes and then the effort is lower. Both of which makes the film and which provides.</body>
</review>
