<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los liantes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another film jewel of this trio of luxury, that view forward may cause more laughs than any current comedy.</summary>
	<body>They are no longer posters as the yesteryear. Synthesis of the movie in that small box. Esteso and Pajares tied by a few wives with a roulette as the background table. We already know that it will play. And below, for those who were not aware, Roulette, a beach, and a comic drawing of the fashionable couple pursue two young girls. But with the exception that are the Spanish deck cards. Boundless subtlety from the poster.The film is about a few types, Amador (Pajares), Fidel (Esteso) and Eduardo (Ozores) that survive in the Costa del Sol messing people. They spend the whole day scheming on the best scam, until that happens the definitive thymus is Amador overlook a man elephant (which gives lucky roulette players) and a millionaire you part of your winnings. All conveniently dotted with women in balls and refined comments that more can we ask?Well, again joins the climactic trio of dandruff in Spanish to give birth to a film that hardly will go down in the annals of history. The beginning is very good, very funny and witty scenes. To highlight the nonsense of the tunnel of washing, that seemed very good to me. Then the thing goes Lachey, as they come to the casino, with cruel on crossed and similar jokes. The end rectifies a little astray which had taken, but not too much. It has many jokes, grumosos most, sexist, racist and in bad taste, but with its funny point. In addition, a number of women seem to bare more than unnecessary naked, touching everywhere do not if not reinforce the storyline of the film.In short, another film jewel of this trio of luxury, that view forward can cause more laughs than any current comedy. And there are young girls in cuericos. Besitos.P.D: "I this see it blond, because I see it very black" they say while they despelotan two girls to make them the photo of the driver's license.Pd2: Many references policies there is, I was very surprised.</body>
</review>
