<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It offers typical Alchemy in which appearances of ultratumba mingle with past tragedy that its nose in the contemporaneity of the living.</summary>
	<body>To give you a fright is very different to spend fear. While a feeling confined to the immediacy of the startle, the other accesses more profound and enduring our psyche. This truism carried the land of cinema, a film can frighten because you get to concatenate several shocks with greater or lesser fortune, but truly difficult is spook, move a sense of anguish able to stay long after the screening of the film. The successful debut of Juan Antonio Bayona in a long so be on the shelf of the tapes of scares. Following the footsteps of the references that have sustained the horror genre in recent years, as some of the Japanese productions recycled by Americans, the orphanage does not depart from conventions set by films of similar profile. It's already typical Alchemy in which appearances of ultratumba mingle with past tragedy that its nose in the contemporaneity of the living. The type of films that deposit much of their success in the final surprise. That same viewers more malevolent threaten to tell the friend looked at the rear of the box office to purchase your ticket. If the surprise of the epilogue is at the height of the previous narrative, and offers the sought after emotionally charged, the result usually like. In my case, I don't know if because the whole seemed perfectly schemed to take me up to this point, not I thought it was the most notable of this good opera prima.However, yes would highlight how important it is the existence of such tapes between our industry. I don't know I think better way than this, a good thriller or of good a horror movie as it is the case, to ensure that our film exceeds the &mdash; sometimes &mdash; unjust labels of the past and can, thus, lift head and attract audiences with similar ability to call than larger industries. Because, although I have always defended this space thing is good cinema, come from where you come, nor I have concealed my joy when the movie quality has been cooked at home.Good decor, careful aesthetics and solvents camera moves technically endorse this tape also bordering to a great height in the artistic aspect, with a cast headed by Belén Rueda, who demonstrates the prosperous life that can also be behind more secure and accommodative television. In order that, without having me dazzled as many of those who recommended me to her fervently, I liked this film blessed since its inception with the timely support of Guillermo del Toro.</body>
</review>
