<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Mi Hermano Es Hijo Único" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For those who want to know with what you will find is my brother is only son is a species of?Tell me? with all its virtues and defects. In fact more virtues than faults.</summary>
	<body>Accio is a young man without direction. Small leaves, family chagrin, the seminar returning home where he realizes that siblings are appreciated and loved him. Soon find a way to feel integrated in a world which seems that it spins much faster than himself. He enlisted in the neo-fascist party by the influence of a family while his brother Manrico leads the leftist revolutions and leads social movements and strikers from his small town (Latin, fifty kilometres south of Rome).The ideology but the camadarería will get that both do not lose their ties over politics or love Accio professed towards his brand new and successful older brother's girlfriend. Accio soon after their journey Mussolinesco realizes social implications and the actions of its movement give a twist to his life linking it over to Manrico and of course the bride from East looking for family recognition which never comes. Accio is a touching character who lives in the shadow of a brilliant and charismatic brother and that is lost during the entire film until at the end get found himself (in the most literal sense of the word). But if there is something that characterizes the characters is that they are true to themselves. Once I heard an idea that could be summed up the vital political journey of any medium Spanish: "We are all idealistic until the 1940s." "Then we are right-wing or start looking to be idealistic and stupid at the same time." Let's say that Accio is consistent with the time that live you and like many others opt for the inverse way already to 1960s and 70 (which are set in the tape) had political repercussions in Italy very similar to the Spanish. As he himself admits at times "a fascist nella famiglia é comodo".For those who want to know with what you will find is my brother is only son is a species of "Tell me" with all its virtues and defects. In fact more virtues than faults. Thanks to the success achieved in Italy and the festivals that have been reaching our rooms and help that finally another movie poster that share its protagonists, Romanzo Criminale, release in our country in January of next year. THE movie data: Is a very free of the "fasciocomunista" novel adaptation (Il Fasciocomunista), Antonio Pennacchi Ramakrishna 5 Donatello awards from 11 nominations and public Un Certain Regard. Cannes Film Festival ' European Film Festival 07Sevilla. Section Oficial.Fue No. 1 at the box office in Italy, with EUR 8 million of revenue in less than a month</body>
</review>
