<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Adiós pequeña, adiós" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excellent debut of Ben Affleck after cameras.</summary>
	<body>xcelente debut after the screens of the actor Ben Affleck, who has adapted with intelligence and restraint the good novel by Dennis Lehane. According to her was reading him was enjoying it more and more, taking from the outset the idea of starring in her. But it hooked le and came to the depths, so decided to do it himself.And check that it has been a great success because it manages to perfectly convey the spirit, the essence of a story with multiple recesses where the ethics of duty well fulfilled struggles to prevail over distant interest perhaps, certainly more clear and safe, but less fair.The characters are not of a piece, but are simply human beings with many virtues but also countless defects. They have lights and shadows and both are interspersed depending on their circumstances.Thus, the protagonist, an atypical private investigator, has a code of ethics of professional conduct not always sees the good way that, at times, still the most obscure way, even choose crime if you think this will end with evil.And the other characters, same thing.The address of Affleck is quiet but crucial. Not just helps in good dialogues and the attractive and enveloping story that was already in the original novel, but convinces the trap, azorar and move the viewer through a clear narrative where the austerity and technical sobriety are at the service of the argument. No because artistic pretensions, unnecessary movements of camera or any flat surplus. Everything is very important and not only interest not lapses at any time but it is expressing despite its long (almost two hours, totally necessary), reaching an impressive final part for its dramatic force and his profound humanity, tinged of sadness and bitterness. The flat end is open but nothing ambigüo. We don't know yet if it is heartbreaking and hopeful, but we fear that, in a neighborhood "where the sheep live among wolves", as says the voiceover of the protagonist at the beginning, the future will not reassuring and exciting.Excellent interpretations. Ah! And that that the case which is narrated in this film and the real Madeleine are like two drops of water, nothing at all. It seem like an egg to a chestnut. Or is</body>
</review>
