<review author="José A. Peig" title="Shootem up" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An honest film with itself and with the public, exemplary action cinema, is its balance between vulgarity and ingenuity to be entertaining without lapsing into unnecessary Bendy.</summary>
	<body>Brilliant hyperbole about action cinema (that not of action cinema) the Michael Davis offered to us in this despiporre of references to the graphic and kinetic style of the comic and the mythology of the so-called z as a whole series. The lack of honesty and consistency to the public and to the very essence of the product tends to be a problem in a genus as the "film shots and call", as in the recent case of the trilogy of Bourne, pretentious vacuous apparatus whose possible validity disintegrated because of an alarming imbalance between history and development (fingido)(cheater) between the deranged and imprecise Chamber of Greengrass (which was intended to be the same action without such action needed so much artificial) and dramatic content-supposedly - motivated throughout the whirlwind of paranoid persecution. In Shoot Em Up we find a naked piece of embellishment that intend to praise this film genre beyond its essential attributes. The same title insinuates the nature of the product: a multiplication of shots and mira points that gradually develop the persecution and the plot until an outcome at the height of the joke already proposed from the outset. One might assume that behind the feast of artillery and hilarious imagination lies the vulgarity and vacuum related screenwriter has nothing to tell and limited to fascinate the viewer with frenetic rhythms. But we insist on a golden rule, take conscience that certain type of film is composed of scents that are stories told with sufficient capacity of synthesis and concisely.If the product knows what she wants to be, and if necessary expository clarity we perceive in the sequence Idea-ejecución of the Idea, other considerations are lost in elitists speeches. Shoot Em Up builds his own style inspired by a vast universe of references to pulse of cynical humor and wordplay as nervudos and electrifying as the same configuration of mounting, that succeeds in creating a magnificent pace of images and linked sequences so that the sensation transmitted by this show of delirium and impossible situations end up becoming the soul of a film perfectly geared towards a realization of libérrima evasion, but certainly vacuous. In fact, unlikely exposed situations is the expression of implicit in the subgenus laws, always taking care that we have that kind of movies that don't take seriously as well same and, more specifically, to the homenajeados cliches. The cinema show proved long ago that their legitimacy lies in the simplicity and accuracy in its proposals, and would be unfair not to recognize the expressive and formal fluidity of this piece.The great pace is added thug wit of dialogue, playing with the puns. The phrase that best exemplifies the narrative construction broken down into two strata of playful evasion which gives it his best film expression: the frantic pace of the images and dialogue that punctured laughing and cynical humor: how empty the pistol. In short, an honest film with itself and with the public, exemplary action cinema, is its balance between vulgarity and ingenuity to be entertaining without lapsing into unnecessary Bendy. Too bad, in any case, that the profiles of the characters are somewhat left by way of simple filling (regardless of the fun duel between Clive Owen and Paul Giamatti), that some - very few - action sequences are not at the height of the whole and that, perhaps, that broadly speaking is an example of a hyperbolic show restraint (thing nothing easy)at times tends towards the bad taste. Enjoy it and judge for yourself, because at least here there is talent for the purpose. If they do not like is not fault our, nor of Michael Davis.</body>
</review>
