<review author="Torbe" title="Superman returns" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I believe that you do not need a Superman today in day, missing a little order in the world and less sons of bitches. The selfishness is what moves the world, and that doubt that Superman can be eradicated it never.</summary>
	<body>Had I about 10 years when my Daddy took me to the movies to see Superman. Hear that music has made in my relive those moments and a chill has taken all my being. That moment! He has been back in the tiempoPero something fails, this movie is not just a reflection of what was the first. Superman for my will always be Christopher Reeve and Lois Lane that delgadurria with angelic face. Times change, Yes, and is now a gay with quiff and Lois Lane Superman a histerica with a huge ego that is half idiot. If we observe well, have protagonist, besides Superman, a family with two parents with a child. Somewhat typical in the American society where the majority of divorced are families and children have several parents.But let's go by parts, analyzing such Allen.Superman: In this movie there are unintentionally the history of Jesus Christ. In fact there is a picture of Superman in heaven with the arms outstretched and head down as if he was on the cross. Your mission on Earth is to save the man, then, as in the Bible, is vapuleado by the bad guys (the Calvary) and when it is believed dead, resurrects as final Lazaro.El of the movie is already in Fireworks, when speaking with his son and you loose modelled words of the Bible, the roll of father and son (God?) (Jesus Christ).I, as I've been so long in OPUS DEI, see right away when there are things like that. By the way, by what Superman flies with two fists forward? Should I go as a plane, with your arms fully extended? If not empezaria to spin as a missile? Hala, shit physics.Clark Kent: Is the descojono than anyone else is of note that Superman is the. Only a pair of glasses and hair differently and nobody asks if it may be the. Today more than ever the appearances are deceptive more than we think.Lois Lane: One of those "pitted" with a House with seaplane in the portico of his house, in the middle of New York. Old Cagate.la Lois Lane was quieter, this is a histeriquilla listen to it just makes me the willies. By the way, the Gee gets on the plane are ordago, and then it comes out unscathed, already is the descojono.Lex Luthor: Not bad but have been given very little Court. You could have been much more game the crack of Spacey. They have focused on the boring and soporifera relationship of Lois Lane and Superman and he has not been much to the Superman using her powers. Stop link and target more cane by ahíEl son: but that paranoia is this that has a son Superman? Do you want to do then the movie Superman and son? What a presentation of the son, killing a villain in a pianazo. Superman kills? UY uy as changing times, a child killing an adult in a movie for niñosOtras things: the movie has not taken into account numerous laws of physics, it is absolutely impossible to lift a plane or a huge mass of Earth from a point so minuscule. What that said of "give me a point of support and movere Earth" passes by lining the Superman, because not only does not have support, but that everything is you bring the sides, to not find consistency at the point where exerts the force.The scene of violence where the bad guys are out with Superman is disgusting and any child may have nightmares with it.The Kryptonite, that someone explain it to me, was not something that away powers to Superman to a long distance? If this tocandola all the time when it takes the rock outside the Earth because does not fall it over? Ah, that is left in a coma, note that things. Superman seems to be immortal and when it is, no one kills him.What a peliculaMas potato things: initially only saves Superman to the Peel, for example a bank people or people of the city of New York, as well as French and Germans. It is that the rest of the world doesn't matter, that fuck you to Africa, and that people continue starving.I believe that you do not need a Superman today in day, missing a little order in the world and less sons of bitches. The selfishness is what moves the world, and that doubt that Superman can be eradicated it never.</body>
</review>
