<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Supersalidos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A nostalgic review of a vital stage in which the daily concern revolved in lathe to her was eager to loss of virginity and the planning of the next party aimed at the Supreme end desvigador</summary>
	<body>Every time the American film debuts a Disney comedy with teens in heat only concerned by an existential binomial: sex and fun. They tend to 'throw' much easy cliché and comical situations more or less tired. Supersalidos, enmarcable being in this recurring subgenus offers something more. First, better built characters; Second, effective humor of fat but sifted stroke by fine irony and most lucid jokes; and third, some other truth about life transitions that separate the carefree adolescence of adult responsibility. All these additions of his screenplay with other recent similar proposals, she is joined by a successful cast headed by Jonah Hill and Michael Cera in the typical roles of a buddy movie, a musical selection full of classic setenteros and priceless pearls as the hilarious character of Fogell/Mcgrory (Christopher Mintz-Plasse).Essentially, the argument is a nostalgic review of a vital stage in which the daily concern revolved in lathe to her was eager to loss of virginity and the planning of the next party aimed at the Supreme end desvigador. He is also remembered fondly that friendship with that colleague of the soul with which shared war stories that encelado every day. Seth and Evan are these two colleagues who are a few weeks away from a transcendent change for both with the arrival of the University and the consequent separation of their destinations.Impending graduation is pressing them towards the goal and the Organization of a party to celebrate the end of course will offer to both the opportunity. Seth will play a trump card of essential element of the party to establish himself, together with his colleague and Fogell, the authentic outsider of the function, in the official suppliers of alcohol. That's where what appeared to be a relatively easy mission, thanks to the false Fogell adult passport, will become an odiseica adventure for the hat-trick of friends to arrive to the party with the 'revitalizing' liquid. To this plot will join of two policemen, in his revive their teenagers partying, added a point of chaladura to the film to lead to that nostalgic look to missed time partying immaturity. In the epilogue it will be clear that the closure of this stage often come by way of the domesticated life as a couple. Pera, until that point, should think the writers of Superbad: that removed us the danced.</body>
</review>
