<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Cube Zero" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Prequel "The cube" that explains a bit of what is going one. If you have not seen the first, not be what are you waiting for. If you've seen her and you liked it, see also this, more of the same. And if he didn't like you, becomes long.</summary>
	<body>We are going with this prequel of the suffocating Cube, that more than one bad night made me pass. In this case speak a sort of prequel, but I say unto you first or are you occurring see rather than the original, as I it out the surprises of the initial. I do not remember too well the two previous installments, but if I have the impression that this and the original are quite better than the mental straw of the hypercube. And that I liked.The film is about a pair of operatives working as watchmen of the large cube, seeing as die that it fall. One of them, the youngest, spends the day questioning elements of their work, while the other does no more than rebuke him. On the other hand, within the large cube, a series of characters trying to survive by opening doors and face the dangers threatening them. Quite suffocating.A film born directly to fatten the ranks of the video store on the corner a priori cannot bring anything good (unless is a porn, of course). But as the above seemed very interesting, because given a chance. This has been given a touch enough gore to ratites, perhaps to wake us up (the beginning is to turn off the DVD and go for a walk). The atmosphere created is just as claustrophobic as always, but double, given that you feel that feeling both prisoners and jailers. And the good thing about this is that you will explain you things. That if you not pass the film removing defects, that if you will not get bored.In short, prequel "The cube" that explains a bit of what is going one. If you have not seen the first, not be what are you waiting for. If you've seen her and you liked it, see also this, more of the same. And if he didn't like you, becomes long.I liked it and angustió me, objective achieved.Besitos.P.D: And how were going to rooms with the door in the ceiling? Thousands of absurd questions such as these will attack him. Arrear a güiscazo to kill neurons, ignore me.</body>
</review>
