<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="En bandeja de plata" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without prejudice to the rest of masterpieces of Wilder, this is one of my favorite. It is the quintessence of the genius, his nasty, his cynicism, his stark vision of a society inevitably maleada by selfishness and pettiness of humans.</summary>
	<body>All Wilder is in on a silver platter. The Wilder manners, shrewd observer of the depictions of the human being and fine stylist of the writing of their vices. It is the Wilder love of rogues and the tahúres, cheats and of the crápulas, people of good living they sacrifice a life routine routine in suburbs apartments for hocicar noses, even if it is mild and wile, in another happiness unlike the written in the manuals of urbanity and the Catechisms of any religion. A corrosive type, a delicacy in the stylistics of their phobias, but a great activist in the cause of their disenchantment by the society and its most sordid handlings.Fauna rogue that atiborra the best moments of the Wilder films spared no efforts to make silver platter a delicate dish, a succulent candy that will lose viewers accomplices, already made to facilities in this manner, and which will give an excellent starter, to the neophytes a say mild bite that devendrá binge when the Wilder effecthis cynicism, his irony, his skepticism, strain into the bloodstream, flood corpus cavernosum, walls of consciousness and these gaps of the brain where the capacity of amazement is short as asleep, beating without effort, waiting for one subject than an intelligent provocation. This is: black humor, lecherous very black humor that deforms and assesses nothing more and nothing less than a fundamental mercantilist society capital, that which Wilder puts so much effort to bother: insurance companies.The skillful Wilder dissects the moral misery, but without overwhelms staff with speculation and grey formulas of deadening sociologist. His scalpel cose and descose the subtle network of human relationships. Hinkle (Jack Lemmon) him you saw of good-natured, but nor does disgusted to an extra money. To the doctor of laws embadurna it peguntosa molasses of all odious characters that have populated its meritorious in this field filmography. The actor chosen could not be truer. The picapleitos without scruples who plays an enlightened Walter Matthau, brother-in-law of the prudish Lemmon, marked by grace, is the couple film absolute. The film is worth only to see them on stage. And this was the first of nine collaborations.Walter Matthau was a fondón actor and down-to-Earth, capable expression frown creasing and resemble a bulldozer about to chew the ear of a candid pablum, allow me this fierce image. The actor spent the straws in the filming: tobacco, one of their vices, along with women and the game (!) took toll on the heart and a severe stroke deviated you from the recording. Recovered, having lost almost twenty pounds, forced to do sport and care for his health if he didn't see the obituaries of glamour magazines and holders of the press in the industry and, above all, to abandon entirely the tobacco and the stress of the LAN and the skirts, Walter Matthau avinagró his gesture, empozoñó their dramatic arts and addressed the character of the lawyer rogue with a kind of internal aggression than perhaps It had not existed if the circumstances were others. For the benefit of the public, his performance was damning. You just have to see the original version and advetir Fudd tone and inflections elocuenes of an actor in State of grace and a unique script. However, Spanish dubbing is formidable, as often.Who has not had the pleasure of seeing her perhaps consents the Pilgrim idea that there is no humor in this Opera buffa the hypocrisy and duplicity of humankind: leave it, configure your brain to attend a major parade of hilarious situations (the visit of the doctor, the watchman of the window.)Sentimental cynicism: here is the mark of the House. Billy Wilder always redeems his characters of excessive tragedies, the excuse with elegance for all the bad milk that they have been inoculando and that suddenly, almost without coming to tale, release in droves, these semantic Cascades also house brand. In this film, abound: there are tons of enmarcables lines of text, situations worthy of the talent compositional Lubitsch and, of course, easily attributable to the genius of I.A.L. Diamond, a type of corrosive semantics and mental agility to the comparable to Lope de Vega and Calderón de la Barca theatrical. Yes, I know, some purists of our sacrosanct literature are going to write a post condemning my boldness. Do-it: I have godparents.If something exciting is this show of mass which is the film, it is astonishment, confusion, the intimate wonder of dislocation: one is sitting in his armchair, perhaps eaten by the fever Ethereal of not having a good day or the suspect that tomorrow is going to be like, and suddenly images, these 24 frames per secondthey are the absolute miracle of faith in art. Dislocation makes you keep sitting in the armchair, but the soul - this invention of the faith but that exists for these cases, rises in a cathartic, liberating flight and is the best place in the world, the joy, the momentary happiness. Yes, then the soul returns to the armchair and The End warns that we turn off the DVD or that we leave the pure and wonderful darkness of the room to confront chaos and disorder, that unruly avatar which is live. No I get pessimistic, although it is Monday and I cost spinning ideas and express them as it should be for the purpose of writing something above fortune cookie, the tape of Wilder. Alex, in his Antarctic, also destripado his love for the master on the far side of this post. Complete this reading with it, and be happy, for God's sake, don't let life procures les more havoc than its course and pressing certain of his sad settlement</body>
</review>
