<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="El viaje de Chihiro" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Disney has died, Japanese animation has earned her a 500%!Hayao Miyazaki is the worthy successor!</summary>
	<body>I quite like the cinema of animation, usually do a couple of films of this genre all the months, I do not remember who I once said Miyazaki was currently the reference this film and that he saw no ANIME was as if it was "dead and buried" so he had a stint with the DVD of "The journey of spirited away" on the tableIt is true that one day I had thought seeing her with "my kids" but did not, and another day had the movie in the player I got my bad sister and I had to call the doctor and since I caught it as a kind of "Juju" to the film, will that everytime someone spoke to me of "Chichiro" (as I call it) I closed strong eyes, and close them after the explosion of a firecracker, temiendome the worst. However, I have taken advantage of this afternoon, to see it! and nothing has happened! (I'm live and my family also), the film, a prodigy of Eastern animation and a movie that certainly could have been conventionally is certainly a landmark film, were not wrong that recommended me. It is true that it has certain air "Heidi" "marco" or any of the ANIME that have come to our country, forgive if not very ducho "Cowboy Beepop" in this field, so I think that it will be the first time that I write something I almost know from hearsay, "Kimagure Orange Road" (which I think it was a manga) and little else. I have little knowledge of anime and manga (Note mental. study over the issue, so that the next not notice that I am as "fish" as Nemo). No doubt if I can say that the film has excited me, with an air to "Alice's adventures in Wonderland" with such - cometé this to not disappear - some references to "The neverending story" (flying white Dragons) and other things that have made me stay with their mouths open and embrace my wife on the couch very satisfied by what he was seeing, while the two sonreíamos, as two young children by what we were seeing, and even us dabamos account that perhaps Hayao Miyazaki had bottomed in our hearts. The soundtrack magical, 30metre, direct and intense, big, very big with moments that fill the film music and make you're almost stuck to everything that it happens with the eyes as dishes. In short: Disney has died, Japanese animation has earned her a 500%!Hayao Miyazaki is the worthy successor!</body>
</review>
