<review author="Jack Torrance" title="Resident Evil Extincion" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Everything in this Resident Evil seems written by a 12 year old boy hooked to the playstation, and is therefore presumably this, its potential audience, enjoy much more than the occasional gracietas without grace and imaginative little of his screenplay.</summary>
	<body>Extinction is the third installment of the series that adapts the eponymous video game company campcom. On this occasion, the argument of the series of games is ignored and proposes a situation in which the infamous virus T has done havoc around the world, ending with the civilization and turning everyone into the usual zombies hungry for human flesh.(Can someone explain how a virus can desertifying a planet in its entirety?). A group of survivors search for food and supplies in a convoy with several vehicles while vague Alice through the desert from the Umbrella Corporation. An approach to the sea of interesting that gives rise to create a post-apocalyptic movie in the style of Mad Max, mixed with the Romeriano universe. In fact, the tape begins Interestingly, showing some zombie by beyond wandering through the desert. Without doubt, the best scenes from a movie that is entangled in an absurd narrative drift that sometimes creates occasional boredom.The problem of this third part is like their two previous deliveries, is the grim script for Anderson, whose obsession by show bad evil of the Umbrella Corporation and focus the argument on them instead of the motivations and problems of his characters, make that we feel no curiosity to know what will happen next, and that we only observe events and action by the mere fact that it exists. A model that is becoming dangerously common in American blockbusters, and they get that you one can bore a tape of these characteristics, as it is the case. The character are not explored or being authentic mannequins that we see Act and whose actions do not help to know his motivations, therefore more minimally, are absurd vague attempts to get closer to them, even presenting them by their names, telling us something of his past, when at any time becomes to know, even in the action scenes. The address is moderately functional, with the almost always successful visual sense of Russell Mucalthy flying over each level of the film. The production design and photography are the ingredients of this production, reminiscent of the Mad Max series tapes and pose a promising visual treatment that make think of a film more solid, so that finally the feeling was diluted as the film progresses, without really advance the story, and suddenly ends with a fight between monster and charisma more heroinpredictable and disappointing. Everything in this Resident Evil seems written by a 12 year old boy hooked to the playstation, and is therefore presumably this, its potential audience, enjoy much more than the occasional gracietas without grace and imaginative little of his screenplay. The spectator fan of the zombie sub-genre will enjoy no doubt with a couple of scenes that, although they do not say anything new, leave them satisfied at the end of the projection. Several plagiarism/tribute? The day of the dead (underground laboratory with scientists who trained dead), dawn of the dead (zombies super fast) and Land of the dead(ese_convoy_acorazado_rumbo_a_.) (Alaska) there is more action, better shot and with more violence than previous tapes of the saga, which make it a most enjoyable show, despite the fact that his story is child and acutely Decompensated than the original.Music dispenses with the terrible techno cheap typical of Anderson to leave a result more decent, although equally poor, than other products that bear his name. Extinction is the most entertaining chapter of the saga Resident Evil, which will be remembered in his triptych as the worst of the possible of a terrifying video game adaptations. Perhaps its Z series air some enjoy Italian post-apocalítica to the Bruno Mattei and Enzo Castellari, that in his 90-minute there is a bit of everything: mad scientists, mutant monsters, telekinetic powers to the storm, cantosísimos touches of Photoshop to Jovovich in close-up, costumes postapocalyptic with CSKA and sunglasses fashion, dogs and zombie crows, wicked chops and holographicHi-Tech technology, Clones of mile in balls and a beautiful map of the mouth of zombies for only 6 euros Tokyo subway who gives more?</body>
</review>
