<review author="Plissken" title="La Luna en Botella" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>'The Moon in the bottle' is notable letter of Grojo, a type that has fought against all odds to see made his own "cosmic Utopia": released his first feature.</summary>
	<body>I see a small, beautiful and brave movie like 'La Luna in the bottle', and I'm beginning to believe that this year has been, however, a good year for the Spanish film. It is true, there is almost taquillazos, but at least there are people debuting (Felix Viscarret, Nacho Cerdá, j. a. Bayona, Grojo) willing to raise the national quality standards.In 'La Luna in the bottle' follow the story of a handful of characters at the beginning of the hand of Zeta (an aspiring writer become "black") and then each one on its own. Their comings and goings of the cabaretero coffee Rossignol, their crosses and shocks, their small dramas and their minimum victories. Everyone seems to inhabit a limbo which will come only when they find a way to say "Yes" and to move forward with their lives.The feature film debut of Grojo, director forged in the world of advertising, and the short is a choral story that surprises, above all, by the force of its staging, trabajadísima at all levels, from the opening credits to the touches of FX. The Rossignol Café atmosphere is impeccable: their music, their decorations, lighting, its colourful clientele. the truth is that you can only congratulate the team of the Madrid director to achieve an atmosphere very close to the universe of Jeunet and Caro, without fear of the inevitable comparisons. A 10 for all.In addition to the powerful technical invoice, the screenplay by Grojo hits to the not be carried away by the easy melodrama or cryptic symbolism with a few simple characters, specific problems and credible reactions within the logic of the film. Each of them separately, directly linked to the last of 'La Luna in the bottle' thesis: a "no" can destroy you life, and "Yes" can restore the sense. Perhaps some plot is something raised, but is worthwhile the effort to have so many intimate deeds without falling or in the boredom nor in the pretentiousness. Special mention deserve the fun flashbacks to the purest style 'Amélie'; the history of the character of Pep Jové which both refers to 'Live', this masterpiece of Kurosawa; the intense musical numbers (perhaps too close together); and the recadito institutional art, bent on monuments to the absurd capable of ending old theatres.In the interpretive section is where the weak point of 'La Luna in the bottle'. Zeta, the protagonist, the character which should be the link between the viewer and the rest of inhabitants of the Rossignol coffee, is poorly played by Edu Soto, the famous "Neng de Castelfa". And the truth is that this character is large at almost all times, to the point that the film works best for all parties in that it does not appear he. Edu Soto strives, but simply isn't at the height, and more in comparison with the rest of the cast, a sober Bárbara Goenaga and a spectacular cast of side: Dominique Pinon, Pep Jové, Leigh Zimmerman, Michael Jenn or two of our most illustrious side, Joan Dalmau and María Elena FLores. And not forgetting the participation of Federico Luppi or Paco Algora, to not compliment at all. A pity about Edu Soto.Pero when it comes to the final assessment, there are more pros than cons, in this occasion. 'The Moon in the bottle' is the remarkable letter of Grojo, a type that has fought against all odds to see made his own "cosmic Utopia": released his first feature. Congratulations and continue the winning streak. A 6'5.</body>
</review>
