<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Superman returns" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If the future Viewer has children, of him a ration of hero. Yes it lacks this profile, go to see Zulo, that goes something else and is also film. And good.</summary>
	<body>This Philo Blockbuster can lead to confusion because it contains the seeds of a franchise, with everything that the movie business is capable of producing, and also certain traits of well-done film with scraps of film worth trying a product as arson filling to the greedy épila of suits that fly and hidden supernatural powers under a raincoat. And Bryan Singer, director fetish of the comic world tra its competent two X-men (not the third, overused by a pedestrian Ratner, sneaks into two hours and average of footage some evidence of her particular vision of the hero, we ignore whether with the consent of the producer, which might jeopardize the box if Superman leaves us a talkative dramatic or a guru of the postmodern mystical.) Singer makes, there is nothing, a religious, adult Superman and so weak, that is, human. Wants to Singer demonstrate that a superhero film can carry out without lowering his pants too and does so with a roster of actors very well sought after (the Donner Superman wasn't manco here) and a millimeter script which locks the purely visual form (bait for comics man-eaters, pongo by case) with a metaphysical background. Yes. What happens is that this architecture of purposes desmembra when the film takes 20 minutes and we have already seen practically everything you expected to see. Kevin Spacey, which leaves her London stage to inflate your account with a nutritional character is Lex Luthor closer to the more morbid Hannibal Lecter that to malo-malísimo, soft in the background, caricatured in previous installments, to which we were accustomed. Saturated merchandising, but this is inevitable. More when the premiere is in summer and the tails of the film amogollonan of entire families in search of two hours of placid rest truffles a couple of kilos of special effects. My son enjoyed the Nice. Father served as a responsible parent and recalled that also, at his age, he was taken by an uncle to see the first Christopher Reeves movie. If the future Viewer has children, of him a ration of hero. It is an icon of this last century who escaped. Yes it lacks this profile, go to see Zulo, that goes something else and is also film. And good. Or turn on your dvd, select 5.1 and perpetrating emotional stillness to excite with Apocalypse now, Coppola. A few days ago I did, and still my pampered memory thanks him.</body>
</review>
