<review author="Plissken" title="Supersonic man" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>'Supersonic Man' is the Spanish response to the 'Superman' by Richard Donner, perpetrated by Juan Piquer Simón, cornerstone of the fantastic cani.</summary>
	<body>'Supersonic Man' (1979) is the Spanish response to the 'Superman' by Richard Donner, perpetrated by Juan Piquer Simón, cornerstone of the fantastic cani. It must be said in its favour, with the four hard would have budget Piquer gets one more than worthy exploitation, because it brings together all the ingredients as their famous American copy, even surpassing it at times:-superhero: of course. Supersonic Man goes red and blue, flies, bounce you the bullets, lifts tractors. What is more, it makes disappear surveillance cameras, trucks, and turns guns on bananas! Morir you with envy, Kal - the! In addition, their only weak point fail it to mention, which with a handful of Kryptonite until I could defeat Superman, but not kidding I risk to be turned into a banana by Supersonic Man-Supervillano: OK, Lex Luthor mola. But here we have the diabolical Doctor Gluk (Cameron Mitchell), who kidnaps Professor Borgin to help him turn his laser ray of death. Unfortunately, Gluk is so sure that the Professor will work it does not disturb or torture him, nor in hypnotize you, or anything. Confined to insult him throughout the film, insults Borgin heroically endures. That Yes, Gluk has hair of truth-evil Army: Lex Luthor too lies only in its fight against Superman. On the other hand, Gluk boasts a deployment of troops worthy of Saddam Hussein. His soldiers take a few weapons capable of green people back, and although they seem not very lethal make a cool firing noise. Also have a truck with a label of "laundry", special operations, and of course, the jewel in the Crown: the superrobot, which asa, gas, launches rockets (two) surface-to-air missile, and has up to a webcam that Gluk believe that he is playing Doom. The movements are perhaps not very fluid, but that Luthor had one?-secret identity: Kal - the coming from Krypton, is raised as Clark Kent and works in a newspaper, Fronte after sad glasses. It is a ducks and insecure in his private life. Supersonic Man, on the other hand, is Kronos, a guy with mask to which it resurrect in a ship to carry out a dangerous mission: that earthlings do not destroy the universe to force of giving birth of evil geniuses. Kronos (Michael Coby) down to Earth and takes the human form of Paul to dry (much more secret than Clark Kent), a guy with a mustache and vest of point that is able to say that he is a private detective, invite to dinner at the girl and even try to beneficiár the first night! In addition, cabin you don't need to be changed, just you talk to your Casio digital watch. And to make matters worse, not cut to fly to the nearest restaurant and poach two bottles of champagne if Miss calls. And also very important fact, he himself SE HACE call SUPERSONIC MAN, not as Superman, which is a hype media.-La Chica: here, the truth very little to say. Superman in love with Lois Lane for what it is, a Superman. Supersonic Man, on the other hand, is linked to Patricia Borgin (Diana Polakov) with their more mundane trickery (lies, he invites her to dinner, a slow bailecito). In addition, Patricia does not give the impression of being the most virtuous girl on the planet: to) is for a measly $ 5,000 ransom and still what you think; (and b) while his father is kidnapped, she is dedicated to zorrear with Paul, "private detective".-music: If the Superman fanfare is one of the great themes of John Williams, the 'supersonic man' comprising Peguri/Izaguirre/Attias (the Stock Aitken Waterman of the dance in Hispanic, so for me) is a llenapistas already wishing for themselves Jamiroquai or the Boney m. All rhythm and four bad few words make up the catchy melody that sounds every time that Supersonic Man crosses the sky of Alicante, with picture of NY back (see "how it became" on the page of Juan Piquer, is priceless). Here let the thing in a technical tie.Total, than the movie is what it is, an opportunity for Juan Piquer get people what they asked, in exchange for a fistful of dollars. And it fulfils its mission, such as Supersonic Man. After this title would come classic from the patriotic gore as 'Shiver', 'thousand screaming has the night', 'Slugs' or 'The crack'. And in addition, a series of adaptations of stories by Jules Verne ('mystery on Monster island', 'The sea Devils'). Before launching to destructive criticism, I recommend visiting the page of this authentic man of cinema. Few Spanish directors have worked with people from the category of Peter Cushing and Terence Stamp. And to me thought me it was a noteworthy by-product: superheroes, the Spaniards, what the hell. Visça Superlópez!And a last fact: 'Supersonic Man' was seen by 751.625 people. 'The secret life of words', by 664.753. Absent, by 136.906. How much geek had 79, right? Or perhaps is that there were people that, Yes, that took this as an industry?</body>
</review>
