<review author="Kiko de España" title="Alien Space Avenger" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Something like Pulp Slapstiscifi dominated the visual gag, the vodevilera musiquilla and the absurd.</summary>
	<body>Maybe that it do not think, but Alien Space Avenger is one of the worst movies in history with best "history" directed her in 1989 Richard w. Haines, three years after the terribly bad mutants at the University and is the final piece of the excellent leaflet horrorcasposo which began with Splatter university in 1984Y history mola.We are in New York in 1939 and know two couples then: them worried about arriving later to film and they worried not be talking still borrachuzos about comics.Well, just before this a yellow letters on the Galaxy inform us of the escape of four prisoners alien quite montoneros.Back to Earth see the vehicle or car of the kids (quite old, we will not trick) on a remote road at times of day, at times of night parked to piss.Then a UFO fly over the area until crashing in the forest that surrounds the protagonists and want clear, curious about the group to look at.You, as a viewer, already think that what you're watching "again": the pardillo stays with the parasite and will remove the rest of the group one by one.Because you're wrong. There are four aliens, one for each chic @ and as the dumbest opens the ship with a stone are all possessed. Duly humanized decide to then, approaching the town for some plutonium and nuclear fuel.The atmosphere of this part of the movie is something like Slapstiscifi dominated the visual gag, the vodevilera musiquilla and the absurd. After making a stop at a bar where they steal weapons and kill the clientele fled a UFO bounty hunter firing to the ufo with shotguns, hiding in the nave of the bosque.50 years later a few workers (will die in group to discover the ship and open.) They rediscovered the nave (with a shovel). And it is our only aliens to kill masses, go kill one unless violate you, then the human melts.In the current NY live Matt, a cartoonist in low hours. until he sees in a nightclub to these four villagers in the 1930s, they enter without paying. Matt isn't played by him, but could be.Matt becomes obsessed with them (being persecuted by the disco-pub while he draws them) because they seem to appear "from another world" and comes up with create a new comic book in which some terrorist aliens of the 1930s invade Earth. Terrorists is because in a nuclear power plant these ancient men kill 33 employees and steal a thermos with plutonium that was on a Toolbox. The journalist that narrates the events with hull put the adjective. Logical. Office Matt tells the idea to his boss, asking you for a sketch. In the next scene one of the aliens sees the comic in a kiosk and gets scared. Gathered in a water decide wrecking because course, your address is on the back. An alien bounty hunter gets inside the girlfriend of Matt and together they decide to exterminate the threat, something difficult because "they" regenerate debuti.And Matt is based on his experiences to draw comics. In this respect the movie becomes Super copied for good: a comic book artist who has a number of success on a bounty hunter alien exterminator of terrorist invaders of the 1930s. that in reality he is CCU!But the movie becomes embers despite not reaching the eighty minutes. The best thing is that about 70 people die or so. All "waiting for" his shot.</body>
</review>
