<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Promesas del Este" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A Standing Ovation for David Cronenberg is able to elevate the genre to unsuspected heights with a certain balance and drama that is not on a screen so easily.</summary>
	<body>An actor who is able to give life to this mafia climbs only occurs to me and has the face, the body and if you press me the voice of Viggo Mortensen. I don't know if I'm the only one who has noticed that Viggo has the ability to put all the spectators on the edge of the armchair for reasons unrelated to the film. It is undoubtedly one of living beings that vocalizes worse in the history of the cinema. If it was almost impossible to know what he said in his Spanish in Alatriste drag ' or is even worse when leave you the Argentine accent in interviews. Or when it was the imposing Aragorn could avoid talking with the neck of his shirt is normal being a Russian thing worse. The type took very chest thing make a credible role so was to ignite the language to fake accent and the result is that as always there is no way to understand half of what comes out of his mouth and get your half ass seat to see if by proximity listeners better dreaming that you could have a remote control everytime he opens his mouth to raise the volume. Precisely for this reason that Viggo block as perfect mafioso, is a huge, scary, is not understood and has objection to teach their tattoos, characterization or naked If the script requires (and those that have been shocked by the naked should worry more about mamporrazos that berate during the aforementioned scene) and still attracts the Viewer. His recent films have been a genuine Declaration of principles. After the characterization of the Lord of the rings has bothered to Peck by half the world and with the best directors and independent productions more risky without blinking. My most sincere applause for that reason but by God vocalize me Mr Viggo. I have not been able to remedy this and I chopped on the dark side watching you and the version dubbed (in that order) but I must admit that, as always, is resounding multilingüistica English and unquestionably better than adaptation to the Castilian (always with my respect to translators and magnificent dubbers of this country). In fact, Eastern promises is one of those films that is worthwhile to be viewed with subtitles to appreciate the performances and interpretive work of all its participants.In Eastern promises is a driver that monitors the back of the son of the largest mafia capo. A woman dies leaving a baby and a journal with its history that goes to the midwife of a London hospital. Her Russian ancestry makes that very take chest discovering what is written in these pages and find those responsible for the death of the girl so much and his family to be able to deliver them the baby. But we all know how they are Russian with these things gangs so Naomi is consigned to a couple of quite interesting trouble to dress with a bit of glamour the history of violence and mafia intrigue of this group. Indeed the emergence of Naomi Watts, although they sold otherwise, is merely incidental. You are welcome to see a friendly face among so many manly testosterone and settling of accounts but in reality the important eastern promises is Viggo Mortensen, Vincent Cassel and Armin Mueller-Stahl with very decent and risky work of interpretation. Reminds me of the good films that years ago made our screens and where we learned to value a villain in his authentic measure, although updating technique, methods and giving to the wild and realistic stamp of its director. That Yes, a Standing Ovation for David Cronenberg is able to elevate the genre to unsuspected heights with a certain balance and drama that is not on a screen so easily.</body>
</review>
