<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Matrimonio Compulsivo" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Compulsive marriage is another of those tapes that will end up at the bottom of the memory and perhaps with the passage of time is mixed with all her classmates and then disappear in the immensity of the bleary-eyed comedy.</summary>
	<body>If I am a sadistic. If it had to know of before. There are two things that I love in a comedy: one is the regia Peter Farrelly and Bobby Farrelly or what is the same: the Farrelli brothers. I recognize that only a couple of gags in his early films made me laugh but there ended my short and intense romance with them. Secondly, Ben Stiller. Possibly there are only another actor that irritating me so much as he (use euphemistic way actor) and that is his colleague Adam Sandler. Some consider that the problem of Ben Stiler is that he has not been a role to its "interpretive level". I tremble to think what you can do this guy to a good movie and pray sincerely so that it will not happen ever. The thing is that in spite of that I remain true to my principles and see every movie that any of these individuals removed only for the pleasure of discovering that he has not changed the dynamics and still do not find the point. Profanity, vacuos comic blows and absurd blows and cheap eschatology laugh jokes. More of the same. Not have surprised me this time with this small slapstick with little interest from the point of view of the script. Seems that the big players of comedy has become older and young people still cannot meet their place arguments rotate during a season on the tedious double world: Casar you with me, until that cure Nos Separe, Os Declaro husband and husband, and the latter seems to indicate that the public responds quite well so Dios caught us confessed to withstand a good batch of silly comedies about the joys and woes of the sacred sacrament of marriage. As well, I have to say that in marriage compulsive (whose title, once translated painfully into Spanish only charged sense at the end of the tape) a pretty stale Ben Stiller decides to marry a girl just know moved by the desperate feeling that everyone lives in couple to her around. It will be on the honeymoon trip when he will discover that his girlfriend is a little psychopath and will fall in love with another perfect unknown. With so little consistent raw is normal that film makes water everywhere only covered in the interpretative capabilities of the actors (as I mentioned are not of my tea). Why compulsive marriage is another of those tapes that will end up at the bottom of the memory and perhaps with the passage of time is mixed with all her classmates and then disappear in the immensity of the bleary-eyed comedy.</body>
</review>
