<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The orphanage is not a film of terror to use if not rather a fine exercise of psychological terror with a fair dash of drama away from the easy scare.</summary>
	<body>I needed to at least five trustworthy people tell me that the orphanage was worth seeing to encourage me to take the step. Not memory have been so reluctant to see a Spanish film in my life. But as rectify is wise here am, singing the Mea Culpa and recognizing that Juan Antonio Bayona knows what it does. Belén Rueda is not of my devotion. I recognize that in this film his portrayal is flawless but there is something in his tone of voice that follows me proving highly tiresome (which dubbing of the shining). But removing these nuances which without doubt are very subjective and personal it makes a fairly credible role in this small turn of nut to the horror genre. The setting of the film is everything. Thanks to an impeccable work of production anyone is capable of believing the desperation of this mother looking for his son who has been "kidnapped" by ghosts, imaginary friends from his own childhood that the House where they live was the boarding school where she herself grew from small and wants to become a home for children with special needs. The line that separates the tension and uncertainty of terror is very well drawn what I have to say that the orphanage is not a film of terror to use if not rather a fine exercise of psychological terror with a fair dash of drama away from the easy scare. It is scored as the game itself proposed the ghostly inhabitants of the House, is a game of treasure hunt which stretches until the outcome in the form of final turn attractive and meditated. It is difficult to square pieces of such dramatic form in a first film but Bayonne has had a master such as Guillermo del Toro to help and guide, and the putative father of the tape. But the orphanage is also a cheat film, is a tape where they give you all the keys of the mystery from the first moment and you lose during the footage with subterfuge and rare tracks. Throws you into the paranormal world and you drag toward the past which the protagonists find it unknown to then bring to light myths, stories and games for children. So much straw is difficult to spin as fine and that possibly in the hands of a director with more filming would have given more are just depleted in passages which has no outlet inside the claustrophobic mansion full of ghost peterpanescos. With these defects, on the other hand perdonables, the orphanage has earned the recognition of the public and has achieved an exceptional box office, which is worthy of thank and another virtue to value on the tape of this newcomer.</body>
</review>
