<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Un funeral de muerte" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hilirante, black up to but not power, with a dramatic tinge of truly desirable and endearing characters that go really wrong and either at the same time.</summary>
	<body>Frank Oz, a director not too prestigious but always effective, is back with an incredibly funny black comedy. Death at a funeral is an exercise in English taste (though, anyway, American) that it does not stop at any time and get more than a smile, a laugh in each of her scenes. Hilirante, black up to but not power, with a dramatic tinge of truly desirable and endearing characters that go really wrong and either at the same time. This film is, above all, a waste of very intelligent talent, a kind of English drama told in an exquisite way. It can cross out of being out of sync in some of their scenes (of the uncle on the toilet, very thing Farrelly), or rather present dyes nothing own Hollywood in an environment so typically English. It is also somewhat repetitive, but it already is.Its main objective is to let us pass the best possible, although no doubt the final speech leaves us with hair-raising. It is what it seems, entirely. And it is that black comedies are not intended to be nothing more than samples of a smart and mischievous smile. Your script is extremely wild, although does not lack detail. Without doubt, enviable and completely round, and even manages to make us cry with laughter with several of his scenes. This is an English humor more than American, a humor where the Viewer makes more than cry of laughter: think. And I am not saying that death at A funeral is the height of the depth. By God! This is a first class entertainment, but not have touches that can out. Yes, perhaps the death treated as something with which you can play. But I doubt that Oz is going down this path. He is poised to introduce an alocadísima comedy in an apparent tragedy, and this is, without doubt, irreproachable and very successful.Situations that happen to the characters in the movie may be too out of control, but I assure you that taking into account the set of the film, not worth stopping to think if they are or are not at all appropriate. They are simply great. And enough to utter the word "valium" to understand that, perhaps, more this causative element of such tragedy, the death of the Patriarch with his, do terrible?, consequences. Screenwriter Dean Craig, rather than rely on a bàsico topic such as death, represented in such a way that it remains secluded behind the family entanglements.And, finally, to say that all the cast of the film perfectly fulfills its duty. The figure of the main comic is here left band to offer all them properly and similar ownership. In addition, none of them is particularly famous, so glad sight to a server to be realize that many of them are true and new stars of the black comedy. Let Steve Martin or Eddie Murphy.En final, a great American English style comedy that it will provoke any viewer who sees more than a simple smile. A prank done, above all, way careful with humor that seems to be a mix of American with the English. This is probably one of the most entertaining of recent years films.</body>
</review>
