<review author="Patri" title="El sueño de Cassandra" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interestingly, the number of tracks that Woody Allen is giving throughout the film on how he will end it, in the form of dialogues apparently unimportant.</summary>
	<body>Woody Allen is one of the few that never fails to its annual meeting released a film that may be better or worse, but is always superior to film garbage that invades us, I feel fortunate to be able to enjoy each year of the creativity of this man and I do not demand to carry out a masterpiece each time that it opens, because that would be a miracle, however it seems that many critics are intent on each piece of Woody Allen should be as good as mysterious murder in Manhattan or Annie Hall. The dream of Cassandra has received so many bad reviews that I went to the cinema to see her with questions about what was going to find me, and I started thinking that these criticisms were Foundation, the first half hour is really boring and nothing interesting happens at the beginning of the film, but when he really started the movie, I realized that was before another good movie that worth seeing and do pass a wonderful time in cinema. The introduction is too long and the end too short and abrupt, although the latter did not bother me at all, instead I created a sense known to just experiment with films and Hitchcock, Woody Allen as a certain burden of irony and complicity with the Viewer. The protagonists are Ewan McGregor, in this film makes a complicated role, a supposedly cold person and that proves capable of anything in order to get prosper economically, without apparently feeling remorse and Colin Farrell, who is his brother, a mechanic got in the game world and alcohol, which will trigger a series of events that are twisting sothe thing just like Greek tragedies to which referred several times in the film. The number of tracks that Woody Allen is giving throughout the film on how he will end it, in the form of dialogues apparently without importance, something that is also linked to the use of random element which decides on our lives, much more developed in Match Point, which only that failed for my taste was the actor is very interesting main (Ewan Mcgregor had embroidered it). With regard to Match Point, it must be said that the last three films of Woody Allen (Match Point, Scoop and the dream of Cassandra) seem to form a trilogy with the same obsessions and the same background.It seems that the "trilogy" has ended, so you know of the famous movie filmed in Barcelona, it seems it will follow the same paths. Do not be if someone else will be realized, but curiously, it seems to me that the actress who plays the girlfriend of Colin Farrel, is very much like Scarlett Johansson, was chosen on purpose? Unconsciously? Or are they mine imaginations?</body>
</review>
