<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Driving Lessons" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With the exception of a couple of fans of the apprentice magician will enjoy with Ron Weasley doing a role more agreement with its age the rest we are heart broken trying to understand and admire his companion on the road with little success.</summary>
	<body>It is a disgrace to be a niño-actor. If your colleague of Daniel Radcliffe fatigue opted to undress on the London stage always covered by his tireless and orondo Uncle Vernon, forgiveness, is the subconscious meant sponsored by Richard Griffiths, Rupert Grint has decided to be seduced by an old woman who is also anecdotally his mother in Harry Potter. What a lovely coincidence! That my "I would say English". Ben Marshall lives in an average family in London. Her mother is a kind of addict Italy and his father. His most beloved and overbearing mother played masterfully by Laura Linney maintains his son with overbooking of tasks between the religious meetings and the household chores concluding with his particular driving lessons. When Ben Gets a use of "boy for everything" to Evie, an old actress that actually seeks a friend, the even brightest Julie Walters (Yes, the same who taught dancing at Billy Elliot, age and the characterization also take their toll) that will return his world upside down trying to provoke a reaction extreme in his lethargic life which has just reached a sort of psychedelic Road Trip to Escocia.Parafraseando this misunderstood genius of the small screen that is Homer Simpson: "I aburrooo!". And it is that British trajicomedias have a double edged sword, or are very good or very bad and with the exception of a couple of fans of the apprentice magician will enjoy with Ron Weasley doing a role more agreement with its age the rest we are heart broken trying to understand and admire his companion on the road with little success. Very easy tear and too much addiction to the common places of films aimed at copar Saturday afternoon hours (Yes, those based on real facts that accompany the NAPs after opíparas meals for the weekend).</body>
</review>
