<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El séptimo sello" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cult film of the deceased Ingmar Bergman about a Knight who plays chess with death while you search for a meaning to life. Essential to see to be able to say "I saw 'The seventh seal' and it is not so peñazo as I thought..."</summary>
	<body>Duration: The time when referring to Bergman, is a very relative variable. For my medium Zucchini that has slept the two times that I've seen, it lasts until the scene which acts the Buskers. If awake, stand a little more than an hour and a half.Premiere: The movie is 56, but it premiered on Spain on March 20, 1961, in the Palace music (I think it lloviznaba slightly, but to me fails the memory, heh, heh).Spectators: 32.675, although there is no human being not claiming that it is a peñazo, what get me 48 million viewers only in Spain, right?.Spanish, Franco is dead, this, not that I've been busy. Spanish, Chinchan Tito has reached maturity as a human being and can affirm, with knowledge of the facts, that the seventh seal is a film for viewers of fine palate (or a peñazo for the rest, of course). Why? Because we have seen her, not one, if not twice. Thus, with two balls. Therefore, and for the present, you can call me Excentísimo e ilustrísimo gentleman of the Court Imperial intergalactic, Mr Tito Chinchan. It is said.The film is about a gentleman and his faithful squire who return to their native Sweden after 10 years of battling in a holy war of those. Upon his return, nothing more making landfall, you are presented the death to tell him that his time has come. That I said that could have said it before you paste the Holy Land palizón - Sweden, right?. Total, the Knight tells him to death that they have to play a partidilla chess to see if he has the time, or not, that he is very jover to die, and thus step to clarify doubts about the meaning of life. And all this happens in 3 minutes, warn him that you may know that it is dense.Let's see, this film is not to do with colleagues while you smoke you some canutos and eyes give laps as the cherries of the slot machines. With this you have to sit at a decent time, with a glass of water and a guide to explain the film, that if you will not be with the same face I am I. At the beginning, the thing promises, but as it progresses, it will espesando and ends turned into a paste with a strange ending. Eyes of a critic with cinematographic knowledge this have many crumbs (which I've reported in the went), but my feral eyes, not. I'll stick with the scene is that tells the Squire a girl something like "Do you know cooking?" You've saved and you want to make love without violating you. "I hope that my wife is dead, so I need company, we will." And the girl will follow, of course. The hecatomb.In short, cult film of the deceased Ingmar Bergman about a Knight who plays chess with death while you search for a meaning to life. Essential to see to be able to say loud and clear "I saw 'The seventh seal' and it is not so peñazo as I thought."To tell the truth, it is a little boring, but not as much as they say to those who have not seen. In addition, over the years makes me think that in his time he had to be very impressive, since very increases tone (not sexual, boeotian) scenes have.Besitos.P.D: I've seen twice that my medium avocado I mess and promise me it won't sleep. That if, as the saying goes "or have given me ass or I will return to give". There is that.Pd2: One thing if that bag in clear, religion, the more far better.</body>
</review>
