<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After seeing the new Robert Redford film, the first thing that comes to mind is that more than Lions for Lambs is should have titled sheep for sheep.</summary>
	<body>It is paradoxical and at the same time incredible the ability of human beings to revive some events almost in a cyclic way. And it is also surprising that a society as the United States need a bloody and terrible war to awaken his social conscience and begin a new era. It happened thirty years ago with Viet Nam and is happening today with Iraq. And cinema is not immune from this catharsis, and is beginning to get films that not only denounce the injustice of the war in Iraq but also serious injustices social and political society who live "the American dream". Reaches the charts the new job as director of Robert Redford, which deals with such hot topics as the Iraqi conflict, political corruption, the loss of freedom of the press or the apathy of the society to undertake changes from three different perspectives. In principle, it's an attractive proposal which raises numerous questions, but however to go on the minutes, the opening speech of Redford is will be diluted. The freshness as well as the intention to offer something different is losing, and the script just falling on own American patriotic film topics. Lions for Lambs is an empty movie without any content and that will cause a great disappointment among those spectators eager for an intelligent film that shows the harsh reality that immersed the strongest power in the world. After seeing the new Robert Redford film, the first thing that comes to mind is that more than Lions for Lambs is should have titled sheep for sheep. And the new work from Redford cineasta promises much, raises some interesting questions, but fails to clearly wet. What is more, even gives the impression of exalt certain jingoistic values (that not patriotic) in the country of the bars and stars.</body>
</review>
