<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Elizabeth: La Edad de Oro" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Elizabeth: The golden age is a historical misrepresentation exercise as not seen in the film from the era in which Errol Flynn jumped in mesh around the screen.</summary>
	<body>In these times that since certain sectors is cry that it breaks Spain, the premiere of a movie like Elizabeth: the golden age will be doubly controversial. Perhaps for this reason, since Universal Pictures Spain have decided to change two sentences that appeared in the first folding trailer and replace them with less hurtful expressions. We say that it is doubly controversial because on its single tape give much to talk by its peculiar reading of the history. Yes, this is film, and even more, this is a film criticism and not a thesis on the history of late 16th century, but it is inevitable that the judgment on Elizabeth: the golden age is not deeply influenced by historical each viewer's notions. Firstly, it must be said that Shekhar Kapur not should not even know the expression historical accuracy, and even less its significance, and is that we strongly recommend that anyone who knows in depth history go to see the film, under penalty of severe mental or coronary disorders. The hagiographic treatment of Queen Elizabeth I was totally predictable (why if Mary continues to be Mary, Elizabeth I have to call her Elizabeth I?), as already happened in the original film, as it was hoped the ridicule of everything having to do with Spain, what contributes enthusiastically Jordi Mollà its unfortunate composition of Philip II. The tape has some scenes become pathetic, like the almost dreamlike and naïve implementation of Mary Stuart. The only positive points of Elizabeth: the golden age have their own name, and are Cate Blanchett, Geoffrey Rush, Clive Owen and Rhys Ifans.Elizabeth: the golden age is a historical misrepresentation exercise as not seen in the film from the era in which Errol Flynn jumped in mesh around the screen. Anyone who has a minimum historical notions will be swearing in Aramaic and cinema regretting deeply having wasted two hours of his life in such crappy.</body>
</review>
