<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La Jungla 4.0" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One leaves cinema with good flavor of mouth despite the conviction that the time has come to retire John McClane.</summary>
	<body>The return to the screens of a legendary character as John McClane could not be but one of the film events of the year. If the already known and well proven charisma Bruce Willis will add some young actors and a director of true prestige among the new breed of spectators, not in vain Len Wiseman is the director of the correct "Underworld" and "Underworld: Evolution", the result could only be a commercial success &hellip; and artistic?Let's talk about this &hellip; I would like to emphasize that this film has been titled "The jungle 4.0" (Live Free or Die Hard) as it could have titled "Bourne it gets", "James Bond against the world" or "Transporter 3 and a half". The only thing that unites this film with the previous is the name of the central character, a couple of references to his ex-wife and the actor who embodies it, Bruce Willis, true engine of a movie without him would have no sense. He filled with his charisma and his force on screen the holes of a script that has the justito and little else. Opts Wiseman for a hyperbolic cinema more in line with "Transporter 2" that in the of "the Bourne Ultimatum", so we understand. A type of action totally dependent on Visual effects that allow McClane to jump on a plane, shoot down a helicopter or single avoids flying cars. Once again, as you can imagine, the spectacle through the dramatic.What saves the film of the wreck, as well as Bruce Willis, is does not intend to be nothing more than what is and therefore Wiseman endows her with a fairly intense pace which takes you for an action in another (could be phases of a video game) without that look at the clock in the two hours that lasts for the film.Thus one goes on film with good flavor of mouth despite the conviction that the time has come to retire John McClane. Just the opposite happens to Bruce Willis I believe that, in the action genre, as in others, yet you can give us many joys.Moonfleet final valuation: 6 out of 10</body>
</review>
