<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Siete Mesas de Billar Francés" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good script, good actors and good management offer us a good example of how, without large budgets, film the good in Spain can be done.</summary>
	<body>Gracia Querejeta is not a Director to which it him has taken the measure due to the lack of knowledge I have of his earlier work. I saw "My side again when" a few years ago and I remember that I had liked but I have not seen "The last journey of Robert Rylands" nor "Hector" despite the good-looking they have a priori. Therefore went to the cinema to see "Seven tables of Carom billiards" without knowing very well what I was going to find and brought only by my good vibrations before the film. And what I found finally? Well, a film which should mark the reference to one of the possible paths that must pass Spanish cinema. I say this because, while it is clear that the public demands more movies of Spanish genus, with large budgets and well done, believe that proposals such as Gracia Querejeta not only have room in our charts but they are necessary. "Seven tables of Carom billiards" it has a good script, work of the Director and David Planell, able to create characters of flesh and blood, of which one feels as their own; and it also has a handful of terrific actors able to give them life. To make a good film need little more, of course a solvent director to carry forward the project. But to be a box office success in the 21st century Yes else need: a good marketing campaign. This is where I think that it is has failed, probably due to lack of a more loose budget. As I say, the script is an example of construction of characters. Why hate me error that I can not understand as the resolution of the story of el tuerto (Enrique Villén) which I believe little consistent with that seen in the rest of the film and somewhat improvised. I also have the feeling of that could have been lessened something the total duration of the fim, which extends some of the stories, as Evelin (an impeccable Lorraine Vindel) despite the predictability of its resolution. Small stick to an exemplary script. That Yes, there in the proceedings, cannot have any downside. Blanca Portillo won the award at the San Sebastian Film Festival for best female performance but could have also gained Maribel Verdú and it had not been an injustice. The two are incredible and the fight by Goya will be really tough this year. The rest of side is equally superb. Of so, in this film, the child, Victor Valdivia one of the promises of Spanish film, acts well. For highlighting someone and take it as a disregard to others, I would like to mention an Enrique Villén it takes several years stealing scenes to his co-stars. Part of the credit must be attributed to the Director who knows how to plan each scene to make the most of the talent of the actors. His calm and almost transparent staging is a demonstration of confidence in the players and a gift for the Viewer. Little more I can add. We have a good example of how, without large budgets, film the good in Spain can be done. Final assessment in moonfleet: 7.5 out of 10</body>
</review>
