<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Las 13 Rosas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Brings together the compendium of vices and misery that have become our homeland cinematography best repellent for the Viewer: Manichean, boring, poor and is incredibly poorly written, performed worse and worse directed.</summary>
	<body>Dear Bomarzo: Do you know when finished to note that "The thirteen roses" is bad guts?Then at the end, when the platoon fired on the girls, and relieved, I thought for my himself that goodness, that it was time that was hungry and, finally, a rich ham and melted cheese sandwich could eat me. It's like the of the "Jeanne d'Arc" of Luc Besson, when they finally beat him fire the Jovovich, I applauded to break my hands.Sorry to begin this letter with what might seem a boutade without grace or, even worse, a lack of respect for the memory of those thirteen girls, vilely assassinated by the Francoist Government at the end of the Civil War. But it is not. Contempt for his report, in any case, is given by a painful and shameful film, whose viewing causes embarrassment.It goes without saying that seems special to our cinema to continue diving in important events in our history, as do the cinemas around the world. And I don't care to continue the same Civil war movies that Americans roll cyclically films about the Viet Nam or the Mundial.Pero War II, please, that the resulting product has a minimum of decorum, anything to "The thirteen roses" does not reach or to rub. We started with a start when two girls, uploaded on a stage, are trying to encourage the masses in his Republican zeal. The sequence has so much realism that seems performed by a cast of Famóbil Clicks and transmits the same emotion that a catalogue of Ikea.Y, from there, all the same. Characters that appear and disappear if we know or who they are or what painted on screen, a few design fascists resembling Armani models, a Manichaeism and a simplicity as long that you did not see on a screen. and the interrogation sequences? If Jack Bauer lifted his head.In fact, they say evil tongues that the strike of the writers in the United States.UU. It has been motivated, precisely, by having seen "The thirteen roses", demanding that the word "Script" disappears from credits that appear in its place, the legend "Pamphlet", "Cobblers" or "Sinvergonzonería".Is that I'm writing, I'm Recalling moments of the film, and I am turning even more that while he saw. The sequence in jail, splashing water to the severe prison officer. The mother running after the truck.Finally, dear Bomarzo, the road to hell is paved with good intentions, that the tragic history of thirteen Red Roses worth be told, but that this monstrosity perpetrated by Emilio Martínez Lázaro, disservice makes to his memory, and even more skinny to the recovery of historical memory dignified and respectful. And, as film, of course, is a new torpedazo in the flotation of Spanish film line, "Las 13 rosas" brings together the compendium of vices and misery that have turned to our cinematography patria in the best repellent for the Viewer: Manichean, boring, poor and is incredibly poorly written, performed worse and worse directed. "Las 13 rosas"as well as being a fraud and a fiasco, a disappointment, a scam and a penalty is, in a Word, a pigswill.Dear Bomarzo: are what we talking?With all love, OTF-outraged Patón.</body>
</review>
