<review author="Andrés Pons" title="El anticristo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Horrifically evil moments filmed with an aura of nightmare that could be felt at every level, totally credible interpretations above all of the dazzling star accompanied by a spectral soundtrack gave him a pesadillesco aspect today not leave indifferent.</summary>
	<body>Alberto de MARTINO is another of the great Italian directors of the time that exploited piece any success of the moment or fashion with lower budgets.Author among others of Holocaust 2000, puma man &hellip; &hellip; &hellip; &hellip; &hellip; etc. Amply demonstrated the talent of a good worker of the genre which confers always entertainment pleasant despite modest budgets and little original scripts or literally copied.Other names are in all good exploitation, screenwriter VINCENZO MANNINO was a collaborator of RUGGERO DEODATO in work not too familiar "The conquerors of Atlantis or gang of future".On the picture one of the key names of the time provided their services, JOE D´ AMATO author among many of GOMIA. Terror in the Aegean Sea.Among the cast include ARTHUR KENNEDY that same year acted in the Spanish, not desecrate the dead dream, great MEL FERRER who with his career playing end could not stop participate in series b, death trap, the attack of the Atomic including ZOMBIES. The protagonist CARLA GRAVINA had enormous prestige films in his filmography. RUFUFU, first love, showed his great acting.With all these names under the good the Director you can enjoy a dignísima sample of visceral horror. A really terrifying principle with great atmosphere in all its scenes contributed you a really chilling dramatic density.Horrifically evil moments filmed with an aura of nightmare that could be felt at every level, totally credible interpretations above all of the dazzling star accompanied by a spectral soundtrack gave him a pesadillesco aspect today not leave indifferent.Little budget left to notice a makeup and Visual effects something poor though not claw him removed at any time.</body>
</review>
