<review author="José A. Peig" title="La invasión de los Ultracuerpos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The best trump card of the film is a remarkable work of mounting and the use of the set to create an unsettling atmosphere from beginning to end.</summary>
	<body>The invasion of the body snatchers, signed by Don Siegel (1956), was already a remarkable tale of terror with sociological implications, inspired at any given time of the period of the cold war and the collective neurosis provoked by Senator McCharty. That film was playing with an idea that affects a fear so universal and deep as the fear to lose the soul (or discover that our close beings, are suddenly no longer be themselves), or - using a language free of religious connotations - of losing the humanity. This resolved with few economic resources but great talent in using black and white to emphasize the feeling of paranoia through the play of light and shadows, a great script that could deploy the costumbrista description, through film noir to the reality of the nightmare that leads progressively. The invasion of the ultracuerpos (Philip Kaufman, 1978) is the perfect example of a remake as never unnecessary provided that the potential of a story be given to revisitaciones that allow us to glimpse new nuances to the pace of the times, so accelerated as the colonization of bodies and minds exposed on screen. In this case, Kaufman produces a much more current and generic, allegory for the invasion of the said title and narrated nightmare can be a warning of what today's society might be if the homogenization of styles of life, the loss of values and interfere in a network of relationships, purely productive, impersonal and subject to the clock of the social machinerythey continue gaining momentum. Expressed as well it sounds bombastic, but the truth is that we are talking about an allegory on slavery and unconsciousness in today's society, and the paranoia of humans known victim of itself.Perhaps the prologue, in which we see the extraterrestrial origin of the drama-causing biological organism, it is too explicit and drowns the possibility of speech WINS ambiguity on its route between the approach of a collective neurosis and the on-site Royal of beings from another world. Therefore an unnecessary preface, but the description of how a plant cell group land on Earth and begin to develop on the leaves of trees due to contact with water is filmed with the appropriate Cadence and fixation in detail, predicts subsequent anxiety when the protagonist of the film makes his first appearance to boot an outbreak of the flower coming out of this world while the Kaufman Chamber draws zigzags to recreate the vision of the character (Robert Duvall) that rocks on a swing with some children. Someone monitors. The best trump card of the film is a remarkable work of mounting and the use of the set to create an unsettling atmosphere from beginning to end. The streets and the looks from a background which hint at the control, the violence isolated as an omen of the moral decline. An important detail is the presence of characters acting as automata already from the start, reflection of a society which begins to decline without that hardly anyone is aware of this. We enter a world dominated by the clock and threatened by pollution and the carelessness. Our protagonist (Donald Sutherland), a rude health inspector, shit of rat in the stew of a restaurant, and berates the person responsible to then find a bottle of glass on the windshield of the car. Dehumanization begins at the level of known social order for later manifested into a nightmare of science fiction.Human culture is based largely on our capacity to feel, moved, the sensitive perception of the world and its phenomena introduces us into a spiral of painful contradictions. If we eliminate the sensitivity, we remove our vulnerability. The only goal is to survive and kill all those who resist being mere automata. The visualization of Kaufman builds the crushing loneliness of two people harassed by the new order dehumanizing; the map sequence shows the legs of the two main characters walking down the street to meet other legs moving in the opposite direction, until they notice the identity of two "outsiders". Then again on his steps to begin the ruthless persecution. The social majority conspires inspired by hatred of the different. The same gestural language of ultra bodies focuses on this very effectively: arm extended forward and the finger pointing to the "stranger" at the time that uttering a cry of animality. Dehumanization deep what we can get.Note also the varied assortment of characters, which contributes to a narrative that becomes quite fun despite being a much more pervasive - and dense - allegory than it seems at first view. Special mention to the charisma of Donald Sutherland, the always justified overacting by an actress as Veronica Cartwright and the eccentric pose of Jeff Goldblum. If we put Mr. Spock - Leonard Nimoy can be an insane cocktail, but the case is that it works, and the characterization of the central human block that will fight against the invaders is an essential quality in this film. Concluding, the truth is that it is a great story that can get a lot out: as a horror film, as science fiction film, as sociological reflection (disturbing aspects of human relationships, lost confidence in the human being, the globalization and the end of diversity, towards a society of automatons, etc). However, if we look at the possibilities of its content, nor the version of Siegel and that Kaufman's exploit its full potential. Therefore, being two exemplary works in his field, the invasion of the body snatchers still waiting a master hand that raise to the deserved State of perfection.</body>
</review>
