<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Which manage to overcome his audancia in the Assembly will forgive those excesses and enjoy a very meticulous film with a flawless picture and a couple of ideas thrown in the air that work decently.</summary>
	<body>I hate when movies make me "trap" and when the montages are planned so that you see only what the director wants to give you the remaining data is one of the dirtiest things you can do in the film. That is why when you start Atonement feel that I'm going to raise the Chair with a terrible discomfort. Especially in the beginning with these continuous flashbacks, something repetitive and only seemingly dispensable managed create uneasiness that I hardly recovered in the second part of the film.I said very carefully second part as it is structured in three different temporary spaces and follows the three protagonists along his "scapegoat" journey: Briony a antojadiza and talented girl of high rank, his older sister Cecilia and her lover Robbie Turner (son of the housekeeper of keys). The story begins on the hottest day of 1935, the war I said start and the busy atmosphere, a small meeting in an impressive Palace of field serves to introduce the protagonists of this story from the outset seems dramatic and that knowing the author of the book, the British Ian McEwan, specialist in romantic fiction leaves many doubts about the content of the remaining footage. Accused of a crime he had not committed by the sister of Cecilia lover ends in jail and by the historical circumstances in the war. But I must admit that as soon as they calmed down those frantic jumps to the past to see the story from the points of view of all stakeholders and returned the coherence classic come back to get you fully in the history where all the characters seek a rematch and will be spinning the questions left unanswered in his past. Is true that the majority of the reactions are predictable but in some ways is what is expected of a dramón of epic dimensions like this.It is perhaps the turn of the third party who has left me a little indecisive when it comes to position me to this mixture of poetic narrative and well-intentioned fiction. Anyway once exceeded viewing initial many things fit, the initial reluctance disappear and you find a épico-bélico tape - pretty interesting romantic. I admit that the second time you see him you take much better the gracia.¿Es a great movie? I don't think so, it is rather accurate. If you need forty minutes to decide to accommodate you enjoy in the armchair is something goes wrong. Precisely this boldness to which I refer is so confusing that many do not give the opportunity to own film explained to likewise. In all case which if succeed in overcoming this barrier can forgive these excesses and enjoy a very meticulous film with a flawless picture and a couple of ideas thrown in the air that work decently.</body>
</review>
