<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="La Dolce Vita" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>La Dolce Vita is therefore a kind of?Don Quixote? everyone has it on a shelf and has heard of him but if get it in the fight with the windmills you discover that no one has read it actually. It doesn't disappoint.</summary>
	<body>Recently in a dinner with friends were talking about classic films and he came to light a quite disturbing theme for any film buff. Have anyone had seen La Dolce Vita.¿Esa film of Marcello Mastrolliani that bathe in the Fontana?It is the maximum amount of information that I could get out of my fellow sufferers. La Dolce Vita is therefore a kind of "Don Quixote" everyone has it on a shelf and has heard of him, but if get it in the fight with the windmills you discover that no one has read it actually. And to follow with this literary analogy happens more or less the same, despite the fame of the scene of the fontana La Dolce Vita is not the love between the journalist who interprets Mastroianni and Anita Ekberg, is only part of the mills. Indeed it is the evolution and decline of Marcello Rubini, a multipurpose journalist accustomed to wealth and ephemeral beauty that surrounds their world and that gradually leads to its self-destruction. A dreamer who renounced their ambition to be a writer of success blinded by the melancholy excesses of the "dolce vita" Italian where you will have to face their moral principles.A total of seven stories taking place in the Italian capital fully self contained with a single point in common, his home in Via Veneto, one of the most famous and glamorous of Rome, streets that illustrate the values and attitudes of the antihero: the famous local need of admiration in his lowest moments, the international star Centre of all eyesthe miraculous apparition of the Virgin that generates a catastrophic dimensions media circus, a reunion with an old friend in a very revealing dinner, the visit of his father, a party in a castle that starts the journey to the absolute decline and after a fateful event which I am not going to espoilear finally the man in which Marcello decides to become. I.e., like the mills appear in the first chapters of Don Quixote, Anita and their whims will disappear after half an hour of footage (La Dolce Vita lasts two hours and forty minutes). A brilliantly orchestrated and perfectly shot structure. Certainly of exceptional beauty is the relationship of Marcello with Steiner. One of these conversations that pass to the annals of cinema with an ending that will manage to excite anyone.The question on whether or not a work overrated depends on the tastes of each. It actually has no doubt is that this film represents a time in Italy in which wealthy Europe used it as a valve of escape from their problems. The glamour and the decline of an entire sector of society that found a paradise in developing (a Rome under construction which was still one of the major European cities) for power head-on at your leisure in continuous parties and without obligations, where the paparazzi were the most sought after journalists, sexual liberation reached unsuspected heights (always within the Italian machismo which still remains) and any news could be boughtsold or auctioned. All scenes travel to Roman life, its festivals, customs and nightlife, and sometimes shows a little more of what should, that earned Fellini a reputation of offender and the film a river of ink on their excesses.There have been two great myths in European cinema that will survive all time: Alain Delon and Marcello Mastroianni. La Dolce Vita helped create and maintain the myth of Latin Gigolo deservedly. Until that point the role of the film and real life crisscrossed is only a mystery over the film of Fellini.Cierto is that after The Rocky Horror Picture Show and Blade Runner only La Dolce Vita deserves the title of "eternal decommissioned" and is difficult to find in stores (although recently a pretty decent DVD edition was released) if join you for the terrible duration is not exactly easy to program in television)(never remember seeing in a grid) and for his subject was very censored at the time by sexual liberalism and the image "cheerful" of the Italian middle class that made her unpopular in Italy since its premiere only the passage of time and the international reception have saved La Dolce Vita from oblivion, or by what I have seen of the iconographic oblivionthe next step is to cheer up and see it. It doesn't disappoint. FOR the MITÓMANOS: The scene of the Fontana is one of the most reproduced worldwide. Little they know really that this scene represents freedom. Sylvie, an antojadiza American actress gets to bathe, and encourages his partner at night to mess with her. Marcello ceases to see things and posprimera time in the film acts accepting the invitation. The bathroom actually means for those who have seen the film the first step for the freedom of his characters, the first decisions that will shape their future. It was so cold the night of March in that shot that Mastroianni had to get swimsuit underneath the dress and drink a bottle of Vodka, his co-star spent hours under the jets of water without complaining.The Roman Government grew tired of people emulase this scene and the Fontana is monitored 24 hours a day, become Marcello now costs a fine of 400 &euro; for adventurous moviegoers who still dare.DATA of the film: La Dolce Vita won the Palme d'Or at the Cannes International Film Festival in 1960 also won two Academy Award in 1961 for best foreign language film and best costume design (designed by Art Director Piero Gherardi). The film was banned in Spain by censorship, as the newspaper of the Vatican, L'Osservatore Romano, described her as obscene. Not premiered in Spain until 1980. Never had much success in his home country, has been the time which has become a classic of Italian cinema.</body>
</review>
