<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Shaolin Soccer" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Eastern film about shaolines who play football. To see her surrounded by chums, with beers and other narcotic. An ideal remedy to combat any depression. Great, without paleativos.</summary>
	<body>Director: Stephen ChowDuración: then I tell you what lasts.Release date: 3 June 2005 (according to the IMDB).Spectators: According to me, he has not released in commercial cinemas.See details in the IMDB is the closest thing to the Bernarda pussy. You are on the one hand, that duration goes between the two horazas and the hour and a half, depending on where you've seen her. The release date is Spain of truth that I I do not think, because I am convinced that in cinemas not it premiered. Moreover, in DVD not her have edited in Spain, which tells me that her have not translated into the Spanish (in English if it is). Rebatanmé, if you have what to have.The film is about a former player of Chinese football, after an incident, falling in disgrace. Over the years, discover a kid with a formidable force in the leg, so dare to do a shaolines with capacity football team to defeat the team of evil (Evil) clear dominated the Championship.The first time I saw this film (which was longer than the second, I am sure) was in Korean with English subtitles. Crazy. And I thought dying of laughter. I have now seen in Latin American Spanish her again and I almost small laughter. Let me explain. Get the number of "Champions", Oliver and Benji with a field that length that was the esferidad of the Earth. Not bad. Hire people, cut the fields so that they can arrive in less than 3 episodes, olvidensé of talks means Party on the honour and friendship, leave the catapult the brothers Derrick, the pepinazo brutal in the eye of the ass of Benji, stop relying on the post of Oliver, infernal inventesen some shots more than these and will result in Shaolin Soccera more original and funny films I've seen in life.In short, Eastern film about shaolines who play football. To see her surrounded by chums, with beers and other narcotic. An ideal remedy to combat any depression. Great, without paleativos. Great surrealist.Besitos.P.D: The team of bigotudas women. The captain of the team that dropped a wrench before starting the game. The slippers that plays. The shaolin t-shirt. The talks. Dancing in the middle of the street to tell anything. Coups and other absurdeces. For framing it.Pd2: And that nobody would encourage to bring it to you in Spain.P.D.3: Has the rarest special effects that have been made. Mixture of cutrez and genius. Impresionantes.P.D.4: And in the end it isn't more than a drama.</body>
</review>
