<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Resident Evil Extincion" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Third installment where everything is gone to shit and the few remaining instead of suicide, wander aimlessly fixed. As you know that you can find, therefore not was disappointed, but hate to sacrifice innecesareamente the script.</summary>
	<body>Do you have an invasion of human flesh eaters zombies in the door of his house? Nothing, nothing, do not be alarmed, you close the little door of the gate and already they do not fall. Who do not I believe? Then watch this film of Milla Jovovich and will see as despite being dead, they are extremely educaditos. Incidentally, the mile has less hairs on salva is the party that the barby in her pussy himself. Or at least their clones.The film is a future in which a lethal virus has wiped out life on the planet. The Poles have become cubes, deserted forests, and human beings are zombies that have only desire in life as nibble the faucets to the few humans remaining. On the one hand, the hordes of zombies do not know very well what they want (very funny en who have stayed in their jobs and homes). On the other hand, the Corporation that has mounted this, trying to fix it in their own way. And the good we have a caravan of survivors and the Milla Jovovich has more danger that a sack escorpiones.¿Que what seems to me the movie? So that from the moment the zombies do not cross the gates I realized that this is nothing more than an homage to films as zombies Party or even the great Hitchcock birds. By that does not tell me anyone that the zombies do not give laughter (it coming out at the end somewhat less). The argument is what you can expect from a film, but am very sorry for not to strive a little the writers. Do not they electrificaron the fence of Jurassic Park that did not escape the bugs? Because so, at least. Is that have special effects, and a visual display that is the cane, but the viewer that carried the film, the brain or is leave it close (in the car for example) because he realizes that he does not hold.In short, third installment of the saga Resident Evil, where everything is gone to hell and the few remaining instead of suicide, wander aimlessly fixed. As you know that you can find, therefore not was disappointed, but hate to sacrifice innecesareamente the script.The Milla Jovovich this has a remeneo, I think if you clones it, with one you stay for the nights of cold and zombies beyond the gate, right?Besitos.P.D: those who were thinking that there would not be a quarter, I can assure you that there will be. These are crosses.Pd2: Evil has a moment towards the end very large, but much much.P.D.3: Hosts, which I forgot. The central computer of the Beehive has human form to interact with men. Because it is pinned to a neighbor of mine who plays the piano. That am.</body>
</review>
