<review author="Yul B." title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Authentic adventure film that, although it slightly resembles the first installment and weakens in its infancy, will leave you wanting more. The third part of the saga is expected to be presented.</summary>
	<body>I am sure that more than one crucificará me by what I say below, though I hope a bit of indulgence.Going beyond: the film has seemed very good, but I only liked his second hour and quarter. The first 75 minutes found me very weak for the expected (and desired). For this reason I will divide my criticism in two very different parts, as it is the hour (and fourth) valued.Before that it was appropriate to recall what the argument of "Pirates of the Caribbean: the chest of the dead man": the Hunter pirates Lord Cutler Beckett (Tom Hollander) of the East India Trading Company, and Captain Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp) are obsessed about the so-called dead man chest. According to legend, who possesses this chest can control terrifying pirate Davy Jones (Bill Nighy), the master of the depths of the sea. This precious object, Beckett intends to exterminate until the last pirate of the Caribbean and dominate the port trade, with Sparrow tries to get rid of the debt that has slope with Jones to avoid doomed until eternity to a life in his service. Both used to Will Turner (Orlando Bloom) and Elizabeth Swann (Keira Knightley) to achieve his goal. But to reach the chest it is necessary to overcome numerous dangers that none ever would have imagined.The story about the role is promising; However, once implemented, it sank by the bow, and insulting and spectacular floats by the stern. The first hour and a quarter.The (inevitable) need to chain the first installment of the franchise with the second, and the excessive length which has been used for this, has seriously harmed this part of the tape, which the continuity between both films seem forced.In the majority of the aftermath, it is vital to remind the viewer how and what are the characters of the original tape to place them on the new plot. Sometimes, the temporal difference between the release of the original film and its sequel or sequels is minimal (one-year or maximum year and a half), with which the Viewer remembers perfectly to those characters, and therefore the footage you need to use to place them on the new adventure is reduced.However, in this case, has been roughly 3 years between: the curse of the Black Pearl and the chest of the dead man; so, it was inevitable to refresh the memory to the public about the previous adventures of Jack Sparrow, Will Turner and Elizabeth Swann. Unless one has spent the DVD of the first installment of both see it, or one of those fans that has embraced the Caribbean pirates Marathon organized by several cinemas in the country (project two films consecutively).But did not require that memory be extended both. During the first sixty minutes they are remembered and cited events in the first film in a way too spaced. Once reached the 75 initial minutes, approximately, it is when really begins the new adventure.On the other hand, there are too many preliminary. I guess that it is that in this second installment is already have three devoted Hollywood stars, namely Johnny Depp, Orlando Bloom and Keira Knightley, while the first only was Depp. Therefore, the producers of the film and its director Gore Verbinski have been forced to to more pitch them all, so their corresponding fans can enjoy more each of them.For all that I have explained above, this part of the tape becomes eternal, and one becomes impatient waiting to see when the action begins.The second hour and a quarter.Here is where the tomato starts. Spectacular, disturbing, with pace and many surprises I can not reveal.This is what I wanted to see I (and surely more than one of you) during the footage.In this part of the film been tapped absolutely everything that could give this new adventure. And, on top, has been reserved for this time the best, and most impressive and amazing movie: the KRAKEN, a giant octopus that sweeps any ship in which Jack Sparrow is found (or anything of his clothing).I have been fascinated this second hour and a quarter. He didn't want to end. And above, has a piece of end, who you going to fall back. Surprise perfect to link to the third (and final?) installment of the Pirates of the Caribbean, and that leaves you wanting more, and more, and still more.By this second time I put the film a rating of "very good".And by the interpretations of all actors throughout the film. You can not forget any of the main: Johnny Depp is the genuine and authentic Jack Sparrow. I do not see any other actor to moving ahead with this role with both success and genius. Although we already know very well the character, and this causes you to lose the magic of his discovery, Depp continues on the same line of interpretation that has enshrined as one of the most relevant, eccentric and influential Hollywood actors. Without him this film would be quite another.Orlando Bloom goes one step further in his career to consider him as an outstanding interpreter. The role of Will Turner has expanded and has allowed to deploy their various interpretative facets (which from what I've seen are quite a few and surprisingly varied). Mix the moments of drama and comedy with great skill, and that has favoured to be recognized as the great movie Heartthrob, beating the classics.Keira Knightley is attractive, sensual and the time, very warlike. Her role as Elizabeth Swann has also expanded and increased number of scenes have been given for herself; so he has been able to take advantage of them, and he has shown his talent of actress with grace and passion.But is that the rest of the cast is equally superb: Bill Nighy as the terrifying Davy Jones, even though his face is full of tentacles; Tom Hollander as Lord Cutler Beckett ruthless; and, as no, Kevin McNally, in its magnificent line as the Gibbs inseparable companion of Sparrow, and the crazy couple of pirates formed by Lee Arenberg (Pintel) and Mackenzie Crook (Ragetti), now more witty and wacky. And some others that I intentionally left unnamed to not reveal surprises.In short, a genuine adventure film that, although it slightly resembles the first installment and weakens in its infancy, will leave you wanting more. The third part of the saga is expected to be presented.</body>
</review>
