<review author="Jack Torrance" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Worse of all the experiment it is passed its ecuador begins to immerse in a tedious dynamic and with little dash, sosa and leadership without passion that make what could have been a good slasher is deadly dull.</summary>
	<body>The work of John Carpenter being revised by the machinery of hollywood with poor, lazy, mediocre film results. The hope of seeing a personal version of Rob Zombie, that is probably the most influential film of the American master created expectations of witnessing the less curious insights into the myth of Michael Myers. The results are not alarmingly catastrophic, but by no means novel or some interest. They are simply mediocre.Raised as an exploration of evil seen through the origin of psychopathy in a way authentic, Zombie devotes a good portion of the film to explain the children of Michael Myers. The deconstruction of what in the movie by Carpenter worked well in a covert manner isn't as annoying as they could expect the purists of the foundational work of the modern slasher and against all odds, turns into the most interesting part of the final product. The first minutes, who calmly we see who is Michael Myers and observe as the disease of pure evil you has to stop being the same, still evokes in the viewer a fascination and fear by the psychopath, although this time penetrated more psychological and scientific in what was once an almost mystical evocation. This new and fresh vision of the origin ends when Michael escapes and the film ceases to be focused from a standpoint closest to him and the plot turns towards his sister Laurie Strode(un_gimmick_no_presente_en_la_original_Halloween,_surgida_en_la_primera_secuela_deel_film).At that time, the film becomes a proper remake of the original, which could well happen for one sequel. All the Halloween night of the original is told here in a similar way, perhaps with a small plot change here and there. The deaths of the original reproduces plane by plane and the same moments before creating tension, here do not generate any printing. A second part which seeks to operate differently from the original thanks to the development of a first act - prequel that leaves their interesting lines of development in pursuit of play the legendary first movie in a ultramimética way. The worst thing is that the particular style of the director barely makes an appearance in the second half and, except a little more violence and unhealthy sex, not are perceived many resources used, except this time an excessive use of close-ups.Worse of all the experiment it is passed its ecuador begins to immerse in a tedious dynamic and with little dash, sosa and leadership without passion that make what could have been a good slasher is deadly dull. The tension or the horror are replaced by constant sound blows, in the style of production of low estofa horror. A penalty see as a director of undoubted creativity not risks and is limited to trying to address a conventional Slasher. At least, Zombie if he shows his love for the original material and its usual cinephiles makes an appearance. There are many and varied winks to the saga and respect for original material. Rob Zombie Halloween is in part an interesting look to the classic JohnCarpenter but am disappointed as the work of the more capable director of the Devil's rejects. Unfortunately, it won't be to the list of Remakes that equate to the original work as dawn of the dead or that exceed it, as the hills have eyes. Not even come within them are not bad as the Texas Chainsaw Massacre. Halloween is an unnecessary Remake, which could have been better if the same idea of script had been treated by someone more capable, the big problem that drag Rob Zombie is that he can't write.</body>
</review>
