<review author="Ram칩n Besonias" title="Adi칩s peque침a, adi칩s" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Goodbye small, goodbye is a film that uncomfortable, and only that upset feeling worth be Preparatoria. The weight of integrity.</summary>
	<body>Goodbye small, goodbye is a film that uncomfortable, and only that upset feeling worth be Preparatoria. Who go to the movies without knowing beyond that is a wise production of Ben Affleck (which some could be a handicap to not see), well played by his younger brother, Casey Affleck, and with a careful staging, will be surprised by the evolution of a script that slides from the police thriller of pace slowly but agile to a moral drama in which the viewer must participate likes it or not.And it is in this soft but final turn of the script where it resides much of the virtue of this opera prima of an actor (i.e. a, because I know) has decided wisely to prove excellence as a filmmaker and has no bad been the result. And it has done so in the hands of his brother, Casey Affleck, an actor convincing, natural, leisurely look, fleeing with wisdom of the easy pantomime of the histrionics of laminated paper in which his brother is master. What not just function in this work so sober and reflective is the role of comparsa of Angie (Michelle Monagha), the wife and partner of the protagonist. Does not have any function or narrative depth throughout the film, except at the end, where it is used by the writer as a moral counterpoint to the dilemma of the detective Kenzie.No is new in the crime genre the suggestive idea of placing a detective private in a moral position after deshilvanar the Hank of misery that surround the case investigating. But this time this detective isn't drinker, nor has a murky past, it knows all or smoke, and is not even alone or under the spell of a femme fatale, as it is normally the case in a genre too marked by the genetics of classic noir. Kenzie is young, seems it or does not give the feeling of being a guy hard or clever. So far it has devoted to cases of lost objects. The case is large, or seems it. You will have the advantage of knowing the neighborhood, his logic, his confidants, their miseries. And it is a full, professional, honest man.That integrity (synonym of civilization, rights, legal protection, etc.) will be precisely which will be questioned, forcing the Viewer to readjust his map, good and evil, justice and injustice. The director may recuelga in excess in a seasoned Catholic imagery of these unnecessary monologues of the protagonist may occasionally, but they serve to position the viewer in a family model which will be questioned later in the form of moral dilemma. Not in vain Gone baby gone is a work of the writer (Dennis Lehane) that we also acongojara with the forceful Mistic River. In both works dealt with issues of difficult host popular, such as paedophilia or abuse and murder of children. Some have seen as an opportunistic Act by the director recreate a story that reminds us too the disappearance in the girl Madeleine Portugal. Debate a pilgrim both, given the tone that is taking the script over the tape.But despite the sobriety in the staging and the agile glibly of the script, Gone baby gone is a work that would have perhaps required a greater distance on what counts. Taking as a reference point to Mistic river, the work of Affleck becomes too predictable in its moral claims. It is played without more letters that the presentation of the final dilemma, and his characters not boiled with bed rest as for the Viewer to appreciate its contradictory folds. This psychological finesse is evident in the work of Eastwood and dignifies the set by his manifest humanity. Even in Million dollar baby - equally divided by a script that plays to be another gender - are profiled the characters without monocromatismos, fleeing to be defined and forcing the Viewer to get lost in the murky but necessary tide of emotions.However, this not worthy a worthy attempt in the hands of a novel that has woven a plot suggestive, but without the nuances that requires any work aspiring to excellence. Ben, you expect in your second. But please, stop the actor.</body>
</review>
