<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Fresas Salvajes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bergman: the image that speaks to us.</summary>
	<body>Bergman is among our most recent Classics (already in posthumously), but he himself baby with avidity of those other not so recent classics, from the Greek Theatre and to weave the vital volume of a plot, they invoked rather than the power of the physis (the pure image) stripped of logos - theatrical resource preteatral and Dionysian roots - but this internal dialogue that every human being kept with you until death shut you your mouth.Bergman that same death silent us and in turn makes us speak (by way of indignant lament), as Miguel de Unamuno would say that another tragic called. Greek tragedy invented the inner voice, the conscience, the flow of our live through the mediation of the language. And this metaphysical attempt is itself an unsuccessful attempt to revive us without the pain that we feel to be fatal and drowned anger who knows that death always wins (and not only to chess, all the games), despite the eternal attempt of the hero - Greek or modern - for cheating through the language, through in the end of art, of beauty.Art, more specifically his seventh son (film), has sought anesthetized with beauty this human determination, thereby invoking a contingent disguised as eternity. Blockbusters naively ironically with the possibility of serving childish drug the viewer adormilado by the modern dream of Peter Pan. With the film never we will die, at least during the footage of the film. Movie, popcorn and Coca-Cola will serve as a factory of ephemeral illusions that entronizan the pure image as opiate the masses satisfied Western Idol. Bergman lived in the Antipodes of the post-modern cult of the film image. For him it was almost an ethical demand desmitologizar the human being facing him dry with its determinations. "Know yourself", reads the Oracle. This invokes, as did the Greek dramatists, the logos, the honest word that comes from us not to communicate with each other, but to be saved by them. In the film these others are evoked through immemorial ghosts or limit situations that arouse images blurred, forgotten to delude ourselves or does not suffer.Read Sartre that the human being is an illusion impossible, and can do anything by ceasing to be so. Without this attribute essential and existential art, and with him the film would not be possible. All art - of Bergman's almost pornographic, explicit way - is metaphysics, rebellion against the contingency of bodies, who know that even living, each breath they know that they are already dead. According to Bergman film is a tragic fight against ourselves (lost), an expression of discomfort that sits in our minds since we are born.Woody Allen would sign this thesis, although with a more hilarious and hedonistic metaphor. Why cinema should uncomfortable reality, resist it, and only to support it as a substrate of memory, that memory personal, biographical, which keeps us alive, with a mission. The past, not as footprint of what is no longer but was, but as ruin our imagination reconstructs as you can, is the material which uses Bergman to cheat death, or deceive himself (to be fair). Without this aesthetic (and ethics, but without morals or cassocks) mission to deconstruct our last, life would be bleak, a valley of tears.Here's a scene that has no waste. Woody Allen has signed similar scenes career, but never with the torn tone of his master. In the hands of Allen narration would have diluted under a tone of humor somewhat comforting. Postmodern redemptions do not fit under the gaze of Bergman. We are forced to watch us face to face. That is why perhaps the work more bergmaniana Allen if anything is another woman.</body>
</review>
