<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Here must be the shots of the new cinema of commitment made in USA, artifacts of proven narrative coherence, fantastically interpreted, but marred by a retranca ideològica of, at times, difìcil digestion</summary>
	<body>Lions for Lambs is colossal lies and reprehensible moral principles. The consistency of its message lies not in the independence of its ideology but exhibition coherence of his footage and the brilliance of its cast. The admirable sense of the opportunity not blurs the suitability of history and does not seem that you have specified, as dictates of history writing, wait some years to write it with the appropriate, should distance from selfishness, less overload the revanchist download or the mere political pamphlet. The Manager of the lujuriosamente political film is Robert Redford, Robert Redford less expressive that yesteryear - surgeries and creams have the fault - but more loaded than ever of reasons to put in check the orthodoxy and patriotism of the lambs, in very wise sentence, which sent the Lions to defend with their lives the wars that invent behind a table of Wyoming oakwith a framed cover of Time magazine on the edge and a red phone that communicates the hell with voters in line 1. The film does not work miracles, but invoice - on occasions - products that accommodate noble materials that allow reflection. The liberal Robert Redford, symbol of the yankee industry and, at the time, bastion of the indie didacticism and exemplary heterodoxy always present in the culture of bars and stars opens here an ambiguous speech, very enjoy narrated and sobrado of pedagogy. The problem is that you abused an impostado, murky humanism in his teaching and narcotizante if one attends the theatrical proposed without the sufficient acquis geopolitical, to put it in some way. Case that this film did not exist there would be to invent her. Perhaps encouraging discussions lit at the door of the cinema or catch fire pazguatos easy impressionability temperaments. For their benefit, we are witnessing a fascinating job of acting and a wonderful montage. When we went to think what they have told us starts rough landing on the slippery surface of the foreign policy made in uses, and hence - reluctantly, with some uncomfortable feeling of rally to exit poll - the Lambs and the Lions become skilled soldiers of propaganda. Da like Mr Redford has said that the film makes no answers but open questions or would have never put their enthusiasm and talent - who hesitate them - cover a lukewarm show by way of soflama that shocked the public updated on colonialismos and imperialist symphonies and that, on the contrary, extremely pleasing to the audience engrossed by the Eaglebars, stars and music of the lion of the Metro. Gives equal to let us give to the good of Robert the possibility of Stoke us up pastillistas colors: because there are many and some (inevitably) produce chromatic daydreams of 1,080 horizontal lines, i.e., high definition to batteries. It comes to happen around here anyone has views of foreign policy uses and instead calla with room price when you are required to public demonstration on the domestic politics of his own poultry. The high concepts that levelled the characters of shaft of the film - illuminated Senator, scorched journalist, humanist tutor, the brilliant student, aware soldiers - only cover a sector of the palette of ideas. Commitment, freedom of expression, the allegiance to ideals or the defense of traditional values - usually orchestrated by cabinets of marketing or business beyond polls and counting - sound a lot in dialogues: there are moments that would like one a tiny break, attend the ambigú - lie: already there - and return to the armchair having chopped the grumo historical and convinced that we have resources to tacklecleared, the inventory of magical formulas and phrases of ideological Cookbook that still fly over the Capitol and Arlington National Cemetery. When does an Oscars ceremony was reckless and almost suicidal to register the Iraq war - the so-called axis of evil, the Viet Nam of the 21st century, all contributing Democrats bore and pride in Republican coffers - now is to show the world the American disappointment, war wounds and the reasons for the invasion is fashion. Producers always sweep for House and, in fact, says Redford guardian to his he/she and promising pupil, everything ends in a masterful exercise in buying and selling. Like the master sells students, politicians sell smoke, illusion, sell prestidigitadores of Blues semantics and candies with viagra. In these times the consciences rumble with less cultivated languages. Suffice it to recruit the mindless shift, well stocked of patriotism, suitably indoctrinated. Redford evidence that censor here: that the war is a Hollywood script than the richest country in the world has taken the global gendarmerie and does not consent to any tribe to dismantle the belief of its citizens to be living in the corner more secure on the planet, in the most opulent in the better equipped to meet the challenges of the future.The constraints that govern the film fate of the tape should be elaborately analyzed: of what he speaks Redford is the background noise of mass manipulation usually exercising the chieftains of the administration of the public to continue in Office and create in his sentimental shareholding - policy is sometimes a feeling - the illusion that they truly do something useful and deserve our respect and our consideration. Or perhaps this rather than brave tape - like it or not - get returns in the United States, motherland that always ends up breastfeed-, but not in Europe because here we are already quite contaminated superhero action and imperialist catechisms and scale that suddenly, to galore, the directors of renown (Haggis, De Palma, the own Redford) have open field to manuscribir - with neat handwriting and careful syntax - the disasters of war and blindness of those who enact them. And over little delivered actors to express their political sympathies (Cruise) look at this project not only with a dramatic desparpajo immeasurable but transparent text lines and risk.</body>
</review>
