<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Cuando llama un extraño" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A cock in a props high-tech: I swear that had ever gathered in one same sentence terms as found.</summary>
	<body>Strictly speaking, when a stranger calls is not a bad film. It isn't to contain meritorious Visual findings that elevate it above the mediocre products invoiced under entirely commercial premises, barely interested in the genus dignify and subjected to financial torment of the box office and promoting teenage grey massless, although cram in gadgets, hastío and (perhaps) I desconsuelo intellectual, but that is already harvesting of this chronicler. Its more than simple plot premise stretches unbearably until a climax that seems agonizing, but it (looked without enthusiasm) naïve, predictable and up exemplary.In a less strict sense, when a stranger calls is a vacuum, endless film soporíferamente vacuum, and that (oh thank you) lasts less than an hour and a half, an exercise of terror very modern with psycho-killer bolted for the Candida beauty of a baby-sistter task, installed in a House of sublime luxury, a kind of Gothic mansion designed by architect high - tech. I do not know if I explain: psycho-killer, baby-sitter, high-tech. This is one of those movies in which the semantics of their contents, the linguistic signifier of the friend Saussure, dictates the props and executes the plot.The narrative corpus is minimalist: harassment and demolition of the morality of a girl well, posh of balance, dazzled by the undeniable level of sophistication of the House of their heads, which is an absolute architecture without morality prodigy, as they said OME in the eighties, jubilant, almost solves the trance to decide whether we had a fun time or have taken us from the hair. I I am by oblivion. Some coloristic framing and even some sense of that lavish household items seem to come alive and arrogate to itself the power to be scary do that we can consider Simon West, the director of this felony, as a craftsman industrial, an epileptic artist - at the exact rate of time-, nervous writing and ease appalling to hook to the adolescent experiences on the edge of the squeal pandiatonic goloso. There are commercially irreproachable Con Air and Tomb Raider for vouching for the subject.The monumental Castle of cards built for the benefit of spectators of startle helpings falls as the film progresses: last half an hour, the tape is over, even if you are sixty minutes of pure filler. The pathetic, forced reprise occasionally lengthened to the twisting, could have been censored and the entire tape, converted into one of those endearing episodes of Alfred Hitchcock presents that they occupied the adolescence of other generations more honestly treated by the heavy machinery of the entertainment industry.The fear bubble bursts without noise: the psychopath is concerned, but not overwhelming. ("Would you have gone to see the children?"). It remains the consolation of seeing a pretty face (Jill Johnson) making grimaces, mohínes and facial pretenses and graceful and sensuously moving ass between intelligent appliances. Some of intelligence, we have at least on screen.</body>
</review>
