<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Dead silence" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>They may have been invalid expectations which had to fear that night with her or my bias, but this new Odyssey of James Wan seems that it gathers enough merits for a comfortable approved.</summary>
	<body>Judging by the presentation comes wrapped her second movie, Dead Silence (2007) (renamed in Spain as silence from evil), seems that the young director James Wan wanted this time take the opposite direction of the tape that made him famous, Saw (2004); on this occasion we will not find almost offal or fixation by torture, much less the bathroom left the lost frames of David Fincher. While there is one that gore later in this story, the director has chosen this time by a new recreation of the American Gothic, in which the ghost of a ventriloquist named Mary Shaw makes present to kill the young wife of the protagonist. Guided by the Doll left at the scene of the massacre, this now has to return to the village of his childhood, a place in decadence where the inhabitants even dare to revive the memory of that spectrum that triggered revenge on their families. This is the beginning of a film that I will say at once, I enjoyed at all times, in spite of the bad press it has received. They may have been invalid expectations which had to fear that night with her or my bias, but this new Odyssey of James Wan seems that it gathers enough merits for a comfortable approved.The plot will undoubtedly recall many plot part of nightmare on Elm Street (1984), and the truth is that similarities do not missing, at least with the first delivery, before that Freddy Krueger became a full of jokes comedian. That is not the only source to which its screenwriter Leigh Whannell and Wan we refer, references to the best work of Dario Argento are more than evident, including a climax in an abandoned Theatre whose images have been practically modelled Inferno (1980). The plot also follows the same structure as a more or less recent film: in the darkness (2003), of which very few have been mentioned and that however has a nearly identical story in which the main difference is the lei-motiv of the ventriloquismo. And speaking of this, please, forget to Chucky, very that a sinister doll is the center of the advertising campaign of Dead Silence, there is no any similarity. What do recognize you Wan is managed resurrect this type of film that runs away from the easy guts and is dedicated to the construction of "scenarios of fear": the ghost town, the old cemetery devoured by the forest and the huge abandoned theatre are elements that are inviting us into a world completely fictional, characteristic of those stories of terror than, until not long ago, they shunning the sociological content or the force of "impact". Who see the film will have to decide whether it can succeed or not. For me, I insist, is done quite well.Much of the negative criticism it has received this tape are due (I think) to its director, Saw was a film that sparked very mixed reactions, so the desire to crucify James Wan will have been large enough for many people. In any case, I think that on this occasion has given us a film more ambitious, very different from its predecessor in the style of terror that seeks to show, and that among some of their virtues has the go to the point: "research" of the protagonist not extends forever, and the story moves fast and so that anytime something is happeningwithout long and tedious transition sequences or romantic sub-tramas to disrupt history. At the narrative level, the greater downside I can find perhaps the character of a polyphenic Donnie Whalberg, which adds absolutely nothing apart from an inexplicable comic and thuggish tone completely out of place. Beyond that, the "villain" is very well made, and the film contains some genuinely sinister sequences, as the flashback tells the origins of Mary Shaw, as well as some of his appearances that stand out for their use of suggestive rather than the cheap scare or free brutality, something which many filmmakers nowadays seem have been forgotten, and that certainly did not expect to find in the alleged Saw.Por director who has problems; of course many of its best moments are taken from other films and of course that the script has several outputs implausible and elitists, but no more than the orphanage (2007) or 28 weeks later (2007), films that enthusiasts have earned praise from many that calling this tape soon in southern Lebanon less than garbage. I would encourage to take a look. At least I've been pleasantly surprised.</body>
</review>
