<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Resident Evil Extincion" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Need film being raised over 100 million dollars in USA. Resident Evil like "and long". 3 Movies of the saga of perhaps the most faithful to the game with that none of the 3 is an absolute parallelism.</summary>
	<body>This is not to assess a good script or is not pigeonhole this film between "good or bad", not because Resident Evil is much more than that. For all fans of the video game in which the trilogy is based, see on the big screen which will have surely been for us a good part of our adolescence (weekends full playing Resident Evil in the play) is outside all objectivity. Still I will try: Russell Mulcahy brings us this sequel which seems to be the last for the moment and that is not exactly true to the game, but some are so geeks that we are satisfied. This director who seems to be to settle in the genre as it has in preproduciión "Zen in the Art of Slaying Vampires" (not saying nothing.), gives us a breath of fresh air in the saga Resident Evil. I must confess that I do not I had liked excessively the previous ones, but this is different. In addition to being everything much more careful, photography, costume, makeup (sometimes you retouching digital in exajeradisimos makeup, there's first flat primerisimos mile seems that the face of wax, I do not know if it's intentional or not, but stay, is horrible) the arguento connects perfectly with the previous films, which they were not able to do consistentlyExtinction at least preserved the coherence not only in if same fate with his predecessors. Mile is much better directed and even seen a slight evolution in his character, calmer and to dominate the situation. We already know that it is not a great actress, but she is a good actress of action. It is still too thin for my taste and especially for the role, but they fix well poniendole an overdose of costume (poor mia so sheltered in the desert) with which it sure had to be raising chicks. In conclusion this is a kind of necessary film and the truth is that it has been collected over one hundred million dollars in USA. Resident Evil like "and long". Of the 3 movies, this is perhaps the most faithful to the game with any of the 3 is an absolute parallelism.</body>
</review>
