<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Una historia violenta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>That vision pure violence, desmaquillada, gives the film an innocence. Who would say that trying to Cronenberg and with a hyphen ex officio assassins and vendettas and grudges hyperbolic</summary>
	<body>David Cronenberg is a sick director who wallows with avatars and the vicissitudes of his illness. None of his films could have done Steven Spielberg, for example, but he would have it done, successfully, I have no doubt, the Terminal or the Empire of the Sun. It would have checked them with the humor corrosive him, hidden in the least perceptible fringes of history, solvents always. With A history of violence, Cronenberg made a film that, in principle, was not yours. He resembled more a project of Brian de Palma or Tony Scott. This alien material lacks the usual formal apparatus with which Cronenberg rummages in his obsessions and visually explicit their perversions. Has A history of violence absolutely nothing to do with the fly or Crash or came within de.o Spider... Or no longer speak of inseparable, jewel of the insane cinema, cult movie and probably the best performance I have seen very notable Filmography of Jeremy Irons, but good, not desbarremos. A history of violence is the survival of a style of life and mutilation, if not the absolute elimination of memory. Tom Stall (Viggo Mortensen, formidable, restrained and sober as always) erases its past and begins a new life. Random rescues this past and begins a crusade to regain his identity, something which, in the end, in a marvelous picture, contained, is evident. Then there is Ed Harris, a magnificent actor which still lacks an absolute chocolate so people recognize it by the street and the studies you trust newsprint flashy and not, as now, as almost always, outstanding second. What deserves separate chapter is the treatment of violence in the film. Apart from the aftertaste of the director by the lowest instincts of humans, the film obvious violence in an almost Cartesian manner, but her extracted from underground of the soul of his characters when the famous script needs so require. Like when the Hispanic uncover. "Sends it the script". And there they came and went thighs and pubic half to encabritar staff, novice in these iconic lides. Here manifests very dose violence, but strong. I read that Cronenberg wanted a natural, brutal violence of the kind you see in the street, without elaboration, descontaminada of pirouettes, choreography and all that trash symbolic of unnecessary gestures and false kicks to the Bruce Lee that populate the tape action of these days. That vision pure violence, desmaquillada, gives the film an innocence. Who would say that trying to Cronenberg and with a hyphen ex officio assassins and vendettas and grudges hyperbolic.The footage, hour and a half very little, not enfanga the purpose of the director. Strain half-hour more irrelevant material could have distracted the viewer of the primary role of the main show, i.e. the destination as a magnum of 32 encañonándo us the temple, although the years pass and not realise from the pressure of the Canyon in the skin. That happens to Tom Stall, basically. She has lived years provided and now comes memory to collect its share of screen. At the end, I will not gutting the outcome, don't worry, they earn good, as always, but we do not know who they are. Today I will not recommend to open the armarito of DVDs and pull file. If after this binge of violence, it would be good place in the tray of the player the quiet man of John Ford. And if you look, notice, that at the bottom in the same rugged and stark background of always, it's the same movie. John Ford omits inherent in all forms of violence pornography and sweetens the cliché of the man who cannot leave their past (without forgiveness by Clint Eastwood) with relaxed Irish grasslands and generous taverns that smell whiskey in malta and storm of October. In the end. We are a few romantic.</body>
</review>
