<review author="Bloody Will" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pure political pamphlet of Robert Redford on the situation of the United States currently.</summary>
	<body>Pure political pamphlet of Robert Redord on the situation of the United States currently. Thus it is 'Lions for Lambs', one of the most political films I've seen since ' All the President's men the', and who coincidentally also has the actor on his cast. Commercial career of this film has has his worst enemy in itself: that is not commercial. Actually I wasn't quite sure what he was going to see in the seventh movie as director Redford. political thriller?, does war thriller? &hellip; the truth is that with the trailers expected otherwise. Quitemosle about thriller in all its meanings. The little hour and twenty that lasts the film is more than enough to tell what the director intended: the mistakes they commit the USA with its presence in Iraq from the point of view of one of the sides this is a partisan documentary with narrators of luxury, neither more nor less.Three unique scenes are the backbone of the film: A Congressman (Cruise) that uses a journalist (Streep) to launch the new strategy military in the country in conflict. A Professor (Redford) who tries to motivate some of its best students (Andrew Garfield), and two soldiers (Michael Peña and Derek Luke) lost in the line enemy. With only these three situations, Redford is mounted a do ético-moral of hangovers with an underscore so lengthy and cumbersome as his criticism of Bush.El problem of having things from a point of view is only in the end not is if it has is a pretentious or have every reason in the world. From the distance of not having controlled the political systems in the USA all sounds to me Chinese, which should be comparable to project in American theaters 'Las 13 Rosas', 'Libertarian', 'Wolf' or 'GAL', but with the subtle difference that in these last at least has a plot. 'Lions for Lambs' ends with an inevitable: ' do and now what?, in that we have been? &hellip;' constant discourse about whether the war is good or bad, if the money invested is much or little, if the politicians of the country are a few interested or not, whether soldiers are the innocent, about how much involved should be one with the circumstances &hellip; to weary, rhetoric and propaganda redfordiana that really doesn't interest me, or at least not in this way. Let's see if 'in the Valley of Elah', which aims to be equally critical avoids sank in as much moral depth.Already accepted the fact that the movie has nothing and is only a political of $ 35 million program, go to drinking all of their footage: its actors. The best thing that can happen to the film is that one be a nomination to the Oscars, at least to be able to boast of some success in the project. The nomination shall not be the Redford, which repeated undaunted its deep man pose, and everything points to Streep and Cruise as safe candidates.Sincerely, extensive conversation with Congressman and journalist in the Office have been the unique moments that I have taken out of absolute boredom. What talk is still political 100% but is curious to see how they are handled two such different actors face to face. Of course Streep WINS by a landslide, as always, but I pleased to say that Cruise brings an excellent note, with a paper short and fair, ideal to not make mistakes of overacting and perfect for a secondary nomination. Everything will be.Ultimately, difficult is judging a script when everything is information, policy and State speeches. I am now as if you just see a Michael Moore film without less thank you very much, without as much bad milk and with much artificial fire to encourage him. More difficult is valuing its players when all do in favour to mark speechs of those that are very well on screen but do not contribute anything. Difficult it will be to mouth not ends up with its box office. 'Lions for Lambs' will go down in history as the story of the most expensive American Democratic Party of history. Some will seem more than correct and poignant, but I still think it has squandered an opportunity of luxury for a thriller of those that cut the breath. That could be expected from Redford when grab runout &hellip;</body>
</review>
