<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Fracture" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More of the same, infinite loop of the same patterns, even if there is a desire to introduce something new, some unexpected twist... Everything easy and friendly, pleasant to see and easy to forget. Very nice, very simple, very elegant.</summary>
	<body>Fracture, unlike other thrillers judicial or tapes moved by the hypothetical perfect crime, not abused clichés: confined to loitering the gender patterns and solve any possible affinity with the trash usual tape billed on identical parameters with a lower, more adjustable to the classic melodrama impact end - where the bad guy always pays, but no gruesomeness or moral writhing - which in the film black or to the aforementioned film of dedicated lawyers subgenre criminal and them know all.Anthony Hopkins outboard the role of rich bored of his life of rico and pissed by the infidelity of his wife, which kills a dry shot in the head after surrender. Between the shot and accountability the perverse murderer built a monumental plan to sneak in the prison and the film recounts, impeccable technical Bill and predictable in their narrative twists, the alembic of inquiries and mcguffins of winks to the intelligence of the viewer - not overly forced, dígamoslo here will not be that someone thinks that this is a prodigy of modern noir - and mild strokes of moralina Christian in which the criminal not out by yours by the stubbornness of a curious lawyer, at least. It happens that when the yuppie picapleitos works moved by the cravings of the triumph and its hierarchical and personal prestige does not give foot with ball and get inevitably defeated. Instead, when he realizes the deepest roots of evil and pain, is work the miracle as his stubborn intelligence of lawyer know-it-all glows and is gaining positions in the race towards the unmasking of the culprit. The script, while not bad, does not always work and there is significant attention slippages, forgetfulness calculated to administer the (scarce) effect of the plot coups and, finally, cheap fumetti unnecessary notes as the romance of Fund in the offices of the firm or the tribulations of the nothing tapped character of the police unwittingly added to the criminal case. Hopkins is a case apart: already not outboard roles. It is even possible to say what has happened to work in the chapter to update its dramatic register and adapted to the profile of the character that should be interpreted. Hopkins is a plenipotentiary Lecter, Lecter, a modeled Lecter of one film to another. Even hinted at an effort of production by extending ad nauseam the Machiavellian, cunning and disturbed character of Thomas Harris Sir Anthony created in the basic film by Jonathan Demme. Gregory Hoblit is not a craftsman, but complies with what you ask. The two faces of truth, previous work semillado by the same interests, exceeds this review of the perfect crime, without that it needed here loa because it was not great in its genre. I remember Tyrone Power, Charles Laughton, Elsa Lanchester, Marlene Dietricht and the sublime hand of Billy Wilder and then my heart (inevitably) shakes and feels rewarded</body>
</review>
