<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Un Corazón Invencible" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Michael Winterbotton has opted for the simpler and less risky giving the role protagonist Jolie with that style of House so pseudodocumental it is divinely when you want to make a serious film.</summary>
	<body>I am sugestionada. It is the fact that I have lived in a hippie commune surrounded by French who knew better or worse to speak English, so when I heard Angelina Jolie trying to imitate gabacho accent I've felt a little upset. The story that revolves around to an American to strive to portray a foreign role when there are so many actresses of the Gallic country could do so without having to resort to subterfuges such regrettable, well, help a little your husband put the peel to make the movie is funny. Although doing so loaded the credibility of the main role, but who cares! If Americans are going to herd everyone they will praise while having no or remotest idea of how talks about a Frenchman in English. Or you can to happen what really happened and the people feel much better ignoring the tape and going to see less committed and hard fiction.The main weak point is precisely that Angelina is the center of the world. Understanding that the aim of the film is to denounce a regrettable situation in Pakistan through the drama of Mariane, a French journalist still intended there has to undergo the abduction of her husband and the desperation of the uncertainty is while expecting their first child. In the drama, there are many ways to approach a story ten terrible and deep and Michael Winterbotton has opted for the simpler and less risky giving the role protagonist Jolie and neglecting a good roster of side for greater showcasing of Mrs. Pitt with that style of House so pseudodocumental it is divinely when you want to make a serious film.An invincible heart is a film inspired by the novel A Mighty Heart: The Brave Life and Death of My Husband Danny Pearl written in first person by the own Mariane Pearl so better not they could have captured the experiences of the couple but there is something that seems distant and insubstantial in everything what counts. Much was said during the filming and seemed rather a media circus so that at the end unless the objective was that people speak of what was happening in Pakistan even if it were only to go down to the illustrious couple and the Entourage of kids but is a pity indeed drama ends up devouring the complaint.</body>
</review>
