<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El marine (persecución extrema)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a former marine muscled which has to recover his wife kidnapped by murderous thieves. For lovers of action cinema, it stands out for its candor and simple development. It is bad, but it meets what is asked.</summary>
	<body>Director: John Bonito (I am going to resist to make the joke about the tuna, muahahaha) duration: already did not occur to me more synonymous with an hour and a half.Release date: March 16, 2007.Al see this film I was reminded of Uncle Rafa (husband of my aunt Carmen is quite rotten, to see if it improves). Well, my uncle is a big movie buff, not of great classics of cinema, if not of entire film that you have in your distribution to hard grips + shots + explosions. I think that we had seen all of the genre, as well as to speak of them in the same way that others fill the mouth of directors who among all his films do not reach the audience of one of Ozores. Large type my uncle, big type.The film is a marine to which miss the body by jumping to the Bullfighter orders of commanders and obliterate with a camp of the bad guys. Returning to be civil, must accept a job of segurata (this only put it to fill and that the movie not lasted an hour). As throw you to the second two, will travel with his wife, but with such bad luck (not be for whom) encounter with guys who kidnap his wife fled with a few diamonds. So the bag of muscles must go to gnaw a few faucets to win back the girl.Let's see, what suggested it the name of the film and the uncle handles this? Because a film makes very see explosions, easy jokes, characters esteriotipados, topical hard and other types of action cinema. As film is very bad, but it's just what is spectator of this genre you want to, so we can not criticize there. The goal of mata mata is more than achieved. I thought funny (in addition to that a human being can have the biceps bigger than the head) the waiter after spending thousands of hardship ends without more scratches than a flick in the moflete. That are men and not the shit that there now is down the street (I'm home, hehe).In short, film about a former marine muscled which has to recover his wife kidnapped by murderous thieves. For lovers of action cinema, it stands out for its candor and simple development. It is bad, but it meets what is asked.Besitos.P.D: Has a Terminator touch of the most significant.Pd2: Between the director that chracter Bonito and the actor that is dinner, this seems like an advertisement for Calvo, jajajajaja, the festival of humor continues.</body>
</review>
