<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very estimable political Ribbon, which deals in a credible manner a topical.</summary>
	<body>Excellent movie, well directed by Robert Redford, the pair that performed by himself and a group of few but great actors/actresses.Eminently political film, which deals with a matter of the most topical, important for security on the planet with moderation and good tone. The goings of American policy with regard to the performance of their troops in the armed conflict Irak-Afganistán (which already you can add with any intention to Iran and its apparently real nuclear threat), left expressed credible and truthful, taking past and present, data that reveal the dark bastard interests of the U.S. Government. And to express it, Redford tells it in three aspects, three additional phases. Of a boy, a student at a University, thanks to world events occurring continuously, has lost the illusion in a better world where peace and justice prevail, unchecking the personal struggle that could contribute their bit in solve it.The second aspect make it up the two soldiers, old and very bright students of the University who have a rosy future, earned thanks to their efforts, prefer to take party enlisting in a war in which do not believe, but which they consider should take part in an act of social responsibility towards their homeland.And the third, the Senator and journalist, where we see with clarity the perverse connections between politics and the press, with politicians trying win her favors to have its collusion and have easier the blessing of their unsuspecting citizens who certainly mangonearán without any shame.All that counted in only slightly more than an hour and a half, so the script cannot be measured and adjusted, rich in good dialogues and, as I said before, excellent performances.A very estimable movie, that help to reflect on an issue of vital importance, making it a very fun way and nothing Manichean. It promotes free thinking and personal integrity, against wolves that threaten the confident lambs</body>
</review>
