<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Once" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spielberg: "A little movie called Once gave me enough inspiration to last the rest of the year &#8221;, if he feels well I am not going to be who take you the opposite."</summary>
	<body>Eleven, which has nothing to do with the number that goes behind the ten if not with its English meaning translatable as 'once' and with good reason because films like this are only "once each long", is a perlite. To see the tape reminded me the dogma films well done. It is a musical in the broad sense of the word (nothing to do with the media and the presumption of dancing in the dark) but a different and street music where musicians assail the action with tremendous melodic pieces. It cannot be a great musical because the grace of the film is the collected environment and intimate, actually harmony Gets a small, delicate, round film being delicious band sound is truly perfect and absolutely touching. "Falling Slowly", "If You Want Me" or the funny songs performed on the bus are musical jewels to adorn a tale of love and sincere, exciting and poignant rapport. Their actors are truly unknown and have previously been musicians in the streets and with a style of singer-songwriter very risky. The strength of the film cement in the interpretations of its protagonists the Irish Glen Hansard (professional musician and frontman of the band The Frames) and the Czech Markéta Irglová, a young instrumentalist of nineteen years. Both acores amateur but with a broad background and perfect for this old-fashioned love story. Guy (marked as well in the credits while she appears as a Girl and curiously using their own names real during the plot) plays on the streets of Dublin, in the bustling Crafton Street entertaining the Irish and tourists in the main pedestrian street in the Irish capital. His passion for the music makes them combine their afternoon playing with the family business and keep dreaming with a professional pitch until he meets a foreign girl with which begins a friendship based on their mutual love for music and to help you turn your dream into reality. No doubt with a simple argument get a really beautiful effect by the incredible work of John Carney, director and writer with some success television in Ireland but unknown in the rest of the world at least so far but that must keep track after this eleven, United States has already been a resounding success, thanks in part to the inspiring words of Spielberg: "A little movie called Once gave me enough inspiration to last the rest of the year", if he feels well I am not going to be who take you the opposite.</body>
</review>
