<review author="José A. Peig" title="Supersalidos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A juvenile comedy that laughs at adolescence to discuss it with great sensitivity.</summary>
	<body>It was not easy to imagine a review of soul beat through the new icons geeks, and much less combine rightly boorishness testosterónica of a teen comedy with an initiatory trip fun that, indeed, he communicates the essence of an underground tragedy. In recent weeks had received "warnings" that had reached the charts a work of art disguised as - with much intelligence - tontorrona comedy for flat minds, awakening my - so far - no interest for this creature. After the screening and the implementation in common we believe that it should not give excessive significance to a product designed for the amusement of the púberes but that piano piano, ends up nailing a hurtful estocada at the heart of much of the adult spectators. Say that the film is a profound critique of our society that hides the protest against (our) culture of the botellón, or has enough potential to renew as not only a film genre, but the same style of life of our young generations, overshadowed the loss of values and the desperate flight forward to which are forced in a world that has subverted the hierarchy and respect for elders. The only alternative - if already you can not grow in company of parents and teachers - is to seek the identity and self-discovery learning to survive in a hostile world, drifting along with the confusion prevailing (!)What world disgust).! The writers used the satirical tone to reflect our society. This society we see represented on the screen is not the Royal Society, but hyperbolic cartoon that brings together some factors of great importance in the life of the teenager who lives in a society (post) modern and tech. While it is true that the delusional stroke with which the writers build profiles of the characters and situations not allows to produce a faithful reproduction of the society, the strong construction of dialogues gives rise to director Greg Mottola use the expressive possibilities of the satire applied to the affective and obseso-sexual of the adolescent universe to talk about society. What the difference, therefore, the teenage comedy content without any artistic merit, is here used in the main stratum figuration - with which the public can have a hilarious time - to develop (in a UN texto implícito) a process of awakening; the awakening of sexuality, discover the value of friendship in its breadth of conditions, discover that in life you will be not always appreciated for what you are, but for what it aparentas be, or the "pleasure" of breaking the law and order (in one of the scenes most controversial, we see the exaltation and the revelry at the sight of a burning police litrona and balazos.luego car will be returning to this.)The soul of the three protagonists is a soul beatnik, losers who get involved in a crazy night race in search of affection (don't know if Jack Kerouac would like this film, but without him it would not exist). Specifically, the character known as Seth (Jonah Hill), is the pre-adolescent nerd equivalent to Dean Moriarty, beggar bocazas that hides in the background, the sadness of the helpless. Fogell is the archetypal freak that holds the tension in the confrontation with the world that is strange as the world is for him. Evan, counterpoint to the intelligent and normal boy. Three boys without friends and without any social success. And yet one of the things that will learn at the end of the road is that it is not the same having social success to be loved and that, sometimes, you have to choose between two paths. Alcohol makes the intercourse, but distorts the sincere expression of feelings. Or that never you know your best friend as well as the crucial moments. It would appear that this film has no script. Interpretations are unexpected transparency because the actors interpret themselves, having understood perfectly the role played, each of the three contributes to the excellent construction of characters, depicting feelings and obstacles concerning the immaturity to all, to a greater or lesser extent, have gone. Mention aside for the couple of policemen accompanying Fogell on his journey of discoveries, which hold most of the satirical burden and are the element that breaks the rules. In the key scene, Fogell, with the complicity of the two policemen and after a delirious scene that becomes exaltation of reckless driving, contemplates the patrol car on fire. And act followed, holds in his hands his first gun as if it was a rite of passage. The conclusion of the scene, with Fogell excited at the sight of the fire that consumed the car, is the moment that best exemplifies the unorthodox nature of the film; Yes, comrades, a tontorrona comedy would not solve the scene with this harshness, that final silence. (talked us to the boy sitting in the armchair next to made logical prediction, thinking that I was watching a movie to use: you will now see, shoot and falls of ass).Forgive the "wildcard", can not help it. Say that, after that smile, a tear. Exaltation of violence?. Are Seth, Evan and Fogell a faithful portrait of what is happening in reality?. Us worried about emerging youth violence? At least we know that Fogell is becoming "man" according to learn how to paste puffs cigarette, have fun with the driving reckless hitting fire to a car and then riddling it without him shaking the pulse. Do they need our teenagers do these things to feel loved?. Yes, better still if you goodbye spree classmates with their hands in handcuffs accompanied by two cops who take you to the station.In conclusion, it is the natural and precise way to view situations which makes that the characters have that emotional impact from the base of the simplicity of things which are real as life itself; the flat end of the escalator going down while Seth loses sight of his best friend, as waiting for something disrupts the goodbye to happen. Pure and simple friendship, homosexual feelings, or a constant in the lives of all those who know that grow is to say goodbye to many things that you love. In any case, a sad and intimate look at the world of adolescence and the misfits, and perhaps also, criticism of the dogmas that define social success as Candida ages: drinking alcohol to be more "cool", to demonstrate some type of violence against the forces of order and against the law to be more "interesting", the bias which hinders the proper understanding of friendship and sexual relations in a youth comedy that laughs at adolescence to discuss it with great sensitivity.</body>
</review>
