<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Superman returns" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Write a more than correct page in the history of film of the character, although still without showing us that work teacher that we deserve.</summary>
	<body>Everyone likes Superman. You that lee also likes. And if not, you should. If someone does not like Superman, it is because simply wrong fall you superheroes, and before that already cannot be nothing. The man of steel is, without doubt, the archetypal heroic par excellence, the equivalent to Hercules in our time. It was created by two Jewish youth in the 1930s, but now it belongs to everyone. During the cold war was used as a means of propaganda (adding to its phrase "for truth and justice" the climax "and our way of life") but all of that is already happily behind. Superman symbolises the most noble qualities which is able to mankind, only contained therein are in its purest form. It is the highest symbol of the righteous will fall from the sky. In other words, Superman summarizes the great messianic desire of Western culture.Perhaps that is the reason why there has been no film adaptation which has left everyone satisfied. Because come on, put you hand on the heart and tell me that some of the previous Superman films is really good. The first, 78, was a masterful soundtrack, was starring a huge Christopher Reeve and showed a really great part in which the origin of the superhero were all luxury of details, but from there everything is descalabraba: the scene in which Superman returning in time was ridiculous even for the era, and the man of steel didn't have a rival who was at its height. The second had some interesting villains, but in the end, the way in which they were defeated was so pathetic that did you cry of impotence. To make matters worse, the two films were with Lex Luthor in my opinion nefarious: a Gene Hackman who was more a comic character than a genuine threat. The third and fourth, while less talk better.Two decades it took to realize the project of a new Superman film, and the charge was Brian Synger, who had already proved to know the world of superheroes with their two X-Men movies, especially with the second. Partly following the "example" given by Christopher Nolan with his Batman Begins (2005), exceeding by far the versions of Tim Burton, Synger decides to reinvent his version of Superman, doing a sequel to the second part of his and pretending that the third and fourth were nightmares that never occurred. What was already a first success, one of the many Superman Returns (2006) offers.Because if there is something I admit is that Superman Returns has bad moments. However, the good parts are very good.The Messianic content mentioned above are here everything less "content". Synger does not seem make every effort to show us Superman (played here, rightly, by an actor almost unknown to the general public) as a sort of demigod called by order "divine" to save humanity no matter what mess is goal, also showing an interesting in modern man dichotomy: the supplicant need to be saved at the same time manifested openly otherwise. This is, without doubt, the most interesting aspect (for me) of the film.However, not everything is good. Unfortunately, Superman Returns is still showing a Lex Luthor worthwhile. Kevin Spacey resembles more to the idea that we all have character, but as Gene Hackman, is a clown. A cruel clown and despot, but to the end and Cape pasayo. This, confess it, I do not like at all, especially after that the TV had already offered us two excellent versions of the character: of the new animated series and one that gives life Michael Rosebaum in Smalville (take here to vindication this fabulous series). So I can not say that they had no easy to give this character depth it deserves. In addition, when we take into account that in the current version of the comic, Luthor is President of the United States, the choice of an "apolitical" character seems rather cowardly.Another problem in this regard is Kevin Spacey, a totally inappropriate actor. Spacey is simply too effeminate to be Lex Luthor, and this is very noticeable in the scenes in which angry. To make matters worse, we should not forget that he appeared in a cameo as "Dr. Evil" in Austin Powers 3 (2002), that of entry it is impossible to take seriously.So, ultimately, Superman Returns writes a more than correct page in the history of film of the character, although still without showing us that work teacher that we deserve. However, is still recommended by his grand scenes of action and lavish of his emotional manipulation (especially everytime sounds John Williams fanfare).There are already several that have fallen you over to this film, in a way which is, in my view, exaggerated. I imagine that it will be the time that do qualify this unjust refusal, and that Superman Returns is, along with The Hulk (2003), one of the films based on comics more misunderstood of this decade. It will be impossible to satisfy all fans of the character, but at least this film may be the first step towards a definitive interpretation of the myth. Hopefully.</body>
</review>
