<review author="Andrés Pons" title="Rec" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This cross between the Blair Witch and 28 days later is a new way of making films in Spain as well as deal with the Zombie genre little explored in our cinematography by removing specific examples. The saga the Templars, not desecrate the sleep of the dead and to a lesser extent some dandruff by Jesús Franco.</summary>
	<body>Horror movies is a genus that its maximum premise is the be scary or at least cause agonizing feelings in the Viewer. With the passage of time many deviated from this purpose by mixing genres comedy, action or even eroticism. In other circumstances be argued for Al GORE to make an impact with the blood but leaving aside the option of causing real nerves to the Viewer.If someone tells me that two Spanish directors seemed cuddly serian which encargarían after a long time serve as an overdose of real panic, an appalling horror at all times without any ornament or artifice. Here to shit pants without nonsense, really not I believe. Jaime Balaguero and Paco Plaza are the culprits that more than one suffers a heart attack in the coming months. Balaguero considered by all critics a sort of Messiah of the genre with success in all his films "DARKNESS, FRAGUILES" in my opinion it was a good director technically speaking but without the minimum hook for surprising or bring anything new.Paco plaza with ROMASANTA or second name showed the same for both more INRI as they joined in the joke called OT the movie. Nothing might therefore be expected in this new partnership, silent me the mouth making the best film of genus of long, using actors in very little weight just remarkable the name of presenter cuatrosfera Manuela Velasco transmitting at all times good ways that course handled the means to interpret virtually to yourself.This cross between the BLAIR Witch and 28 days later is a new way of making films in Spain as well as deal with the ZOMBIE genre little explored in our cinematography by removing specific examples. The saga the Templars, not desecrate the sleep of the dead and to a lesser extent some dandruff by Jesús Franco.</body>
</review>
