<review author="Bruji" title="Las 13 Rosas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Martínez-Lázaro puts the humanism ideology to rescue thirteen names of oblivion.</summary>
	<body>Martínez-Lázaro performs an accurate portrait of the two Spains of 1939. Captivating from the opening credits, brilliantly performed, precise artistic direction and breathtaking soundtrack Spanish film puts the humanism ideology to rescue thirteen names of oblivion.Away from history books, small episodes human that comprise the so distant, so this war of 36 and its implications, have come to many of us in the form of simple testimonies told in first person, which is not always corresponded with what the film told us. Perhaps that is why the flat, nearly linear tone which takes the narrative of Las 13 Rosas, is, for the first time, close. The film of Martínez-Lázaro will always be history that rescued thirteen names from oblivion, and did it as it had never before addressed the Spanish film: by putting the humanism ideology, in an exemplary exercise in good European cinema.When a director decides to show a fact historical - clearly, impressive - so exquisite delicacy and impartially, without fanfare, highlights and colors peaks, it shows not only a huge respect for the memory of the protagonists and their families, but also for the Viewer. Inherent in the own period, indignation and sorrow, are eclipsed, in not a few passages, by the sense of continuous fear that characterizes the society of all dictatorial regime. Remember the recent life of the others, set in another country, different time, different thinking.Las 13 Rosas, as a whole, is notable for its successful plot approach, unfortunately, lost in the first half of the footage, showing a poor choral. Flat sequence not always manage to link the different sub-plots, by which they are introduced in a forced manner and at the wrong time. Mounting tape, captivating from the opening credits, seems now insufficient to show the scraps of five lives touching the confusion.All this, however, does not deprive of cinematic delight that produce many of their scenes to compose valuable documents. The intentional improbability of the opening level, in which some "bad actresses" encourage resistance to some few citizens tired that they yearn for peace, not must have been very different from that lived in 1939. The blessed unconsciousness of the youth and its powerful ideals trying to avoid the disaster of a lost war: "What is peace without freedom, without dignity?". The relationship of existing affection between members of the two Spains, that culminates with the repeated warnings that Félix Gómez (magnificent and impressive performance) dedicated to Julia: "You do not know how things are". Pain and powerlessness that followed. The uncertainty of the vanquished chokes against the joy of the winners, splashing of anguish and fears to the Spanish referred to them in seventy years later. The young Falangist requiring the greeting to a depressed town, that few years earlier was governed by other symbolism. The second part of the story manages to be transmitted with greater solidity with a single approach. The thirteen players agree prison for an unexpected path without return. It's that time where movie fan memory, inevitably, recover the figure of Salvador and the last death sentence signed in this country, to see the injustice of a cursed stage in which the murders that came in the form of attack - as any killing, unjustifiable - saldaban making use of the "red prisoners" tothen populated prisons. Nothing had progressed in thirty-five years of history. At a technical level, the tape get overcome with more than the average of the latest national productions. The overwhelming and masterful soundtrack composed by Roque Baños is the perfect replica in the precise and well documented artistic direction, the excellent photography of José Luis Alcaine, the work of clothing, hair and makeup. Neither the composition of the script performs Martínez de Pisón, nor of course the staging of a quarry of young actors that can give great satisfaction to contemporary cinema passes unnoticed. Pilar López de Ayala, always a step above, heads a cast that Veronica Sanchez performs the best role of her career, Gabriella Pession and Nadia Santiago give moments of invaluable interpretative beauty and the great Marta Etura begins to take off. The outcome, very decently treated, leaves a window open to the hope that pleading the lack of rancor. A message conciliator, collected numerous testimonies of the surviving protagonists of difficult assimilation, which is shaping up as the only one able to close wounds that are still open.</body>
</review>
