<review author="José A. Peig" title="El graduado" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The interpretation of Dustin Hoffman, as straitened monochord register, more repetition in a series of plans laying down excessive narration, make the same emotional core that holds the film is reduced to a stereotype, very suitable for the late 1960s countercultural sensibility, but that already shortly can provide a current perspective.</summary>
	<body>I want to be different. The silence as a single response while Simon and Garfunkel harmonize their music with the emotional state of the protagonist, a young man of 20 years with life by discovering and without a defined direction. His face is all a long plain first until that becomes broadly to define the man in society. Arrives at the House of his parents, congratulations, the camera does not lose or a detail of its expression apathetic to the reiteration of the social informality that overwhelm him, almost the image of a society reduced the gesture conventional, without capacity to understand what really is concerned about a young man who isn't yet prisoner that hypocrisy and that accommodating thought. When it seems that there is no way out and that the rite is going to follow the logic of social correction, an attractive woman (Anne Bancroft), friend of his family, will be the element that dinamite the situation to encourage violation of established schemes. I wanted to be different, and the challenge is presented under the figure of woman naked and irrational, point at which begins the adventure of being young: lack of preset plans and flow with the temptations.It seems that Mike Nichols (1967) is interested in both build a convincing and exemplary character of a generation as a caricature of the niño rico faced with gaps of the family system and the relationships between people money altogether. Dominate the flat long in order to emphasize the introspective impulse towards the central character, but the interpretation of Dustin Hoffman, as straitened in monotone registration, more repetition in a series of levels that set the narrative in excess, make the same emotional core that holds the film is reduced to a stereotype suitable for the late 1960s countercultural sensibility, but already little contribution from a current perspective.The final race in search of the forbidden bride and the violation of the space and the rictus sacred in a church, with the cry that breaks the tranquility of the normal course of events, is the final reaffirmation of that young man, wanting to be different, ending to love through wild impropriety, including the snatch cross of his sacred room that will serve as a tool to shake the pressure of a social majority.</body>
</review>
