<review author="Patri" title="La tumba de las luciérnagas" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The protagonists are so human and are wanting so much that his story touches deeply and leaves no one indifferent.</summary>
	<body>The grave of the fireflies was directed in 1988 by Isao Takahata, author of the popular series framework and Heidi, Takahata is a major character in the world of Japanese animation, having founded along with Hayao Miyazaki Studio Ghibli, which have come out masterpieces such as the journey of spirited away, Princess Mononoke and Nausicaa. It is based on a novel by Akiyuki Nosaka, who was inspired by his own experiences, he had a sick mother and a younger sister who died of malnutrition during the war.The grave of the fireflies tells the hard and tragic story of the young Seita, of 14 years and her little sister Setsuko, 5, children of a Japanese naval officer. During World War II, his mother dies after a bombing and, after a brief stay at his aunt's House, where they are not welcome, both will remain homeless having to take refuge in a cave, in a time where the food and aid are scarce. It is a story of survival in extreme conditions, a portrait of the human miseries in times of war. The protagonists are so human and are wanting so much that his story touches deeply and leaves no one indifferent. It is a beautiful film that tragic, its beauty is really touching scenes such as the cave lit by fireflies or the principle, when, after the death of Seita narrated by himself, appears the old Tin of candy Setsuko and his brother gives you the hand. (Watch the movie for the second time this scene is understood better)The Japanese animation film is probably the best that exists, for decades they are doing true works of art that are beginning to be appreciated in the West now, they are films with a very deep and human background, sometimes dramatic, like this or lighter as Miyazaki's My Neighbor Totoro, but always worth a visit them, not only for its beauty but also for its message and pacifist contentfeminist and environmentalist, like Princess Mononoke, in which there are three.</body>
</review>
