<review author="Estesoyo" title="Spiderman 3" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This Spider-man is a hero for children, dull and infantiloide, and convenient to see below the teletubbies. Only lacks it the hug at the end. But that guy more bland by God!</summary>
	<body>Taking advantage of the output in dVd of the film touches review the big premiere of the season. This spider-truño of Sam Raimi continued in the descending line of quality that we already tries to get from its first part. I am not clear whether it is a child or directly a scam. For my part zero insurance.Another two hours and peak of continuous truño. If we make memory, the first part had first half an hour really good, with a presentation of characters quite adjusted to the comic. and little else. In the second at least we have a bad with charisma (with the great Alfred Molina) and a tremendous scene (which stops as a mono-rail can) and again little else. But this third already has nothing to what power grab. There not bad with charisma Summit moments. even the own Peter Parker makes it unbearable.But the truth is for now while I don't expect none of Sam Raimi, an individual who works better as commercial that as director. He began making gore and has ended up selling his soul to the industry. Already it had fogueado with television series for children, type Hercules and his cheerful company (series that good are very to do with your children from 8 years, it must be said). But now released to the blockbuster series Spider-man, which threatens us with go and go until exhaustion, makes water everywhere.First the story. Damn, they are super heroes and may not be very deep, but more than two hours should have something with a bit of criterion, not confined to amass characters who change sides as if change of jacket. Explain a bit what happens usually is not bad, Sammi. The argument is unfortunate and is dedicated to stun the Viewer: the man of sand looks good but then is bad and at the end that he regrets. then the Goblin is bad, then you lose memory, then bad again and good end until it dies. the black spidy is bad so when he has no powers. The relationship between them not achieved and with each one seems that it could have been something more.Then the special effects. go Uncle effects shit. Even my 4 year old daughter realizes that is a cartoon. It is very poorly made. And the action let alone. All the while receiving blows against pipes. Clonk! He fights the man of sand. clonk. he fights the Goblin. clonk. with the black spidy. clonk. a fucking healthy pipe in all New York must not be. That Yes, all stood as if nothing, total, such as super heroes. Fights are too confusing and do not contribute anything. I personally bored me quite during all the action. Finally the characters. While it is true that they usually do not have too much depth here the loop is crimp and they are quite flat and linear until exhaustion. That Spider-man has it very thought... becomes unbearable because of the believed that has it, that if the bride is sad because not triumphed. therefore throughout the film unbearably sad and ñoña. If someone has doubts of what is a linear character and only flat development has to do is film. Very bad, and the characters are emetics. The actors adapt perfectly to the role doing a really bad job, it is high time to renew the faces of the players, because from now no longer have apart from worsening.This Spider-man is a hero for children, dull and infantiloide, and convenient to see below the teletubbies. Only lacks it the hug at the end. But that guy more bland by God!, in the comics at least has some sense of humor, but in the movies is a terrible truño. And the trouble is that we are going to continue to endure so long, that despite everything he has been one of the successes of the season.The thing is so bad that scared thinking how it will continue to deteriorate in the next part.Summary: history does not interest, the characters induce me disgust and effects are shit. guess the result.Score: Zero stars (0 / 5)</body>
</review>
