<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Luna en Botella" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Moon in the bottle is a fresh and innovative proposal within the Spanish film, a deeply Bohemian history punctuated by touches of magical realism and Surrealism.</summary>
	<body>Make a movie in this country is a really risky and complicated. Very few are novice filmmakers who come to get the necessary funding to carry out his work, although the misfortunes have not just here. Because it is difficult to make a film, it comes to see if you can a job worthy of Hercules, and if not they should ask to Grojo, whose directorial debut, the Moon in the bottle, going out with less than one third of the copies which would in principle. Once written these lines as a form of protest at the treatment which has received the tape (as happens to Nacho Vigalondo and their Cronocrímenes go no further), there is to say that the Moon in the bottle is an atypical film within schemes following cinema (not only the Spanish) at the present time. It is a joyful, deeply Bohemian story that conveys a great freedom to all those who see. That Yes, in order to enjoy the viewer must take a leap of faith and immerse themselves without prejudices in the universe so particular that proposed Grojo. Obviously the film is full of references, winks and homages, ranging from Manuel Gutiérrez Aragón to the great maestro Fellini. Aesthetics and the setting of the film, among which excels the music of René Dupéré, is very successful and collaborates to transmit that Bohemian joy that follows the film. To give some negative point, perhaps the end leave more than one slightly dislocated, and the truth is Eduard Soto isn't at the height of the excellent group of actors by which it is surrounded.The Moon in the bottle is a fresh and innovative proposal within the Spanish film, a deeply Bohemian history punctuated by touches of magical realism and Surrealism. It is a film that comforts and returns the illusion and makes us believe in utopias cosmic even if only for an hour and a half.</body>
</review>
