<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Adiós pequeña, adiós" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very good film which proves that the genus black and criminal is the best and most appropriate vehicle for filming social realism and do so with emotion, but without sentimentality. With pace, but without pyrotechnics. With talent. With so much talent.</summary>
	<body>Much has been concomitancias that the plot of "goodbye, little, goodbye" has with the history of the Mc Cann: a girl blonde who disappears without a trace, the pressure of the media, the police action, etc, etc. And yet a see view the wonderful film directed by surprising Ben Affleck, the subsequent conversation led us towards other paths, which also have to do with children and with other news ranging more than the Mc Cann and on which won't talk about, for now, to not condition to anyone viewing of "Goodbye"", small, goodbye", originally titled "Gone, baby, gone".Ben Affleck, that already won at the time the Oscar for best screenplay for his libretto on the indomitable Will Hunting, has based on a known novel by Dennis Lehane to typing a superb handful of pages that tell us a terrible story, but in a measured and adjusted to the maximum way.We are in Boston. A girl has disappeared. Or she has been kidnapped. I remember that, when studying English in school, in the famous book by Arthur Newton, had a passage in which the reckless boy left his car on the street, and when I went back to collect it, it was gone. Paragraph ended with an expressive "It's gone". I remember that I translated it as "Gone", but the Professor interrupted me. Had to translate it as "They have taken him".And it is that, as the film is responsible for show, it is not the same, one "gone" than another. However, early on there, both the police and parents, convinced that the girl has been kidnapped, so the creature aunt hires a young couple of local detectives to investigate on their own, apart from the police, given that you know all the people in the neighborhood. This form of gambling den in den of interview in interview, two detectives are peeling multiple layers of the onion at a point of no return. And up there can tell because the argument serves as a perfect mechanism of watchmaking, with turns and twists in the plot, so unexpected and surprising as, finally, logical and reasonable.Benefits of the film: many. The hyperrealist atmosphere of a Boston marginal, ugly, outlets and outskirts. The most crappy bars in the world. The more dirty and asocial in the universe tipejos.Characters, perfect combination between primary and secondary, with the always sober, credible and magnetic Morgan Freeman and Ed Harris, carry the entire weight of a film that, while there is shooting, fire, blood and violence, never there was action, in the sense that we are used in Hollywood films. It's a dry, stark, violence that hurts.And it is this vast penalty flowing from the screen. A photograph and a design of production feístas, dark, turbid. Some stony faces. Some cool conversations. All in "goodbye, little, goodbye" oozes despair, bitterness and a huge sense of broken dreams of defeat, of abandonment.A very good film, in the style of "Seven" or "Mystic river"-that "goodbye, little, goodbye" both shares in addition to the paternity of Dennis Lehane - shows that the genus black and criminal is the best and most appropriate vehicle for filming social realism and do so with emotion, but without sentimentality. With pace, but without pyrotechnics. With talent. With so much talent.</body>
</review>
