<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Luz de Domingo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sunday light is the weaker film José Luis Garci has signed over several years, not being this obstacle so proved us once again his extraordinary mastery of the language and cinematic storytelling.</summary>
	<body>The film, like life, is full of injustices big and small, and one of them is that not is measured with the same yardstick. You can also pass by circumstances extraneous to the same film, a filmmaker or an actor fall into misfortune or subjected to swingeing and unjustified attacks. This has happened to one of our greatest conductors such as José Luis Garci, who remember won the first Oscar for the film Spanish makes a whopping 27 years.With light Sunday, Garci is closed call "Asturian trilogy", which began with the magnificent You are the One followed by an even more extraordinary story of a kiss. And to be honest, with similar precedents, Domingo light is situated in an absolutely unequal confrontation that has just clearly losing. That does not mean that, regardless, Sunday light is not a good movie, whose main defect are the ups and downs in its history. The most critical Garci will be honing knives, but this defect not can preparations are you only to him, because if the history of Pérez de Ayala was adventures, he has still managed to significantly improve. And it is that the story gains integers in the moments in which speaks of the tyranny, while low in the most romantic sequences, occasionally reaching the kitsch. The loss of intensity may also be due in part to the presence of Paula Echevarría, yet softer and less interpretative qualities than Elsa Pataky. The counterpoint put him about Alfredo Landa and Carlos Larrañaga, master that fill the screen in each appearance, starring in a stage duel of height in the sequences that coincide together. The technical work of the tape is simply magnificent, from the picture of Raúl Pérez Cubero to the artistic direction of Gil Parrondo. And above all, the extraordinary leadership of José Luis Garci, who many should criticize less and learn more about him.Sunday light is the weaker film José Luis Garci has signed over several years, not being this obstacle so proved us once again his extraordinary mastery of the language and cinematic storytelling.</body>
</review>
