<review author="Patri" title="El último show" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Death is present throughout the film but not in a tragic way, but with some sadness, resignation and perhaps a reflection of how he took the imminence of his own death.</summary>
	<body>The last Show is the farewell of Robert Altman, shortly after finishing and when this film had not yet been released died. He already knew that he was dying, and it shows by the theme chosen for the film and the tone, between comic and sad. Death is present throughout the film but not in a tragic way, but with some sadness, resignation and perhaps a reflection of how he took the imminence of his own death.The film is set during the last broadcast of a radio program that has spent 30 years in antenna and broadcasts live from the Fitzgerald Theater. It is a program to the old-fashioned American radio, with musical performances and ads cantandos. But not only will see how broadcast programme but also what happens behind the scenes, both comic and dramatic situations that affect all those who are there in one way or another.In some moments for the viewer who even knows this scene of the radio as it is my case, you can become a little boring, but in general the film are well raised and have some good times.There is a good cast of actors, as it is customary in the films of Altman, stands out above all Meryl Streep, whom I had never heard singing and here do really well. I liked it so much Kevin Kline, for me the best character in the movie, is a role of a type which supposedly is responsible for the safety of the theatre, but rather it seems that you are there penalty or friendship, it is a disaster and a very rare type, always dressed in clothing from the 50. also featured Woody HarrelsonJohn C. Reilly, Lily Tomlin, Tommy Lee Jones, Virginia Madsen, and Lindsay Lohan, that I did not like anything, found me something sobreactuada above all at the end. The last Show will not go down in history, but serves as a good director farewell, and to see her Gets a good time, even though you do not like the country.</body>
</review>
