<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Pitch Black" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a guy named Riddick that falls on a planet where darkness brings some bugs to picnic. Extremely original, it leaves open many doors in the face to sequels and prequels, which makes semi cult film. Very recomedable.</summary>
	<body>Vin Diesel this has me fried. Mira that my medium Zucchini does not like these movies of guys grips, but it turns out that this guy if. That if very well, is that if patatin if potatoes. Continue making movies, I I take a plane and escupo you in the eyes (not pretendereis two hosts that you stick to the handles of this makes me a knot). Heh, heh, certainly me are cool movies of this bag of muscles.The film is about one more distant future, in which a shipload of settlers which are directed toward a take on the left ass falls on a more arid than the monegros planet. In "travelers" is also a serial killer named Riddick, and a bounty hunter that leads the way to prison. Total, which once reach the planet see than the previous settlers - geologists came out too hasty, given the two Suns light do be never at night and that there is a kind of Giant Anteaters that give something of resentment.What most surprised of this film is its originality, with its toquecillo of fear, its share of humor, its good dose of action and the baton which can establish the principle of "who come alive?". Vin Diesel is within these grips actors, of those who operate better, with always very similar roles, in which fits perfectly. I like that he invents a world and outlines it, leaving things in the air in order to make other stories concerning this sinister place. It has a bug of these script, as for example bugs that go years without eating suddenly die of starvation, but more serious things we have swallowed.In short, film about a guy named Riddick that falls on a planet where the dark scary light given out some bugs to picnic. Extremely original, it leaves open many unknowns facing sequels and prequels, which makes semi cult film. Highly recommended.Besitos.P.D: Mola mazo tron, which read years ago.Pd2: I do not understand how he had so few viewers.</body>
</review>
