<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Las crónicas de Riddick" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Second installment of the muscular Riddick, that nothing less is assigned the task of saving the universe alone. Lastra Le it the length, but is a type of film with an audience of wide spectrum of a handles which kills and gracietas.</summary>
	<body>Director: David TwohyDuración: more than 2 hours, which was the Court of the director.Does premiere: August 24, 2004.Espectadores: 873.743 humanos.¿Quieres beings see Mr Diesel with a wig as the Melendi (with less alcohol in the blood)? Because clearly this is your movie. Too bad you have this waiter greñas, after meeting him always as the ass of a baby. By the way, I have a fellow in the Corral, the Spartan little, that looks quite like this type. I'm ask him to see if he is the son of Vin and I contracted for the next film. Who knows.The film is a guy with the eyes with cataract and stronger than vinegar which is retired on a distant planet. A good day they chase him about mercenaries, who want him to capture by a kind pays a bestiality by him. So after dispatching them with the tip of the Dick, he decides to go see such that both pays, to see if it is he owes money or what tripe has been broken. When he arrives there, the nocróferos, also arrive to destroy the planet, Galaxy, and the universe, for those rare reasons that have the powerful before shouting muahahahaha plan malevolent laughter.The alleged sequel comes after the origininal and surprising Pitch Black and we very disappointed. For starters, it is second delivery by the protagonist and an actor is the same, as if it could not be independent films. Totally. I I expect a continuation of the action of the first, but nothing at all. The strong point of the film are the decorations and in minor part wardrobe, you I has a medieval touch - space very curious. The trouble is that the action is tad erratic, the slightly loose plot and the result much longer than necessary.In short, second installment of the muscular Riddick, that nothing less is assigned the task of saving the universe alone. Lastra Le it the length, but is a type of film with an audience of wide spectrum of a handles which kills and gracietas. Quite acceptable.You lose much freshness of the original, but WINS effects.Besitos.P.D: The scene of the cup of tea is very good.Pd2: Gives equal what planet you are, will always be human.P.D.3: For those that you are interested in this information, my medium Zucchini fell asleep twice, different. Obviously, I've seen twice, for a change, heh, heh.</body>
</review>
