<review author="Calaf" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a dish of palomitero tasteful for the summer that I recommend without complexes.</summary>
	<body>Until 5 rooms of 12 of the multiplex which was exhibited the premiere the second part of the trilogy of pirates that is spraying fund-raising records. He broke on the first weekend in USA, recovering nearly half of what it cost, and is already in the ten most successful history.The question is: deserves it? The answer is NO. Is it entertaining? If is it worth going to see the film? If you have quality as so let's head to fill rooms entire cinemas around the world? NOEntonces by what this success? In my view they are a set of circumstances. No one has the key in the world of cinema. But it is clear that producer Jerry Bruckheimer (Top Gun, Armageddon, the Bar Coyote, Pearl Harbor, the search, CSI) has been able to find the key to combining a series of elements that has opened the chest of success: film adventures, stories of series B, humor, action and. Jack Sparrow.Hablando already in the movie, the first half-hour I didn't like. I was a little awkward the way of telling the MacGuffin or plot excuse which would put up the adventure.But soon we get some outstanding action sequences (then comment them in the section best) who put us squarely on the tape with more than smiles.The film, being long, is not heavy and achieves no doubt entertain the Viewer. The characterization of Johnny Depp as Jack Sparrow is one of the pillars of the same. It was risky to give free rein to an ambiguous, drunk and amoral character who however has been Street worldwide. Other characters and situations of humor (although type Solo at home) are also credited the entertainment. Special effects are spectacular (as he is expected, of course) and issue of costumes, locations, etc., he has spared no expenses. But once again we are facing exorbitant action, roller coaster, which aims to reach the largest number of public by expressways without quality entertainment. The secondary roads of the art is not interested in money. You want the main highway.Just have to look at the other films on the list of the most blockbuster: Titanic, Star Wars, E.T., Jurassic Park. except for Independence Day, I would say that they are all better than this. In fact, the keys to success are not new: adventure and humor of B of Star Wars and Indiana Jones series. However not I noticed the excited people out, nor do I think that you cale in the collective memory as did the sagas of Lucas and Spielberg. But today globalization has done that once achieved the ball of success, this becomes much larger to achieve levels that have little to do with the film quality.Still, it is a dish tasteful palomitero for the summer that I recommend without complexes, because it is clear that we will entertain and amuse, without great emotions, but enough to pay an entrance fee.By the way, on Cinemanía analogies of characters in Pirates of the Caribbean I read with Star Wars. And are not on the wrong track: Luke and Leia as Will Turner (Bloom) and Elizabeth Swann (Keira). Han Solo (Harrison Ford) as Jack Sparrow. C3PO and R2D2 as the couple of the canijo tuerto and el gordo. Up Will Turner seeks to save his father in disgrace (Bill the boots). And that sentence of. "the dark side of ambition"?</body>
</review>
