<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Promises much more, it becomes much less, although if planting some foundations for what could be the political cinema of this Millennium.</summary>
	<body>Thanks to a draw in which only took part I, and only I won I (thanks Miles &amp; Mary to 50% than good is that read me) went to see this movie, honestly, expected with some impatience and, once again, after viewing, I left quite cold, and it is that, after the promising start of the same, Reford, only get gently scratching the surface of the conflicta conflict that USA should begin to assume as "lost" and, like Viet Nam in his time, not be the bloody navel of the world, and see, although with some disappointment, as sometimes go with the Superman S to the chest, only happens in the movies.After this mini-reflexión, in a loud voice; those who know me (and here I'm going to support something that Mary told me yesterday), you know that I am very little friend of controversial and perhaps, I am the person in the world that least appears to be what I am, or think as I think, but my almost 31 spring is a little late to change right? And is that, (and I know I repeat myself), Reford tape, apply all possible clichés of the story, exaggerated at times, and boring in others (e.g. the character of Cruise comes to cause yawning in the audience), and removing a couple of details (the role of the soldiers) and all texts from the film appear in Castilian (blessed mounts)(, hopefully this repeated in the film from this film.), the rest of the tape, although excellently well designed stays in a bland experiment that could have been a little better, but it seems that, as said Valdano, someone has felt in the film "stage fright".It is a pity that a cast so compact, solidly built, and brought under the baton of Robert r. Miss those clichés, I said earlier and that, when it seems that one goes into a diatribe about the Iraq war and this battalion of interests created by Tito Bush and his henchmen, the tape, it slowed down both drythat ends up leaving the stupefied and gaping spectators in the audience.In short, promises much more, it becomes much less, although if planting some foundations for what could be the political cinema of this Millennium.</body>
</review>
