<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Luz de Domingo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good movie by Garci, who will go down in history as Alfredo Landa the last performance in the film?.</summary>
	<body>Personal adaptation, together with Horacio Valcárcel, from the novel by Ramón Pérez Ayala.Es personal because Garci, with its peculiar Cadence, with its narrative tempo as yours, it makes extremely in that regard to previous works, but also gives it that peculiar touch, that some like and others hate.What to my respect, I like it much.I am not saying that negative aspects, which are liked by Garci, but that really sin the little natural, contrived there are no. For example, some "prints" eclogues, where the characters, one or two at most, appear in the central part of a remnant of the nature, beautiful in itself, but overly prepared for the occasion.The light, the simpar photography, very yellow, magnificent precious landscapes in which the action unfolds as well as rhythmic music. And performers with an once magnificent Alfredo Landa at the head do wonder (Alex Gonzálesz appears occasionally to both forced before the literary dialogues should declaim, a character taken, I am afraid, Gregory Peck in "Big country" (see the scene of the pulse with the evil son of his hateful father)(véa_se_la_escena_deel_pulso_con_el_malvado_hijo_de_su_odiosos_padre))(remember in its spirit to the fight with fists between Peck and Heston). In the perfect setting with other great work of Gil Parrondo.Tan only, in addition to what I have already said above, I would say in the flat negative that the script, especially at the beginning, gives some fits, showing various scenes as if they were pieces, without much hilazón with the whole. However, and as the story takes body, in my opinion everything appears as it emerged perfectly, although I recognise that this narrative is not much taste / as spectators. Garci to do this and point.I guess that they will return to give this last film released by Garci from all corners, but I think it is interesting, for as long that is not bored nothing, and has no doubt dramatic force in some moments, as well as pieces in a good mood, almost always in charge of the couple Kiti Manver-Manuel Galiana, both splendid. Yes, I usually like the film by Garci and on this occasion, also.</body>
</review>
