<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Arma Fatal (Hot Fuzz)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Second installment of the creators of zombies Party, only which parody detective intrigue movies. Very good, with hilarious, but hampered by the first master moments delivery. Highly recommended.</summary>
	<body>Director: Edwar June. duration: two horazas.Release date: December 5 creators 2007.Los and part of the cast, again load after the amazing zombie Party with a very similar one, proposal unless nestled in the police establishment. It is very complicated to avoid references to the previous when we talk about this, since ending not understand without having seen the previous. Why? By the absurdity of the first making it saw clearly that it was a joke, and with this those tonteces are not detected by the apocalyptic end.The film is an excellent London Police a good day is destined to a small village where the crime rate is zero. The reason? It is so good it is leaving to ridicule to all my colleagues. In its new destination practically nothing happens, except that minor offences the resolves as if terrorist acts they treat. Within this village, awarded several times as the most beautiful people, in addition to police (of joke) is a neighborhood Brigade very concerned about offenders as the living statue, or even the kids with hood.We have more of the same with regard to Zombies Party, with caveats. The same shocks of pace, where we spend of be killing Undead to take tea and see if these are gone from the window has lost a little. Here don't have anything of that, more than rapid movements of camera and crazy approaches that end up dizzy. The script is very interesting, with a plot of intrigue worthy of great films of the genre and some similarity with an episode of X-files or even one of the Simpsons. And all this truffled Concierto and jokes. The trouble is that it does not become tronchante with laughter, with exception of the last half hour, where Gets the level of the zombies, with great moments at all.In short, second installment of the creators of zombies Party, only parodying detective intrigue movies. Very good, with hilarious, but hampered by the first master moments delivery. Highly recommended.Tad long, that Yes.Besitos.P.D: References to the first are several, such as the scene of the fences, in addition to the election of the principal actors.Pd2: Not be so translated, but VO leave Mr cock and blowjob Lord.</body>
</review>
