<review author="Marta" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It sometimes seems that in Spain let us dazzle for well done anything to get out of the more usual productions. A highly recommended horror film. No more, no less.</summary>
	<body>At this point I must be the only one who has not written yet on "The orphanage", which seems to have been already taken the title of "film of the year". And it isn't because it has very little to say about it. I liked it, Yes, and I was very scared, but I do not think the work of the century. And I am convinced that it is a mistake to submit it as a candidate to the Oscar. Let's start with the good news. Juan Antonio Bayona confirms that Spain can make movies without resorting to postwar drama or comedy of entanglement. It was not the first, but it seems that even not us so we believed at all. This horror film, focusing on the story of a woman who loses her son in strange circumstances, is very agile and entertaining and, above all, gives a long, very scared. It is clear that, of itself, claims children are always very disturbing, but would not get anything if they were not accompanied by a compelling script and, above all, a staging superb, with pace, agility and distance at the precise moment. And the work of Belén Rueda is essential. Who would have thought only a few years ago that this woman would become such piece of actress? The truth is you eat the rest with potatoes, starting with her husband in the film, Fernando Cayo. But of course, is that the poor man had a role of the superfluous, as if the subject were not too much with him. And there begins the weaknesses of "The orphanage". First of all the characters. Some are fine, and others, been half-hearted or are disconcerting. Does it come that a figure would be as Geraldine Chaplin says "police mola" to half of disturbing scene? Very funny, Yes, but is stuck with a shoehorn. And, if the appearance of one of the most "horrific" protagonists (Montserrat Carulla) will cause the laughter of the audience in the most tense moment possible, certainly there is something that is not working too well. On the other hand, the truth is that the argument is lame at times. The script is good, is not stupid and hooks. But there are details that do not fit at all and, although not to call too much attention in a first screening - possibly because it is easy to "get" in the story and ignore the inconsistencies-on further reflection jump in sight. It is not the only thing not just square. The visual approach is sober and elegant, and uses more psychological stress than the terror of blood and viscera. So that when the camera chooses to recreate in unpleasant and efectistas images, the result seems forced and free. The end is also excessively long and redundant, and the last scene is completely. It is the eternal question: should make things very clear so everyone it is very clearly, or is it better to be subtle, although some Viewer just not understand everything? I bet, definitely for the second, but it looks that Bayonne does not share my opinion. "The orphanage" is a good film, I could not say otherwise. It is correct and effective, and very much afraid, which is his goal. But it is not the best that has been done in Spain, and I do not believe to have chances to win the Oscar, precisely because it may well be an American work. The award of non-English speaking usually lie with much more personal works, which can be identified as characteristics of the country they represent, and this is just the opposite. That is not counting the terror does not seem to have too much recognition in this competition. If at least it was something original, you still trust a little in its possibilities, but it is not. I too know the gender, but no to look far to find notable similarities to, for example, "others", both in history and in photography, the atmosphere, the Visual resources or pace. And if Amenábar failed, I do not see why this "gifted student" was going to do, as much as his work is very well done. It sometimes seems that in Spain let us dazzle for well done anything to get out of the more usual productions. And things are not so simple. Even so, "The orphanage" continues to be a highly recommended horror film. No more, no less.</body>
</review>
