<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El buscavidas" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Undisputed masterpiece of cinema. You can not go more to the point when it comes to settle a headline.</summary>
	<body>You have perhaps been boxer made that Robert Rossen was a film director with wood from failed Boxer or moving the camera as if he alojase a derechazo in the air or try to knock out the opponent with a good straight to the gut. He was also a Communist. So we have a Boxer and a Communist who desentonaba in the Hollywood glamour, Cole Porter and costumes of fiesta in carpeted rooms, swing and champagne. He was then called by HUAC, the House UN-American activities Committee. Ypacarai director to portray subterranean worlds, marginal júbilos and embocadas lives to disaster had to be a dangerous type. Also in body and soul and the political were not especially sweet: the two come to tell that the world is, by nature, tragic and that as one escalafona in decision-making responsibilities therein more is abandoning ethics and is hence to corruption and to the desasimiento of the noble ideals that marked his idyll with the future and everything good and beautiful life. Rossen down to the ring or eaten offices of nicotine and depressing furniture of political parties for writing his disappointment. The sticks we got in life are not written: are scripts. Called to a notary to give faith of our desolation and saved the testimony in a safe so that someone, thirty years later, check encabronados we were or how unhappy that were our days on Earth. Rossen filming with bad milk so that generations to come attend, impávidas, between the sadness and admiration to his grey guignol, to his costumbrist stamp of deep America that which all American managers talk at some point of his filmography. Rossen is an America of boxers and players of billiards, politicians with large pockets and detachable ethics.The political commitment made him leave the United States, once he refused to give the names of the colleagues of ideological revelries. No talk of John Garfield, with which linked you it short trousers and gloves and sands of the words, this cumbersome area in which those in power do not want to enter for fear of losing it. The politician loses the innocence in his working tour: Starks, a wonderful Broderick Crawford, ends up corrupted, disenchanted, hosted in the same barracks vices and sins himself criticized on foot of a wagon, lacking the oratory with which engañará in the future, but invested of sincerity and convening power. McCarthy did the suitcases. It was recorded in Italy, Spain, Mexico and to the Barbados Islands. The return to the country (1961) was an apotheosis. He returned to dig in the same wounds. The Hustler is an absolute masterpiece. One of the best films in the history of cinema. Without palliatives. What's in this film? Honor perhaps. Life to dry. The field of battle of yesteryear humongous in a modern simulacrum.Low-life smell hot beer, black stale smoke and sweat. Add the curious reader a billiard table and a powerful light that illuminates the, a large group of vocationally idle men and perhaps a props jazz music and we have the perfect setting for a film noir film. If we put a glass of fine glass of mouth broadband well filling of Jack Daniel's or a good malt whisky because then the scene is simply perfect. The lady who long ago that ceased to be so, it escote generous, narrow skirt, painted and very long nails, lurks the game and hoped that their gallant devote him a look, a breath of smoke or a nod accomplice. The life, times, needed eyes, puffs of smoke, winks accomplices if one has lost along the way the esteem and hope that something good can happen. The billiard table, as the sand of the circus as the ring, as the bars of the bars is the quintessence of these low-life.You have to see Jackie Gleason, the fat of Minnesota, moving around the table with her body amazing, move the stick and apparently, at all times, which is going to collapse or that the heart is going to burst you is to attend a master class in how to move a camera and how to make movies. Point. Minnesota Fats is not only the name of a character: is also the mark of a famous and reputed pool stick. There are also in Madrid, told me a friend, a club of billiards with the bombastic and mythological name of Eddie Felson.El Hustler is not only the mythical character of Eddie Felson, the fast, the lightning, a loser, a memorable anti-hero. It is the story of the search for purity, perfection. Gives equal Rossen to give emphasis in the ring or on the pool table: the instinct is the same, the voice is the same. It is a morality of containment, painted in the color of money or the epic of survival or amoral men. Rogues, tahúres, sick of love, disenchanted, villains domestic, suckers and HUSTLER soulless: the dappled fauna Rossen used in that grey theatre which is the the pool table, Mythic territory and superb metaphor of life.Absolutely essential secondary characters: the "raging bull" Jack LaMotta, that makes bartender; George C. Scott as that kind of taco Pimp; Piper Laurie as the self-destructive Lady in love with the loser Felson.Jackie Gleason was never better. Piper Laurie borda. Paul Newman (what risk writing this) the best role of her life.</body>
</review>
