<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Shootem up" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spasmodic, fun, adrenalítica: one of the best films of evasion that might be in the placid intimacy of a movie theater...</summary>
	<body>Descerebrada, adrenalítica, intoxicated dreadful action, Shoot ' em up is (by far) the best possible evasion film proposal. Little or no plot, it strips all vocation of seriousness and arrambla lujuriosamente, with all imaginable topics, he satirized them, wrap them in a still choreography of savagery, which do not obstruct the sense of irreverent comic, orchestrated by a very intelligent mind (Michael Davis) who has managed to twinning clichés of action - killers with soul cinema, of bad guys that do not die ever, rocambolescas situations that always end successfully for the hero - with coarse humor, shockingly uncouth times.Shoot ' em up is pure cartoon, although the model is not graphic. The construction of the characters is archetypal, the script is symbolic: the only thing that ensures entertainment is a prodigious Assembly and an excellent sense of rhythm. Each scene is a consequence of the previous and enables the following. The shots are lines of text, but the actors are credible and gesticulate and move as if to take the joke seriously. The official criticism, the matrimoniada with the purity and a classic sense of forms and intentions, has made pieces. Perhaps disagree to any film to mark a soon or a later in frivolous or sublime or palomitera history of cinema, but at least there is a rigid observance of a sometimes forgotten approach in those who are engaged in making movies: Entertainment. Outside of this historicist rigour, the unbiased Viewer has before his astonished eyes a great spectacle, an operetta of gunpowder and impossible stunts I would already like to Yes John McClane or some inspired Steven Seagal. Clive Owen is not any action hero or the movie promises franchisee who squeeze his success at the box office. There perhaps rid the charm of this surprise and everything is regulated by other parameters. These here presented reduced its field of action, never better said, to pure escapism, the movement as the essence of the art of hila an image with another in a film montage. Battered its high doses of violence is legitimate, even necessary, but Davis makes apology for the destruction or praises the cainita engine of the human soul. If Tarantino has vindicated the plasticity of violence, Davis - this amazing tape - claimed the leisure component, naïve. The difference between the two (this idea offered me my wife at bottom of seat) it is that the first is not ironic, and the second, at least in this remake arrogant, Yes.Devoid of breaks, ametrellada in a poetic end - in rustic prose of its plot - Shoot ' em up can be considered as an anthology of scenes of action, a sort of greatest hits. There is no filler material: everything shines with the same wit, identical-minded joke. Until the hero emptying his pistol loader while it copula - said without shock - with the moza Bellucci, which is every day more carnal and beautiful - produces hilarity, but there is no ridiculous one. It seems that we have seen that image throughout life, in lots of movies. Its dynamism her brainy analysis excludes whoever to do those things. This frivolous bagatelle consumes little neurons of the risky spectator who sits in the Chair knowing that it will attend a stunning session of shots without hardly rest. Its unbelievable hubris needed complicity. Only that. The rest is literature. As a partner of reviews, "an honest film with itself and with the public, exemplary action cinema, is its balance between vulgarity and ingenuity to be entertaining without lapsing into unnecessary Bendy" (J.A.P.)</body>
</review>
