<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La habitacion de Fermat" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fermat's room is a film that initially caught by its disquieting atmosphere, but it sinks because so little credible are the characters and actors, except Santi Millán, which interpret.</summary>
	<body>There are certain actors, directors or writers, who have partners mentally with a type of film or programme, and it seems inconceivable that they can do something that drifts away from what in what are encasillados. Luis Piedrahita and Rodrigo Sopeña have always moved in humor, as lead partner of comedy shows, such as the Club of the comedy, nothing x here or the Hormiguero.Sin embargo, for her first foray of jointly in the film, they put aside the comedy and was released with a completely opposite gender, suspense film. Fermat's room is a film that attracts by its more than interesting initial approach, four mathematical locked up in a room without output, which is shrinking gradually, and because he is a type of suspense different from that usually offer the film. However, within minutes, one of the major failings of the film is discovered, and except for Santi Millán, there is not anyone who believes that Alejo Sauras, Elena Ballesteros and Lluís Homar incluo, are a few brilliant mathematicians. But the defect lies not only in the choice of actors and their performances, but also because the characters are poorly built and worse developed. The atmosphere is very successful, providing fair concern and the burden so that the tape pass on that feeling of suffocation that catches the viewer completely. But oh, this atmosphere is only kept the first half hour, the same that lasts the originality of the script. From that moment, the plot happens in a hasty manner, becomes monotonous and predictable, losing all the excitement, to result in a resolution artificiosa, simplistic and nothing credible.Fermat's room is a film that initially caught by its disquieting atmosphere, but it sinks because so little credible are the characters and actors, except Santi Millán, which interpret. The film could have been over it with a more polished script, a more elaborate and less hasty resolution, and a more careful casting.</body>
</review>
