<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cinema of adventure, palomitero 200% where the only thing to be is what is achieved, entertain the audience.</summary>
	<body>Returns the captain Sparrow and all their friends in this new installment of "Pirates of the Caribbean", a film than expected with desire, after the pleasant surprise the first delivery and according to critics, the resurgence of the cinema of pirates; as well, again we have all the ingredients that made us enjoy the first film, and at the same time, all things that we didn't, because both seem to be cut by the same pattern, and while in a pleasure and an honour, (cannot be otherwise in this kind of tape), reconnect us with Jack Sparrow, Will Turner and Elisabeth, the film loses freshness, since we already know the characters as if they were lifelong friends.Both Johnny Depp and Orlando Bloom are excellent in his well-known roles, so not Keira Knightley, which bit her cannot be, unless the circumstances face and make mohínes, unfortunately his performance does not give for more, special mention of ILM special effects, and it is these "mutated" with sea pirates are excellent, in addition to "their" beard of Davey Jones, after who hides the always versatile Bill Nighy.Antes that I forgot the hundreds of references (to the game Monkey Island and Star Wars) on all... would have to open a chapter apart to the soundtrack Hans Zimmer, who has managed to take all the best of the score by Klaus Badelt and improve it, adding in addition to his label, the exciting "fanfare" for the film.Finally, adventure film, palomitero 200% where the only thing to be is what you get, entertain the audience and let good taste.Incidentally, dedicate, this my criticism today excellent charge of "restoration" of Actaeon films, for their patience, affection, sympathy and others, made our purchase in the facilities nice. I hope to understand the irony.</body>
</review>
