<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="La habitacion de Fermat" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The room of Fermat is a movie with very good intentions but whose end result fails to be entirely satisfactory, although neither is an insult to our intelligence or anything.</summary>
	<body>After having gone through the Sitges Festival, finally reached our screens room Fermat, Opera prima of the tandem formed by Luis Piedrahita and Rodrigo Sopeña, starring Alejo Sauras and Elena Ballesteros, Santi Millán, Lluís Homar and Federico Luppi.En she, four mathematicians are invited by a such Fermat to a meeting in which he challenges them to decipher the more complex mathematical problem ever conceived. Dam of curiosity, the four scholars will be brought to an abandoned barn, in whose interior you will find with Fermat, who before exposing his conundrum must leave in haste in direction to the hospital where his daughter is entered. Since then, the four guests will begin to receive mathematical problems through a PDA with a minute of time to solve them. If take longer, the walls of the room in which they are locked will begin to wane to crush them.I have read reviews and quite harsh opinions about Fermat's room and, the truth, nor do I believe it for both: while it is not no genius, nor much less, must be recognized his wit, in which we could consider as a mixture of films such as Cube or even Saw with an atmosphere to the Cluedo, A corpse to desserts, or what is the same, to as Agatha Christie.En first of all, applies to Fermat's room is set in a very dynamic way, unpretentious, with a pace that, despite not become hectic or anything, we do catalog as enjoyable. Secondly, I think is quite right that their creators have opted for expose simple mathematical problems because, on the one hand, the approach of some intractable puzzles would have not facilitated the complicity of a spectator which seeks to resolve them and, on the other hand, its simplicity plays against the own knowledge of the characters, located in a far superior to these puzzles intellectual ladder.On the contrary, one must recognize that the outcome of Fermat's room, despite not reaching to be frustrating, yes that can detract from the rest of the film, in a succession of findings and allegations whose cabos are tying up at a rate of exponential to the final conclusion; on the other hand, one of the biggest sins of the film is the wastage of the actors, or rather, its lines of dialogue, with which none of them seems to believe his paper, and far from evoke the profile of a gifted for the figures. And it is that the characters of Fermat's room could spend anything less Eminences, because at no time we awarded for game play with a hint of genius or with an inspiring look, so its credibility is non-existent for the Viewer. To that, add a couple of jokes rather out of place that pesard and be funny some of them, do not belong in a theoretical frame of suspense.So, in short, the room of Fermat is a movie with very good intentions but whose outcome does not become entirely satisfactory, although neither is an insult to our intelligence or anything.As they would say some, in worst places we toreado.I am a 5'5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
