<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="The invasion" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is more of the same. Both gives me if they are aliens as if they are zombies, the scene of the protagonist escaping desperate to a horde of monsters humanoid that run like the devil, I start to have very view.</summary>
	<body>Before entering matter I would like to make it clear that I have nothing against the realization of remakes. It is a phenomenon that occurs from the beginning of the film and will not stop producing precisely now that the imagination is conspicuous by its absence. That said, I think that the least that you can demand that a remake is a look different to the same story or an update of the original elements. I.e., because we are going to do the same thing that made others before, at least do it otherwise.Therefore, despite the fact that there are two really good previous versions and that might seem already excessive the realization of a fourth version of the same subject, Oliver Hirschbiegel directorial choice gave the sensation of being motivated by the search for a new approach to history.I don't know if it would be by the novelty of the approach of Hirschbiegel but the fact is that, once its mounting, the producers decided to hire the Wachowski brothers to make some changes in the script and James McTeigue to direct additional scenes. Among others a total change in the end and a few scenes of action (sounds bad, yes).I do not know how it would be the initial Assembly of Hirschbiegel but change it, for having done something different, seems to me a good idea. Such things do not usually work and this time wasn't going to be different.Because if a problem is "Invasion" (The invasion) is that it is more of the same. Both gives me if they are aliens as if they are zombies, the scene of the protagonist escaping desperate to a horde of monsters humanoid that run like the devil, I start to have very view.Of little use that Nicole Kidman and Daniel Craig are equal to expected in them, because the failure of the movie is to have no soul. He too notices has been comeback and the final result is totally unbalanced and is topped with certain clumsiness.Gives the impression that the idea of the matter was to reflect on whether the loss of our humanity is too high a price to pay in exchange for not having wars or poverty (priceless seeing Bush giving his hand to Chavez) but this reflection is dropped without deepening the slightest therein, with intention to give the film a philosophical packaging thatin fact, it lacks.It is curious that "first version" has more than 50 years and is much more bold and has a message more radical than the film before us.On the positive side it should be mention that the film is entretenidilla and boredom does not take possession of the Viewer. Of course this is a poor consolation to decide to spend 6 euros at the entrance of the cinema.</body>
</review>
