<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Promesas del Este" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The script is bold, amazing, perfect, but need a director of talent and the Summit of his inspiration to create a so round like this work.</summary>
	<body>Two years ago, David Cronenberg was surprised friends and strangers out, apparently, his usual film and premiering that for many, myself included, was his best movie to date: "A history of violence". After that I was wondering if Cronenberg thought continue betting for this type of film or, as did David Lynch after "A true story" (his best film), would return to a more closed cinema that left happy fans.Fortunately for him and for all Cronenberg has opted for the first roads and it has given us with "Eastern promises" (Eastern Promises) another wonder that well could be considered part of a diptych composed it and the aforementioned "A history of violence".Since the beginning the film shows signs of greatness. Within five minutes have presented us to the main characters, the situation which will cause all the history and the city in which occurs the action; a multicultural London filled with sordid and gloomy corners, more akin to Jack the Ripper than to the postcards.Cronenberg and his screenwriter, Steven Knight, we introduce in the underworld that beats under the best-known London and show us what happens when hairdressers or restaurants close their doors. A rarefied and inquitante world that fits, in the background, with Cronenberg's lifetime, although many of its fans do not know realize.All this is possible in just 100 minutes by the narrative concision of a Cronenberg is impeccable and the existence of a perfect script that is a real gift for the director and some actors who, moreover, are in State of grace.Vincent Cassel composed a frightening and pathetic unbalanced at the time which is, in my opinion, the best interpretation of which I have seen him.Armin Mueller-Stahl returned to the place that it deserves, and demonstrates the good actor that is, to create a frightening character without fuss. His smile or the simplest of questions coming out of his mouth ("does a newspaper?") serve to produce chills in the Viewer.Naomi Watts is in his line and becomes gradually one of the essential of our time.But above all, I would like to highlight a Viggo Mortensen which demonstrates that the prodigy who performed in "A history of violence" was not result of chance. His performance is memorable. Its simple form of look or move make him appear fearful or sensitive according to the occasion and without apparent effort. A shame that festivals, critics and many fans do not know appreciate not histrionic performances because the actor deserves all the recognition of the world.Cronenberg returns to make it clear that the world of violence and the emergence of this in the life of ordinary people is an issue that will as ring finger and adapts perfectly to his way of filming. Why is both capable of shooting one of the fights more brutal and shocking in the history of the cinema (as well as sounds), as of a shoot loaded of an immense nothing sentimental tenderness.Well it is true that, as I said, the script is bold, amazing, perfect, but need a director of talent and the Summit of his inspiration to create a so round like this work.If above is Howard Shore and it consists a wonderful soundtrack, can not ask you more function.Final rating: 10 out of 10</body>
</review>
