<review author="Plissken" title="Los Cronocrímenes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Triumphant debut of Nacho Vigalondo in its passage to the feature film, everywhere less on the other side of the Pyrenees.</summary>
	<body>Thanks to the magnanimous CINEMAD organizers, a handful of lucky kids have seen the very enjoyable release in the direction of lengths of the hyperactive Nacho Vigalondo. I say fortunate because, for who still do not know, 'Timecrimes' is a Spanish film that has already won a couple of festivals (Austin and Trieste), has secured distribution and remake in United States and has filled rooms in very few passes of festivals who has frequented. And fortunate, too, because 'Timecrimes' is anyone who dares to exhibit in their country of origin. Now, go and take the blame for the crisis of Spanish Cinema Internet, the big American studios or the Spanish public, which is very Platypus.Surrealismos aside, Nacho Vigalondo debuted with a small mechanism of timepiece that traps, especially for his screenplay hotel. So delicate is the balance of the story telling that, as he is warning its own director for some time, the minimum slippage when writing an impression about the film affects the small big surprise which is to assist their development. Therefore, for once I would not dwell on the narrative: 'Timecrimes' has the tremendous journey undertaken when Hector (a haunted Karra Elejalde, in State of grace) Decides to investigate a strange event in the forest that surrounds the cottage. There are more, of course, but is a better discover it with Héctor. Vigalondo part from a minimalist approach (a few actors, a handful of locations and little else), and surprises the viewer with a history that we have already seen, Yes, but that rarely is told us in a very coherent manner. The work of direction is quite careful, without being spectacular. In fact, the sobriety (others call it poverty, but it is just lack of money) the production plays even in favour of a dark and claustrophobic development. Little music used is included with great success, and the darkness of the flat Nocturnes and foreign (fruit of a surely lower than 'The orphanage' budget) helps to understand the oppressive climate surrounding Héctor from very soon. Could they have done better? With more money, no doubt; with the same, hardly.In the interpretations section we have a sober and effective Bárbara Goenaga; a Candela Fernández who does not bother, but also falls in love with; and the same Nacho Vigalondo playing a key character gesture of the film, courageous (and usual) it, but which sometimes takes some power to the final result. Fortunately, 'Timecrimes' entire revolves around Karra Elejalde, and it endures without problems the weight of history A defect? The truth is that you can ask little more to an opera prima Spanish and gender, but I dare to say that he hoped a final. Wow, that would prefer other end. It is horrible that to not have anything about a movie.Triumphant debut of Nacho Vigalondo in its passage to the feature film, everywhere less on the other side of the Pyrenees. I look forward, for once, the American remake. There will be more media, the same director, the same story, and maybe, get a taquillazo in their country of origin. 8.</body>
</review>
