<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El vengador tóxico" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a boy that mutates in a toxic Avenger devoted to exterminate all criminals of his people. Comic Gore with sexual dose became a cult film. If you want to see one of the genus, which is this.</summary>
	<body>Director: Michael Herz and Lloyd KaufmanDuración: Na, or 80 minutes.Release date: 1985, in the ass the hinco you (is to follow with the tone of the film).In pornographic films we can find several ways of doing so. On one hand, pneumatic women of impossible curves and fleshy lips (both) that they trajinan as if a studied ballet, developed gentlemen were hyper with less hair than a frog and phalluses of apocalyptic dimensions. Course, that porn is somewhat distant from the viewer average (and the integer also), that often go for productions less professionals, with real characters, such as which is on the other side of the screen with the pants to half leg. Why am I telling all this stuff? In the "gore" film we can find with the same. Incisions and cuts of movies as Hostel or Saw end up bored to the Viewer, tired of so much perfection, and it makes producers such as Troma his hole with products like that today bring it.The film is an alelado kid who works at a gym of a city called Tromaville. All they get with him, and him they putean, to such an extent that a bad day ends falling into a bucket of acid which coincidentally was at the door of the gym. Following this, his body transforms in a super hero who is responsible for ending the more than excessive crime in the city.Let's see, the film is very bad die, for starters. But what it makes a cult film that put on the map to the productoria Troma? Well, this film marks a line of genre comedy - gore - grumosilla that must have spectators by noses. The dialogues, taken out of context are tremendous, but stuck in context are even worse. The storyline is the worst of the worst, but engages in a bad way to go see how to deal with the Avenger of each one of the bad guys. The gore scenes are pretty good with cheap effects that give the pego. One thing, not cut with nothing, there is nothing of respect for anything and you can find anything. Also have nude unnecessary, so you need something else to see?In short, movie about a guy that mutates in a toxic Avenger devoted to exterminate more brutally all criminals of his people. Comic Gore with sexual dose became a cult film. If you want to see one of the genus, which is this.Over the years keeps it just as bad, but endearing.Besitos.P.D: Scenes like the cieguita reading the hand to the monster are priceless.Pd2: Detail of the MOP seems very good.</body>
</review>
