<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not you will be given a prize important and surely, it won't be to the anthologies of the history of the cinema, but the five euros invested in box office are well, but very well spent.</summary>
	<body>A film that in your footage boats, sea, adventure, pirates and the famous "Ron, ron, ron the bottle of rum", also includes a fifteen men on the chest of the dead always count, of course, my most sincere and enthusiastic sympathy. I.e., to enter to see the new adventures of Captain Sparrow and his boys, Sacai and I were cheerful and optimistic and funny.Prior to this type of film paraphernalia advised to equip, as do the kids of popcorn, potatoes and sodas, that not every day is an opportunity to rejuvenate for two hours and a half, such and as long as that takes footage from a film genre which, however, breaks with many of the typical topics of the adventure film.The characters, for example. Everything is spoof in these pirates of the Caribbean. Each imposing pose one of the protagonists is immediately followed by a little humiliation to his ego: a coup, a fall, a whack. Sword fights are anything less heroic, leakage are rocambolescas and, at times, it gives the feeling that the Marx Brothers are going to leave one of the cabins of the Black Pearl. And what are these "Pirates of the Caribbean II", which are a cartoon with his pace, his gestural comical, their persecution, their gags and its rigging. It's like a cartoon film. but big. To the beast. Because producers have not repaired in expenditure to achieve a lavish decorations, a perfect ambiance and, above all, some spectacular special effects. Thus, the emergence of the Dutch Errante and, above all, of the Kraken and its sinister tentacles are absolutely spectacular.I admit that the first part taking quite forgotten, had moments in which I lost arguably, without knowing who was who and why, suddenly, had laughter celebrating jokes for beginners. And is that this franchise of Sparrow has rendered fans who have seen the first part more than three to four times, fans that will return to the cinema in the coming days to delight with the waste of this second part imagination and that, when appeared The end screen, began to (des) count the days that they are still missing for the premiere of the third film in the seriesalready filmed and announced in the spring of next year.This is a film with no claim of significance, however, is refreshing and stimulating, flexible and fun. One of these films of summer you reconcile with the sea, the wind, adventures and memories of childhood; It is with joy, enjoy with pleasure and makes you have a delicious time."Pirates of the Caribbean II" will not give any prize important and surely, it won't be to the anthologies of the history of the cinema. Surely, it amasará a fortune at the box office and, perhaps, it will make any kid to discover to Robert Louis Stevenson, but in any case, the five euros invested in box office are well, but very well spent.PD.-agree not fail to look at this unique witch lover of Voodoo. A wonderful secondary character who, hopefully, in the third to give more prominence. He deserves it.</body>
</review>
