<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Beowulf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One must recognize that Robert Zemeckis film intended to, although fails it entirely, go beyond mere aesthetics in an entirely virtual world, which is worthy of praise.</summary>
	<body>Certainly some, one of the most awaited movies of this 2007 is Beowulf, epic fantasy based on the eponymous Saxon poem which has been directed by Robert Zemeckis and starring a few digitized Ray Winstone, Angelina Jolie, Anthony Hopkins, John Malkovich and Robin Wright Penn among others.Beowulf situates us in a time of heroes, in Denmark, where Hrothgar reign lives under the shadow of the giant Grendel; on the other side of the sea, the mighty warrior Beowulf will arrive to kill the devil, thus provoking the wrath of its monstrous to seductive mother, in a conflict that will transform a King in legend.First of all, I would like to specify that a server has not had the opportunity to enjoy the film outputs 3D stereo, as it seems that they sent the canons, but in an Orthodox, although of considerable dimensions display.One of the most striking phrases of Beowulf and which, on the other hand, sums up perfectly good part of my reactions to the film, is that the vassal of Hrothgar converted to Christianity shouts in the final stretch of the film: the sins of the parents. Why? Because Beowulf has exactly the same mistakes (although to a lesser extent) that it lacked the previous attempt by Robert Zemeckis, Polar Express, digitize their characters.After this ominous outbreak of criticism, now move on to talk about the virtues of Beowulf, on the other hand, are not few: the new film by Robert Zemeckis is, as expected, a visual wonder, with some dazzling sets and a fascinating history, a noisy and catchy soundtrack in many of its passages and an epic aura which, without a doubtIt is the best of the film by far.On the other hand, and as I said at the beginning of this critique, the characters in Beowulf are not always at the level of their environment, at least graphically, as the price of their close-up and his hyper-realism are partly marred with some of their movements (when riding, for example) as for his tertiary characters, very little defined in some cases. For this reason, and despite the first visual impact of Beowulf - even more (I guess) if her fine we in stereo 3D - one cannot have the sensation that is watching a long introduction of a latest generation console game.In favour of Beowulf can be said that its history, despite predictable result in general terms, nevertheless interesting, above all thanks to a few not too extensive, although dialogue effective, in addition to surprisingly verosímilies on the lips of their virtual, rather more consistent players than many actors of flesh and bone in other movies fantastic. On the other hand, one of the greatest achievements in the Robert Zemeckis film is that, although it may be paradoxical, not abused the special effects, based on a relatively calm and sober narrative pace in general except for its final stretch, which no doubt helps own the footage epic status.The epicentre of this footage is, if anyone doubted it, the character played by Ray Winstone, the legendary (though slightly swashbuckling) hero, noble and haughty, proud and bold, which change all those virtues required for a lifetime of adventures in favour of the stability of a reign, and perhaps something of lust. Thereafter, Beowulf goes from being a hero of legend to expose as a cowardly traitor, but why not be undermined in the eyes of his Entourage or the Viewer, actually, the myth has become man, nothing more: a be vulnerable, mundane, that with the passage of the years will realize his mistake and he must face their own fears givingCuriously, the redemption his soul yearns for. Why does Beowulf but portraying man as Monster and vice versa, message, especially lately, we find in greater or lesser degree in new productions as in the case of this copy/paste called invasion, the most recent example.Thus, the epicidad of Beowulf is guaranteed, as well as the waste of sober special effects and, like 300, snapshots to remember, but one must recognize that Robert Zemeckis film intended to, although it fails at all, get beyond mere aesthetics in an entirely virtual world, which is worthy of praise. That, and the fact provide us with a fairy tale without connotations children, as has happened with this pleasant surprise has been Stardust. ASI and everything, still think that the same movie with meat bone characters would have been much higher.I give a 7'5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
