<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Rec" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It starts with a strong expectation, continues with a central stage that combines scares and sense of humor, to make an impact with one of the most tense final crescendos and taquicárdicos of horror in recent years.</summary>
	<body>With the exception of the award for best film, which has deservedly been the particular poetic Odyssey of Tarsem Singh The fall, the great winner of the Festival of Sitges 2007 has been [REC], winner of the award for Best Director, prize for best actress, the audience award and prize of the critics. and Paco Plaza and Jaume Balagueró have signed a truly commendable filmshot as a mockumentary, as in vogue in recent times, where the tension reached unsustainable levels - especially in its second half-that a server for a long time that not experimenting.[REC] tells the story of Angela, a young reporter for a local television, that one night continues with his camera firefighters of Barcelona, with the secret hope to live live a striking fire. But the night elapses extremely quiet. And when they finally receive the call of an old woman who has been locked up in his house, he there is no choice but to follow a group of firefighters during his rescue mission. In the building where the old lady lives, residents are very scared. Too much. Women, enclosed in his flat, shouting some heartbreaking. The firemen destroy the door and followed by Angela and the House, found the semiconscious old woman, surrounded by dozens of cats. Suddenly, the woman launches on a firefighter, biting him savagely, in front of the incredulous fellow and the lens of the camera. It is only the beginning of a long nightmare and a dramatic feature unique in the world: when other firefighters carried the wounded, discover that the only way out of the building is blocked by the authorities. The building has been put in quarantine. It seems a strange virus has spread in the interior.Certainly, [REC] collects many clichés of the horror film, starting with the inevitable reference to the draft of the Blair Witch, as well as certain similarities with 28 days later and clear homages to films like Infernal possession. It is also true that the movie Plaza and Balagueró not scary really, if anything in certain specific passages, and that his formula works more with scares that recreates a visceral horror.But, as well, however, [REC] is to draw the hat.With a hyper-realist style, [REC] wanders between a strong expectation in its initial, truly disturbing stretch, a central stage in which a community of neighbours hilariously feasible enlivened the plot with a relaxed sense of humor that seems to lead to the film in directions not expected to make an impact with a final crescendo - with easy resolution, it must be said - that iscertainly some, one of the most tense and taquicárdicos of horror in recent years.As I said, [REC] does not offer anything new in itself, but is admiring the Plaza and Balagueró ability to combine existing elements forming thereby a new product, Amen for do jump from their seats to all those attending the screening. And it is that Paco Plaza and Jaume Balagueró have signed, conscious or not, a true milestone, an extreme experience that installs the national horror film at some levels never dream so far and hardly surmountable.On another hand, and this as a personal note, do not understand how the prize for best actress has gone to Manuela Velasco which, while it meets more than the purpose of portraying, isn't at the height of the excellent performances of Catherine Keener in An american crime, Rain in I'm to cyborg, but that's Ok, or even Jess Weixler in Teeth. But the real question is. Why not is [REC] at the Oscars, rather than the orphanage?I give a 8'5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
