<review author="José A. Peig" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Superfluous and harmless, but is a perfect synthesis of narrative about the political and social concerns that shake our present, and a perfect use of mounting that can correlate thoughts and situations in various social fields.</summary>
	<body>It is an ideological film which deals with the current war seizure, the valuation is made (always to the light) will be subject to currents of opinion easily identifiable coup of politicos topics bored while they asquean to the movie buff concerned about craft and intellectual honesty of the filmmaker. Those of the no to the war talk she sympathetically disguised (where less hypocritical or in a so-called wisdom on the truths of the conflict between civilizaciones-intereses strategic macro, blah blah blah.), on the other side may sharpen the knife and clean the field of ingenuidades pseudoprogres until you see the light at the end of the long roadthat demands us a price to pay (as if it didn't.). So, not us we empantanemos with mental diarrhea and go to ours. Robert Redford, who is a person and not a God who knows the solution to all conflicts in the world, directs a film motivated by good intentions. While it is true that at the ideological level it does much more than the mere exposure of some common places, at least manages to his speech (perfectly structured and developed, on the other hand) to be as sober as full of sincerity. A sincerity, say, manifests itself - and becomes palpable - in "good feelings" to introduce a sensitive element to the contradiction; the University young (Andrew Garfield), with whose face in close-up and pensive look on television begins and concludes the film narrative. This character will also mean the same conscience of the character played by the same Robert Redford, faced the difficult role played by new generations.We have a brief and simple speech, but he manages to accommodate concerns of different signs with enough consistency and ease, allowing the filmmaker tell his "truth" without excessive disrespect to contrary trends. Draw the concern of the citizen aware of the hypocrisy of the American ruling class without involving close our eyes to the visible problems in the society. It is better to try to move the world with individual initiatives that sink into apathy. But, of course, beyond the strong wording (and well constructed which is the relationship between the teacher and the student), Redford gets carried away by the mannerisms to lead a disturbing anything.Profiden Tom Cruise smile has never been so appropriate to embody falsity, since neither he nor the same Viewer can believe his role. What is a defect becomes an efficient interpretive attribute, without ceasing to be crude. Perhaps because Cruise is a lousy actor, or for the reason behind it, the truth is that it seems a profile designed to tell the viewer that this guy does not believe the Jets said. Meryl Streep contrasts a sensible journalism that strives to glimpse his truth, discovering how the press has given and has become an instrument of power media. And finally, the plane that closes the speech leaves the doors open. Appears on the TV news of strategic change and in parallel an idea that remains floating in the image, emphasizing the undefined and ambiguous tone. What note you will put?. The note is the human evaluation that a teacher can make his student, whose intellectual dignity shall be measured in accordance with overcome the sense of helplessness to a world ruled by politicians with dubious intentions. The human potential is there and can rise above the chaos.Superfluous and harmless, but is a perfect synthesis of narrative about the political and social concerns that shake our present, and a perfect use of mounting that can correlate thoughts and situations in various social fields.</body>
</review>
