<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La Huella" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An entretenidilla movie that remains light years of what might be and that, in fact, already was.</summary>
	<body>I've already said several times that if it was not because the director was Kenneth Branagh this remake not I be interested slightest. And it is, in general, I think doing remakes of great films of the past is unnecessary. But the task becomes daunting if the film, in addition to being a jewel, is a unique and unrepeatable tape. Examples might include "Casablanca", "Laura", "Jennie" &hellip; or "Footprint". Branagh, an excellent director squandered by the industry, try to uncheck the original tape through a completely different scenery, changing the Baroque style of the decorations by the simplicity of the free spaces, removing all visual obstacles that in the original tape helped create the atmosphere oppressive and morbid.The problem is that, as indeed the oppressive environment must create it as, Branagh is forced to take a similar visual solution and so need to locate the camera at impossible angles or focus the scene through a security camera for framing the character visually move the feeling of being trapped. This solution visual, intelligent, sometimes works and other shows excessive and forced.For the same purpose is used the "technology" of the House. But, in addition to showing us the most universal remote in history (an only button controls dozens of functions other than the House), is extremely forced the Michael Caine character change the light of each room in which to enter, or project multiple images in two facing mirrors or, finally, atmosphere the scene to taste of the director. The film is trick, Yes, but it should not be noted.Despite this, or perhaps for that reason, the work of Branagh ends up be the interesting thing about the film with the interpretation of Michael Caine, a monster from the scene of the largest in the history of cinema, and a Jude Law that is able to keep the type.Patrick Doyle's soundtrack is also that attract attention by their quality, something that should not be surprised seeing the copyright of soundtracks of "much ado about nothing", "Hamlet" or "sense and sensibility".Harold Pinter where I see another problem of the tape is curiously in the indent of the nobel. Because while the dialogues are still bright and resourceful, Pinter decided to introduce a homosexual to the story, dot while some see signs of this already in the Mankiewicz, here shown as a key in the history.And there I do believe that they are wrong because, in this way, you lose a little sense the theme of the game by the game, the duel of wits of revenge for revenge. I think, indeed, that this "epilogue" remains part of the sense everything what has seen earlier in the film.Posts to comment on fallito, and here it comes a SPOILER of the fat, I have to mention that a shot of adaptor can not launch a body through the air: a trap very blatant and totally unnecessary if it weren't for the obsession of the contemporary cinema to show everything on screen.As happens to me almost wherever I go disappointed by one of the great directors I have stressed more negative than the positive in my criticism. But that that I don't think that we we have a bad film because it is not. Strange thing, coming from Branagh, nor it is good. "Footprint" (Sleuth) version 2007 is, in short, an entretenidilla film that remains light years of what might be and that, in fact, already was.Final rating: 5 out of 10</body>
</review>
