<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Sombra del Reino" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The shadow of the Kingdom is just another patriotic film made to morale in society American, it tells a story with heroes and villains in the purest style of Hollywood.</summary>
	<body>From the first years of life of the film there have been films whose primary function was to exalt the patriotic values of the society, and this has not only given in United States. There is more to do the bulk of the film which took place in the post-war Spain and in the first years of the dictatorship. But yes it is true that the American is the case clearer made propaganda film.After the brutal attacks of 11 September, and after leaving spend time so the society cicatrizase his wounds and cure your pain, Hollywood has found a real patriotic Philo in terrorism. The shadow of the Kingdom tells the investigation following a savage attack on a residential complex for Americans in Saudi Arabia. From the beginning, the film openly shows his cards, and is not masking his patriotic speech. The script is quite simple, vulgar, devoid of all credibility and very predictable. The American agents are portrayed as if they were superheroes, who must do their work in appalling conditions, in addition to addressing the indifference or hostility of local authorities. But as it could not be less, no lack of the character of the local police who agreed with the arguments of our heroes, and to follow the tradition, from the outset well known what will be their fate. The film has two parts well differentiated, the first research type CSI, while the second is filled with well resolved action sequences, that Yes.The shadow of the Kingdom is just another patriotic film made to morale in society American, it tells a story with heroes and villains in the purest style of Hollywood. The problem is that in real life not distinguishes so clearly the good from the bad, and everything related to middle and United States is much more complex that it showing the film.</body>
</review>
