<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is indisputable that one stays indifferent after the final flat master and the whole of this irregular, but necessary film.</summary>
	<body>We are undoubtedly facing a stage of film rebellion against the USA policy; before a rise of committed and commercial cinema. And this, obviously, is a good thing. Lions for Lambs is one of the first examples of this new proposal (and protest), and is responsible for Robert Redford more active than ever. Director and protagonist, the American Democratic thoughts gives us a lesson about consciousness and, above all, of the current situation of the war of Afghanistan. A political complaint which is not just an approach to the current problems, but which also teaches us to raise us once and for all and realize what really is happening. And it is, above all, his film commercial, and therefore, that prevents some anger that I know that he has inside and is not completely portrayed. Yes, this is a film that manifests itself for an hour and half with the slogan "no to war" in each one of their planes, but this removes some episode of soldiers is not, unfortunately, credible and truly in the purest Hollywood style. And why? Therefore perhaps for fear of enfurecir to too many Americans or by the director's own thoughts, which are like the majority of Democrats in the United States, not at all ends.It is true that the complexity of the subject to be treated can be confusing for many (and I include myself in them) when we look into the film, but also it is really true that after seeing Lions for Lambs you're not indifferent. Somehow, consciousness to the viewer that not everything we report what is really true. Or perhaps Yes and precisely that is what we just we are worried about. Robert Redford has been able to create a kind of attack against the policy of his own country as well as ñoño tribute to the lambs that sent to war. By the tante, what would you rate of irregular, but I assure you that if we only focus on political messages and concienciadores of Professor Redford and the masterful duo between the journalist and Congressman, we would we be before one of the films most promising on the war in recent years. As you would expect, the trio protagonist Star (Cruise, Redford and Streep) look incredibly, with a respective interpretations truly realistic and do not seem assayed. Perhaps the episode of Congressman sinneth somewhat theatrical, but this probably allows to make Mr Tom Cruise look as it has never done. And the sad thing is that it is virtually impossible to film him falling any nomination at the next Oscars, although it does have any chance latter to qualify even for the award. It would not surprise me, but I would find it unfair if they were not also two other veterans.The sensation that causes Lions for Lambs is none other than the of having attended a debate entertaining, concienciador and with three heavyweights that support most of the footage. It is clear that the experience of Redford in the film has been shaped with subtle intelligence, and just have to see the composition of the film. Agree or not with Redford's poses, that it is not another thing than the reality, is indisputable that one stays indifferent after the final flat master and set an irregular, but necessary film.</body>
</review>
