<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Arritmia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Arrhythmia is cinema's complaint in its purest form, is a film that makes us think deeply not only about what is happening and surrounds to Guantánamo, but about the very nature of the human being.</summary>
	<body>If the nature of the human being measured by their acts, it would be impossible to determine if our nature is good or bad. Because acts of extreme generosity or kindness, or the extraordinary sensitivity of certain artistic manifestations, we have acts of unmatched hatred and cruelty. As example is what happens at the base military at Guantánamo, a disgrace to humanity as a whole, and by which history will judge us.Vicente Peñarrocha in his second feature addresses this problem, but does so from a new perspective, unlike what was Michael Winterbottom. A Guantanamo prisoner manages to escape, and a dancer in Havana welcomes it in his house despite the danger. In arrhythmia, nothing is what it seems, and anyone who wants to discover what the mystery hidden in the depth of the film must pass through box office. Arrhythmia is an innovative and risky proposal, complaint in State pure cinema, although it is not terrible or disheartening for free. Suggesting rather than showing, Peñarrocha manages to convey to the viewer all the anguish, humiliation, fear and horror suffered by the protagonist. Powerful visual aesthetics that has managed the Valencian filmmaker, as well as the rhythm that gives the history, contributes significantly to this atmosphere of terror that exala the tape. And all this accomplished cemented in a solid script, in which everything is well explained and detailed, despite the shortage of dialogues. Rupert Evans performs a formidable job, as a seductive Natalia Verbeke and a disturbing and masterful Derek Jacobi.Arritmia is cinema's complaint in its purest form, is a film that makes us think deeply not only about what is happening and surrounds to Guantánamo, but about the very nature of the human being. And in addition, is an innovative proposal and more attractive, with three players in State of grace.</body>
</review>
