<review author="Bloody Will" title="Beowulf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the almost two-hour film I have not had the feeling of boredom or boredom, but a sense of that was constantly expecting something finally Zemeckis no me ha dado</summary>
	<body>I still remember when there by 1992, just when he had just released ' Terminator 2 &prime; and the T-1000 had become a milestone, Cameron announced a film shot entirely with computer-generated actors. In 1992 this was madness, there was no CGI, digital effects came out as much for 10 minutes in total of a film and above to recreate human factions was sloppy. How much has changed the film, and who would say that 15 years later would be something like 'Beowulf'.After enjoying as a dwarf with the new by Zemeckis, I have good news and another bad: good, 'Beowulf' is impeccable visually, with a decent script and some as brutal scenes (beware of lead to children) as specific, which makes viewing more than entertained. The bad news is that the expectations that we have created, end up being correct isn't enough, with some disappoint. To put that in the almost two-hour film I have not had the feeling of boredom or boredom, but a sense of that was constantly expecting something finally Zemeckis no me ha dado. It could start a controversy about CGI Yes or CGI, but it is clear that after seeing 'Beowulf' there is nothing to prevent that this film was made with real characters very much in the style of 'The Lord of the Rings'. Moreover, the scenes which combines the appearance of deformed, mythological and fantastic beings faced with the hero of the story are not so many as to justify an entirely digital film.However, and sticking to road, the perfection in texture, skin and movements of the characters Ray real image, with that I say everything. Let's say that Zemeckis him trouble as go with players waiting in the caravan.The story is simple: Beowulf (Winstone), a specialist in liquidate monsters, lands in the land of King Hrothgar (Hopkins) to kill Grendel (Crispin Glover), whose main occupation is to kill the entire population on party nights. After executing his work, the mother of the Monster (Jolie) searches for revenge. I would not like to dwell much more that he was unaware of the second part of the story of the protagonist of the legend, and that he has ignored part of the cast trailer, will leave it continues.With a very basic premise, Neil Gaiman and Roger Avary has taken almost 10 years in shaping a script that obviously gave to mount an epic film in its entirety. Finally what remains is an amalgam between much macho cry (' I am Beowulf!)(' is repeated 15 times without), much empty talk and any inconsistency, where priority is given to relations between the characters and less epic struggles &hellip; but milk, I have not gone to see a Jim Jarmusch film, so the mere fact that the plot runs of fluid forms and serve as a preliminary to the scenes strong me is more than enough not to fall into deep sleep. Perhaps we expected a round product, and with someone like Roger Avary was aboard sensed more consistency, so satisfied with something simpler and without desire for significant complications.The strong point of 'Beowulf' is therefore its image. Impressive the invoice technical Zemeckis has permeated in each frame of the film, where has been treated in a thorough manner every last detail. His greatest achievement is to make you forget that everything shown on screen is created by computer and some scenes are basically perfect, though, and there's always a downside that the capture of the characters in the image and likeness of those providing his voice (Robin Wright, Angelina Jolie, John Malkovich, or Anthony Hopkins) takes you sometimes to distract you looking for their defects.Priceless two of the best scenes seen so far: the fight between Grendel and Beowulf, and the final 10 minutes, they get to lift the film at a time where the dialogues between the protagonists begin to wane. The trouble is that the appearance of the mother of Grendel, requeterepetida in the trailers released by the Studio, loses the impact that was supposedly intended to Zemeckis, therefore is in the retina a magnificent Jolie, covered in gold, and a little horny. Thus, expected an endless succession of fights, jumps, and epic battles remain something disappointed after checking that they are 4 times that we are going to see Beowulf handling the sword. There are few, I know.Two things that we get lost along the way: Crispin Glover, the voice of Grendel, whose dubbing into Spanish has deleted the excellence of his performance, and the lack of rooms IMAX which release it on a massive scale. This is a spectacle of colors and movements, and the lack of preparation of our films in 3-D rooms will do much harm.If we stick to the lack of enthusiasm that has been received the film in the USA, I reiterate what was said in: overdose of expectations that has inoculated us the distributor with a few impressive trailers is dissatisfied when it comes to check virtually all spectacular Beowulf is condensed into 30 or 40 minutes, which is a put ** if we proceed to compare with the great Leonidaswhich lacked the encouragement to continue handing out left and right.That a film does not have a dash of 10 does not mean that you can not enjoy the wrapping around him. I have enjoyed my Beowulf, the monster Grendel and a finish that leaves you at the edge of the seat, and this whilst I am aware that there will be a unanimous opinion about how good or crappy. For lovers of the fantasy epic without the pretensions of a Tolkien &hellip;</body>
</review>
