<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="El asesinato de Richard Nixon" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good first job after the Chambers of his filmmaker. A hard but necessary, film that makes us think to go much further than the vision of a long-announced human tragedy.</summary>
	<body>Hard first movie of Niels Mueller, sober and unforgiving as few.Through a pace calm, but relentless in the direction to the most painful internal hell of a man unhappy, full of good feelings, but doomed to deeper failure by his uncontrollable social extremism, we witness the self-destruction of the protagonist.Mueller takes his time to make progress in the development of the fall of that person, that we should not forget, there was really; and it does so relentless, crushing.Sean Penn gives his character of a lost soul which we feel close, that we give you reason in the Fund, as their wishes are ours, but however, we can not get with him given the injustice of their acts. This dichotomy, strange and frankly annoying to the Viewer, as we see injustice that must endure on a daily basis the protagonist, but we cannot familiarize ourselves with him because although the Fund assists, the shape and the far that takes everything you think or do, requires us to reject it. That same make which surround him.Moments like some conversations with his wife, his brother, his boss (magnificent Jack Thompson) or the interview with the man that could give you the opportunity to start a new life of honest businessman, azoran to the Viewer, feeling something that moves between the tenderness and the embarrassment. How much you want to the protagonist we applaud, but at the same time we know that it is impossible, that in this materialistic and selfish society is an Entelechy, a mere dream and even a social danger. What would happen if all act in the same way as him?A hard but necessary, film that makes us think to go much further than the vision of a long-announced human tragedy. Superb soundtrack.</body>
</review>
