<review author="Jack Torrance" title="Rec" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>From some time the film oscillates between the terrifying, the boring or the ridiculous. Even so, the show offers plenty of scares and moments of impact to ensure an hour and a half from entertainment.</summary>
	<body>The project of the Witch of Blair (The Blair Witch Project, 1999), was a kind of reagent for the 1990s horror film. Emerged a decade full of light and aimed at the teen public movies, mockumentary of Myrick and Sanchez continued the wake of the tremendous Holocaust Cannibal (Cannibal Holocaust, 1980) and made use of a new film weapon: internet viral marketing, or how a minimum budget film can become Gold thanks to Word of mouth. Their insane success at the box office, the film itself was boring and terrifying in equal parts and their supposed Postmodernism not let place to the development of an effective script for the benefit of the likelihood. After the financial resurrection of the genre and the current time of remakes of horror, that film begins little by little to notice his influence in the genre of horror. After a hiatus of almost a decade we have movies as the announced Cloverfield (2008) by j. j. Abrahams, that mixes the attacks of monsters Godzilla type with first-person point of view. The zombie subgenre returns with three inputs: the diary of the dead (Diary of the Dead, 2007) by George Romero, The Zombie Diaries (2007) and the Spanish [REC] (2007). Romero tape uses subjective circumstantial form format, only to provoke immediacy, not neglected in no time the classical film quality and proposes an elaborate script that leaves site to total verisimilitude. [REC], however, proposes a trip purely focused on the realism through the television format of reality television programmes. As if it were a witch's train, [REC] is nothing more than an honest película-experiencia which takes full BWP style to have, in their own way, how to survive a zombie infection to the 28 days later (28 Days Later, 2002). Far from being a nightmare of unsustainable horror, the tape turns out to be a rather commercial work, as moments of tontorrón and light humor, and that continues to be a fairly common film of "scares". Its objective of seeking the ultrarrealismo formidable begins with the presentation of the main character, beautifully played by Manuela Velasco. His naturalness before the camera is ideal and paler performances seen in this country in a long time. Unfortunately, the amazing work of actors (such as the elderly couple) is invalidated by little credible interpretations of many, too many, cast members. For this reason, part of the original premise is invalidated and from certain point the film oscillates between the terrifying, the boring or the ridiculous. Even so, the show offers plenty of scares and moments of impact to ensure an hour and a half from entertainment. One of the problems it shares with the Blair Witch Project is its lack of a prepared script. There are several more or less improvised dialogues and many moments of shouting, chaos and confusion which, under the excuse of realism, reveal a lack of ideas written on paper. The lack of a purpose is supplied based on good planning and virtuosity in the Mise en scène, always credible and well done. Another drawback, perhaps unrelated to the product itself, is that it is far from its real possibilities. The film seems to boot, but does not really even the last section of the film, when the protagonists have to face the dangers in order to escape. The mcguffin of the search for a key in one of the upper floors seem to have been discovered too late and so far there are several sequences of narrative stagnation and turns to the same place that makes that they are not used effectively mechanisms of the subgenre of horror. So, the journey never becomes an intense experience from beginning to end. In this regard, worth mention the previous Balagueró film to enter to live (2005) as an exploration much more accurate of the possibilities offered by scenarios such as a block of apartments, or the long corridors of an apartment engulfed in darkness. Therefore, [REC] disappointed in his use of explored space and the artifices of horror first-person, insufficient resulting in more compact and less successful than the previous work of one of its directors. The end, uneasy, it is one of the more chilling moments of the film, and although so far the film means a move away from the ghosts and sects typically Filmax, Plaza and Balagueró seem to not be able to get rid of characters with dark secrets and recovers at the last minute the (very common in the work of the second) cuts of newspaper, which on this occasion are little appropriategiving a farfetched, delusional and ridiculous explanation to the origin of the infection. Although it doesn't develop their full potential, the end product is a more than decent approach to the zombie revival, perhaps not placed one step ahead in the subgenus, but rather the opposite. There is a certain naivete in dealing with certain clichés of the genre, which are aided by the use of levels seen in recent successes of the living dead film. Thus, the use of a fat woman in nightdress or the level of one infected child, to which a character gets naive, to being bitten then are too symmetrical them in dawn of the dead (Dawn of the Dead, 2004) so that the tape not appears, nevertheless, true aroma to exploitation. And although there is nothing wrong in it, [REC] is a tape of very functional gender that is not intended to be more than that, a tape of opportunistic and commercial exploitation. The irregular career of Balagueró and Plaza consolidates with a perfectly enjoyable, easily consumable divertimento and that doesn't fool anyone. A good example of palomitero film posed an interesting conceptual opening for the fantastic homeland, which could well open a good trade gap in other subgenera to which we are accustomed to patriotic film makers dealing with horror.</body>
</review>
