<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Recognizing that it is not a film for all types of viewers, I recommend it because it is interesting, it generates debate ethics, is it has a huge capacity to make us think and reflect on our actions.</summary>
	<body>After what happened on September 11, 2001, history and especially the Americans split in two. In recent years we have enjoyed several tapes directly or indirectly taking this fact which still hurts the whole world. But within all elaborated so far, this new film directed, produced and acted by Robert Redford would like to emphasize that for 7 years was absent from the issue of the direction of films after the movie "The legend of Bagger Vance". And is that within all made this a political and some complaint interesting, bold, daring and clever character that after everything, puts on the table the necessary elements to focus on reflection.Lions for Lambs is structured within a supremely present time, taking events, involving characters and institutions or spiny and vital systems in the events which today have been developed as a result of 9/11. Three specifically are these elements Redford brings into play: as a place, used the war of Afghanistan, as a system policy with the weight of all his power and as characters to a politician, a journalist and an idealistic Professor. A film where arises every minute the importance of taking action against what is happening around us and punishes our indifference and apathy to tackle them and be truly split, because we really are built with them. These three characters represent a contrast of our society, no doubt, but that in essence, enclose the soul of the 3 professions that can most influence the minds and collective thinking.The same Redford embodies one of these characters, the idealistic Professor, the rest compose it the twice winning the Oscar Meryl Streep and almost lifetime nominations which makes the role of journalist and who shares for the first time set with Tom Cruise, producer in addition to this project. With them is built a few very good, long and heavy dialogues that should not be to the liking of the public but that enclose approaches that go beyond a superfluous discussion meaningless. Involve the importance that charge the media in this type of problems is something transcendental. A slight feeling of guilt glimpse of this tape to the lambs of the media to take power they handle responsibly. Responsibility than to past unnoticed, because we must not ignore politicos lions have derailed the strict freedom possessed by the media. Nonsense debatable from the film for the reason that I just outlined.Another interesting approach is the idealistic teacher seeking with his wisdom to produce changes or be a common thread of the dispersed young minds. But that in turn contrasts at the end of the film, as a result of the decision that two of their students take act with wisdom and responsibility towards the society. It is this point that more controversy and disquiet generated out of the cinema. Questions like: does worth leaving the comfort to fight for ideals confused in favor of acquiring the peace to as place?, does worth leaving, even by some time, our daily lives: study, work, etc., to fight with limited warranties? And if I interiorizo this problem more, might ask: I would leave a son embark in a war, as hard quota imposed society me to do part of it?, are some of the questions that easily and deeply leaves us this tape.Surprisingly, the restraint with which are totally and absolutely subjective theories about the foreign policy of the United States. However, it is that same subjectivity, which can disturb many viewers that she see a merely film suitable only as a resource or almost a desperate cry of the defeaters of Bush, next to finish his second presidential term. Here, I can say that Lions for Lambs recreates a very intimate situation of Americans and their political system is a speaker of a significant percentage of those who do not share the absurd war that has cost them plenty of dollars and that them has been immersed in debts unthinkable years ago, so they are carried out under the pretext of applying justice to a fact that cost the lives of more than 2,000 innocent people. In addition I believe that rather than discuss the decisions of a Government, this film shows, the very first need to address everything that happens around us and we wake up to the importance of taking action as part of a group to which we belong, is for me a "enough already ignore", ceases to be lamb and turn you into a furious lion that advocates commitment to self-interest and the other low principles of harmony and peace.On the other hand, to focus the plot on 3 different spaces, the narrative of the film is lost a bit, as well as raise a self-paced for each situation what "you crazy" in some way to the public and that remove you the points needed to be a perfect movie. Despite this, the effort to move away from traditional productions of commercial cinematography of the greater the film industry and be seen as a film almost independent type at the expense of risks that this implies rescued this tape. In fact to a week of its release it has managed to raise little more than 20 million dollars.Recognizing that it is not a film for all types of viewers, I recommend it because it is interesting, generates debate, is unethical, has a huge capacity to make us think and reflect on our actions and to many critics will be part of the nominees in the coming Awards Oscar with true aspiration to take any. We'll see what happens.</body>
</review>
