<review author="Dragon negro" title="Stay alive" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without being anything out of this world, the film comes to entertain, but not to panic, which coming from a tape of terror is a major drawback.</summary>
	<body>Correct debut and little else of William Brent Bell in this horror film where the protagonist is a video game that gives its name to the tape. A boy dies in the same way that in the video game that was playing, a group of friends and fans to video games in their belongings discovers video game that I was playing and decide to play all networked, they will soon begin to fall one after the other and you will discover that what happens in the game is applicable to the reality, but the game will go a little beyond.A priori the premise itself is nothing original, we change the tape of The ring by a game and we already have. And as every teen horror movie, is foreseeable to the spinal cord, you know who is going to die at any given moment, you know who is going to survive, etc. where is grace in this film then?Because certainly two key points, the first is in the short duration of the film, just 80 minutes, which makes that the scenes of deaths among the protagonists of form rapidly, as soon as you know that someone is going to palmarla makes it fast, not recreates in persecutions, in create tension or resolved to fall in the easy scare, dies and point, which makes the film to earn a point to not bore with more of the same. The other advantage is the last half an hour, when the film looks set to fall from the half of the footage in the pure boredom, manages to lift the flight in an interesting and entertaining half-hour final in which will discover as the game works and which is their source. Without being anything out of this world, the film comes to entertain, but not to panic, which coming from a tape of terror is a major drawback. You can see it if you will the genre, if you have nothing better to do or if your are video games.</body>
</review>
