<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="La camarera" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Delicious film more entertaining to most of the comedies in poster still being a romantic tragicomedy fledged and sweeter than Chocolat.</summary>
	<body>More than three months ago some friends began to eat me head on a movie I had seen so-called Waitress about a waitress who was adept at making cakes of different types depending on the inspiration of his own State of mind and putting the names more implausible and colorful of the experiences that made him create them.I recognize that when someone gets so much enthusiasm for good or for evil I'll stick with the mantra and now that the film is about to be released in Spain I have to indoctrinate readers about the need to visit the rooms to see this delicious sweeter than Chocolat film more entertaining to most of the comedies in poster still being a romantic trajicomedia in every rule.Jenna has a talent for his work which not only couple make "Feet" delicious if not for attracting the sympathy of all those who surround him. When he discovers she is pregnant realizes that her desire to flee her husband will be slightly disrupted. Trapped in a depressing marriage in a mediocre work and waiting for a child who doesn't want to gradually begins to understand that life can be accompanied by good things in the most unexpected places.Two of their successes to part of the script are its two protagonists will be the sea of television: Keri Russell (Felicity) and Natha Fillion (Firefly) whose chemistry and grace is indescribable. Sundace brought to the public of street thing which was logical but at the same time surprising that it's a modest, small but very meticulous and manufactured tape with much love. The recipe proposed by Adrienne Shelly (Director and screenwriter) had no waste. Written while he was in her eighth month of pregnancy the Director could thus giving life to a real, confusing, reckless character and in search of happiness that causes the empathy of any viewer instantly.</body>
</review>
