<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Piratas del Caribe: En el Fin del Mundo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More of the same, and it will three.</summary>
	<body>There are franchises, more than pelícuasl, we confinamos to indolence: laziness apathy to remind them, see, but who went caught up in jubilation, recognizable in the guise of greedy consumers of adventures, with three screaming and popcorn cinema rows above. Hollywood has its most significant income in this chapter of sale but not the most seminal. Pirates of the Caribbean: At the end of the world relates to this already tired formula of exploiting ad nauseam the baptismal benefits of the product, that is, the fresh and appetizing first installment. Because this Jack Sparrow, Hector Barbosa, Davy Jones or the here revitalized Will Turner and the cohort of Bivalves, agusanados spectra with right to Parliament and mother-of-Pearl eyes that open portals to unknown dimensions is not anything other than a product, one of prodigious invoice and appalling technical means. So far all right: popcorn, pirates, treasures, tentacles and colors to galore. Music not at odds and the figure beloved Captain Sparrow's already well accommodated in the freak of certain generations, Avid heroes of the modern cartoon, characters subject to the marketing and merchandising ad hoc Vertigo. In addition to all this, the tape entertains, missing more, but not as much as it should (at a glance).That entertainment plus takes it before your dedicated operators deploy the magnificent props and get into some laboratory high-tech so that millions of white crabs move a boat by the sand of the desert, which is (by far) the best scene of the tape and almost the complete series, at least for this already talludito chroniclerOf course.Not can one go to the cinema with the certainty that is going to have a bad time. In any case, unless we have the age of my son (10 years) going to lose - that with a small mouth - two hours of our always precious time, we could well have consecrated to admire the granitic purity of the Bogart of his best black series of 1940s or the Magisterium by Siodmak in turning a vulgar melodrama of fumetti (only heaven knows it)(, Imitation of life) in a dramatic prodigy worthy of the best classics. But we do not desabarremos and return to the nervous crab and deception filibuster, the slippery script and the (burdensome) excessive accumulation of branching stories that ultimately impedes an easier understanding of the primary narrative material. And after all, we have a movie made for teenagers. Or is not really so?The meritorious fascination of images override all lowercase reluctance. There are scenes of a breathtaking plasticity, worthy survive in the memory of moviegoers without prejudices and less demanding public, in general. I would like to (and sometimes costs, I know) be spectator more easy happy. The ship in the sand, the sampán flying between stars or the condemned souls that sail in "chalupas" a dark sea of ululantes omens and wonderful mysteries, dialogue with the living, are pastillitas with hear on this lengthy collection of patchwork that just, for work of a lit editor and a certainly responsible direct, in a passable filmdiscreetly passable, when (at the sight of the herein and felt) might be a monumental roll, an affront to the adventure film and a discredit to the intelligence of these adolescents who religiously pay a good handful of euros that industry (that cuasifantasmagórico body) will shape the imagination and build them, in the absence of Julio Verne, Robert Louis Stevenson or Emilio Salgarian accessible inventory of heroes.The great machinery of special effects and humor go to trompicaba genuine and playful the arguments of the previous installments here dwindles outrageously. There is no continuity, but some complicity. Those who have not seen these tapes very bad lead him to get into the skin (scabs and pustules, if you prefer) of it. It was perhaps my case. I got lost in the story and had to be rescued several times to reconnect with the plot and get away at the end, so happy always.Identification with the characters (any child or juvenile literature of quality Foundation) loses the bellows of yesteryear. Sparrow, the humorous and bufonesco captain, has been blurred and no longer of that profile hooligan, histrionic and loquacious and up the damsel of rank that becomes a pirate who plays sosamente Keira Knightley is lost, despite his WAD of lines in a ragbag plot, in excessive with the story that the forge and debt reduced to a fractured compendium of solvents sketches, but inevitably boring.There is a will of sophistication that annuls the primary mechanisms of the film pirates, impregnating the set of a perhaps unwise trend the grandiose spectacle without addressing the basic spirit of things, some simplicity highly desirable to excite, not overwhelm, to entertain without breaking the patience of the Viewer.The trilogy here completed his journey by box office and Windows of toys. Commercial exploitation does not terminate: the pirate continues its journey in the seas of the gain and the forging of a myth. The epics now operate differently: belong to languages less lyrical, although of a strength plastic brutal, devoid of references solid and based on literary models of height, sustained in entangled intrigues that strangle the fluidity of the frame and obstruct any possibility of true enjoyment.Last mention and separate mention is the disturbing presence of the legendary guitarist of the Rolling Stones, Keith Richards, who came to the set of filming drunk and little ductile to be carried away by the orders of the director. What they wanted?</body>
</review>
