<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Rec" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A save who can shot and played with great skill. Effective and forceful. A real Dragon Khan located in the interior of a tunnel of terror, with the only drawback that there are no harnesses or seat belt...</summary>
	<body>Jaume Balagueró I always has left me indifferent. Darkness was so loose that I sleep almost in the film (in fact, a colleague of mine did), and fear, rather little. Fragile was correctita, but not fulfilled, at least to me, his goal of acojonar; rather, it made me laugh, because the final bisho was a copy made wrong typical Spectra ghostly - overrated-Japanese horror, which is both fashion - copy-now. Not to mention OT: the movie. And the unnamed, yet have not seen.But REC, his last creation together with Paco Plaza, has left me fascinated. and mournful xD.El catalanovalenciano dynamic duo get recycle a genus which needed several electroshocks to pull in this entertainment business with great success. One of the top used for this movie, is the format of the fake documentary camera in hand, to what the project of the Blair Witch. And as I said, works.Currently, very little people is afraid to see four or five hungry zombie blood and viscera chasing staff. But as they have shot the film Balagueró and Plaza, get gives that whole (at least 98%) the room up to a climax of tension in darkness, hysteria, and uncertainty. Get the Viewer to be considerate and put nervous; It shrink in the armchair and cover the eyes. either to stay completely flabbergasted before the screening, without blinking and without losing any detail, no shadows, no fright. All ignore altogether where the shots go. Because we have a movie that has predictable situations that ultimately end up not being, then surprise you from behind. And that in a film of this genre is appreciated a lot.The pace is a non-stop; not it decays in no time. Only a quarter of an hour of relaxation in the eighty minutes of footage. The rest, a save who can shot and played with great skill. Effective and forceful. A real Dragon Khan located in the interior of a tunnel of terror, with the only drawback that here there, nor the witches have brooms to hit you, only his bare hands and their foul JAWS harnesses or seatbelts.We are, by its refined environment and because it is fucking great and entertainingly frightening, one of the best horror films of the Decade, and one of the best Spanish films of the year, making him shade in a way admirable aplaudiblemente to the commercial Titan for the orphanage.</body>
</review>
