<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Supersalidos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What about new old? Nothing, and much. The plot is very overused in this "genre", but the script (written by the same as the Nice "Virgin at 40") is cachondísimo.</summary>
	<body>It is not easy to convince someone that watch a movie like Superbad cannot be bad. More than anything because it's a film about teenagers, and clear, the prejudices many people to the movies about teenagers yearn for in life, for the moment, only desvirgar, are very strong. Myself I have. But among so much shit you can find mini IA as it is one called those University revelries, starring Luke Wilson and Will Ferrell, or even the first American Pie, which is not bad. And now, Superbad (Superbad), which has more or less the same as always, but in a rather peculiar way.The premise is very clear: in one of his last nights as university students, friends and misfits Evan (Michael Cera) and Seth (Jonah Hill) will experience a legendary Odyssey throughout an afternoon in which will try to buy drinks for a party. in which they planned, to the less Seth, wet that you and I know, for the first time, before going to the University what's new old? Nothing, and much. The plot is very overused in this "genre", but the script (written by the same as the Nice Virgin at 40) is cachondísimo. There are phrases or hilarious gags almost every minute, some good and even very good, and others something malillos, but oh, how you laugh. In addition, cast, except perhaps the girls, they interpret to perfection their roles, highlighting above all trio sobre protagonist (Evan, Seth and a piece of Misfit who calls McLovin - see photo-, the best of the film). And despite comic that becomes, has some component bittersweet and nostalgic about adolescence and the value of the fairly strong friendship, that it is noted especially in the final quarter, and that left me me Recalling billion things about that time during the rest of the day, putting me blandorro as a tontorrón.The major drawbacks are that, in some conversations, both sex saturated; and stretches far enough too (did we really have to leave both clowns policemen function?). In addition, the address is nothing another Thursday.But hey, fun and entertaining, without more.</body>
</review>
