<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Soñadores" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Wasteful, dreamers emulates many films, pays homage to many films, and although coated film of political and social commitment, is a sincere tribute to cinema, culture, wonderful and last instance.</summary>
	<body>By age and intellectual preparation, I lack the sentimental acquis that had allowed me to see dreamers with other eyes. Mine did not see the French May 1968. My hands not erected barricades. My pen did not write pamphlets and placards, incendiary prose to burn the routine and change the world. Nor I was born in Chicago in the violent 20 (the roaring as) and, on the other hand, I appreciate and me involved in film noir and patterns that explicit. In any case the French may, by cultural contamination or because of lack of it, is more far. Blame the must have our postwar policy, which led to Spain to isolationism by the work and grace of the warlord and his regime. It was more tolerable a mafioso docked a bank or that a couple of small-time criminals planted corpses of five States in the passage of his misdeeds as a revolutionary ideologist calmly proclaim from the rooftops their total objection to the law and their disregard for traditions, including God, the Church and the order established, usually by force.But Bertolucci, which is an old dog, has not clearly portrayed that world of University and commitment to freedom and progress policy. Or, at least, has not portrayed only that aspect of the plot, by others, tiny, almost negligible.The history of the two incestuous brothers who stay at an American University attraction to spend a few days in the apartment in Paris besieged by chaos (is that, at the end and all, which meant in those turbulent then the revolution: chaos, a release, combustion, a very planned disorder) becomes an exercise of sick sex, nostalgia, discovery of the own experience as an engine for the world and, above all, a fresh imposing on the construction of the ideals that enlighted the society in which we are. So much ambition sinks: just being demolished by a frivolous vision of things, barely attached to such high ideals. Dreamers is not the last tango in Paris, although some so it had to benefit of cinephiles of showcase. Dreamers is little thing at the bottom: three Brats with the settled life that entertain the time between ejaculation and progressivism, Cortázar's Rayuela and Charlie Parker records in the pick up. Correct in excess, although carnal in the demonstration of the gallant adventures of these three revolutionaries of divan, tape entertains, gives rise to an interesting discussion about what counts and that, not counting it, it hints. That Paris which created the Nouvelle Vague, the Paris Jazz and poetry of Baudelaire, the intellectual decadence and hippies dressed in terrestrial verses to the Whitman and a complete lack of prejudice in the sexual field (which Bertolucci gives good account with a trio delivered protagonist to stage this promiscuity without sin, that activism venereo that it was not only looking for tremor)(, the mere pursuit of pleasure but also the audacity of his execution, the recklessness of their propaganda).Commendable the Bertolucci stubborn in opening a door is not open almost never: of ideological cinema as a cultural label as a reference, as a sentimental treasure of generations who have learned to live and to love the movies. That makes it here, and does so with significant naturalness. Then there is the political aspect, the revolution that was then - walking distance from urn - a failure and became outburst to benefit of nostalgic inventory or, at best, as a matter of conferences and manuals on Social and political thought in the twentieth century, that thus forth. So the film is a parade of bodies who love, of bodies who love and speak of impossible characters (combines) exemplifying the oft cash and Honoree feeling of youth of the 68: sex, drugs and cultura.a lack of rock n' roll, less well seen to the bebop, blues or the song protest, more easily exchangeable into accessions genera. What happens is that these heroes only led his bourgeois sense of leisure, his instinct domesticated between four walls that exude anything except wanting to wanting to change the world.Isabelle, Theo, and Matthew are, to post, sacrificables pieces of magna opera that Bertolucci wants to show: his utopia is in the books, is in the film and in the halls of corridor after a school of philosophy in the University, but these utopias do not permeate society. The real revolution requires sacrifice, votive offerings, pieces that are inmolan to magnify the ideal, and they operate at a lower level (different, frivolous) occasionally, of minor relevance. Isabelle, a fractious Virgin, a vestal with explosive uterine dizziness, occupies lot screen. It focuses tour the full text of the tape. Eva Green is not Jean Seberg announcing the New York Herald Tribune in the streets. The young delivered to the ideal of the revolution is also a perverse girl who breaks taboos and ironworks, based on winks moviegoers and convoluted parliaments on freedom, ethics and political responsibility, his own desvirgue, which is performed by the best candidate, an American who was fascinated with the nattering pseudo-revolucionario and very well versed in Mao, John Coltrane or Chaplin or Keaton. The film is pure voyeurism. The culture also.However, a nice film, well hilvanada, devoid of fundamentalisms and occasionally corny, but dignified and attractive.</body>
</review>
