<review author="Alex Largo" title="Scoop" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is obvious that it complies with its mission as a comedy (you laugh) but you don't have enough "hook". Lacks it something. The film is certainly a "curious" exercise of film, a very well done comedy and is still a little flojona.</summary>
	<body>I'm not a connoisseur of the Allen film, in fact I am a complete ignoramus. It is more "Scoop" is the first film I see of the eccentric director.And I have to say that the movie I had. "surprised".Surprised at all. From a simple script, with the bad and the good that this entails (Yes, a simple script can be good), actors moving between right and those who are great in his role (straight talk: Allen is in the second group and the first everyone else).When I say that the film has "surprised me" I mean that the film is. rare? a comedy to dry? Not be how tell it, the truth, but it is, in plain, is a rare movie.It is obvious that it complies with its mission as a comedy (you laugh) but you don't have enough "hook". Lacks it something. Let's say that the film is a "curious" exercise of film, a very well done comedy and still is so. "plof".As I said, perhaps I am not best placed to talk about this film because I don't know the film of Allen. But in this film have found work good by actors (which not excellent, with the exception of Allen) and a good work by Allen after the cameras.In fact I would say that maybe the tape is everything that is incumbent upon Allen, since his character (who reserve the best quotes) to the script, part of an idea not good, but very good, and, although it develops and concludes well just. do disenchanted? No, disappointed is not the word. Imagine that they see a ship approaching from the horizon and say "Oh, go boat approaching", and when you have it on the side, is not as much as you thought you had to be but it doesn't disappoint. More or less this is the impression I get of the script, and by extension the film. I understand?</body>
</review>
