<review author="José A. Peig" title="Beowulf" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It reduces the soul of Beowulf a medley of Visual plagiarism when there is not the filmmaker, but production and the prefabricated idea.</summary>
	<body>In a translation from the literary language until the of the cinema, and more specifically in a gender motivated by laws of entertainment nowadays derive from a model that aims to restore the epic sense of the legendary adventure, sword and sorcery, the most important aspect is the created style - or create - that the written legend may have a significant film expression.Either because the original text does not have sufficient attributes, or because the adaptation lacks fluency and imaginative impetus, the truth is that Robert Zemeckis's Beowulf shows a texture warm and impersonal, a pure technological apparatus of dubious utility. What we want to digitize the human characters if this technique does not exceed - or not equals - the expressiveness of the real actor?. If the characters - since the same conceptual basis - are doomed to be clichés default in all their acts and words, use them as technological excuse is to trivialise the product from the surface to the potential depth.For dramatic purposes, the first fifty minutes contain elements of interest and the bulk of the epic intensity, while the final stretch is reduced to a digital circus starring the Dragon and the twilight King, to a logical conclusion and subtly embodied in the last game of plano-contraplano. This shows that we have a proper entertainment film, but that does not get its own framework to raise the dramatic intensity essential in this type of film, the end as apotheosis of mythical characters.Great work, Yes, photography and artistic design, producing an environment of legend in which we can glimpse a superfluous brushstroke (often with poorly explained details) about the error, lying, and the curse that pursues the Royal lineage, with as theme sexual promiscuity, and combating the myth that imprisons the mind of Beowulf. Pity that Zemeckis display reduced to a production of pure industry, with landscapes, flat, chopped and drawn from the trilogy banding Peter Jackson air progressions, 300, or the Galactic hexalogía of George Lucas. I.e. reduce the soul of Beowulf to a medley of Visual plagiarism when there is not the filmmaker, but production and the prefabricated idea.</body>
</review>
