<review author="Bloody Will" title="Super Nacho" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a Jack Black, but Jared Hess film written and directed by what their mood touches the absolute idiocy, and can fall from grace in Spanish public.</summary>
	<body>If I said, nothing good comes out of the Jack Black-Jared Hess hybrid. I don't want to do advocacy of alcoholism, but a couple of mixed drinks, two or three compadres and eager to joke are necessary to hold the film from beginning to end.The director of the invention is also President of "Napoleón Dynamite", and met with a boom unexpected after becoming the film cult for the "losers", nickname are typical losers geeks of movie of American Institute.That does not mean that it was good, and the bad news is that Hess so believed, giving it carte blanche for this product is now "Nacho Libre", entitled of incomprehensible manner as "Super Nacho", perhaps looking for the morbid thematic superhérose, which completely lacks, and leads to a severe delusion to the Viewer.A simple summary: come to the cinema with the mind blank, if not, her odiaréis you. A folio and half is no script, and the first 20 minutes contain as much 6 complete sentences, everything else are grimaces and poses of un-day so-called King of comedy, Jack Black, removing that verbiage that made him so well-known. His throne falters in favour of Will Ferrel, which also premiered film this weekend in Spain. I will like to know by who opts the cañí public.What we are going, Ignacio (Jack Black) is a monk of Mexican village that plays the role of chef in an orphanage. His dream however is to be star of Mexican wrestling, that put on Galavisión on Sunday afternoon, and that that fight was a real circus. With the help of a real tiráo, (Hector Jimenez) will form the duo Nacho-Esqueleto, plundering sticks everywhere, but very well paid. At the same time it tries to impress the nun cañona (Ana de la Reguera) from the orphanage, will fight to reach the combat with more superstar of the fight and get money to orphans.Piece argument, simpleton over not being able to, and that effortlessly fills the entire footage from the tape. The best moments gives them the magnificent Hector Jimenez, which only has teeth and eyes, hence the right nickname of skeleton. What they volean up and down, while the Black belly can do much to save him.Atypical comedy to more not being able to see without complexes or pretensions. Not espereis chuckle I constantly is not such. If not cojeis to the grace principle, you shall not do this throughout the film, and you seem it long as none. It is not at all the type of comedy that has made Jack Black over these years, and I stress, it is not a Jack Black, but Jared Hess film written and directed by what their mood touches the absolute idiocy, and can fall from grace in Spanish public.The penalty is to lose something fundamental: the efforts of Black to speak at inglés-mexicano, which is the only thing really funny film. Dubbing it will turn into "manito" meat, "andele" and other mustache arrocet coletillas.A note: my wife fell into a deep sleep after 10 minutes of psicodélica-mejicana environmental musiquita with Black circulating on a motorcycle. I followed until the end of incomprehensible for her form. So is this movie: you look like a stone is going to your head, but you did not take off.</body>
</review>
