<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="La Sombra del Reino" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ambiguous tape on a topical theme.</summary>
	<body>Little convincing work after cameras of the actor and director Peter Berg, which tries to guess, contribute their bit, for general reflection to a topical subject, as it is the spread of international terrorism. He tries from the point of view of pure action cinema, where the suspense and intrigue are its two powerful weapons. Powerful on paper, but that on this occasion not seduces much to say, given the farragosidad of the speech, as well as its socio-political ambiguity.It is also narrated in a nervous manner, often wanting to give the impression that everything happens to forced marches, with dramatic tension that makes everything be speeded up, as it would be normal in a topic where terror causes death and destruction where you want to go.For this reason uses a montage I guess tell Berg is vertigionso, but is actually something sickening, with plenty of close-ups free in my opinion. The script is not very successful, and there are quite a few moments killed by its central part that make the pace to decay.Luckily, at least we will know better the character of Colonel Faris Al-Ghazi, which in my opinion is the best character, beautifully played by Ahraf Barhom long. Their loyalty, honesty, courage and sense of Justice, are indeed commendable and it is to appreciate really. The best is undoubtedly its last part, where the pure and simple action takes over, finally, the whole shebang. Is shot with lively pace and although they continue to see some dark levels, at least the dramatic intensity is achieved, to reach a final decision quite acceptable, with that double whisper into the ears of the protagonist to her partner and the grandfather to his grandson. A whisper that clarifies what really constitutes the essence of terrorism and the actions of the special groups that are fighting against him too often: the revenge.Ultimately, as action movie can be entertaining, but that don't like absolute itself has tried to make us reflect on a burning issue that threatens us all alike.</body>
</review>
