<review author="Bloody Will" title="Maleficio" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will happen to the story as the film terror of the 2006, but with so much crappy Exorcist come less and nonsensical remakes, is appreciated more than consistent argument.</summary>
	<body>First before, pure lie and lasts of the TV spot that promotes the premiere, a hoax blatant to the Viewer. So that in 1818 not be what a curse, and is repeated in the present is the furthest of the essence of the film. The film is set in 1818, so you do not fall into my error: wait and see when it starts to happen the same in the current era, because it takes 50 seconds, as much of the footage.That said with the slap to the distributor already I can say one thing, would "The prophecy" of 2006 have maintained the tension as does "El Maleficio". Remove you a thing of the mind, this film is not "The Exorcist", or "The prophecy". You will not see heads turning nor possessed assassins. The girl running through the Woods on the announcement seems "Texas Chainsaw Massacre", and that, nothing at all. In this film the holder body goes beyond violating horrible torture in its objectives, and you can discover it as it passes the story and you acercáis at the end.Based on real facts (such as the teleplays of antena3), it tells the story of John Bell (Donald Sutherland) after violating the rules of his Church to the detriment of a neighbor, blame you this both to him and to his hijia. After this curse, the younger, Betsy Bell, will start a real calvary of possession which will bring the head to his mother (Sissy Spacek), brothers, and even a local teacher. But not everything is what it seems, and being evil has a role to play.It is true that the movie is full of clichés. Perhaps the interpretations are not just magnificent, and the use of a Steady-cam as a trick to give life to the spirit of the film is something chabacano. Even so, and as I said before, the tension is maintained effectively during the greater part of the footage. Those films whose surprise unveiled very at the end, is what is appreciated after warmed-over end where, with a prayer and holy water, everything ends.Once notified of the deception that can induce its trailer, get to the idea that it is a film that you hàra hang out, without great special effect and nothing to make a summer blockbuster, so it is a way of escape to both palomitero product.It will happen to the story as the film terror of the 2006, but with so much crappy Exorcist come less and nonsensical remakes, is appreciated more than consistent argument.</body>
</review>
