<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If it separates the straw of the facts dealt with in the film of the substantive arguments, the tape builds a solid speech about the growing social apathy in relation to those who govern us.</summary>
	<body>The Filmography of the director Robert Redford seems to be subconsciously equidistant of the Redford actor. Aware of having abandoned years ago his iconic role as seductive irresistible, this legend of the Hollywood star-system seems to want to prove that he has much say as director, something already proven notable prior work as a Quiz Show, the river of life or ordinary people. Now, with a tape clearly thesis and theatrical structure, Redford wishes to clear his opinion about the current political moment of his country. The imminence of elections to which Bush son no longer appear seems the main wake-up call that led to this tape. However, in the words of its Director, Lions for Lambs is intended to go beyond the socio-political situation in their arguments.And in my view that manages to go beyond mere criticism circumscribed to the questionable international role played by USA in the era post-11S. In fact, if separates the straw of the facts dealt with in the film of the substantive arguments, the tape builds a solid speech about the growing social apathy in relationship to those who govern us and build our destinies as peoples. It is true that Redford suffers from an excess of bias and builds stereotyped characters to lend the Ember to its sardine. But so too his brief footage seems to be designed to stay with a unique idea and avoid losing other accessory.Probably, the tape would receive a better grade if a play were, the environment where the Matthew Michael Carnahan script would have felt more comfortable. But I do not think that it is a waste of time to attend its screening. First, to ratify the existence of a dissenting public opinion of the Bush Administration's policy. Second, to attend a healthy exercise of self-criticism among a society that we condemn it as arrogant and overbearing. And third, to enjoy a splendid acting duel between two great as Meryl Streep and Tom Cruise. Magnificent, and dusted some of his best work as the Magnolia, is Cruise in his role as political leader capable of terrifying with its decisions and seduce with its magnetism in similar proportions.Although it is not a film for posterity, the viewing of Lions for Lambs is only advisable in these times.</body>
</review>
