<review author="Plissken" title="Rec" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Balagueró and Plaza point somewhat large base to the public what it wants (video games, realities, morbid...) and add one accurate bad baba and a terrifying final stretch.</summary>
	<body>21St century: leisure, as we knew it, has changed. People no longer confined to watch shows, being the passive subject of the already outdated audiovisual media. Instead, he has discovered the interactivity of the game, and more and more and more consumers opt for this fun way to pass the hours. Aware of this, Paco Plaza and Jaume Balagueró, Luis Berdejo have created 'REC', a cinematic experience closer to the reality we perceive today that the vast majority of films released this year. And this has double merit when 'REC' is a tape of terror, zombie subgenre. Almost nothing.The initial overview, no credits, no music, no nothing, you immersed in the experience to the first round: Ángela and Pablo, two reporters from the local TV program ' while you can sleeps ', cover a night's work at a barracks of firefighters from Barcelona. The first call of the night leads them to an old building where an elderly woman is scaring, with her screams throughout the neighborhood. And in barely a few seconds Ángela and Pablo spend the routine work to witness an Apocalypse of neighborhood courtyard and fight for their lives (and their exclusive).The big bet of Balagueró and Plaza in this "survival horror" film is not constant terror or the oppressive atmosphere, but a tremendous amount of bad milk bathed in reality, and seasoned large-caliber scares and homages to the genre. While the proposal recalls 'The project of the Blair Witch', the big difference is their kid sense of humor and review intendionado to all the common places of the subgenus: Group of diverse, dead characters that revive, blackouts, shoddy survival plans, shortage of weapons, isolation. There is time for everything in the most entertaining of recent Spanish film eighty minutes, even, how not, for terror, which ceases to make intermittent appearances to settle permanently in the stunning (and full of clichés, also) the last twenty minutes of history.The absolute protagonists are a splendid Manuela Velasco, giving life to an Angela in the other hands could have done 'Rec' a disaster, and Paul, of which I speak later. The rest of the side, with the exception of some less realistic time, get you enter perfectly in the joke that we see every day in the 'happening', for example.In the technical section, Pablo Rosso, director of photography and camera real and "Pablo the camera" in fiction deserves special mention. Its excellent double work, technical and interpretative, is something that is overlooked when analyzing the film, and a key element of 'REC' seems to me: never go to the character, so you now to the character. You, the Viewer, you're Paul, the camera, and are always in the first line of fire. Any amateur video games will know what I mean. Among the other sections include the shocking FX and makeup of Inside FX, which have the added difficulty of look magnificent in the midst of a plane sequence, camera on his shoulder and an anticinematográfica light. Chapeau for them.And in the negative section, apart from the less spontaneous interpretative moments, could just cite the drawbacks of the aesthetics of home video: lacklustre flat, dizzying movements or chaotic sound. But it would be an exercise in cheap hypocrisy to criticize these aspects, because they are elements that give the necessary credibility to the whole.In summary: Balagueró and Plaza point somewhat large base to the public what it wants (video games, realities, morbid.) and add one accurate bad baba and a terrifying final stretch. Objective fulfilled, gentlemen. 9.</body>
</review>
