<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Bee movie" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It has certain effect and a corrosive acidity coups in some of their dialogues, but these small conatuses of genius naufragan in the meaningless sea of brilliance and originality which is, broadly, the Dreamworks film.</summary>
	<body>Bee movie is the new film by Dreamworks.Dirigida by Steve Hickner and Simon j. Smith, and based on a story of comedian Jerry Seinfeld, the film features the voices of Jerry Seinfeld himself and Renée Zellweger, in our country dubbed by Arturo Valls and María Adánez. the film account history of Barry B. Benson, a bee newly Graduate University found something disappointed your current occupation: making honey. One day he meets Vanessa, a florist in New York. Their relationship begins to flourish and, after discovering that humans steal honey bees then for comecrcializarla, Barry decides to sue them.It seems that, at least in this 2007, Dreamworks has been in the wake of Pixar, its direct competitor. Titles such as Shrek the third or this Bee movie have nothing to do next to this little gem of animation that has meant be Ratatouille, and even the purported largest desparpajo nor that acidity characteristic of the factory Spielberg have been able to deal with rival global product. So happened with the loose third installment of the, on the other hand, still profitable OGRE green, and little more than the same occurs with Bee movie, even though it is a somewhat more complete than its predecessor tape.Bee movie has really unforgettable moments, certain master effect blows, constant references to the world of the show and a corrosive acidity in some of their dialogues truly intelligent but, unfortunately, these small conatuses of genius naufragan in the meaningless sea of brilliance and originality which is, broadly, the film of Dreamworks.Siguiendo with maritime metaphors, could say that Bee movie will drift over your footageas if never achieved find North, with a story that changes course on several occasions without reaching fruition in no time. By the way, the dialectical spark of comedian Jerry Seinfeld makes us glimpse in lontananza something genius, timely blows of rudder which pretend to put course to land, but who are unable to avoid that the film should be into the sand in an I want to and I can not.Bee movie, as I said, seeks to both have fun effect blows and gags punctual as send a message of hope for all those who feel trapped in the world around them, noble intention (somewhat moralistic, although most of the films of animation pequen, even the focused supposedly more mature audiences), but fails to materialize at any time. Or gags with characters known as Sting or Ray Liotta, nor the humanization of an animal society (which we have already seen in other titles from Dreamworks as Antz, Chicken run or British) or acidic comments appearing intermittently in the film get rid of a desazonadora feeling that tells us that Bee movie not known at any time towards where you intend to go.As well, however, is a fun, with specific truly hilarious moments film dialogues occasionally uncouth and intelligent, but they seem to give off even a greater moralina than competitor products. In addition, the dubbing of Arturo Valls does not help much, the truth.I give it a 6 out of 10.</body>
</review>
