<review author="Bruji" title="Encantada: La Historia de Giselle" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After an intereante approach, the writers appear as lost as the Princess of tale in the current New York.</summary>
	<body>After titles mythical as Mary Poppins (1964) or the witch freshman (1971), the Disney pursues relentless new history that will mark the children of another generation of moviegoers. So far, between pajaretes and ratoncicos, that of Giselle is lost between the simplicity of form and the chaotic complexity of the content. "A tale too long" for children. For adults, a sympathetic disappointment.In the words of a movie fan six years beautiful, "a witch who lives in a fairy tale, pushes a Princess, who also lives in the tale, by a well, and the Princess appears in reality." Who, because of age, have seen some movies, and not rarely, not discern so clearly the line that separates the reality of what is not within the screen; We remind you that, in the history of the cinema, never missed characters that, vagaries of the script, eventful vicissitudes of fate or unfortunately charms, erred in world. Some authentic deities of exuberant forms, left Olympus to, in the form of Ava Gardner (Venus was woman, 1948) or Rita Hayworth (the goddess of the dance, 1947), make dream to mortals. Others, naïve girls of flesh and blood, is simply lost on a path of yellow tiles, traveled by "Lions, Tigers, Panthers, my God!", he would take them home (the wizard of Oz, 1939). And even those who adapted to her new life, resisted to undertake the path of return, Kate and Leopold (James Malgold, 2001) or mannequin (Michael Gottlieb, 1987). In the case of Encantada, we must seek immediate references in the classic Disney Animation. In the poisoned Apple that offers snow white, the wicked witch in the shoe of glass and the pajaretes couturiers of Cinderella, and the conviction that "a lovely day, the Prince vendrá" had Aurora when it was still not sleeping. Course, to adapt the story to put in the 36 corner with the 48, the glass becomes a model of Manolo Blahnik, the fairy godmothers are replaced by Golden credit cards and the offer of princes soars. Even Giselle is highest, more stylized and redhead than any of its predecessors. A kind of Ariel who lost the infantilism with fins. The first part of the footage offers a history of the old style of Disney's animation. A short story that crowns the three acts that comprise an excellent mount and that, as it could not be otherwise, is resolved with too much precipitation. However, the end turns out to be just the beginning, and the fall of Giselle by the moat, which fails to impair the opportunities of the protagonist to achieve happiness, does manage to truncate all the possibilities of the film to emerge from the mediocrity. And we can say that, after an interesting, although little original approach, the writers are as lost as the Princess of tale in the current New York. In its second part, the Royal, the plot is based and is reduced by the creation of obvious situations comic, of whom unfolds in a Habitat that is not ("would someone kind enough to tell me the way to the Palace?"), conducted by a reckless character that insults the intelligence, and giving way to the incursion of animated beings who have lost the magic and displayed as static figures of paintings on the wall. Good intentions be tarnished with the clumsy and scarce musical numbers, or perhaps the overwhelming simplicity that hides a dangerous message: are foster evil the brides parents?. A question that is not cleared in the chaotic denouement, which, after two hours of unbearable product, in a who's coming, who stays?, makes a superhuman effort to ensure that all eat partridges,-matters little how-forever never. Of course, the film causes furor in USA. It is normal that those branded "smoke" the innocent Sesame Caponata correct the behaviour of a girl adopts rats as pets, make dresses with the curtains in the lounge and sings through the parks. Although, of course, a good thing emerges from all this as we listen to a fragment of the soundtrack of the Little Mermaid "I want to see something special, I want to see a beautiful dance.", enjoy the majestic costume, or find the security that nothing is as powerful as a kiss of true love. And it is that romantic love is only a fantasy. unless you fall in love you. Within the cast, the bland performance of the egocentric Prince and the formal correction without the Prince of the advocacy Fund, they are outweighed by the impressive staging of Susan Sarandon and the know-how of the delicious promised of Leo DiCaprio in catch me if you can (2002). She, Amy Adams, the Oscar-nominated by Junebug of Phil Morrison, stands out in a history of exhausted resources to become its unique appeal. And just when you start to scare the idea of insensitivity, be too major to allow that the Disney Magic crosses the hearts, a small "minimoy" suggests behind me that "this is a very long story". Perhaps that is the essence of the criticism that I was looking for.</body>
</review>
