<review author="José A. Peig" title="Rec" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If any quality could have this film is its significant capacity to create the atmosphere. But after the first sequences of horror, it stagnates in a few repetitive efectistas tricks, thus the narrative becomes repetitive and mechanical.</summary>
	<body>Jaume Balagueró and Paco Plaza present us this new immersion in the myth of the "loss of the soul", which removes many unconscious fears in humans, fearful of degenerate until losing the humanity, and that in the cinéfaga culture has taken the form of the zombie, mostly (since Romero Lamberto Bava, Argento, Stuart Gordon), or the other great classic and which have recently spoken on these pages, the invaders of bodies.The Fund is always the same, although the plot pretext varies and it can go thematic ranging from science fiction to the religion or the sociological ínfula. Balagueró and Plaza proposal refers to more than one reason, but, however, the intention of the authors is not build a parable about collective psychosis post-9/11, but a reality show of horror that induces a one-dimensional and permanent record of sensations.The film opts for a disproportionate strident tone, puts so much emphasis on being "realistic", in the end, the critical Viewer discovers easily emptiness behind the feeling. Cinema of sensations, feeling of fear, with passages loaded with a murky and insane horror. If any quality could have this film is its significant capacity to create the atmosphere. But after the first sequences of horror, it stagnates in a few repetitive efectistas tricks with which the narrative becomes repetitive, mechanical, and under a visual treatment and a few without intentions of singularity (Blair Witch Project, among others). Another rule of thumb for intelligent but cheats filmmakers: If you don't have imagination to develop the story without falling into the esquematismos, can increase the intensity of the induced sensations. Thus, at least nobody can say be a boring film. It is not. But, although the feeling is the foundation of the horror film, the history of this film genre has shown that it is more than that. The human set offers some nuances about the reactions in extreme situations, addressing attitudes such as selfishness, empathy or xenophobia with a commonplace treatment, almost a routine to try to save - without success - clear plain of this expression Mannerist and plagiadora.</body>
</review>
