<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Apocalypto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Expect a Hollywood movie with a character &#8220; anthropological and documentary &#8221;, is to my unwise and other pretentious.</summary>
	<body>Good movie it!. Directed by the actor, director and producer Mel Gibson tells us a small piece of life of the legendary Mayan culture. If no more than assume the theme chosen by Gibson on this occasion; This film is missing in their pockets many points in its favour, narrate and be a thousandth part of everyday Mayan life is something quite interesting. However, Mel Gibson as you would with his other film the passion of the Christ, in Apocalypto are very well chosen every one of her scenes and displayed with such passion, that delves into what each character should reflect: his anguish, their fear, their pain. and visually described in a fascinating way. So much so, that the film without long parliaments and a simple argument, through the images surrounds us in its history.This is already a feature of Gibson movies and that is why they are so pleasant to go see on giant screen. Apocalypto is thus a movie that moves you, keeps you expectant throughout his life; as well, generate you a duality by showing us a "dark side" of that culture, with great fame and importance for humanity for his great contributions; as the calendar and as advanced concepts in such complex subjects as astronomy, mathematics, physics, etc., that is, perhaps, a bit difficult to understand even more today, full of "civilization". I.e. once more Gibson generates controversy. The controversy is there, and you want to tell us the other face of the Maya. In fact, this film has been accused of racist and little faithful to reality. You are Mexico and Guatemala course, where there are still descendants of this culture, views have not been different and many voices have been heard in this regard. They accuse it of being a violent, extremely barbaric and racist film that puts the image of the Spanish colonists by end of the culture, making them see as saviours of the same.In this regard, I think that their perceptions are exaggerated. We forget that this is a "Hollywood" film, that what is intended is usually show the spectacular nature of the film and where you cannot get and carry the public Viewer. Expect a Hollywood movie with "anthropological and documentary", is for my a bit "silly" and pretentious. Truth or not, exaggerated or not, this is a movie that made the imagination of Gibson and is a sample of good movies, and of course, the type of film that fills the box office.</body>
</review>
