<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Ases calientes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite the fact that it makes use of many aspects seen in other films, this story has much authenticity, footprint that wanted to impose and print its director is notorious.</summary>
	<body>Ases Calientes which he returned with the tape after the successful Narc movie of the year 2002 which chronicled the corruption of a police agency and made worthy to its director, Joe Carnahan, the Sudance Festival spirit award, and like the previous one, is its director and screenwriter. NARC was a film obasionada by the critics of recognized media written as "The New York Times", "Detroit News", "The New Yorker" among others.The previous film of this director was catalogued as a fairly complex drama and with the same nickname we can describe this new tape. "The last letter" title which is known in my country, is a film loaded with information, with an endomoniadamente agil, frenetic pace and action 100%. Since the beginning, already becomes inevitable fact evoke tapes as "Pulp Fiction" in 1994 and the sagas of "Kill Bill" 1 and 2 of the years 2003 and 2004, both of Quentin Tarantino. This happens not only by the Enigma that is handled, but for resources as black humor and al gore that in both cases, were so well delimited and use was so subtle suprementamente that never get to do uncomfortable to the Viewer; in fact, they give you one condiment for this film loaded with many elements at the same time. I'm not the only one to see "smokin' 'ace' reminded the Tarantino films, but if there are very few those who value the fact that the director dared to draw their own version of the tarantinesco genus and for this reason see it as one more copy. To my I particularly liked that he converted to the last letter in a revenge to the American very well thought-out and teaches us to introduce the use of gore in a subtle way is valid for whom we are not so happy of the.On the other hand how much rescue as the director tells the story; He weapon all a tangle in which involves an infinite number of characters with which enriches the plot, characters some more famous than others but with a profile very well marked and worked. From the experienced Andy Garcia, Ryan Reynolds, Ray Liotta, Jeremy Piven and the rookie singer hip-hop Alicia Keys enjoyed generally good performances. Bad debut of Keys by the way. Different thing with Ben Affleck who neither I mention because his appearance in the film is little and definitely does not convince me. With regard to Piven who plays Body, should be trained by an expert and so told with advice from a Scottish magician R.Paul Wilson and even as part of the entretamiento was a member of one of the most popular shows in Hollywood at the Club "The Magic Castle". Thanks to this arduous preparation, we can enjoy real scenes in which this actor shows us his ability acquired with the handling of the letters. Mounting and photography also are a highlight of the film. The shooting kept his magic filming in Lake Tahoe, a huge and Crystal Lake located between California and Nevada and was also scene of Coppola in the film the Godfather Part II, as also a place of recreation of Sinastra and his closest friends. Great tape is despite assemble everything a plot enredadísima with which it is sometimes mislead the public, in the end does not disappoint, because with immense ease with which grandmothers desenredan the strings of a seam, Carnahan Unveils us the final with an incredible surprise factor.Despite the fact that it makes use of many aspects seen in other films, this story has much authenticity, footprint that wanted to impose and print its director is notorious. A movie that I recommend for those lovers of action and gender políciaco. Hopefully will see more than once to enjoy it and understand it better.</body>
</review>
