<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Babel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film perfectly describes the differences generated by males due to our cultural roots, language and borders.</summary>
	<body>Babel is a very good film, the young Mexican director Alejandro González Iñárritu, which is already accustomed us to see good movies with their label. Other titles like "21 grams" in 1993 and "Amores Perros" of the year 2000, also confirm; In addition to these same films, are part of what he called the "death trilogy", according to the recent interview in "Critical eye" program of CNN in Spanish. Babel has been awarded the Golden Globe Award as best film drama, at the Cannes film festival, received the award for Best Director, and was also two award-winning "Gotham", afforded by the New York critics, and award gives recognition to the independent film. Now, it is one of the big nominees to carry one or more of the Oscar Awards. This film is nominated in 7 categories which include: best film, Best Director, best supporting actress, best band Sonara, etc.Babel is a film that represented quite a challenge for both the director and the cast, because it was carried out on three continents and in four languages. In fact, this is based the film; barriers generated by language and cultural differences. González cost a year to finish the filming of Babel and according to their same actors was all a journey physical and psychological, as they live each of his characters. In this regard and in his own words, this has said its director on the film:. "the best of Babel was that I started shooting a film about the gap between human beings, the physical and the language barriers, but along the way I realized that was making a film about what unites us"love and hatred. "It is very possible that what makes happy a Moroccan and a Japanese is very different, but what makes us feel bad is the same for all". And with regard to sharing this mentioned: "..." "It is one thing to lead actors in a language you don't know, but also is directed to people who are not actors in a language you don't understand."Regardless to this film is one of the big winners or not, on the night of the Oscars, I recommend seeing this movie, I hope, on the "big screen". It describes perfectly the differences generated by males due to our cultural roots, language and borders. Not particularly I attach to you excellent rating, because its end left me wanting to see a final palpable, seen and not one that the viewer imagine. I wanted to really know what happened. But the two films that are part of this trilogy, can go to see her without a problem have been. But I really recommend to do so, in particular 21 grams with Sean Penn, Naomi Watts and Benicio del Toro who qualify for excellent.</body>
</review>
