<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Cerdos salvajes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film many unpretentious and simple to disconnect a little routine, stop to rest the mind of concerns, bad times, etc and have fun.</summary>
	<body>I will not dedicate many lines to this film, because this new film by director Walt Becker nor warrants. I can tell you then, it is a slight but quite fun Ribbon. It is not to see the strictly critical perspective; then do so, the film happen without penalty or glory and insurance "was not the exam". Rebels with a cause is a single film without many pretensions to disconnect a little routine, stop to rest the mind of concerns, bad times, etc and have fun. In fact, not forces you too though, to be absolutely vigilant, you does not exhaust. It is in quiet short, relaxed and fun.The cast is luxury, all very recognized in the world of cinema, highlighting the actions of William Macy for me. Its subject matter is interesting, since thinking in a "fifties" who want to give a "Canaanite in the air", can be very identifier for some, reflective and motivating others. Who perhaps does not reach that stage of life, where probably many things have been left to be done, where absorbs it the everyday or their prejudices and fears not let him, to think of giving this chance to have a good time with old friends. Well there then, does this argument, comedian, crazy and something different. The film then based on this idea, creates 4 characters: one odontológo, another an unemployed, another a computer programmer and the latter an expert in security, all with same denominator; oppressed by the pressures of everyday life, decide to go then, to an appointment with if same, leaving aside, their families, their children, their jobs, cured in their bikes a journey without equal, unique and probably unique. Who isn't like you do the same, at any time of your life?There are many moments in what really you loose to laugh almost non-stop. Given the genre, this is a major success of the tape. Finally to be honest, I do not recommend it go see movies. As always I say, in these cases, this is to enjoy at home</body>
</review>
