<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Diario de un escándalo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The final seal of this film is determined by his music and so they used an important composer, Philip Glass, characterized for being manimalista when composing his scores.</summary>
	<body>This film to come out of Billboard this week ending in country, and that in the majority of other countries was released between March and April of this year with the exception of United States; was a film nominated for 4 Academy Awards; Best actress, Dame Judi Dench, best supporting actress, Cate Blanchett, best adapted screenplay and Best Original score. Although it won none of these awards, recognition through them is more than deserved.Diary of a scandal is a film adaptation of the novel with the same name published in 2001 by Zoë Heller. The film is directed by Richard Eyre, known for its Iris 2001 film, winner of several awards, including the Oscar and Golden Globe, which also starred Judi Dench. Like the majority of tapes that are adaptations of a novel, the more difficult for its director was to simplify what has been considered a novel dense, in a script that covers everything contains it over their pages. Diaries of a scandal, is a rugged of a teacher, hard, dry and rough narrative whose obsession towards his best friend; also Professor, and the secrets that both hide, carried thinking, schemed and handle various situations. Judi Dench, Barbara, who narrates and turn intrepreta writes the history. Their role is certainly exceptional. Another Professor, is Sheba Hart, starring Cate Blanchett, who in his interior, hides a terrible love story; After support romance with a student of only 15 years. Of course Blanchett, turns out to be the perfect companion in the great performance by Dench. In fact confirm both nominations in the past Oscar.No doubt that there are many positive aspects of this movie; for example, without seeing me the novel, the adaptation of the script for me, is accurate, it is a film that keeps you waiting all the time, which is very well defined the beginning, development and end, that they are very well taken. All this accompanied by a perfect setting for the tape, with a photography and lighting very well achieved. And to accomplish this, they used two important elements; the scenario was mostly recorded on the outskirts of a coastal region of London (Eastbourne), and on the other hand, the majority of its scenes were recorded with hand-held camera, which allows to give spontaneity of movements. The final seal of this film is determined by their music, and in doing so they used an important composer, Philip Glass, characterized for being manimalista when composing their scores; i.e., it uses few sentences that are repeated. Among the works featured in the film are: El Thruman Show (1996), the hours (2002), Opera (2003) and the illusionist (2006).I reiterate that this is a very good tape, which tells the obsession of a teacher, after his solitude; authentic reflection of nowadays living residents of large cities. Diary of a scandal has been catalogued sensationalist, because in fact his title does honor to its theme. A scandal of vast proportions, but that for nothing is far from the reality.</body>
</review>
