<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="El buen pastor" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>De Niro, not passes the test in this film, as he had many tools in their favor to have brought forward a very, but very good film.</summary>
	<body>I have a duality with respect to this film. It seems to me something cruel about branding her regular, but I am not so convinced qualify good. The second film directed by Robert De Niro, after "A history of the Bronx" in the year of 1993, tells the story of the beginnings of the CIA, as also the link to the famous sect "Skull and Bones", whose members are the innate cream of the American aristocracy, those who manage the reins of that country and the entire world, the famous Yale University students and that they say, belongs all the descendants of the Bush family; in fact, this was one of the most difficult aspects, when it comes to carrying out the film, because as sect hide that he is, was not allowed to produce even take photos on the outskirts of the beloved cloister.Since the 1990s he joined De Niro document to carry out this tape. Passionate about the subject of the spies, the policy and as United States handles a culture secret and powerful when it comes to store information; He is interested in these characters hidden, sinister and loyal to your institution and above all the scope arriving to have, even at the cost of his personal life. In his search he met Milton Bearden a spy retired CIA, author of several books on this subject. He became instrumental in executing the tape; so much so, that led to De Niro to tour various cities in Asia and Europe to illustrate vividly and unveil some secrets.All this I have told them and the time of documentation which took De Niro to develop "The good Shepherd", was what I believe, it has resulted in a film too dense and complex, so confirm that their nearly three-hour (2: 47). Hence I can enumerate them several unfortunate events for a film with good idea or theme. The film is loaded with many "flashbacks", some unnecessary, apart, each event is so detailed that his Payan is "overly" slow care. This is the most outstanding in the film; This gap in the pace. A film, so dense and complex, full of flashbacks and so long, had set aside a good share of scenes with more action or emotion. The story is so cold and calculator at the same time it becomes cansona and heavy to assimilate.I am not criticising the cast, that of luxury if it seems. Dammon, Jolie, De Niro and others fulfil their quota in the tape had not been, it would have been much worse. I not give to his greater cast transcendence, because I find it inevitable to rely more on the intention of the film, his idea and how it was carried out. Summarizing them, De Niro, not passes the test in this film, as he had many tools in their favor to have brought forward a very, but very good film. The problem was then as the good Shepherd was carried out. I guess then the conflict represented for him and his scriptwriter to develop the script, to achieve a well summarized, synthesized tape and round, a real subject with invented characters.</body>
</review>
