<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Las vampiras" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The most prolific director of Spanish Cinema cult film, where a vampire he is eating what fancy you a chatunga. More bad to stick to a father with underpants I suda. To say that you've seen one of Jess Franco.</summary>
	<body>Director: Jesus Franco or Jess Franco, as they like.Duration: 89 minutes.Release date: 1973.Espectadores: 236.615 human beings.The other day was watching a video of Mariano Ozores (with an Esteso in a deplorable state, everything is said) and mentioned that there is a Spanish director who has made more films than he. Which would it be? What a thrill, what a thrill. Turns out that Jesus Franco changed its name to Jess Franco (he wanted to Jess Franc, but could not not be why) has made more than 150 movies. Nothing, nothing, let's see one of so illustrious director, think who like women in leather. "The vampiras", which in German is something lesbians vampiras that draw me much attention, which seems to arthouse.The film is (recognize that it may not be my version too faithful to the reality) of a girl that not be what happens. Total, a voiceover tells that a King (or similar) got his wife into a Palace to cal y canto to see if he died (the real divorce, which call it) with a hundred slaves. Time passed and the girl was more solid everyday and more dead slaves. Over the years, which seems to be the wife of the King (or similar, I insist) still nibbling the pescuezas to young girls that are provided.Let's see, I have not seen the entire film. And that salén aunts in pelotas eating bodies licking and lengüentás. But it is that it is unbearable. Flat amazing, as in the climax follarín of the players focus us a Scorpion walk (leave as 20 times), then a moth trapped in a network and other insect that I have deleted memory to get the cover of the brand today. Dialogs are the worst, with an argument that is understood, or hooks, or nothing at all. Come on, it is that it is unbearable, with what no wonder that has become something of a cult quickly.In short, the most prolific director of Spanish Cinema cult film, where a vampire he is eating what fancy you a chatunga. More bad to stick to a father with underpants I suda. To say that you've seen one of Jess Franco.Besitos.P.D: sensual levels the truth as to leave the hips to culetás, it is said in honor of the truth.</body>
</review>
