<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Bender´s Big Score" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>First of four DVD films designed for the Futurama series which is a breath of fresh air to the fans that we are left hanging with the suspension of the series. In my humble opinion, brilliant and essential.</summary>
	<body>Director: Dwayne Carey-Hill. duration: more than an hour and half, as five long chapters.Release date: 27 November 2007 directly on DVD. In Spain, God will say.After two years without new Futurama things (as they are responsible for telling us in the film) again with a lot of force. Instead of doing what they did the Simpsons to his film (I found is not equal to many chapters) have decided to snag a few stories about all the characters and get a hiperlargo chapter as great as the best in 22 minutes. Exactly what we wanted and we wanted the fans. Gracias.la film is about many things, but basically nudist guys get through spam techniques, take over Planet Express. But not only that, if that fail to gain control of Bender through a subtle and elaborate computer virus, in which everyone could chop (if piqué I the day that got me a window messenger type "Bea says: Hi handsome, do want to see my webcam?" that I almost assume the mouse of emotion, is that you can chop either). Finally, it is also (the best resolved I never saw) time travel, love, friendship and many things more. Very completita, if Mr.Well, needless to say I'm a Futurama fan and am thrilled with the result. The stories are very well engarzadas, without great loss of rhythm (perhaps the part of the narwhal is something rare), and with an interesting argument. Each of the characters in the series out with roles more or less long (too bad the doctor Zoiberg who does not have more interventions). We have many references to other films, such as the saga of the war of the galaxies and some more winks to the audience are welcome. Humor is always, although I would say that they have bolted and they have gotten jokes in the series I do not remember they dare, as the why Al Gore lost the election against Bush (great, sure the latter will make thank you very much).To sum up, first of the four DVD films designed for the Futurama series which is a breath of fresh air to the fans that we are left hanging with the suspension of the series. In my humble opinion, brilliant and essential.We must see it.Besitos.P.D: See original version brings curious things, as Bender is actually Spanish and many words said them in Spanish, such as beer.Pd2: In Spain at the moment it has no release date on DVD, but the American version has the subtitles in Castilian, which can make the investment.</body>
</review>
