<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Una canción del pasado" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting drama with remarkable human cargo and intellectuals, especially literary notes.</summary>
	<body>Interesting drama with remarkable human cargo and intellectuals, especially literary notes.The film is a good adaptation of the novel by Ronald Everett Capps. A history of secrets, mistrust, lack of affection and family memories, reproaches, redemption and love.The interest is on the rise according to spend the minutes that at first it takes to catch a little the tranquillo characters. We will little by little understanding them, as they relate each other. But it is true that costs a little enter situation, inter alia by the large but necessary and particularly consistent, provide intellectual, with abundant literary quotations, for whom is not placed in this, it can mean a setback in what regards to concentration. These appointments are, as I have said before, completely coherent, not in vain the two male protagonists are writers and for them the books are more important than the vida.o perhaps not.Good dialogues, a sober staging, without technical fanfare, with a very accomplished use of music and a beautiful landscape of New Orleans, although they cause real pain knowing how were and perhaps they remain, some of them after the catastrophe of the Katryna.Pero, without a doubt, the best of the film are its protagonists, above all John Travolta, perfect in his self-destructive charactera paragon of defects but intimate and emotional. "Scarlett Johnasson brings a certain maturity to his character and the plot, despite his youth, and the third in discord, the for me unknown Gabriel Macht, secunda les perfectly.""A song of the past" will not go to the history of the cinema, but that is a good showcase of human strengths and weaknesses that leaves a good taste in mouth, although it has its formal defects. But the dignity conferred the various characters of the film are sufficient to respect and give a positive mark.</body>
</review>
