<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El próximo Oriente" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the comedies most intelligent and fresh of recent times, with a cast of actors as unknown as wonderful and one of those scripts, exemplary and anthological, bringing memories of the great mess of Hollywood comedies.</summary>
	<body>I have a tremendous bitch with that expression, "tolerance", referring to immigrants. Being better than intolerance, of course, I do not think that be tolerant with foreigners and with people of another color and another race is sufficient. Tolerance means bear, admit and hold that they exist, but nothing more. Means leave them paragraphs, do not mix with them, draw a dividing line that separates us. We here and there, you quietecitos and annoy.However, there is a neighbourhood in Madrid, Lavapiés, which has taken a step that goes far beyond tolerance, as the great Fernando Colomo tells us in her delicious, refreshing, utopian, carefree and happy film "The Near East."Now that the Billboard is dying, with only Pirates of the Caribbean, all that we endure in August in the cities and support all those returning from vacation we go in droves to enjoy one of the most intelligent and fresh comedies of recent times, with a cast of such unknown actors as wonderful and one of those scriptsexemplary and anthological, they bring memories of the great mess of the classic Hollywood comedies.Two brothers. Cain and Abel. One is handsome, posh and trápala. She has left her lover blangladeshí pregnant and puts land of through, with his wife and daughters. The other is a pringao book. A clumsy and inept gordito with a heart so big that did not fit you on the chest. He will assume the role that his brother has fled by legs and consigned completely to the ins and outs of Islamic, traditional and conservative family of the Bangladeshi immigrants trying to survive in Madrid of the 21st century.With laughter, jokes, gags, replicas and contraréplicas to everyone more ingenious, chaotic and hilarious, Colomo speaks of themes as topical as the clash of civilizations, racism and xenophobia, happy tolerance, the exploitation of the poor, the fear of loneliness and immigration. And does so with a joy and a desparpajo showing that, to talk about the major issues affecting humanity, it is not imperative the get serious and solemn."The main characters are luxury, secondary, with the meat to the front, unpayable and actors who give life are up to colossal calling the script with a full of nuances and expressive interpretations.""Near East" is a film which claims, above all, the joy of living. One of those movies that you reconcile with the best cinema vindictive, critical and teller of the social reality of a country, but shot from humor, intelligence, wisdom, and experience by Fernando Colomo, a rare bird in the Spanish movie scene: this rolling what you want, that there are the stories that you want to and that makes it as you want.Dear Fernando, after laughing hinged jaw with "Near East" only have one thing to say: at your feet, master.</body>
</review>
