<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Redacted" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This mockumentary belonged to that style of films made to an audience that will see something risky, something that touches them and conciencíe. Do not miss.</summary>
	<body>Simply devastating last and unrecognizable RAID film the great Brian de Palma. While us has taught master's degree with some sublime untouchables or left indifferent with an unattractive dalia, already veteran director of the famous Scarface changes fully register to offer a truly stunning mockumentary, hard as a stone. Is entitled Redacted, which give the following meanings: "Edit or prepare to publish a corrected document that uncomfortable, confidential or personal information has been stolen." "Describe documents in which censorship has been committed". Yes, truly terrible and unjust is this Assembly that many bring between hands for not bringing to light certain atrocities. And this is the reality in which we live? Unfortunately, and well known by some (not all), Yes. Palm as a thousand directors, has transmitted to the public a plea against the war by something such as film, something which I think is necessary and very intelligent; but certainly has done something even more meritorious, and risk to such an extent that we ourselves want to cover us us eyes to see that images, because despite being, many of us, aware that occurs in Iraq, can not bear the raw and hard reality happening several kilometres. Nor is it our fault, but the true essence of the message that has been sent to us by the director.This mockumentary belonged to that style of films made to an audience that will see something risky, something that touches them and conciencíe. Palma makes a virtuoso travel, brutal and baffling at various times, to place the viewer in a world apparently known. There are many scenes, dialogues and Redacted pictures which we dipped in a naughty and manipulative universe: the stark reality. And the message I want to send is none other than the absolute recommendation for anyone who cares, although it may not improve the world in which we live. Do not miss.</body>
</review>
