<review author="Nisuyaves" title="Maleficio" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The worst thing I've seen for some time. Offers phrases as: "Be careful, the night is dark"... do seriously?</summary>
	<body>I do not usually see this genre of movies, and I reaffirm after seeing this desecration of the film. Consists of a curse that is to let you go cold on the girl child (he removed the blanket every few minutes) and hitting slaps! We are going to highschool with the poor Betsy.Unos believe that it is an entity, others not, some say "but have not seen?", others "not saw nothing", "her were slapped", "was with a cane" do?. you already imagine.But they still have time to think about marrying poor Betsy with 20 years older Professor. The film, to call it somehow gives us phrases for posterity like these: "Be careful, the night is dark," do seriously?Now is comuncica with noise "does that is a Yes or a no?" I assume. "When a witch of blood stain the clothes of someone, means that it is going to." "To what?" "you have to tell me."-We are cortitos eh!. And scenes of the more cumbersome as the typical religious ritual, reading the Bible, with the camera rotating in both directions.When the girl is playing with the spirit girl and that you miss water, hehe, you echo I tí, hehe, ahhhhhhhhh that you're a bad bug!Doors and Windows are closed, dizzying cameras, the fire which is aviva, the scene in bed as the Exorcist girl, eyes blank. at least the spirit sees in black and white, good from time to time.Ah! and has a scene flying, which Javier Bardem in Mar Adentro. Ignoring the "plagiarism" is the best there is, if it is a good thing that it can be drawn.Anyway, that in the end, nosé as tell it to not tell (forgive the redundancy), the case is that what hit you age., madremía to tontuna, but best of all is that history repeats itself, but well that kind of depraved parents there are in this world!Conclusion: The worst thing I've seen for some time.</body>
</review>
