<review author="Cp" title="Beowulf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An epic story, without many turns of script, direct, but why not simple nor boring. With heroic characters, but with all the possible sins. Technically impeccable, although I would have preferred a film in the style of 300. Recommended.</summary>
	<body>Okay, but &hellip;...That was my phrase anything more out of the film. Beowulf is a film that I liked, with quite epic, good characters, a simple story, without too many folds, where interesting thing is to discover each of the characters, their way of acting, his personality, his ideas, and even as they keep changing. In that regard, this quite well, not always must be given forty laps to make it to the script, traps and surprises, and above all, is an epic story. Beowulf is a hero, of course, is not afraid and is facing the bug as necessary, but also this lover of himself and of his legend, and does not lose opportunity to increase it. The other characters are quite archetypal, with intriguing and cowardly Advisor, the lecherous guerrero, the young Queen married the King old and decadent, but all have its history and its background, which makes them attractive.On paper, it is a very good movie, but everything changes when deciding like shooting her. The problem, at least for me, is the style used to shoot her. I have worked as a computer scientist doing 3D, and I like a lot, but even so, I just do not like the style of digitizing the performance by an actor. I prefer the system Final Fantasy based on an actor and do entirely digital or on the contrary, the style 300 of real players in a digital world. This clear that Beowulf achieves a great result, with beautiful scenes, funds and setting very well designed and worked and even the designs of strange beings very spectacular, especially the Dragon and the mother of Grendel, although of course, taking the curves of Angelina JOlie as a basis, already is a good start. But I just do not convince. Often, characters have very rigid faces and their movements not just be fluid. Above all, as said Gatonegro is noted in excess the rigidity of the hands, so much to pick up objects, as in the moments in which the character not used directly, lack them great expressiveness. Much to improve technology exceeds, in details as hair, for example, noted that spending hours in animation not reaches the level of Final Fantasy and its fluidity. This same movie with real actors, the same director, rolling exactly alike and all the effort of design scenarios and funds would have been an absolutely spectacular film.In short: Epic, direct, with characters that reflect another era in his act, well directed and mounted, would have been a film unbeatable, having followed the wake of 300 and place real actors in a world built digitally. Even so, a way of telling a story that hopefully will repeat.</body>
</review>
