<review author="Jokin García " title="Rec" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>REC turns out to be a good movie on the subject, quite realistic (within realistic which may be a film about undead) well done and with intensity and tension more than successful.</summary>
	<body>A Spanish film, zombie, the director of "operation triumph: the movie" and with an aesthetic that is a plagiarism of the Blair Witch Project. The truth is that with this letter many eludirán see this movie thinking that they will find a casposa cutrez and infumablePero nothing further from the truth. REC turns out to be a good movie on the subject, quite realistic (within realistic which may be a film about undead) well done and with intensity and tension more than successful. Proof of this is that the typical "insurance which will now happen such thing" scares get scare although it passes it seems that it will happen. More predictable scares get the start of the Viewer.The film raises a format which, without being original at all, is very bold, as it is shot entirely in the first person, and everything we see is through the House of a journalist. There will be anyone who says, and not without some justification, that it is not very credible journalist don't burn, and that the first zombie that camera just thrown on the floor, but hey, is a concession of realism for storytelling, which in this case is quite necessary. The approach is quite simple: a team of journalists; the reporter and the House, are recording typical agenda style "Mirror public" or "Street" (programmes of various stories) and the story leads them to the place where all the action takes place. And there, little by little, the thing goes from gradually "site where something strange happens" to "total crisis", as in every good movie genre.I dare to say that this film is going to be one of those movies that you love or you hate her, play with things quite experimental and there are details, although I particularly liked, likely to be bored. Not play very much in favour of the film, and that I mean, the beginning of the movie, where the first 10 minutes foreshadows a pain in the ass. But no, pain in the ass anything, the viewer who has a little patience will be with a great movie of great tension and completely claustrophobic.Worth as collateral that 7 people that we went to the cinema to you 7 seemed to us a wonderful film, and if we realize that we were a group of people with very different cinematographic taste, even sometimes conflicting, that should give some clue about REC.And well, curiously, it has the earmarks of those movies that win on the small screen, but nevertheless I commend to readers that non-crappy and see in the film, that the film deserves it.</body>
</review>
