<review author="Ram贸n Balcells" title="Rec" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A roller coaster truly stimulating, disturbing, terrifying until but not power; a real demonstration of cunning, devastating, really impressive. Brutal.</summary>
	<body>If there is something that fascinates me is the originality. For my own taste, [REC], lo nuevo de Jaume Balaguer贸 and Paco Plaza, is one of the most impressive cinematographic experiences of recent years. A roller coaster truly stimulating, disturbing, terrifying until but not power; a journey without end towards the most primitive of all human beings, a true demonstration of cunning, devastating, really impressive. Brutal.Su plot premise is simple. Now, the tandem of filmmakers get, through a prodigious camera in hand and an absolutely baffling credibility, the spectator experience this pure fear and ends up believing such seemingly ordinary history of zombies. And in addition, associating himself with terror, are costumbristas scenes of astonishing realism that associate them perfectly with our habitages, our habits. [REC] is probably one of the films more intelligent of the past years, since nor misleading, or resorts to any common topic in the recent film Spanish. It is, simply, an originality and boundless creativity. A perfect key to understand the film, something which should bring and be experienced by the Viewer. And without doubt, this film get something as big as introducing one, not in a conventional manner, but in devastating fashion. Someone like Balaguer贸, a director that I used, in his films, a subject as fear old-style, used here to something already not so little common today: bringing fiction to reality. Camera in hand, terror of the good, unforgettable and totally unexpected shocks, laughter, excellently written and interpreted characters, tension, grisly end &hellip; more can ask for? Because simply not make its remake, the Yankee thing unlikely, because it is already underway shooting. And it sounds really weird this that our ideas employed in Hollywood (the second Spanish wonder of the year, the orphanage, will also have its American version) to the point that "steal us" ideas. Do you know what? Worse for them. While we improve, they worsen. Something amazing, but as real as the wonderful film in question.Technically speaking, we could say that [REC] lies in something approaching the Summit of perfectionism. It could cross out unfinished, heady, its low budget, etc. But really isn't it the real way that the viewer experience the fear? If its principle might be an introduction to what it is going to happen, something calm and senzillo, its plot development is a real marvel of the unexpected, unforeseeable events and a rare strain. And then, as a final Fireworks, one of the outcomes more terrifying and overwhelming of the past years, a splendid plano-secuencia which would jump to more than one viewer of which are usually not shy away. Undoubtedly, the script is sublime, is perfectly structured and few disruptions that prevent it a masterpiece contemporary. Although it is true that at the end of see it, one has the feeling of having gone to something spectacularly perfect, and subsequently found some other somewhat forgotten detail in the film. And it is that as I say, it close to perfection, with an innovative aesthetic and a brilliant direction. The actors, all virtually unknown, shows his most terrifying, more humane facet that instinct of survival that we have all had (or will have) ever.A real breakthrough in the seventh art, and the clear demonstration that good and original film can always be made, but with a work and previous ideas. There is no doubt that [REC] is the Spanish film of the year next to the orphanage, both very different, both splendid. Balaguer贸 and Plaza have worn, and this prodigious work deserves, at least, twenty minutes of applause.</body>
</review>
