<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Beowulf" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Obviously actions and situations that are generated are really topical and there are no surprises on the final outcome or on acts of the Warrior because to Zemeckis that actually puts are the píxelesy it shows a little.</summary>
	<body>I think that Zemeckis has freak clamp. After Polar Express taste to that of animation that decided to put its efforts to create a fully digital world took you so much more real. Three years without directing and producing almost entirely animated. The problem comes in that since there the actors no longer nonsense create them in pixels. I.e., if we have the senseless idea of creating something that does not exist is very well used animation techniques to achieve this but rebuild Jolie when you to the authentic side wearing a maya and stuck balls is an absurdity. You spend money, spend time and get a false version of a real actress.I will not remove merit. Technology has advanced much in these years. Some characters are very real but still have that hyper-realist unfocused halo both upset of creations by computer. In nothing we can enjoy films made entirely by a computer and maybe we don't need nor generate them previously with actors &hellip; who knows! Can I return to have Connery Bond making or watching movies starring James Dean &hellip; hence there will be limits and surely if there will be some that another row for image rights. Anyway perhaps Beowulf wasn't prepared to be released yet. Movies with aesthetics as powerful as 300 or Sin City any viewer can not escape you the question: not would have been able to do is otherwise better? Apart from the technical aspects that can be, without doubt, laudable as questionable, I must say that we we have a film entertaining, accurate and well raised. Its raw material (an Anglo-Saxon epic poem of 6th century comparable to our Cid but with dyes of fantastic adventure closer to Tolkien is actually only the basis of the adventure is its fidelity to the 3182 verses that compose quite low) is not bad. Beowulf is a warrior tanning in the fight against monsters and demons who comes to a quiet village hit by the curse of Grendel, a demon that has the little healthy habit of invading the room where villagers celebrate their holidays and z eating occasionally a few. (After ending he gets charged with killing their mother 8más than anything because an angry mother is worse than one minor demon) but when it comes to the beast doesn't seem to be what I expected to find and the hero must decide on its principles and grow his fortune, his legend or both. Obviously actions and situations that are generated are really topical and no surprises or on the final outcome or on acts of the Warrior because as I have already mentioned to Zemeckis that actually puts are pixels and it shows a little.Indeed, with so many computerized orgy we have forgotten to say that Beowulf was already brought to the film. Specifically in nonsense with the same title, starring Christopher Lambert. Later Gerard Butler (Leonidas returns to the attack) which ended with the monster in Beowulf &amp; Grendel and clear, a next premiere television called Grendel.En summary Boewulf can be seen but a little disappointed.</body>
</review>
