<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Starship Troopers" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a distant future in which humanity is faced with some giant bugs. Excellent film of pure and simple, fun with very interesting moments, and barely slippages of pace, which makes it a cult classic.</summary>
	<body>Director: Paul Verhoeven. duration: more than two horazas, but comfortably on the couch happens agustito.Release date: 30 January 1998.Espectadores: 664.288 human beings, but sure that everybody, at least a piece the we will have seen on TV.Films like this remind me much the magnificent game Starcraft, religion in Korea. Moreover, one of the scenes of the movie is sospechósamente similar to a video game. Although surely it is coincidence, given that they are of the same year. Well, also reminded me to Dune by a pair of little scenes, but they are already very geeks. By the way, found me a very interesting film from the point of view of parity. Already understand why.The film is about a distant future in which the Galaxy is colonized and you can live on different planets. Humanity has to deal with the bugs, a species of giant insects which are attacking palautinamente, massacring all what caught (which are currently being human). A group of three friends decide to enlist in the army to fight the bugs and step to obtain citizenship, in different bodies, with the promise of always be friends.This course is a classic unclassifiable, nestled in science fiction that is auto parody with touches of humor, romanticism that sucks, equality of sexes, superiority of humans, extreme journalism, honor, duty and all this mixed in equal parts with cutreces and great special effects. Touching the genius, no doubt. Why I say about parity? That seems to me that scenes like the shower, all together and women drop by mouth worthy of the most seasoned Mason phrases, or that the boss of the human universe is a black woman, without giving importance, is a path without stridency and normalizer of truth, without that it crash. I was delighted. Not so the performance of the girl that plays Carmen Ibanez (her pilot protagonist) that between hair lacquer that you have and how little that gesticulates, seems an awful blur in this great movie.In short, film about a distant future in which humanity is faced with some giant bugs. Excellent film of pure and simple, fun with very interesting moments, and barely slippages of pace, which makes it a classic of worship for my taste.Very original.Besitos.P.D: The news live are great, very acidic, with a revindicativo touch that I love.Pd2: A question that I have I, the oxygen of these spacecraft, is where removed? Not is if they will generate it on the fly, loaded it into the Earth or that. That if in space there is nothing, no raw to generate oxygen. And if I go taking land, will have a moment that it is not more. There is that, as a reflection of the day.P.D.3: Is there a second part (there is talk of a third) that I began to see and when I realized that all the special effects that we were going to get were nothing more than courts of the previous film, I had to remove it urgently. As can tarnish the memory of a great movie with such truño second part? To see if I see her and I can criticize to taste.P.D.4: since this has gone astray, you to know that this is based on a book of the same name. Although according to recognized the director, it has failed to read the tremendous pestiño which is the book, so it only has the name.P.D.5: has who given this hairstyle to the protagonist? We are thus left without an ozone layer.</body>
</review>
