<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="The Nanny Diaries (Diario de una Niñera)" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Nanny Diaries (diary of a nanny) is a miserably failed attempt to join the Disney comedy with a serious analysis of New York high society.</summary>
	<body>Let's see, they raise their hand which have never dreamed to have Scarlett Johansson baby sitter, and here not worth no one is escaquee. Such plebiscite would obtain a safe and overwhelming majority that are the most those who want her being themselves already creciditos. No doubt it's a film that will give much to talk about all the messing and reveries will generate on this issue.Because despite the fact that already in the first Nicholas Art scene (one of the most envied children on the face of the Earth by more adults than kids) are you missing above the poor Johansson, then change radically and receives literally kicked out. The poor kid is not aware yet that due to this strange dichotomy should spend the rest of his life lying on the couch of some greedy psychologist. No less extraordinary is the blindness of the character of Paul Giamatti (why in first appearances managers want hide his face us to then reveal it without more?), which until the last third of the film not repaired in the innate skills of Johansson as a nanny. We strongly recommend that these great mysteries of humanity be investigated in depth by experts in the world of the paranormal, because they are beyond the capacity of the human being. The film lacks even the customary final speech, and on this occasion the Johansson touches him as partner Teddy a defenseless bear, who must suffer as the poor spectator such nonsense. If were not enough, and despite the fact that have sold us the film as a Disney comedy of postadolescentes, it is not at all, and is being raised as a field research in the field of anthropology. And well, The Nanny Diaries (diary of a nanny) has both anthropological research as big brother of sociological study of human behavior.The Nanny Diaries (diary of a nanny) is a miserably failed attempt to join the Disney comedy with a serious analysis of New York high society. And it also serves to see how far can go two great actresses like Scarlett Johansson and Laura Linney as bad characters with a hyphen so nefarious.</body>
</review>
