<review author="Dragon negro" title="Beowulf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Beowulf is the animated cinema closer to the reality that has been done to date and is worth seeing above all on a big screen, where most appreciate both its achievements and its flaws.</summary>
	<body>Yesterday I went to the driver, the only place in Barcelona where Beowuld is projected in 3D. The first sensation is quite spectacular and during the first minutes one is overwhelmed by a lot of details that seem made exclusively in order to enjoy them in that format, things that appear behind one object that appears will collide with you and camera movements to enjoy and that makes you feel as if you were in the movie. Once past this first sensation one gets used and the film enjoys equal, up almost forget that this one watching it in 3D, just highlight characters ahead of others and ahead of the scenarios and specific scenes, especially the battles, one again to enjoy the 3D in all its glory with amazing effects. Years towards that did not see a film a movie as well, the last was one of the last films of Freddy, specifically the final stretch where you put the glasses and thus entered the nightmare, the sense is similar but somewhat improved now.Entering himself in the film, Beowulf proposes us a trip to the human ambition and then repentance and redemption in the hands of the protagonist. We work on the characters and he ignores quite continuous action, there are scenes of fighting but these are strategically placed so that the scenes of dialogues do not become bored and where the spectacle that is likely to achieve, with a few movements of camera and very successful and amazing choreography is. Action we consistently puts in a village that gives the feeling of being very small and has few inhabitants and a small and gloomy room where celebrate the holidays, has been omitted from therefore seek a flamboyant stage and the, already cansinas, scenes where the camera flies over the impressive structures. This subtracts epic grandeur, and the story that the general feeling is that everything is happening in a small and isolated place and that it lacks importance or greatness.In the animation, it must be said that things have much improved since that Final Fantasy, though still way to achieve a credible perfection. And it is, by very successful that it is here, there is always some scene, some focus and some character that sings in excess. The male characters are those who best standing out, both the King and Beowulf have truly realistic moments. In the negative section we have women, especially the young Queen and the other girl in the second half. These characters where most see the limitations of animation and more cold and unreal seem. And this seems as to show real faces they have to have thousands of imperfections, freckles, spots, wrinkles, hairs and more, when these defects appear, sometimes in excess, the faces are articulated in a more precise and real. But in the case of two young women whose skin is white and smooth, it shows that it fails there something, even in the female character most successful is that of Angelina Jolie, there are moments where something fails and seems more porcelain than real sided.Anyway, Beowulf is animated cinema closer to the reality that has been done to date and is worth seeing above all on a big screen, where most appreciate both its achievements and its flaws. In the film it must be said that it is very entertaining and that it is not for nothing film for children, but that it is clearly geared to an adult audience, which is appreciated. If we add to this the luxury of seeing in 3D, the experience becomes something really advisable.</body>
</review>
