<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Canciones de amor en Lolitas Club" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Love songs at Lolita´s Club confirms two very worrying data, on the one hand the absolute inability of Vicente Aranda for filmmaking, and on the other the decrease dive as actor Eduardo Noriega.</summary>
	<body>The film, like life, is full of a cruel and terrible irony. And it is that while many directors sweat blood to get funding for his works, despite having amply proved their worth, others her get smoothly to his recent films are counted as a fiasco.This is the case of Vicente Aranda, returns to the film after its disastrous strained white, one of the worst Spanish films of recent decades. The truth is that after seeing love songs at Lolita´s Club should give reason to the gossips, which say that Aranda already only films to enjoy more lush of the current film scene with the presence of some of the actresses. The film there is no where take it, is that after five minutes one already has tired of listing errors. The story is more insipid and tasteless and fails to engage and excite is not credible in no time. Vicente Aranda mistakes of bundle not only improper from a filmmaker of his career, but improper from a novel director. That scene at the beginning where the camera focuses on the mouths of the actors portends the worst, but fortunately the capricho de Aranda will not more. They come to be pathetic levels of a regrettable and absolutely denied Eduardo Noriega driving, not to mention the levels which should appear duplicate. It is also difficult to understand the need to Yohana Cobo, Lara of Miguel and other actresses who interpret the prostitutes of the club with accents strange instead of having caught South American actresses. The only positive point of the film is the work of Flora Martínez, that brings forward as a misspelled and worse developed character can.Love songs at Lolita´s Club confirms two very worrying data, on the one hand the absolute inability of Vicente Aranda for filmmaking, and on the other the decrease dive as actor Eduardo Noriega.</body>
</review>
