<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A declaration of principles.</summary>
	<body>Lions for Lambs seems a priori a play, not only because their personajes-arquetipo (the press, politics and citizenship) are defined by the discursive position that represented the political universe of his filmmaker, but also because it seems to build on three fixed scenarios (University, White House and Afghanistan) from which these characters recrearán his dialogue. Redford is aware at all times to offer a personal, intentional, discursive work and without more action than that necessary to explain or illustrate the political arguments that the characters are desmadejando over the tape.Characters not interested in his private life, even if they are beings of flesh and bone. Do not describe emotions of intimate interest or illustrate the mechanisms of certain relationships. Lol Characters are defined by public or political positioning in Lions for Lambs, and are recognized as a decision making capacity which necessarily entails an ethical attitude toward social life (American), in this case embodied in the when less dubious international policy of President Bush. University, the Senator and journalist (and partly the young military serving as nexus and emotional storytelling claim) are political archetypes that compel the Viewer to reflect and, if they so wish, take party (or not) of the premises that hold those characters.Lions and lambs is a committed, in the sense of morally urge the three most important political classes of any modern democracy (politics, press and civil society) to take sides and make Act of contrition about his passivity or on the contrary its unjust action against acts that insult the most basic sense of human right. We are all guilty (responsible, would be more correct but less effects) of omitting or act without considering consequence of our approach.A Government that is installed in the lie, failure by a fourth power more concerned by the share of screen that by telling the truth and serve with this honest mediators between citizens and political power is guilty.And the citizen is guilty when you prefer to be numbed by the TV stop to think what is going on with their country and what has that to do with him. Redford is a convinced democrat. And when I say Democrat I am not referring to the formal democracy (institutions, elections, etc.) model, but to the active role of civil society in the construction of social life, that will not let the politicians to make decisions without being heard before.Lions for Lambs is an idealistic film that not utopian. Idealist because imagine the possible that hypothesis a day given to journalists and citizens by think twice things and exercise their right to think and express themselves freely, and say no to be complicit in a power that based on smiling sophistry wants to convince us that beat is the same as having the reason (be on the side of good).We cannot fault him Redford its sesentera, own naivety as soon of all fable that seeks to revive the morality of the Viewer, but this does not mean his honesty as an artist and its more than good intentions to offer us a product so (although it seems lie in the times they run) risky. In fact, Redford had to count on the independence of the United Artists which directs Cruise to your project to come to light. No such luck, everything would have been problems.Even so Redford cannot, if you want that your political cinema cale in the spectator, less that allow licenses narrative and dramatic inertia who are somewhat tramposillas clearly. This is the case of the two soldiers dying with their boots on, or before progressive journalist now illuminated by an outburst of integrity. They are things that go with the moralistic Fables.However, this statement of principles of Lions for Lambs a film made necessary, but not to the use of what you might expect in a movie theater. The average viewer is more accustomed to think that when he goes to the movies offered a story, not a speech. Lions for Lambs can be disappoint the viewer go believing that obtain a suggestive political plot in the style of all the President's men. It is not the case. Not why it would be a suggestive and reflexive experience close to the video store and watch it when it comes out on DVD.Dare, not lose much by think about things twice.</body>
</review>
