<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La joven del agua" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great fantasy film that will delight all fans of Shyamalan film and horrorizará to his detractors. They lose it.</summary>
	<body>This time M. Night Shyamalan presents a tale, a tale with nymphs, fantastic, good and bad animals. And it does so with a fidelity to his style which is commendable. For some time, the director us has been presenting impossible that we had already seen other times but narrated stories with a naturalness and realism that has made them more credible than ever before. He does not have fantastic stories in a fantasy universe, but it tells us fantastic stories perfectly nestled in our real world. Its originality is not in these stories, but in the eyes which projected onto them.Change only requests us that we create and if one is not able to accept its plot premises should not go see their movies, the same way that if one does not accept that a man can fly should not go to see "Superman Returns".As I say, the film is Shyamalan in its purest form and again the framing is a capital importance. But not only that, also what is outside table is chosen very carefully. A typical detail of Shyamalan film is to show us a seemingly bland plane whose greatest mystery is just what we do not see on screen. Nor need the director, supported in a beautiful score by the usual James Newton Howard to his appointment with the emotion and there are a couple of scenes in which isn't hard to drop a tear (or more, if you're an emotional pirate like myself). That Yes, that emotion is compensated with a humor that makes an appearance more often than on other occasions. Possibly this is a formula chosen to help make more palatable the fantasy tone of the tape but it has made me want to see how desenvolvería Shyamalan in the most complicated of the genera.It is not something that is usually mentioned but Shyamalan usually get brilliant interpretations of its actors. Is true that Paul Giamatti has already been a few years wow everyone and don't have to prove anything to anyone, but is a joy to see him carry the weight of the film with a character more complex than expected apparently in the trailers. Both Bryce Dallas Howard, featuring his eyes more than many other actors with a thousand words, as other side offer the best of themselves.Perhaps as negative points I would say that there is eventually resolved with some precipitation and that the script is basically something simpleton. In any case it is not surprising that we are, simply, to a story for reading in bed (but how well cash!). I tell you, certainly not exempt from certain morals that surely not like some but I find it more natural.I don't want to lengthen my comment (attention to the portrait makes the film critics) too so I summarize by saying that it seems to me a great fantasy film that will delight all fans of Shyamalan film and horrorizará to his detractors. They lose it.</body>
</review>
