<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Rec" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Say it is the best Spanish horror film of recent years is risky, but it is true that it is one of the few who shun the typical "easy road": autoriles claims (on one hand) and dandruff (on the other)</summary>
	<body>Long before its release, and after his recent tenure in Sitges (whose famous projection, unfortunately, not could attend), REC (2007) came wrapped in an aura of incredible expectations, perhaps too much for something that, ultimately, is an extremely simple film whose highest virtues are exactly literal in its proposal. Even so, it is surprising to see how something that began more or less as a project of marginal of its two directors (Jaume Balagueró and Paco Plaza) has ended up becoming not only one of the more effective this year's horror films, but also the work stronger to date for both filmmakers, to those who Filmax should take into consideration more than ever.For those who have been locked in a bunker during the last year and a half, I inform you that REC is basically a zombie film narrated from the point of view of a video camera that records the outbreak of the epidemic in a Barcelona building besieged by the forces of order, and that bad luck has wanted that two leaders of a local affairs program remain lockedalong with firefighters and a few neighbors. Already commented similarities with films such as the project of the Witch of Blair (1999) are, at best, limited only to the format and superficial: Unlike what occurred with the mockumentary of Daniel Myrick and Eduardo Sanchez, REC does not seem be mounted, but should be composed only by material rough of a camera that records a violent fact"real" and visceral in which the protagonist ends up being pretty invisible camera "Pablo" or television reporter, not the public that receives each and every one of the shaking.If above said that REC is a simple film he did in a pejorative term. Contrary to what happens in the canonical zombie film (talk about here obviously films of George Romero), the tape of Balagueró and Plaza does not demonstrate second readings or interpretations of any kind beyond sample (sometimes in humorous key) of the miseries that usually seize humans under State of siege. Both directors seem to be much more interested in the way in which history is transmitted and the emotional effect that prints in the Viewer, something that would not be blameworthy that horror movies is, in essence, a genus of emotions, rather than intellectual speeches (though obviously can become much more). In this light, the film gives the nail on the head: once after the introduction of the course programme and initiated the escalation of terror of the argument, what follows is a time of the most intense that have seen in horror movies, at least this year. That I have no doubt.It is that in my opinion the greatest virtue of the film: the capacity to transmit that binge in the viewer along for almost an hour and a constant crescendo that, unfortunately, seems that Plaza and Balagueró not found the best way out. The first uses his familiar formula of creation of environments even with a scenario not very distant of the employee in his previous film, repeating to enter to live (2006). The trick goes well, but to be an experience which depends mainly on the produced feeling and little else, let me show some skepticism when it comes to repeat viewing, which is really when recognizes a great movie. Attach, Yes, that the tactics employed to frighten the staff are very effective although we have seen them many times and even recently: certain images and moments of the film (some of the most chilling) we had seen earlier at the dawn of the dead (2004) Zack Snyder, only that such moments are here tratandos with filter similar to the journalism of war realism.In short, I do not know until that point we can say that REC is one of the best Spanish horror films that have been made, but it is true that it is one of the more honest and less dodgy and overblown, and that at the same time (this is the best no doubt) has not fallen into the temptation to go for the easy way of dandruff. The fact that a film so visceral and direct can hurt your prospects in the future (perhaps), but I cannot deny that you did me go very wrong. And is not that of what will the horror film in the background?</body>
</review>
