<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Rec" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Curious and interesting Spanish horror film.</summary>
	<body>Curious and quite acceptable horror film, whose producer as estimable Mr. Julio Fernández and the Fimax distributor improve Allied for the international market, with everything that this brings positive.It is an entertaining tape, which one, although not terrorized, but which has voltage and is quite entertaining.Principals, Jaume Balagueró and Paco Plaza, ready in hunger for these purposes, manage mix horror, intrigue, suspense and humor, attractive way to the Viewer, who begins seeing the movie with some mistrust and surprise, for more late entering a daily world of cruel and bloody terror.And is that is what more I liked this film, terror is credible (if we accept your premise, clear) because comes not from other distant worlds, but something daily, close, next. from our own neighborhood, from our own stairs with our neighbours as terrified characters who do not know what the hell happens or how to escape from the nightmare.In addition, the humor is very well inserted, with these horny reporter interviews to the neighbors when they still do not know what awaits them really.Manuela Velasco does superbly well (won the best actress award at the prestigious Sitges 2007 international film festival), combining to perfection his sympathy and comedy from the beginning, with the infinite panic at the end. But the rest of performers will not lag behind, getting transmit their fear thanks to some natural interpretations, very worthy.The worst, but on this occasion is understood, it is the way of telling all, with that dance of St. Vitus constant of the camera, that can go mad, although us also gets fully into the sinister history. And as everything is flmado camera in hand so be on this occasion.Another negative thing, but that you can't blame the film itself is that many scenes, more or less, already quite seen in horror movies. But the truth is that it is a competent film that I think gets what intended, is not nothing to scare away a large part of the public (I was going to put "the majority", but with me they have not managed and with other spectators either, as evidenced by the fact of laughter that came from some rows). But the same were laughter caused by absolute terror.In short, okay and like, but you are great these bizarre epithets that some her qualify, as "An undisputed classic of modern horror". Well, well, without exaggeration, that can turn against.</body>
</review>
