<review author="José A. Peig" title="El proyecto de la bruja de Blair" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The great merit of the film is its ability to make the viewer participant of this paranoia, if the Viewer is able to enter in the psychological dynamics of the narration.</summary>
	<body>As is customary in this site often, retomemos past taking advantage of the present and the debate sponsored by the film that titled REC this causing real feeling in our cinemas. Blair witch project is its closest, that play with the same trick to induce the feeling of terror: show the story through a camera inspired by the patterns of a real shooting. This raises many interesting questions regarding the film understood as art (which you know is - almost - only thing that motivates the ratings of this blog.) The sensations. (them enjoy the spectator, so paid and live). I don't - I - not perhaps too delve into this, but it should be noted that if the filmmaker tries to imitate reality with a structured story, you can fall into an inconsistency that makes that the product does not exceed the test of the theatrical to make way for a real effectiveness. And if a homemade shooting can be equated to the care and aesthetic intent of a work film. turn off and we reinventing the cinema. Major problems can lead to expose and develop a terror theme (based on the supernatural or extraordinary) submitting to the laws of "reality", because they limit the potential possibilities of the story. I.e., the film would not be terror, nor the content of the narrative, but the trick used. Eduardo Sanchez and Daniel Myrick made a film in which realism goes beyond a certain use of the camera (and leave aside the impressive advertising campaign, which was a scam for thousands of spectators), with which managed to create fear without resorting to overly extraordinary elements, and apart from supernatural elements. This is a virtue (creating a directly human terror, avoiding the excessive use of clichés) and a default (restricting the possibilities of the horror story). Blair witch project is not a story about witches and demons or not psicokillers to use. First and foremost, it is the story of a suggestion fed each other between the three young actors. In connection with the supernatural or extraordinary human terror, the Royal and which all can feel at a some point in our lives, always is the result of a suggestion induced by external stimuli. In this case, they introduce a series of folk signs (some stones in circle, pagan symbology, etc) that feed the paranoia of the protagonists. The great merit of the film is its ability to make the viewer participant of this paranoia, if the Viewer is able to enter in the psychological dynamics of the narration.In his "realistic" exercise, the filmmakers chose the perfect argument to open the step towards the suggestion. Lost in a forest (which is, on the other hand, an archetypal idea of enormous effectiveness), without a path to guide the safe steps, is the sea of easy, even with a map, since the homogeneous landscape and horizons stretch at the discretion of open space, without having the Wayfarer a reference point clear. The horror story begins when the three main characters realize that have been lost. The horror comes not from disturbing signs that appear in the forest, but the fact of disorientation. The further development is the representation of a psychological state reinforced with external signs of indefinite meaning; montoncitos of stones that appear with the new day, around the tent (a common fact in rural cultures and areas of high mountain. are you sure? that weren't there when they camped attention and selective perception?), sounds in the night fall within the ordinary, the canvases of the tent moved by a sporadic burst of wind (?) while it seems we hear voices and laughter of children (the volume used for that sound stream) It is so low that it is at the limit of what could be real or a simple auditory hallucination. Know the reader, in passing, that a Blizzard in the forest can be easily confused with cries of women or children voices. (It is a well known fact).The critical point, in this sense, is the disappearance of one of the protagonists, who in prior situations had shown signs of incipient madness, and the later appearance next to the shop of eyes and blood inside a bundle of firewood. Many spectators viewing the viscera with the missing character, but there is nothing in the story that will lead us to that conclusion, beyond of the suggested hypotheses.Joshua could have been lost in the depths of the forest, shouting that his two companions heard during the night. In short, although the film shows signs that some intelligence this playing with three boys, there is nothing verifiable outside of the psychological atmosphere that alludes to a human, subtle, terror in the tenuous line that separates the apparent of the real. For this reason, the creation of Sanchez and Myrick is located in a cinematographic expression that transcends the simple theatrical to tell a simple story (of how three boys are lost in a forest, and the psychological terror originated) from which emanates an enigma open to several readings: does sorcery? child's play? a cluster of unfortunate coincidences?.So unfortunate that the conclusion seems to suggest the death of characters. We see recorders precipitate on the ground. What we don't know is the cause: aggression, accident or anxiety as to what they are looking at, you will see. The last picture is the best example of the ambiguous style used; a character, backs against the wall, fixed assets and insensitive to the cries of the terrified protagonist, camera rushes to the suelo.y some viewers say see a hairy arm moments before closing.The reality usually not so structured as in the succession of events and reasons as effectively developed in this film, hence the inconsistency that we said at the beginning, but which at least establishes a chain of causes and effects for a narrative solvent in which the contents and exposure through permanent subjective camera are complementary parts. The film begins with an exhibition - by way of documentary - on the rural legends about witches and ghosts. This, seen through the eye of the camera which, in this case, is the mind and eyes of the three boys, determines and explains the suggestion when from the subsequent feeling of helplessness. The girl, Heather, holds the main dramatic burden, and is moving - as many spectators witnessed, even the most reluctant – the sequence in which reiterates the idea of guilt and asks for forgiveness. Guilt is a relevant theme in the story, and the way in which the three seek to blame others follows a progressive pattern very in tune with the real stroke of human relationships.Depending on the style, scares over what is or is not well understood, the phenomena represented to the detail and the use of archetypes. In a work of art, is more meritorious the kind of terror used in Blair witch project than the strident, banal, predictable and explicit reality show that these days we see in REC. It is difficult to present a situation of suggestion with possible signs of reality in a coherent manner. Take camera in hand, get a group of people in the interior of a building and it come already all paste shouts to the career - ladder up, stairs down - escape of the zombies too, it is so easy as unimaginative. Remember, in addition, Demoni 2 by Lamberto Bava. In Blair witch project artifice is inherent to the theme developed, because the only way to represent stimuli of fear (the specific type of stimuli) is putting the viewer in the disoriented gaze of the protagonists. Only REC is unnecessary artifice in the service of the proposed theatrical.</body>
</review>
