<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="December Boys" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The majority of the film have a sense of Deja vu stale and spiced with its tremendous slowness and excessive length her may be occasionally quite infumable.</summary>
	<body>It is possible that in many States of America they away by what I'm about to say, but it is that I can not help it because to me Daniel Radcliffe makes me much. I am aware that a generational barrier separates us but its newly acquired most of age gives me hope yet but is that it was to see him in Equus and since then not I can remove me it head. This "gifted" actor tries to desperately escape that role of boy wizard with this independent Australian production (that of the same Warner) where a group of orphans is sent on holiday to the beach during the Christmas holidays. While children fantasize with the idea of the largest to be adopted will have more comprehensive and carnal thoughts. Come on, the typical boring film of discovery of adolescence purée with the tedious insistence of the life of the unfortunate orphan. December Boys have that whiff television film mixed with the "My girl" syndrome, i.e. as soon as you see to a kid running in shorts you have the feeling that someone has to die from one moment to another and you can not stop doing cabals on who will be the cold cuts. I will not say if in the end this curse is consummated because I have no spirit Spoileador. In fact the majority of the film have a sense of Deja vu stale and spiced with its tremendous slowness and excessive length her may be occasionally quite infumable. Because despite the enthusiasm that wakes me Mr Radcliffe say that it has happened as well as Elijah Wood &hellip; he has been Harry Potter face forever! (the poor Elijah have even worse because stayed you face of Hobbit which is rather less attractive and much more quietly to the fantasies erotic festive that the type of the wand) therefore when you see the lower December boys kid only thing what you may think is in slap it so his glasses back to Harry.In short, surplus 100%</body>
</review>
