<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El caso Welles" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Thriller on paedophiles, urban Avengers and poetic justice just not surprised by bored of your proposal...</summary>
	<body>The murky thriller scales between introspection to the Bergman - tormented characters that express without language the edges of his troubled soul - and the usual ration of clichés that perlan thriller standard - characters whose past matters little. The murky thriller delve into the morality of this dirty epic, in the nature of human behavior. You care more about the origin of the problem as its solution. So is the personaje-enganche of this thriller muddier than thriller that gives Richard Gere the opportunity to redeem himself of tasteless slips and the sambenito irreconcilable with oblivion which is being (be, who knows) icon the star-system, hombre-objeto around good actor that, occasionally, is. The pursuer of psychopaths who interprets has finished become a kind of calibration obsessive, in a surly and asocial official who has become his profession a crusade that is own investment, hero, champion, standard and, above all, ambiguous executive arm. Rugged of the script for the case Welles (disturbed behaviour, paedophiles, escorados of the rule in general) is his Director (Andrew Lau or Wai Keung Lau, Hong Kong of the already known and overvalued three author parts of Internal affairs, Scorsese infiltrators microbial) a methodical author, striving to have a history of sex criminals and impossible redemptions to the American. Akin to Seven in its stormy aspect in her purulent epidermis, the Wells case brings a new mechanics in the thriller of mystical inspiration (the pursuer become that which pursues), a closed, distant, aesthetic approach articulated by the tiresome (sometimes) Didactics of bleak and unbalanced federal agent that interprets a meritorious Gere, that only seems happy (so to speak) when track tracksit scrutinises the crime scenarios or confirms the unshakeable nature of evil. Welles is also a film of modest claims, despite its cast. The portrait of the private life of the dedicated staff moves the predictable - and here almost non-existent - portrait of the private life of the psychopaths on duty, are not sufficiently drawn or (even) blotted, devoid of narrative autonomy. All that makes that the footage becomes heavy. The demons inside of the conjurado to render justice clouding its mission and arrumban it to another Crusade: their own, that of a lost man, struggling Mills, vaguely spurred by the nobility, but gap to simple and dark revenge</body>
</review>
