<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="United 93" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Paul Greengrass chooses their own version here and moves for 91 minutes, camera on his shoulder, agile and ruthless as a hungry tiger in a chicken coop, without concessions to the Viewer. A film historical, terrifying and essential.</summary>
	<body>In the end credits, the film is dedicated to all the victims of September 11. Because what United 93 shows, is a detailed recreation documentary about the events of that fateful morning. And though there are many and varied the different angles and perspectives of this shocking tragedy, all of them have a brutal dramatic power. In this case, Paul Greengrass, author also of the interesting "Bloody Sunday" or the regular "The Bourne Supremacy" focuses on the fourth aircraft hijacked on 11 September, that which, according to official sources, crashed in Pennsylvania when passengers rioted against the hijackers and tried to regain control of the flight. Greengrass plays with all the advantages that an event of this kind offers. It measured perfectly their own talent and his ability to the data and documentation to recreate faithfully and almost mathematical precision historical events. In this case, sold the film as something supposedly truthful. But only supposedly, because still there are many questions unresolved about what happened with this flight and this attack in general. Strangely appeared remnants of United 93 to eight miles of the place where supposedly crashed and, Furthermore, never were found the two black boxes that usually resist all kinds of collisions. But stranger still is the fact that official sources also ensure that either never found the black boxes of the other three aircraft.On the other hand, and despite the fact that the delay of 40 minutes this flight suffered could have provided that passengers, as in the film, they know of the tragic fate of the other hijacked airplanes and this was the trigger that prompted his mutiny, is surprising that the rebellion came exactly on the plane with less passage of the three abducted45. When the other aircraft had 64, 65 and 92 passengers respectively.There are patriotic and concerned theories that take advantage of the official version chosen by Greengrass, moreover, extol the value and heroicísmo of Americans civilians, fighting and sacrificing their own lives to save the White House. Others, however, much less attractive to the American Government, try show that the aircraft was shot down by an American fighter in order to shoot the aircraft to avoid "bad adults". Some even claim that such communications did not exist and that the airliner was shot down by mistake in those moments of chaos and confusion which in addition so faithfully portrays United 93.Nada is knows for sure yet, but Paul Greengrass chooses their own version here and moves for 91 minutes, camera on his shoulder, agile and ruthless as a hungry tiger in a chicken coop. It tells the real time events, without concessions to the Viewer. Stripping of clichés and dramatic resources his work, without any moralina or adoctrinamientos. Showing with great harshness and sobriety, on the one hand, a millimeter recreation of what have happened inside the plane and, surprise, confusion and anguish of controllers, flight, and its total lack of coordination with a State of vulnerable American Defense, slow and ineffective. Greengrass not within political positions, telling with great pulse and sense of rhythm. Exciting, crushing in the armchair to the viewer and all this, without reaching the position of one side or the other. As already noted at the beginning, in the end credits, the film is dedicated to all the victims of September 11. For this reason, when the kidnappers understand the true situation have resulted and abductees, prisoners of fear and despair, begin to act under the purest and animal instinct of survival, some pray frightened to wing in the cockpit, while the others pray to Jesus in the rear of an aircraft in free fall. A film historical, terrifying and essential.</body>
</review>
