<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Leones por Corderos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>While guys like Michael Winterbotton filmed excellent films, a director of the old guard, paste failed shots with wet gunpowder, when it has all the resources and means to make good cinema of truth.</summary>
	<body>Had just passed away ten or fifteen minutes of the film when Sacai whispered me that we had to have seen prior to its consideration of philosophy, in which he had played lecture about whether we could be happy without policy. Because the more recent film that healthy and Ruddy liberalote is Robert Redford goes that precisely, how important is policy and nefarious is the moral and intellectual attrition are doing our youth of today. The film, as if it were an episode of "24", happens virtually in real time. An hour and a half in the life of a handful of people who apparently do not have nothing do with one another, but whose stories are causally linked through a structure very much in the style of González Iñárritu. But the similarities between "Babel" and these "Lions for Lambs" end up there, in the structural will. Because the Redford film lacks the poetic breath and the ability of the film of the Mexican suggestion, to become a some left-wing discourse as moderate as well-meaning. and more exciting, the truth.The three stages of the film, the war is inconsistent; the academic is, at times, to sonrojante and only the relationship of attraction/fascination/repulsion is established between the promising right-wing politician and veteran left-wing journalist played by Meryl Streep, Tom Cruise offers some appeal. Only in his interview/conversation there is some tension and excitement in a soft and listened, film flat, a frustrating no-brainer. War sequence is already taken so narrowly that virtually spare in its entirety. It does not cause anguish, emotion or penalty. Even though the missing soldiers are two good and idealistic boys, war history is irrelevant, especially, to put it in relation to the conversation that the professorial and discursive Redford keeps his he/she student.A film of thesis, without force or hook, that it seems destined for a confused students and that have most mordant, could serve, for example, that the famous judge of minors from Granada, Emilio Calatayud, used her in encouraging troubled youth to straighten out his life and leave an incapacitating that it does not lead to anything good.It is a pity that, while guys like Michael Winterbotton filmed excellent films such as "Road to Guantanamo" or "Untamed heart", a director of the old guard, usually committed with the American militant left, hitting failed shots with wet gunpowder, when it has all the resources and means to make good cinema of truth. And it is that with good intentions is full hell.</body>
</review>
