<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Habitación sin salida" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A clean example of dark which are of own hotel rooms, especially those dens abandoned in space and time.</summary>
	<body>When they begin the opening credits to room no exit (2007), one believes that he is about to meet another bastardization of psycho (1960) of Alfred Hitchock (the most plagiarized the film director), but these impressions are passing. The movie ends by progressively away from the famous thriller of Norman Bates and family to look back on work much more explicit as in his time were Toolbox Murders (1978) and trap for tourists (1979), dressed with a touch of initial mystery which, personally, I think very well resolved. It is only when it leaves on its conventional side when it loses air, which does not prevent that he is highly recommended at the end.And that room without output is fairly simple, not only in its approach to horror, but even in its duration: the whole footage lasts only 81 minutes, and that including a few long closing credits initials and finals which are obviously inspired by the aforementioned Hitchcock film. The plot of the starting also is similar: couple suffers from an "accidental" mishap on the road and are forced to spend the night in a mysterious motel only to be haunted by someone or something which threatens their lives. Throughout the first half hour is in the creation of the environment and the discovery by the couple of things that puts them in danger in this sinister motel rooms. It is precisely this piece, in which the mystery is dosed, the best of the film, which reaches its peak at the time in which the couple finally discovers the exact nature of the danger that lies ahead. Not count it here because I think it works much better if you do not know what is waiting for you. Only say that it is that the time in which all previous indications converge in a single revelation that makes this film to abandon their connections with psychosis in search of the intensity of a game of cat and mouse.Unfortunately, this is also the time in which tape takes a much more conventional air and it stagnates in it for the rest of their short duration, becoming a Chase uninterrupted it hides little that we have not seen before, except the inclusion in two main roles of Luke Wilson and Frank Whaley, actors that normally we associate with comedies and here showing a dramatic change of registration. Even Kate Beckinsale appears to leave her role as tough woman seen in Underworld (2003) to embrace a more vulnerable character (without abandoning their status as women's claim of history). This second half is that ultimately a bit disappointed not to offer anything new and, on the other hand, delve into the long history of clichés of characters making decisions estúpicas for the convenience of the writers. All this prevents getting locked room to be something more than it is: a clean example of dark which are of own hotel rooms, especially those dens abandoned in space and time. Attention, that Yes, the level final, much more forceful and realistic of what we are accustomed in this kind of stories.</body>
</review>
