<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El Atardecer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The sunset is a sober and elegant melodrama despite respond to the clichés of the genre, not falling into the temptation to seek easy tear.</summary>
	<body>The melodrama is a rather special genus, is a very popular and almost all films of this type tend to be quite profitable. But it is also true that some of these stories working is needed a good Director who can maintain the appropriate pulse of the narration and a special group of actors.Sunset at least meets more than the second of these features, while there first more doubts, that it is the second film of Lajos Koltai, a brilliant director of photography, and if it is not enough to remember his collaborations with the no less great István Szabó. Based on the novel by Susan Minot, the sunset could be considered a typical melodrama, with a story that doesn't lack any of the usual ingredients: impossible love, remorse, errors, tormented characters, tragic loss &hellip; the story kicks off with an old woman on her deathbed, and is in these final moments in which recalls his youth days, which marked its existence of life. These minutes are something disconcerting, because Koltai jumps without notice at a time to another, embarullando the plot and complicating it without, and Dizzy the viewer with so many changes. Luckily, the film acquired a tone more sedate and paused, much more appropriate for a story in which the feelings and emotions of his characters above all take precedence. In fact there are moments in which slows down the pace too much, and there are sequences in which do clear the origins of Koltai, because it seems more concerned to seek levels of great aesthetic beauty that by the appropriate narrative of the plot. But for the Hungarian filmmaker it must be said that it avoids the temptation of falling into sentimentality cheap and free; on the contrary, just signing a sober and elegant, moving and exciting film into perspective. Excellent staff of interpreters, who are largely responsible for the credibility and humanity of history, should highlight a great and contained Claire Danes, a sober and forceful Patrick Wilson, and a Hugh Dancy which outboard a character complex and full of nuances. Vanessa Redgrave, Meryl Streep and Glenn Close, it is not necessary to say anything, obviously.The sunset is a sober and elegant melodrama despite respond to the clichés of the genre, not falling into the temptation to seek easy tear. Lajos Koltai brings to history the serenity and tranquillity you need, while the magnificent roster of actors make credible his characters, and give the right touch of emotion to the tape.</body>
</review>
