<review author="Mario" title="Beowulf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I really think that Beowulf would have been a great film to have been shot the old way; or even an excellent movie animation if that would have been what was proposed. However the end result falls between two stools, as a kind of undead without energy or agitation.</summary>
	<body>The second film with a screenplay by the great Neil Gaiman is not standing in any comic book (although the has been based on its history) and, apparently, does not have any relationship with the world of the comic. Outstanding writer and writer seems to be opening up hollow between the Vortex Hollywood.Beowulf adapts the Anglo-Saxon epic poem of the same name. The story of the Hunter hero of monsters was carried the celluloid at least twice in recent years, with mixed results: Beowulf, the legend, infumable by-product with Christopher Lambert in front; Beowulf &amp; Grendel, dignified and Honorable Canadian low-budget production.Taking into account that the Saxons have dominated and dominate the film business, it is strange that such an account had not been adapted emphatically until this very moment. That same due think Robert Zemeckis, who supported in a unique visual effects technique as used in his previous film, Polar express, was launched to consummate the final version of the poem, which, performed with other more traditional means, would have increased its budget in a few million.The original text, without a title until the beginning of the 19th century - when was it he would start calling Beowulf - is of importance immense for Saxon languages, comparable, for example, to representing the Cantar de mío Cid to our language.The original plot consists of three parts, the first in which Beowulf confronts the demon Grendel and the mother of this, the second fraction in which Beowulf is King, and a third and last in facing a dragon, with final outcome I daresay not now.It is here where you can see the hand of Neil Gaiman at the reins of the script. Signed to pachas with Roger Avary (notable filmmaker and screenwriter, eternally remembered for me as the pen that wrote the history of Butch, the corrupt Boxer in Pulp fiction) it seems that in the end most of the work fell to the British writer.To lock all three parts of the classical poem between himself, Gaiman invented a plot of parents children of the more accurate, not clashes at all with the end result and that fits like a glove the spirit of the legend. In the movie you can listen to as recited parts of the poem in a reliable way, as well as the songs of the Vikings, masterfully inserted.Ultimately, the strength of the tape is not but the screenplay by Gaiman, simple but powerful, legendary as well as realistic. The characters speak and act as the people of that time should do so, and the delicious monsters appearing are embedded in a formidable manner in the history.But, as there is a great small defect (there always is one) the above technique of digital animation used by the director has no force to surprise for more than 10 minutes. Beyond there, what you can see is a kind of lifeless characters that recite interesting dialogues without a shred of emotion or feeling in his words. The movements are artificial and claim to reality collapses like a House of cards after half an hour of footage. I really think that Beowulf would have been a great film to have been shot the old way; or even an excellent movie animation if that would have been what was proposed. However the end result falls between two stools, as a kind of undead without energy or agitation.In conclusion, Beowulf is one project more than interesting and entertaining, born of new technologies and crushed, in my view, also by those same. The elements of the conventional cinema work perfectly, as well exemplifies the extraordinary musical score of Alan Silvestri, and however the Mise en scène becomes often as chaotic and uncontrolled as it is only possible to reach with a computer.Please, gentlemen, stop trying to seem real that is not.</body>
</review>
