<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La brújula dorada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Golden Compass is the umpteenth attempt to Hollywood by copying the monumental success of the Lord of the rings, but stays in attempt for the story so poor that it offers, devoid of any fantasy or magic.</summary>
	<body>The monumental, and for many unexpected, success of critics and public of the Lord of the rings has led to studies should be launched to the desperate search for new sagas-franquicia similar to that envisioned Tolkien. Thus explains the proliferation of films most successful as the Chronicles of Narnia or Stardust, and others completely dispensable such as Beowulf, Eragon or the six signs of the Golden Compass Luz.La adapts the first volume of the trilogy his dark materials, Philip Pullman, a fantastic work of but with profound metaphysical and religious references. But as it's been converted into fairy tale film, have eliminated the mentions of these so thorny issues, which have earned the animosity of the fans of the saga of Pullman. Having said that, the Golden Compass is a fairly simple and vulgar, story that does not stand out by its magic or fantasy or by its originality. Even the most lively tire soon of a plot so child (said in the worst sense) that if it were analyzed in depth would cause more laughter astonishment. The brief appearance of actors such as Derek Jacobi and Christopher Lee does foresee a more dramatic development in the following installments, but even that manages to recover the interest. Visual and narrativamente, the Golden Compass drinks from countless sources, such as the wars (attention to the final moment of the Empire strikes back), the Chronicles of Narnia or Lord of the rings. If outside little, ownership rests with Da kota Blue Richards, which at times becomes unbearable Kinderman. Although to unbearable, we already have the appearances of a Nicole Kidamn and digitally bluish eyes. It is a pity that they have not given more presence a Daniel Craig is the best of the film, as well as its short length.The Golden Compass is the umpteenth attempt to Hollywood by copying the monumental success of the Lord of the rings, but stays in attempt for the story so poor that it offers, devoid of any fantasy or magic.</body>
</review>
