<review author="Jokin García " title="La habitacion de Fermat" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A Cube to the Spanish who not excited to the viewer but not sleep.</summary>
	<body>Pierre de Fermat was a French important mathematician of the 17TH century whose enigma was his last theorem, one of the most important in the history of mathematics. Furthermore, it is also the pennant of insert of this film, in which 4 brilliant minds are invited to a party that will have to solve a puzzle, and once there they realize that everything is a mortal trap, a sinister game in which the rules are clear: if they do not solve the enigmas which they are posing in the established time will die. Inevitable to remember other films such as Cube or Saw.Los protagonists of this film are Alejo Sauras (Los Serrano), who find it funny, used to seeing him as the surly son of Sunia, see here make genius of mathematics; Santi Millán (7 lives), Elena Ballesteros (Mata family), who already coincide with Alejo Sauras in "coffee alone, or with them", Lluis Homar (Borgia) and Frederick Luppi.La film can be seen, and its development is interesting, although sometimes it is a little tontorrona and the puzzles are too simplistic. Okay to allow the viewer play to find them, it seems that it is what it is, but as the characters mathematical geniuses, not very credible is that cost them so much discover them (okay, it may be argued that with the pressure no one thinks clearly) as a little silly is the enigma that allows the characters to "qualify" for the game (although this)(, also is true, that acquires a little sense to disclose the truth) at times gives the impression that her could have worked a little more, especially some mathematical topics and some detail thing fuck in hairs, the typical syndrome of "master plan of the evil in which if you fail a single piece is everything goes to the guano" now let's see if you hath been able to discover the enigma which provides access to the do deadly room, putting the number following (no seáis cheats and not look at the comments before know the answer) 5, 4, 2, 9, 8, 6, 7,? And tip it another: 2, 10, 12, 16, 17, 18, 19,?</body>
</review>
