<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Bee movie" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a tape I recommend see paying attention closely to the details of each scene, without worrying about losing its loose narrative structure.</summary>
	<body>"Dye" Comic movie, look inevitable knowing the background, was handled with a lovely sutiliza. The comedian takes his great talent to satirize the natural human behaviour, to believe the only holder of the goods of nature. The creative capacity of Seinfeld to devise and lead us to that imaginary world of bees, is very large. We are many people on several occasions we think or invent in our minds how they think different animals: ants, cats, dogs, etc and Seinfield, knew how to do this perfectly carried nearest reality that we know on this aspect: the film. In addition to this mode get satisfy the dream of those who tend to create this kind of stories but they are reserved to the purely personal level. Really managed to capture in images as they believe the bees, which make the bees as they feel and see us as. Believing as bees, think like bees was a fundamental premise in the story that was accomplished fully.But becomes inevitable to compare it with the extraordinary film of Pixar, stiff competition from DreamWorks, "Ratatouille" (here read the criticism), which imposed a high point in the animation genre and since that I saw her anticipated that hardly could be achieved, at least for this year, something that overcame her such as Ratatouille masterfully combines technique with history, something lack you a Bee Movie. History of A bee stays on plot and story refers, because they have in a way so carefree that lost hilarity and cohesion, is easy to see how an event becomes another subtracting important explanations. What is more, I could even find a great physicist resemblance between the female cartoon characters of both tapes that caused me much curiosity and acumen. Do as I also wondered: will be that we will be taking the first steps to the stage where we will create true animated actresses? And I am not referring to the already created as Peggy, Deysi, etc. As to this I leave the photos so judge for yourself, also crazy that sounds everything is possible. Bee Movie has managed to raise after its premiere in United States on 2 November and today in various countries, a total of $ 137 million; While Ratatouille approached the 610 million, because something will be.History of a bee at the end I was having more emotion and charisma to narrate the plot and that is why wasn't me so appealing and complete, but probably will be part of the 3 finalists to compete award Oscar in this category thanks to its technical invoice. It is a tape I recommend see paying attention closely the details of every scene without worrying about losing its loose narrative structure.</body>
</review>
