<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Mataharis" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although their stories are small and are glued to the real as a tire to asphalt, 'Mataharis' addresses from the lucidity of suggestion many and varied Affairs of eminently human content</summary>
	<body>Film is more wise and artistic as it suggests, displays, or sugestiona that when he indoctrinated, he lectured and judgment. Probably also conform more to the truth of his story when he creates his characters and stories under this premise of honesty. Icíar Bollaín film seems to evolve, and for good, on this path of plot minimalism which raises questions without offering definitive answers to the Viewer. Mataharis, his latest film subsequent to successful tape social complaint was Te doy mis ojos, delves into this way more polyhedral when speaking about the characters. Three actresses (Najwa Nimri, María Vázquez and Nuria González) embody other so many women at different stages of their lives, distinct much from the other, which should make decisions about how they want to be their life or how to redirect it in its current state.This issue of our decisions at specific crossroads as vital chisel, appear to be present at all times in the film. An example of this is found in the invaluable dialogue between the character of Nuria González, private detective and co-worker of the other two protagonists, with a client that has requested follow-up to his wife that he suspected an infidelity. Confirmed this, man, between shocked and depressed, he wondered aloud: "How has been able to do me this?". Detective Carmen, the friend then of the client, espeta him: "the important thing is not whether it is or not with another, the important thing is why".This sequence, together with others of the film delves into other plot axis: how a person who has lived for years is we can reveal as being strange and almost alien to our existence, noting the cruelty of an accompanied solitude.It is clear therefore that, although their stories are small and are glued to the real as a tire to asphalt, Mataharis addresses from the lucidity of suggestion many and varied Affairs of eminently human content. It will probably not come to the master, but this new work of the Madrid filmmaker confirmed as one voice more than interesting among our filmmakers.</body>
</review>
