<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Romanzo Criminale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The best: Stefano Accorsi and see that Italian cinema can copy the dynamics of American cinema and remain true to its principles.</summary>
	<body>There are films whose main problem is that they are not able to limit. They are so ambitious that they try to count too much and end up lost in the immensity of themselves. This is the case of Romanzo Criminale. Her story could have been a good drama, a Thriller extraordinary or an immeasurable story police or action but as not he opts for none of them is actually a standard example of the same. The side effect of this is that you need two and a half hours of footage to tell their story. A story that occasionally fool not knowing what character is the protagonist or who are the good and the bad. It is normal because the book was extremely extensive and the solution passed to eliminate characters or even join them. Rulli and Petraglia, writers of the film, had to make this mammoth adaptation. The Lebanese, the cold, the Dandy, the Commissioner Scialoja (a modern Javert), all they have a key role in the plot and they have been treated with very delicate strokes. They personalize the clichés of the genre film as well as Italian stereotypes which gives each of them a charisma without which the tape would not be half as effective. The Italy of the 1970s is the ideal setting for the narrative of Romanzo Criminale that recounts the exploits of a group of Roman criminals for thirty years living and sharing the Italian story until 1992: attacks, kidnappings, the murder of Aldo Moro, drugs, theft, blackmail, corruption despite their daily actions.The "band of the Magliana", takes its name from an area of Rome and is a really compact group, because they carry a lifetime together. These friendships that can make people reach unexpected limits. His coolness and actions that levaban out were really shocking that despite its operational cores and have controlled the mafia of the center of Italy they were excessively cautious, secret and violent. Trying personalized in a very insistent and convinced Commissioner justice across of what makes them will continue as it has evolved to make it difficult.There is something that the director has done tremendously well and exploit the idea of the Bandit to narrate the adventures of the characters and create a sympathy of the audience towards them also including the best resources of the social and documentary film with time images or sound recordings (such as the call of the Red Brigades to the family of Aldo Moro to tell them where to find his body)(, the attack of the Pope.). At first to have been the first Tarantino films (which were still bright and not just decent) will see a mount that will be very familiar and cools as the story progresses.The best: Stefano Accorsi (the last Kiss) and see that Italian cinema can copy the dynamics of American cinema and remain true to its principles.DATA of the film: He presented at the Berlin Film Festival. He won David di Donatello for best director of photography, design costumes, editing, production design, script, actor cast (Pierfrancesco Favino) and Visual effects. Premiere in Italy: 2005-09-30. Come to Spain if does it nothing in early 2008 dubbed.</body>
</review>
