<review author="Bruji" title="Rec" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Dangerous mixture between genres in which the technique, which refines an already existing idea, puts to the formality of a screenplay based on flimsy premises of easy destruction. Pathetic misleading terror built based on Dogma and blackouts of light.</summary>
	<body>Who do not afraid to be locked up in a building, without the possibility of contact with the outside and faced a real threat as incomprehensible? To me, certainly much. Who not overwhelms you receive a history through a television camera which filmed shocking figures with night vision? Then there is the only secret of the overwhelming success of [REC]. A unusual movie that works more like "pasaje del terror" than as conventional tape, and only in their last minutes. In these, under the banner of "Let's go fear", light blackouts occur, camera movements are still more sea, limited depth of field becomes non-existent sound losses are frequent, - not always justified - hysteria reaches heights that rub the tachycardia, laughable serenity disappears and emerges a successful game of shadows and lights. But the problem of [REC] is that this part - certainly brilliant - don't fit inside all that it contains. To reach this situation and believe it, the viewer will need to make a superhuman effort to ignore a host of unforeseen and impermissible absurdities that make up the script. Here is that everything suggests that it was designed to be sold to the North American industry. There is more than usual that the police always come late and that the Government systematically, endangers the lives of their citizens, giving way to individual heroic interventions. Even in stories based on real events, makes clear a co-ordination and confusion that alarmed. But, all that is happening in this country. Here can be activated a terrorism unilaterally Protocol, in which the health authorities act under its own discretion without the knowledge of the rest of the bodies that make up the security of the State? It would have been wiser to omit the place in which unfolds the action, since the improbability of the answers is approaching science fiction more astonishing, in which forced isolation reaches communication systems and mobile phones lose coverage. Look at how you look at it, is like that old joke: "you want what that caught me by the bull". This coarse blend of genres always was more dangerous than rabid dogs transmitting lethal virus through saliva. But not content with creating an unlikely situation even for those who we believed us Resident Evil or 28 days after, the writers allowed the lujazo insert an episode of "Here no hay quien viva", in which a group of neighbors "terrified" (and no shortage of reasons to be so), cares more than leaving well combed before the House, and to criticize the feeding habits of the Lord who lives in the fourth right, that of his own integrity and survival. The incredible touches the hair tomadura while experts speak of "scathing critique of intercultural problems", while performances and direction of actors leave a lot to be desired. The beginning of this mess is found in a chilling "Footage", omen of nightmares flashing. Later, the absence of credits seems to indicate that managers might be "discredited" in this project of Blair shot with camera on his shoulder, without music, with impossible picture taken in conditions of very low intensity of light, in a "here and now" without temporary or space jumps. If not for points 6 and 8, the appearance of weapons and the explicit exclusion of "genre films" (that someone tell me a single movie that does not belong to none), we would be faced with a "Dogma film"; that, logically, we overlooked the rest of the Decalogue 95, that that neither its own founders met. Said "God" that "is a pleasure to direct and write is a roll". Perhaps that is why the screenplays are more worthy of praise than the own techniques of filming. In any case, the latter should never prevail over the former. It is the case, in addition, Jaume Balagueró (one of my major weaknesses) adopted with outstanding in both subjects. The nameless is, without a doubt, the best horror film lapped in this country. Scripts of stories such as fragile or Darkness, - so good times have made us move to lovers of the genre-, above all American employers to become the future of cinema that we want to see. The conception of [REC], frankly, disappointed. All of which leads to the belief that the only thing scary in this film are kilometric queues that have to be overcome in albaceteños theaters, to fall on one side of the row two and eighty-five minutes of camera shoulder support. Paul, recorded all this, by your mother!.</body>
</review>
