<review author="Bloody Will" title="La joven del agua" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To Shyamalan not it fails him never an original idea, and always comes with something new. Get that very few cineastan achieved, and is that viewers expect from impatient way each one of his films.</summary>
	<body>M. Night Shyamalan achieved what very few cineastan achieved, and is that viewers expect from impatient way each one of his films. They like more or less, but its screening is mandatory for those who like well structured film.To Shyamalan not it fails him never an original idea, and always comes with something new. In the sixth sense it left us speechless all this way no one saw coming, a milestone in the history of cinema. The protected defrauded many by deviate from the path of terror and setting up a history of good and evil with a rather anticlimactic ending. With signals he returned to a semi-terror with shadows in the roofs and footprints behind doors. No one expected that the Martians appearing, and that cabreó more people. The forest was a hoax for many who, seeing the trailer, went to see a history of horror with monsters and found something deeper and more mundane.The problem is there. If you're going to see cheese, because the announcement teaches cheese give you meat in the film fuck much. The trailer for young water sells a history of horror with ruthless monsters and however we have a fantastic, child and romantic tale with its good and its bad, but a story in short. Who is nears to the cinema to see another thing will be throwing pests.This speech serves to understand why this film has failed with the public. Shyamalan is her has played several times and some may be weary of so many flourishes to tell a story. If above it confuses the staff in progress, Word of mouth can be relentless. The reason for the machaque of critique I can understand that to some extent. He is needed to view this movie go with good clean mind movies, forgetting who is headed and what went before. Putting you in time in history will leave the room with the feeling that have told you the story before sleeping with a masterly staging. If you fail, you can say that the water young is the greatest mental straw until the date of a so-called egomaníaco M. Night Shyamalan. It's clear. I am the first, but I'm not so obtuse as to not understand that you can have seconds to lots.Cleveland (Giamatti) is wrong - everything from a residential one night discovers a mysterious young woman (Dallas Howard) exit of the communal pool. This young man is a narf, creature out of an old fairy tale, and has to return to his world, dodging a monster that lurks. To return to where it belongs, you will need the help of Cleveland and other tenants of the complex, which will have to be stripped of their prejudices to accept the role in the fantasy world of the narf.Paul Giamatti maintains that stereotype of insecure man and tragic past which is so typical of Shyamalan, giving more deferential than the usual Willis or Gibson tone. His performance is impeccable in the meantime chaos, and her scene in the sofa, behaving like a kid of five years to know more of the story where it leaves the narf, is perhaps the best summary of what the film itself, a story emerged from the mind of a child. What seems more incredible is that a normal person questioned so little the fantastic origin of an aunt out of a swimming pool. I guess that digest it in several days to stop the pace of the film, but it collides a bit.The counterpoint is given by Bryce Dallas Howard, which is not to have too many lines despite being present in the footage. Their role is quiet but extremely expressive. He already went well in the Woods, and I cannot imagine what would have been in the hands of another actress. Meets the aim of ample form. Sufficient, but in the negative sense, is the decision of the director of becoming an actor. In other film out in the form of cameo. Here is a fairly major role, and only leads me to believe that he has wanted to reserve role unnecessarily. Makes me have suspicion to his character without knowing very well how explain it, and is without a doubt the worst speaking interpretations among all the cast that makes up the residential where it appears the young protagonist.The young of the water is a film where each and every one of the characters must find its place in the salvation of the narf operation, but also in the world. So many comings and turns can be confusing, but the pieces fit in the end. It is aesthetically impressive. Visually it has no comparison with anything that we have seen this year. But will also be misunderstood among a large segment of the public. It is as if Shyamalan needed urgent way giving all his films a transcendental Fund that overwhelms who has no desire to many complications. This is Shyamalan but the error is in turn into blockbusters with stratospheric pretensions of box office over movies that are primarily personal bets.If creiste that the forest was a joke, with the young of the water will end up in life with this director. Others continue to impatient before each release of a director, that with the threat of being misunderstood by industry, can end up taking turn to their way of conceiving the film, and would be a pity, because even a few we like to tell stories, which is very different to a succession of events.</body>
</review>
