<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="La vida interior de Martin Frost" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting film of Paul Auster, poorly received by critics in the past Donostia 2007 International Film Festival.</summary>
	<body>"Martin Frost, a successful writer, has just published a book when he decides to retire to a country house for a time." Waking up the first morning, Frost discovers a mysterious and dazzling woman lying beside him surprised.Fascinated with her beauty and intelligence, Martin love deeply for her and thinks that he has met his muse will help to write his best novel. who is this mysterious woman who so well know his life and his work? It will be a real Muse? Is it your imagination? "Is she a ghost that has crept into the private life of Martin Frost?"Excellent idea of Paul Auster, fails all its perfect translation to the screen. The film was not well received by the critics of the International Festival of cinema of Donostia 2007 but my yes I quite liked, and during the first fifty minutes or so, I thought was simply wonderful. I believe that, during this footage, Auster manages to tell of how beautiful, a tender and emotional love story between a writer in search of his work and a beautiful and enigmatic unknown that he sneaks into the House of some friends who have given to get away from the madding crowd and write quiet.With only two characters, and with some simple and clear dialogs, as well as intelligent silences, the story flows easily, impregnating the viewer of purification sensations, where unconditional love tries to overcome fears and fears of shameful secrets.The two characters we are close and friendly, very nice and intimate, while it is not known who and what has gone there. This intrigue, to so call it, is appealing and the interest is maintained.However, suddenly, when the data start to shed light on the mystery, the magic of the film lapses significantly, despite the appearance on the scene of a third character, an expert in plumbing and installations homemade, very fun and much derision. Thanks to this unique character we laugh at their fancy literary ideas, but we also saw a fall of rhythm and dramatic intensity, magnified with the appearance of the fourth character, played by the daughter of Auster, Sophie. A beautiful girl with a beautiful voice, but that frankly adds nothing to the story, giving the impression of being a beautiful decorative object for comfort of his father. Thus, by the way, it gives know. However, I think it is an estimable film, although certainly it is more a less. But the general final computer think it is positive. Now, all the critics that I spoke of the film, only to two had convinced them. So &hellip;</body>
</review>
