<review author="José A. Peig" title="La brújula dorada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not simple enough that children can understand it, nor nor uses the dramatic and symbolic items with sufficient intensity and capacity of fascination and to capture the attention of adult audiences.</summary>
	<body>From the first seconds - that mimic the beginning of the Fellowship of the ring, part of the successful trilogy by Peter Jackson - check that, unfortunately, once again we have a brand product, prefabricated to try to repeat the commercial effect based on a few formulas, which recipe for a sure success. New Line bet again by a épico-fantástica history of literary origin, this time tinged with a philosophical, already not so digestible cut for audiences of any age and condition, contrary to the story of Frodo and the ring. Without dare to make forecasts, of course - see the result as a whole - would not be strange to see how the bet sinks and becomes a commercial for a product that dramatic failure for months was announced as the beginning of a trilogy designed to leave a significant mark on the movie fan and popular culture. The content of the story is interesting and has the ingredients all fantastic epic must have, but the narrative fails altogether. Lyra Belaqua embodies the journey of the hero, essential in the cinema of fantastic adventures, as it forces the canon established from the best exponents with an effective outcome: the contraataca(Irvin_Kershner,_1980) Empire or even the aforementioned community of the ring (Peter Jackson, 2001), or within the labyrinth (Jim Henson, 1986). The key is to make the spectator to be involved in the journey of the protagonists, with all the playful, dramatic or symbolic elements that tend to enrich this kind of stories, at the same time, have made the film the best means to express universal reasons through the playful spirit of adventure (literature is an art which has also given excellent results in this area)(, but by reason of saving time, the film is much more accessible to the vast majority of the public). The canon does not establish an inviolable rule, but a sign of the singularity in a specific narrative intention, a compass that leads us to recognize - arguably - what is well done and it is not well done, something that in the end the passage of time shows us, surpassing the test of subjectivity. The Golden Compass has an excellent production design, good use of photography and the contrasts between spaces of a Victorian architecture and the geographies of a desert of ice. The story aims to become allegory on the control of information (the truth), and this is the best weapon of the powers that be. Raises an opposition between freedom and authority inconsistent and very questionable (do have to accept, because Yes, that only can be free to destroy the authority?), inspired by the Catholic institution to represent the sinister guardians of the secret (do?). The interrelationship between parallel universes defines part of the enigma and the situation that the adventurers must amend in next installments. A world of fascinating and visually represented effectively theme, but to which Chris Weitz can't give soul. The dramatic articulation does not exist, but a set of spare parts (lousy use of mounting and irregular rhythm) which, although well sorted for the narration can continue smoothly, appear too half-hearted and fleeting, there is a common thread to concentrate the attention to that small heroin - and its antagonistic - grasp of the hand to the viewer and can it engage in the adventure. And one problem still serious: the own lack of definition of the product. It is not simple enough that children can understand it, nor nor uses the dramatic and symbolic items with sufficient intensity and capacity of fascination and to capture the attention of adult audiences. Ultimately, only results in a bland pastiche, an excellent idea desaprovechada, which only saves some turbid stream, interesting chemistry in the relationship between Lyra and the polar bear and minimal hope that can trace the flight in the two films that are missing.</body>
</review>
