<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Luz de Domingo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cloying at times. Sober, at times. Astonishing at times. Boring, at times. Garci is Garci: a man with a path and a professional ethic technological bomb-proof. It deserves, however, worth going into their game.</summary>
	<body>José Luis Garci is an endearing character. Endearing to the way in which it is Christmas or an autumn walk to the fall of the evening. Garci is one of those men that you can confess your cinephiles without this millstone nor top you Geek of the day. You can drop you that Douglas Sirk has given you wonderful nights on television (blockbusters forty years ago that he stopped to the German master program) or indie film, this invention of the majors to demonstrate to the unwary that are modern, giving you creeps, rash and cholera limited access. Garci listens to you as a good father and is even possible that believe you the Vice of Italian neorealism (which didn't have no bloody idea) or of the nouvelle vague (that you sounded to Marlon Brando putting butter in the ass his plump girlfriend). Garci (follow the thread) can make you understand already forever the magic of the cinema above the film as an industry. And this not so never ever thought and you content with going to the movies, take the time and come out with a bobalicona smile in the face and five euros less in the portfolio. His how great cinema is illuminated the squalid landscape of film information in the idiot box, but morality and the use of good practices banned smoking as a gangster of the RKO and planted to RTVE and took his film, his love for cinema and its always witty (and sometimes invited Plast, see the ínclito Prada De) hometo liven up the Sunday afternoons around a fireplace and a soft jazz good Fund. Garci (already conclude this apologetic Introit) like always. His film falls well also. His classicism, his genuine vision of the made aesthetic can be seen and there is even a label (a recognizable authorship) that permeates dialogues, photography and soundtrack.So the filmmaker José Luis Garci is clear that he has a language (grammar, read in connection with the premiere of the grandfather years ago) and a detectable universe. Azorín, Galdós, Baroja, Clarín, Pérez de Ayala, Delibes and similar provided his prose of bells to the speculation of this man, which draws films with some regularity. Films that inevitably smell to Hollywood, red carpet and canijos, when not invisible Goyas.Garci cinema, in the words of a friend, is stale and perfect, languid and allowed, boring and perfect. The perfect is mine. The problem (mine at least) is not Garci: I am.Light of Sunday, his last tape, is a pure play, a rich recreation in detail of the tyranny of early 20th century in the deep Spain, a story of impossible love, violence rustic - in the manner of Peckinpah in straw dogs or more head-on Deliverance of Boorman, no excessive difference - exerted by gentlemen of people. It is a pure work, without folds language, but I don't know if the purity is important to art or, on the contrary, these modern times, aupados in Vertigo, enfebrecidos by love of money and the unfortunately insensitive to the talent if talent not requires visual pirotecnica, scripts with trick in the last line or assassins in series with knowledge of quantum mechanics and ease in Kant and Renaissance poetrythey do not require Garci movies. It is possible. Until the own Garci (read in some newspaper) you want to see the film as a kind of western rural, castizo, Hispanic and chewed in the light of a bagpipe. The error is in me, curious reader: in the extension of my phobias made public and not projected on the screen. Garci makes Garci as James Bond takes life with Bond girls and permission to kill and fornicate on distant islands of the financial path. Its gap is analog, as we have said, the open road is nineteenth-century which goes on to say that it is not actually breaking ground but - film to movie - you are entering in an admirable and to some extent legitimate time warp, that took him to what we have said: to Sirk, Preminger to Cukor, to all the formidable movies made to be enjoyed by future generationsadmire and consider this - pixel, digital, impeccable in the technical aspect, but orphan of soul - him fails nor to the first roll of coiling.I thought seeing the grandfather in all this and somehow tell here now. This review - except for the strictly temporary detail of the film - could be for the great film of a great Fernando Fernán-Gómez, escaped already knew him or where. The folletín has become: today, at least, has become. Characters abismados in their sorrows and sparsely salvables, worlds of a rusticity resistant movement, players in State of grace (Carlos Larrañaga, who did not remember except for loose scenes of zapping pink, is Goya, I do not know if it is much or little). Light of Sunday (precious title) does not fool any of their two potential audiences: who knows what and which has no idea who he is Garci and to what extent is able to amaze us or suffocate us-based table stretcher, time stamps and impostados dialogues. The film, a lengthy flashback, is - in the background, perhaps in the background - a breath of fresh air inside. Curious paradox: the old ilumiando what's new, the outburst classic imposing his patron to the modern feeling. Perhaps why light of Sunday deserves more of what (I'm sure) will receive. People, these two hypothetical public, are already tired of the variegated ordinary television, never better written folletín. People will not realize the scope of this proposal, its climate rupture within its stagnation, and that (in the light of these already described times) is not the order of the day. The rhythm is right, the texture of the images cloying, but suits the passage of those events that recounts. However, I imagine that the story will continue: you walk Garci already looking for another folletín of time and looking for landscapes, urban of the 19th century in the 21st and expensive locations that express what they Galdós thought. Don't have to go far: just pull filmography, plug the DVD and see his work. The story of the film is reventona of people that has not done anything other than the same movie. I open floor. Garci is the national candidate for the award.</body>
</review>
