<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="La Sombra del Reino" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I liked (and entertaining) enough, but with certain reservations in the USA should start to accept so exhorcitar their ghosts...</summary>
	<body>Since some time ago, provided that I've seen the poster, or trailers of the tape, thanks to my another page ("movie buff Oracle") I was interested, and simultaneously intrigued about this movie, which I fail to excite me, unlike "Lions for Lambs" this, I liked it enough, saving, what I said at the time that in USA are not able to accept that Iraq is becoming for them the 2nd Viet Nam, and that, unfortunately, and much that love them, can't go for the world of "saviours for freedom" (and less maxime) when this is done by dint of shooting.Having said that, I admit that not only the tape I liked, but in addition the 110 min. which lasts approx. it have happened to me flying, both by the script, well-constructed and quite surround, as well as for the performances of Jamie Foxx, Chris Cooper, Jennifer Garner, Jason Bateman and Jeremy Piven, incidentally, Mrs Garner (or Mrs Affleck) has a pretty funny moment in the film, where cannot be avoided "dread" that feels to hear an explosion near (very wise not to bend his yell.)priceless, that moment.The hand of Michael Mann, is noticeable enough, since sometimes the tape seems debtor of this film, also Peter Berg is seen an excellent good do onscreen, and makes every moment, by removing what I have already said and excessively "lagrimógeno" somewhere, so that in his facet as a director, we have a great future director of gender (I see as you do in his upcoming films), I would add also the excellent score by Danny Elfman (as it could not be otherwise), taking advantage of these Arab touches, overlooking the packaging the necessary film to make this completely digested by the Viewer. Bran and short distances you; I liked (and entertaining) enough, but with certain reservations in the USA should start to accept so exhorcitar their ghosts.</body>
</review>
