<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="30 días de oscuridad" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a very dark and entertaining onstage version. Does not make the version of cult, but if it will undoubtedly become a new point of reference for copy and consider when making a new version.</summary>
	<body>They have been very few tapes who manage to stay in my memory of the zombie genre and/or vampires. However, 30 days of night is the exception to something which is already considered to be a personal rule. This film premiered at United States in the last season of Halloween, is the film version of a comic Steven Niles participated in the script for this version and Ben Templesmith whose initial idea was intended to be brought to the big screen but received refusals, became a successful comic whose first publication occurred in the year 2002. In countries such as United States and Spain, deliveries of this comic have exceeded sales unthinkable, turning it into the 3rd best-selling format in the world comic.On this occasion the vampires are taken to Barrow in Alaska, which is the northernmost region of the United States and the population located more to the North around the world to make their own, taking advantage of the event that year after year there, happens to the stay the population two months exactly, in complete darkness during the winter season. Therefore the natural conditions of Barrow, make its inhabitants the perfect feast for these vampires, impressing the claustrophobic atmosphere generated because of the absence of light.It is a 1: 53 minutes where evokes the horror genre to ancient and where the suspense was strategically planned in each of the scenes with a quick pace that contradicts what some comments mentioned early in this regard. Seduces the terrifying characterization made this "species" and not understandable language in which communicate. At this point, I join the voices that highlighted this and mentioned that the strange language that talk about vampires, you more credibility to the tape, unlike many other films, where beings coming from distant worlds or even our but totally isolated to our way of life can understand us and even better talks with us. Furthermore, as beings that Act almost like animals the use of this resource for the good of film is minimal.Within 30 days of darkness or night as it resulted in Colombia, no room for religious salvation, because no Holy instrument is valid for terminating them. Here it is only finishing them behind and ruthless form as they do with humans. For this reason, blood wheel for all parties but not hastía. And after all this serious hits and well-managed events, comes his unexpected final away any pink termination but with great beauty at the same time, with which you're satisfied the film and with a very good taste.As every movie heroes and villains, the battle occurs, but not drew you enough benefit. This is his greatest failure. The fight between the protagonist, a sheriff and the vampire King of the herd, is bland and fairly easily unlike what fans of the comic happens. Incidentally and thanks to the participation of the same creator on the screenplay for the film, each other is distinguished only by some details. The other point, are its main actors Josh Hartnett still not suupera her acclaimed performance in Black Haw down in 2001, but that sorprede for its versatility that we have seen this in various roles in almost all genres and Melissa George, remembered for his role in the film tourists last year, because both do their job even though they do not Excel, especially Mellissa whose performance is little spontaneous. 30 days of night does not ends for sale worldwide and will be part of the Billboard in many countries next year, so I recommend it because it is a very dark and entertaining vampirezca version. Does not make the version of worship that many would expect, but if it will undoubtedly become a new point of reference for copy and consider when making a new version.</body>
</review>
