<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="The Nanny Diaries (Diario de una Niñera)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The problem of this failed film is that not have been fool by a child dye and despite the deal, which is to shoot rockets, not just take off in no time.</summary>
	<body>I'm going to be very bad with this film because for misfortune of the writers being Nancy is something very common for our country when we do this attempt to learn another language. So given that I had the misfortune and at the same time care for kids (9 to be exact as I gave with my bones at a day-care center instead of in a house) and dealing with parents, grandparents, teachers and derivatives.Yes, I admit that put me before that so divine Scarlett playing a role commensurate with its age causes me a certain child excitement that ten minutes has disappeared almost completely. The film narrates the adventures of Annie in the big city. She lives in Jersey with his mom who has taken care to eliminate the Institute and now they have to start their first steps in working life. A little anxious that crisis that nobody in e real world may have decided to take the summer to find herself and by a small accident in the Park ends up being internal Babysitting at a home in the fifth Avenida.Y here is where I get pejiguera that with such mediocre raw at least I hope that me they entertained and a little fun and do not succeed. The writers are going in directions that little or nothing have to do with comedy losing in a tape that rides between the children films and teen film. A product that they dare even to copy (put them on foot) to Mary Poppins, Idol of any Nanny in looming or exnanny that boasts with two staggering references: the umbrella and Supercalibragilisticoespialidoso. I would already like to the Johansson having grace with the children who, even today, continues to have Julie Andrews.El this failed tape problem is that not have been fool by a child dye and despite the deal, which is to shoot rockets, not just take off in no time. Fails a single genuine laughter of the public more than 10 years that to succeed in the Christmas billboard is very well but in the resumes of Scarlett, Laura Linney, Paul Giamatti and even for the idol of teenagers Chris Evans (who is not annoyed or teaching torso so that it entertains me awhile). A penalty have so much and so little.</body>
</review>
