<review author="Iñigo" title="Lutero" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>From the deeper indifference to the most unwavering sopor</summary>
	<body>"It seems that, for some time here, the narrate the life of a historic and important character to fill the lack of ideas is turning in a free resource too overused and not always convincing results.""Luther", the film that concerns us, is one of the most clear examples of this. It's a work possessing an impeccable technical invoice, but not beyond the purely technical fanfare and a couple of ideas without deepening, as it is happening lately with this kind of (super) nature of biopic productions.The film ends up being very irregular, and manages to lose their limited interest even the most renegade followers of Catholic belief. It could be argued that all of their footage is only interesting from the moment that seeks to expose the fraud and bribery of the Church, a fraud that takes advantage of the misfortunes, shortcomings, convictions and illusions of the people with the unique and pure profit.But, how could it be otherwise, as described here as we have seen it hundreds of times in film and literature. Without going any further, films such as "Stigmata" already looked the quote of: "The Kingdom of God is within you, not in the constructions of wood and stone." Part a trunk of wood and I am there, lifts a stone and I will find. "."Eric Till, father of this creature, is that our particular Lutero will not be reflected as a mere rebel, but barely, ends up succumbing. Its intention to place it as a standard-bearer martyr does not stop convince nor move. Only we immerse ourselves in the idea that the character is not more than another victim for the inevitable. A victim of the fallacy that surrounds us in trying to expose the Church, a task, at times, close to utopian after centuries of power. And, why not say it, with possible so unnecessary as destructive consequences for humanity.For this reason, Luther, in certain scenes, could strain as a misunderstood classic, by both fans and detractors. Thus, as yet another occasion, our inexorable fate leads to the error. And the consequences. And the blame. But also to the obtaining of new directions.Unfortunately, as I said at the beginning of my criticism, the film not tells us nothing we don't already know. And is his main error: that shortage in the section of the originality, so patent today in products of this spirit. And the cast does not help to meet its many shortcomings. It is little more than correct in its entirety, with a Fiennes who plays no more than his intense gaze. Not even the great Bruno Ganz (which represents sanity supported Luther) stands out above the average.In short, a work that has interesting although I points very sobados, and half is in almost everything. Fails to deepen enough character nor historical accuracy that she herself begins. And, as a result, ends up producing the most absolute of the indifference.And many viewers to the most unwavering sopor.</body>
</review>
