<review author="Javier Moreno" title="United 93" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>United 93 is probably the best film of what it far this year. Do case to most of the criticism, take scarves just in case.</summary>
	<body>Five years after September 11. That fateful date, everyone could live, attend one of the greatest tragedies of recent history. Many analysts, journalists. They said that that day started the twenty-first century. Three aircraft crashed against terrorist targets, one not.Paul Greengrass, director of films such as Bloody Sunday or the Bourne Ultimatum decided to focus on that plane, that which according to investigations was shot down by a group of anonymous heroes who already knew the previous echos and not willing to be used as a means to cause more victims. Obviously their highest intention wasn't other than save lives, but they did not.We all know the echos, know what happened in that Flight 93, what interest is making a film on an echo of which we know his tragic end?.Pay homage to the victims of terrorism.United 93 is possibly the best tribute that can receive these people that fateful day died because a few bastards decided to start a crusade against the West. We could also take it as a tribute to the victims of terrorism in Spain or in any part of the world, because at the end and all, their only sin was belong to a society away from doctrines extremists.The first 45 minutes of the film, British director them used to situate ourselves prior to the axis of the tragedy that aims to show us. The first moments of that black day, with the impact of the two first aircraft (shown through radar and without using real images captured by CNN except in specific cases), the perplexity of the authorities, the chaos in the different airport control towers and military command occurs, a chaos narrated with camera on his shoulder, from a distance, without knowing who's who. We only have names, anonymous people of which we do not know his private life (as will happen when the director of focus on the plane in question). This distance allows put to us in situation, Paul Greengrass asks patience through these images, everything has to come, and filmmaker knows that he must show, but makes no sense do. With parsimony, unhurried, narrating on time each of the echos and showing us every anonymous hero more than firefighters, who that day flourished in the control towers. One that first detects the possibility of an abduction, Ben Slimey (giving life likewise) that took the decision to not allow any flight more in North American air space, Mayor James Foxx (also giving life likewise) did everything possible to achieve the presidential permission to shoot down the aircraft heading to Washington.En that moment we introduce in the planeIt is kidnapped. Again with camera to shoulder and testimonial music that passes unnoticed during almost all footage we dabble in situation, and surprisingly it makes us feel part of that small group of hostages, we are one more and we espeluznamos to what you see (especially the last 20 minutes). It is here where the emotions unleashed, passengers know what happened, they call their families to say goodbye and we us shuddering at what we see. Passengers revolt against the terrorists, and extolling us with them, we feel the need to open the head to one of those sons of bitches, we believe that there is hope that a happy ending is possible, we reached the cabin with them. and the screen cuts to black. We woke up and it was not a movie, but the recreation of a few real facts, and we are aware that there was no happy ending. Diving in the armchair, crestfallen, one suppressing tears them, others crying openly, we got up and we left the film sorry, without understanding because, without knowing that demons did.There is no policy in this pesudodocumental, there is no hatred, there is no bitterness, no patriotic posts, or an American flag in the foreground, no sign that makes Greengrass to opt for a detail or another, even humanizes the terrorists in what is perhaps the decision more controversy of the film (but which do not you be wanting to raison d ' être). Only people, human beings, victims of the injustice of which we are part. As I said earlier, the estrangement from which is narrated the film, away from apatizarnos, it allows us to be part of it, as each one of those anonymous people who perished that day, we are them and they are us.United 93 is a very emotional film without pretending to be him, United 93 is probably the best film of what it far this year. Do case to most of the criticism, take scarves just in case.</body>
</review>
