<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La brújula dorada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film of epic fantasy and adventurous breath you are Taming in excess. They are doing with him have done before with the adventure or the terror: check mediocrity. That Yes, this is a commendable invoice. Lacks it soul...</summary>
	<body>So much fantastic saga overwhelms, at least; It feels cornered by Golden compasses, power rings, cosmopolitan cabinets and Dragons more ready than a primary. The weight of the responsibility in the Affairs of the imagination infatil and teenager has gone to the major producers of the movie business. Where before flying Gianni Rodari, Perrault, the Brothers Grimm, Michael Ende or now seems forgotten Roald Dahl now plans to the Disney and their greed to make box and on the way, train customers to make box: from father to son. Seeing the film Golden Compass, saw families (mine included) complete showing boredom, excitement, drowsiness or even misunderstanding to what the screen ametraballaba rhythm of zeppelins art-deco, lavish colleges and bears with shell resembling gods of Olympus. Myself, believer in the religion of the fantasy, I was trapped in a cascade of impeccable images, made no doubt that with passion and budget holgadísimo, but devoid of soul. And this is already standard in all these franchises of bonancible inclination, although talented orphan, too outstanding to the box office and the previews of the characters. In fact, before entering the room I already had the opportunity to see how the outrage of lusty infographics Marines loaded in a burger bar by the side of the puppets in the film room. All added formidably orchestrated so that the experience would be multidisciplinary and beatific. The room that we enter what we call context, was packed mixed gender: gangs of teenagers with acne and mobile generation, large families, couples also varied spectrum of sexual e even spotted - distance, as wanting to be unseen - a pair of grandparents, I do not know if lost or well versed in the field, expected with satisfaction face turn off the lights and the thunderous symphonism of dolby surround. Then comes the visual feast tromba: impeccable architecture Victorian, impeccable design costume, impeccable choice of cast. What hurts us, then, in the soul? It hurts that the epic fantasy or, in this case, fantástico-filosófico (and up anti-Catholic) to read is in the film a milkshake though shaken and conveniently administered in collectible fascicles (today the first) of elements already known, already assumed, already tasted by teenage or pre-teen gourmet (the child is not going to catch that a metaphysical powder and a kindergarten boarding school to a retro machine steals one half and makes them adults)(, as if that does not happen only a few years later).The Golden Compass us reconciles with the (endearing) Family Act of going to the cinema if a religious act concerned. Well supplied advertising, tired of see on the shelves of stores and libraries always the Tower of volumes of Philip Pullman (dark matter, three thick deliveries), went to see what we are going to give now, what pastillitas of colors to liven up the leisure of a holiday. The amazement lasts just enough: the titles of credits and a voice that tells the bleak and cuasimístico argument in a plis plas delivered a trip not always understood, cumbersome at times, in which a girl marked by some sortilegio or divine whim or ancestral legend must save the world. The conglomerate of elements of success contrasted in companies such (animal that they speak, until one baby to morro; lavish landscapes; witches that fly and colossal battles; bad very bad and armies blessed.) not given here with the key lighting.Fantasy has its empire, its codes, its polar travel and up his Golden Compass oblivious to this: all the formidable matter herein is to encourage imagination. I have clear to better this gazpacho report (I am Andalusian, want) Magic domesticated than punches to navigate in the lower depths of any finely digitized urban environment. The saga sinks already in his first voyage. It is slap to the clever producer and his entourage of bienintecionados (no doubt) workers how it is possible to leave to the public resptable always so in albis, as sharply raised seat. More parties are clear. I do not know if the second installment opens new illusions. Mine, except imponderables, will as you say, do not go. It will be at home watching something on DVD. Or reading. Long that does not recommend, in the abstract, reading. The reading without commitment. Happy reading. Reading in the light of a flexo while outside the world is delivered to their vices. Some, as we know, ancestral. Today I have at hand the invisible cities by Italo Calvino. I I read some time ago and has returned today. Perhaps some of the movie I saw last night (and now I'm explaining) has guilt. Mysteries of the film.</body>
</review>
