<review author="Raccord" title="Vértigo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Completely overrated and worst of Hitchcock. A story too stupid to take it seriously</summary>
	<body>Praised by critics, and considered one of the best films in the history of the cinema, to my seems completely overrated and worst of Hitchcock. A story too stupid to take it seriously and a completely sloppy character development, with touches of fantasy film stuck with shoehorn. Another bike trying to sell us. Hitchcock appears to have problems to create characters with whom the viewer identify. In fact it is the common denominator of his more loose films (are Topaz, to catch a thief, the shadow of a doubt?). But also appears on some of the best, as for example Rebecca: they are technically brilliant films, with very elaborate plots, but instances of cold and flat characters, that they do not connect with the viewer and which are little credible. In "Vertigo" ", I care very little, what happen to James Stewart, if you have fear of heights, or if he has fallen in love with a spirit." It is that honestly not have given me information that I identify with him and see him wander with the face of concern throughout the film, without the minimum interest for what should happen and believe me its character or a moment.Another recurring feature of Hitchcock is to show two readings of his characters, making the darker side of his personality, hidden to the other characters, is many times the real driving force for their actions. Great successes, are sometimes achieved but in Vertigo, it is very difficult to realize the intentions of the director and the interpretation of the strange behavior of the protagonist is already taken absolutely far-fetched. If you do not read the famous book of conversations with Truffaut, surely not you realize, that I actually wanted to do the orondo director was a study of necrophilia. Surprising, but adds nothing when enjoy the film, and in the case of the preceding paragraph; It produces only indifference. Furthermore I believe that he says little about the quality of his work, who is unable to show its purposes in a clear and understandable way, and expose them cryptically that only fans can decipher them.If we add to this a plot soporifera, improper English master, which consists of discovering with the friend James if Kim Novak this dead, mad, or asshole, we have left a very poor film. There are some tricks of very advanced special effects for its time and a pretty good soundtrack. The rest is boring and very pretentious.</body>
</review>
