<review author="Berto" title="La joven del agua" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entertaining movie, very style Shyamalan, but which has details that do not become the great movie that could have been, is only a tale for children already creciditos.</summary>
	<body>M Night Shyamalan has done again it. Already with his sixth sense sold us a film incredibly boring, Yes, with an end of the very best that to raise the entire film again. Later he followed this with the protégé, parody/tale of superheroes that surround us and that although not bad at all was not what promised. With signs, falls into the easy packaging of Hollywood and alien fashion, that if, with a history a bit higher than the average, and finally in the forest he served a thriller also correct, with far-fetched end and that only highlights the performances of its protagonists. Sack this summary in the wake of the premiere of his latest film, the girl of water, and on this occasion we sold as a fairy story, typical to tell to children before going to sleep. In this story it tells us as a nymph of the blue world, find a special man that can guide men towards a universal change, away from this wave of self-destruction toward which we inevitably. In the swimming pool of a community of neighbours in Philadelphia you'll find with the goalkeeper, which help him escape from a creature that attempted to put an end to it, at the time that she has q find that special person and get return back to his world.Told the argument, placing it in a magical country or plan middle ages, well it could be the plot of the upcoming Disney movie for Christmas, but no, it is a fairy tale located next to our House, and as every fairy tale that boasts the most important is to believe on foot juntillas everything what is happening throughout the storybecause fate? but the 10 minute film we will have to abandon the film to find some meaning, metaphor, or rare thought is a full chimera. Fantastic things are assumed by all the protagonists in a blind manner and without evidence, and that's what we have to do us, launch into the void of seeing is believing. The story has its details, good in some cases, as for example the way to locate the creature, and bad in some other cases again, as for example the way the interpreter read what they have to do, totally misguided for my taste.The main characters, the best by far of the film. Paul Giamatti making goalkeeper of the apartments is simply great, and their interpretation is the best of the film, followed by Bryce Dallas Howard, which this quite well in his role as narf, although on many occasions simply is to put Princess Elf of Lothlorien forests face. By the way, is the daughter of Ron Howard, not as I read out there somewhere that another criticism that she is the daughter of James Newton Howard, author of the soundtrack for the film, also the best of the film, accompanying history wisely.The other characters of the building are quite archetypal, that if the tiny group of colleagues smoked, the old that loves animals, foreign student, the Platypus, the grips chulito, although on this occasion with a rather special training? and what disturbs totally is the critical film that moves to nothing more start the film. Is clear that some criticize something he did to Shyamalan, because but do not understand like this got this character so to shoehorn and with so much bad baba, leaving it to the height of bitumen and launching a veiled poisoned dagger so many critics have criticized up but not being able to his earlier work. Shyamalan also plays a role in the film, which does not like me, were very well their previous fleeting cameos to the Hitchcock, but given a role in the film I think it adds nothing, having professional actors that I fixed, fixed, can do as well as or even better.His work as a director there the movie is impeccable. All his plans have a mission in the film, show what the want to show and none this post there randomly. As only downside to his work with the camera, would be the excessive use of the blur to guide the viewer view where the want to look, but looking for a parallel with the same story you could say that it is something like go to guide us while we read the lines of the story film.In short, an entertaining film, very style Shyamalan, but which has details that do not become the great movie that could have been, leaving only a tale to already creciditos children who still believe that there are fairies.</body>
</review>
