<review author="Dario Lavia" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spiritual concepts in Hollywood film.</summary>
	<body>Raised in the film three narrative strands, differentiated (in principle) by the protagonist (Hugh Jackman) haircut. 1. A Spanish conqueror lost in the thicket of the Guatemalan jungle is determined to find the supposedly legendary "Tree of life", having to maintain his iron will despite the disloyalty of their subordinates or the aboriginal resistance. 2 - Dr. Tom Creo, a research physician who has his young wife Izzi (Rachel Weisz) sick of terminal cancer, run a race against the clock by checking if the novel compound obtained on the basis of a Central American plant species is able to back not only the process of ageing of an ape but also a tumor carcinogenic. 3 - A suprahumana entity that lives in a planetoid with a tree species about to die is rush your trip Astral through outer space in pursuit of a star adored by the ancient Maya.Of the three, is the second (we assume) which raises the real history of the film. It is the beautiful Izzi which gives her husband a book that she has been writing with the romantic story of the Conqueror Spanish across an ocean to save his Queen and find the legendary source that a Franciscan father claims to have evidence that there is. This literary plot is which gives rise to the first story that unfolds as a mythical version of the tragedy of the marriage I think. This vision of reality, jumped to a metaphysical analysis, with the completely shaved doctor and taking the position of the Lotus in order to raise their level cosmic and spiritual (according to the transcendental hierarchy of the discovery that plans to carry out). The error philosophical consider death as an illness resolves in three frames with brightness lyrical, both visual and artistic, leaving clear (at least during the denouement of the film) to die is not a trauma but the most important event in life.</body>
</review>
