<review author="Dario Lavia" title="Perversidad" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fritz Lang addresses a thorny issue and gives that speak to public, critics and censors.</summary>
	<body>Is it possible to make two films with identical ingredients and that both are different? One year Fritz Lang had offered one of his masterpieces of the American period, THE WOMAN IN THE WINDOW (the woman of the table-1944), and the next proposed take their same elements to make an adaptation of the novel "La Chienne" (1931) of Fouchardiere Georges (which had been brought to the screen by Jean Renoir). So starts the story with the timid bank employee Chris Cross (Edward g. Robinson), which leaves a dinner of coworkers in which of the Chief gift him a watch for 25 years of service and stumbles upon what appears to be a damsel in distress (Joan Bennett). Of course, the mature man is fascinated as a teenager of the sympathy of the young, which indeed is bride of a street malviviente (Dan Duryea) who kisses her and slaps alike (its cafiolo). The situation soon becomes subject of tango: she is shown as complacent and begins to ask for money, a Department for live, subtracts it his paintings (Cross is describe painter) and sells them. Again have a candid, manipulated (and even having) Robinson by the circumstances of the fate but largely by the vagaries of the beautiful Joan Bennett (also becomes "woman in painting"). Again, the villain is Dan Duryea and again has bow and straw hat. However, here ends the equivalence between both films of Lang. The tone of the film is not entirely seriously (in a timely manner a crime ends with all possible air comedy), and the course of history is clearly tragic and realistic (as opposed to La table woman who was joyful and dreams). There are memorable characters ("the deceased husband of the table" seems to preanunciar a common situation of the Italian comedy of the 1950s), sharp dialogues and own the most sordid melodrama German pesadillescos and tense climates. And also a milestone, which is to be the first film in which a crime remains unpunished (which in turn joined the modus operandii for the aforementioned murder earned Lang various problems with censorship). Will be the director confessing of an old crime of passion? If that is the case, after the flow of topics, emotions and situations of both films, we believe that we can give you forgiveness.</body>
</review>
