<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="La joven del agua" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Same history itself is the worst of all, with remnants of stories caught here and there, mixed with mythology and popular belief patterns, a conglomerate of inconsistencies in the service of the aesthetic power.</summary>
	<body>Too often the trailer of the film is more interesting than the tape that promotes. That can occur them with the advance of this film, one more in the race to the bottom of a filmmaker, M. Night Shyamalan, which in 1999 reached a global and unexpected success with the sixth sense, the only tape of terror in a built filmography on the combined bases of genres ranging from fantasy to suspense. It is clear that a title so famous it can not live of for life, although some if they can exploit the Philo. The M. Night Shyamalan friend falls into account while the eerie title, caught with pins, is already very far. He repeated in formulas that seemed to work him as well, giving the impression that the multifaceted filmmaker is entering a creative crisis and maybe that is the main reason why has shown on this occasion its interpretative aspect. His latest tale of terror, like the previous ones, keeps in suspense until the end only if not sneaks a clever Viewer in the room and begins to tying up. On this occasion he did not want to abuse the formula because it has opted to not sow recesses of the path to follow, as in other titles in his filmography as a protégé and signals. Predictable at all times, girl with water combined fiction with another type of fiction based on the legend. Fairy tale with pathetic Concierge and boy for everything from monotonous life, is played by Paul Giamatti, which we have seen in American Splendor, Cinderella man and sideways, and the angelic although unexpected Bryce Dallas Howard, who was left blind in his previous project, after Nicole Kidman was new Muse of Lars Von Trier in Manderlay (continuation of Dogville). When all only highlight the most insignificant details? although they will be with me that the parody of film critic is great-, means that we have made a mistake with the libretto and its translation to images? here all of great beauty. Already happened just as the forest: an excellent setting not supported a weak script, so consider that same history itself is the worst of the set, with remnants of caught Tales from here and there, mixed with mythology and patterns from popular beliefs, a conglomerate of inconsistencies in the service of the aesthetic power and dam in turn from their inability to narrative. The film seems inspired by the world of fable which already supported Terry Gilliam to pay the land of illusion where the secret of the Brothers Grimm, emerges another tape failed while we get to know well why this. Than what we can think, and but lack you rhythm and fortitude as a final product, the adventures of our aquatic friend narf, any nymph, entertain. We draw the conclusion that Shyamalan knows well the tricks of the marketing and communication film, namely engage with the audience, throwing moorings but then not be able to anchor the ship. In other words, not thrilled, and if you cannot become gullible by hour and a half, the tale, rather than bringing us to distant worlds, serves only to fall asleep on the laurels.</body>
</review>
