<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Starship Troopers: Héroe de la federación" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unfortunate sequel where a group of soldiers are locked in a fortress, but the enemy instead of being outside is inside. By-product encompassed in serie B, I doubt that you like anyone to see that thinking that it is the second part of something.</summary>
	<body>Director: Phil Tippett. duration: hour and a half long, remember.Release date: May 18, 2004.Hoy have seen Ratatuille (as written) and at the end he speaks a food critic, commenting that after each creation, although your you can destroy it with your sharp verb, there is a team of people who have worked for her. This, is very cute if you see while mice do cooks and the family wins the hand of love, but if it happens to you when someone comes to sneak you a rehash cutrongo as a sequel to a film fresh, clever and witty script, you cabreas and not save on derogatory descriptions. In addition, that I am not a critic to salary, so say what gives me the win. EA.la film is the continuation of the first part (it seems obvious, but it could be a prequel or a saltacuela, i.e., I put the same name and I do what I get of the balls) where men are launching an offensive on a planet of bugs. No os espereis navecitas, or movement, everything that has happen happens in a kind of fortress of Tin, and the ship that comes at the beginning is nothing but a scene in the first movie. It's sad.I am quite outraged with this film. If it had been an original idea, without the name of a good movie followed by a gimmick, he would possibly her more kindly. But to make a sequel is presupposing that it will follow the storyline of the first. Or much less. This gives a twist to the serie B, touching if you want al gore, with moments of those that are not recommended for after dinner (except that give laughter). It's an agonizing atmosphere, that at no time curdled with a carrot in command, a girl believed rambo, a rambo believed harry the dirty, a general who has seen many movies West, and other purrielas who do this nothing more than an infamous product. ALE, as I said.In short, unfortunate sequel to the great Starship Troopers, where a group of soldiers are locked in a fortress, but the enemy instead of being outside is inside. By-product encompassed in serie B, I doubt that you like anyone to see that thinking that it is the second part of something.Cow poop.Besitos.P.D: A girl sleeps while attack you hundreds of bugs, millions of bullets are fired in his ear and nobody was surprised. Las palmas I know I do not touch.</body>
</review>
