<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Ratatouille" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Movie about a rat who wants to be a chef and a boy who does not know what he wants. Another small masterpiece of overcoming and love towards the family, that will delight children and will hunger to elders.</summary>
	<body>Director: Brad Bird. duration: closer to the two hours that the hour and a half.Release date: August 3, 2007.Muchas times it has accused me of fatten criticisms of animated films, which may well be true, but now that I have family that taste children's DVDs, this fattening not is if it will take me to put more than 5 stars to one. Warned quedais. And it is that, if a Sunday at 7: 30 you've had breakfast, you you've dressed, you've drawn, made constructions and what you have left is to see a rat chef, while your small you fits in the lap to scream and jump when they go out mice, that is not valued by stars.The film is about a rat which is lover of haute cuisine. In his family, thousands of inhabitants, they do not understand that fans, given that they only eat garbage and do not want any contact with humans. One day, by chance, our rat knows a guy that you like to be a chef, and works in the restaurant of the deceased chef who likes to our rat.As almost always with these people, the technical quality of the work is more than remarkable, with a humanization of the rat which contrasts with their peers. The use of the hair I was quite surprised, given that it is very natural, nothing apelzamado as it could be in both fur animals. The script is film for the whole family. It shows that by very small or different you are, you can always reach your goals. And, of course, as the family there is no nothing. This is perhaps the only black point of the film, but are so rich ratitas cooking. He has no points of humour causing laughter, but if that leaves the feeling that the world is good and you only have to do a bit of your part to change it.In short, movie about a rat who wants to be a chef and a boy who does not know what he wants. Another small masterpiece of overcoming and love towards the family, that will delight children and hunger that will give the elderly. that Nice!Besitos.P.D: The rest of the Sunday I spent to cook three fires. I have tuppers for the entire week.P.D.2: the scene in which father moves and the baby look you with the face of "¿Quieres the tete?" you will not see in the extras of the DVD;-)</body>
</review>
