<review author="Raccord" title="Una verdad incómoda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A conference with a power point quite cumbersome, which is more sparing in ideas and with many more simplifications that a book of?Sciences of the Earth and the environment? of 2nd of Bachillerato.</summary>
	<body>A conference with a power point quite cumbersome, which is more sparing in ideas and with many more simplifications that a book of "Sciences of the Earth and environment" of 2º de Bachillerato. There is nothing new, nothing unknown or the attention of which was already reported previously; friend Al Gore brings nothing more than his relative charisma, to another on scientific consensus that has existed for 20 years.And it seems that everything in the documentary, and everything that has arisen around him a Marketing campaign. That I know (and anyone who see the extras of the DVD can check) Al Gore, has zero film knowledge (and until few years ago nor environmental, that he refused to us to sign the Kyoto Protocol when he was Vice President) so it is highly unlikely that either his film. It is rather a documentary about himself. What then that this impoverished documentary has become so famous? We are in full crisis of the Bush administration, there is no politically correct leaders (Kofi Annan and Nelson Mandela seems that they are retired and the Dalai Lama is no longer what it was since that is colegui of Sanchez Drago) and above all and most importantly, Bono desperately needs someone with whom make a picture. The cause of solidarity with Africa seems to last fashionable, and consciences bienpensantes need new ideas to "make this world a better place". It was logical that a documentary like this (as insufficient and so bottoms complacent with the powerful) struck in Princes of Asturias, Nobel and other raffles.And with this, Al Gore get a job of environmentalist lecturer around the world, becoming everyone's money and travelling in his private jet, which does not work precisely with solar panels. The lead by example, it seems that Che Guevara died with (cli).</body>
</review>
