<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="14 Kilómetros" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very interesting social drama, reflect and realise what we have to assess it as it deserves. An emotional, fun, hard, tape with great music and very dramatic moments.</summary>
	<body>Good film from Gerardo Olivares, who does well little won the Golden Spike for best film at the prestigious international film of Valladolid (Seminci) festival. A contest where films of social issues are vitally important, fact that is perfectly exemplified in this film.He is a positive social film, where tells the path taken, this time by three people, reaches the dream of reaching Europe, where awaits a mejor.o life that believe them.The road will be hard, cruel, tragic. There are many hazards that threaten them, determined by human selfishness and intolerance, as well as the fact that money is a very important asset to achieve the dreams. but not the only, therefore hope, struggle, perseverance and tenacity and solidarity of human beings good are also crucial.Olivares achieves a truthful, credible, film with a sober, effective, direction with few but rich characters, that we are close because, basically, are equal to us, with the same yearnings vital, although his work vital to achieve them may not be more unequal.Emotional, enjoyable, tape lasts, with great music and very dramatic moments like the journey through the long desert, that does not leave anyone indifferent. And scenes, many, most, where we can see the newborns in the first or second world, enormous luck we have, not knowing appreciate what they have.Olivares makes us clear his position, which is the opinion of the majority of the people, and, instead of trying to flee Africa to get to Europe, it best to invest in Africa, to make it more rica, given the enormous potential. But of course, is you has exquilmado, has been exploited first world of it, that its people are doomed to find life beyond its borders, which are bleeding even more death the huge continent.A film for reflection, well narrated, that is worth to see. And to some but, and should not acharcarse the film, saying that it would have been better that the subtitles (I saw in original version, which is how you should see this film), should have been changed color. Instead of white color should have been blue or another color, because some very important dialogues take place in the desert. And of course, with the sand so white there and the subtitles in the same color.no read well.</body>
</review>
