<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="United 93" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Meticulous, precise, desalambicado cinema of winks to your business efficiency, but necessary.</summary>
	<body>The machinery of Hollywood has no mercy with the blood of their children. When we are witnessing, disturbed, shocked to the terrorist attack on the World Trade Center, knew that he would soon appear a film narrase, between the restraint that deserves respect for the victims and some daring to make the proper nod to the box office, the ups and downs of the very serious events on board the aircraft.They have been slow, but here it is, along with the 11-S project, Word Trade Center, given birth by Oliver Stone, so excessive always with the history of his country, Platoon, JFK, Nixon, although in this case, as we have said, eaten by an unusual meekness, clean edges and sincere, objective almost, in the narrative discourse.The hard candy deal with this film is awarded to Paul Greengrass, director of the blockbuster the Bourne myth, but also architect of films more draught social like Omagh or Bloody Sunday, films who also narrated real developments in the most violent Ireland. What obvious Yes Greengrass is the pamphlet: does not fall into any dogmatism, does not look for the easy tear, does not insist on the brutality of the terrorists. What does and, in my opinion, very accurately, is a thanks still life of the victims, whose tragic end we know nothing else turned off the lights in the projection room.Flight 93 United Airlines became the fourth damaged aircraft in the 11-s. know nothing for sure on the experience of its occupants. There are telephone conversations now exits to the light, but nothing that can be considered truthful. Greengrass, screenwriter of the matter, wheel a worthy documentary.The succulent catastrophic Philo raised by American cinema over the past three decades has, inadvertently, a sad milestone in this United 93, although well would be that it was not well and show that we are witnessing is not but pure fiction, narrative figurative. Concise script, Greengrass pulls a virtually unknown cast. This cultural decontamination suits your message: that what we see is a crude brochazo of recent history, perhaps the less manageable by the American people.Those seeking thrills, have in this film his movie. One of them: one based on arguments that are very directly themselves, even though the flight is American and all know that Hollywood, when touch you your chord is a major film school. Meticulous, precise, desalambicado cinema of winks to your business efficiency, but necessary.</body>
</review>
