<review author="Sara Rodriguez" title="La brújula dorada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"The Golden Compass" is a super production with the ingredients to entertain but without get too excited.</summary>
	<body>On 5 December was released in Spain one of the Super productions of the year, "The Golden Compass", a servant, taking advantage of the mini-vacaciones decided to go to see her, mostly motivated by my unconditional love to Nicole Kidman.Basada in "Northern lights" by Philip Pullman is part of a trilogy (to vary a little, that long ago that we have Gandalf épico-fantásticas.) and tells us how Lyra Belaqua embarks on an adventure to rescue one of his friends has been kidnapped by evil "Eaters" so-called characters while his uncle, Lord Asriel (Daniel Craig), walks around him alone on an expedition to find "the dust" particles able to join this world with the other existing dimensions. "But Mrs. Coulter and teaching will it not be easy.""The Golden Compass" is a correct adventure film to have a good time, something which, accompanied with an advertising and merchandising campaign is sent form part of the perfect formula for these dates. Includes scenes of incredible fights, a beautiful photograph and a few special effects and an atmosphere very cared for. But, while the history of the main characters is veering from a problem to another must be resolved before reaching its final destination, giving some agility to the film, from the very beginning is the feeling that have failed you take full advantage to the book. Maybe that part of the blame is the script which starts by opening too many frames in an attempt to explain the entire universe of fantasy that frames the history and presenting a vast amount of characters without deepening them too, which makes the story progress unless we have very clear why spend some things and the relevance that have certain details in the development of the same. Another thing that helps until the script stops not curdle is let pass the opportunity to dig deeper into the motivations of Lyra and the characters that help to save children and confined only to guess the metaphysical reflections touching on some details of the plot, focusing on adventures and action. Why the characters are not able to awaken in us all the empathy that would be expected and makes getting the end some abruptly showing us that there are still many things to be resolved and leaving the end too open to the two following delivery.To sum up "The Golden Compass" is a super production with the ingredients to entertain but without get too excited. Just enough to not be too child and attract well care of elders, but without moving away from the tone of the tale of sword and sorcery that appeals to children, who are, after all, that the film is directed.Let us hope that if they continue with the same cast in the next installments they know better to Nicole Kidman and Daniel Craig are quite good, but could have been much better.</body>
</review>
