<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Abierto hasta el amanecer" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excellent in its half, impossible to take seriously in his second, open until dawn is a vampire road movie, a joke of 90s and peak minutes...</summary>
	<body>Cafre apotheosis film gore in its final stretch, cynical and even discreetly adult in his boot, open until dawn is an ineffective thriller vampire guidance which offers pouring testosterone and expresses his conviction of film pulp in the visual orgy of his bloody coda: La Teta Enroscada, a gambling den in the middle of the border desert where the monsters play Tejanothey drink as Cossacks and engulf the soul of truckers and bikers with fierce tusks and morbid dentellada. That is where the film loses all the bellows which won in his home. Here Tarantino garabatea his apocalyptic vision of reality, truffled of comic books and B and Z series, tribute to the giallo and its filmmakers of header - from Peckinpah to Scorsese, Samuel Fuller and Sergio Leone-, but burden the technical aspect to Robert Rodriguez, absolute iconographic accomplice (brotherhood continued in the recent pair Death Proof - Planet Terror). Open until dawn can get bored: it is communion with the cutting, of being contaminated by the outrage of amputated members and viscera spreading of bourbon. Otherwise, in their light, in the formidable boot version, the tape is a hypnotic road-movie of superbly pincelados characters (the skeptical pastor, daughter fascinated by evil, the violence of the Gecko brothers, Tarantino and George Clooney in State of grace). Just fun (at least for this digital British) when they come into the den where the gang of vampires steepen the elbow and behead innocent souls fallen into disfavor. This is perhaps the party to fill with enthusiasm to the enthusiasts tarantianos, among which I have, but that sometimes is healthy desparrame and autoparódico joke, here it is not. It stands out, how no, the dialogue: Tarantino is a formidable writer, although - as we know - it has not ceased to write the same script since it hocicó in the star-system with its rupture and hypnotic Reservoir dogs (1992).Salma Hayek teaches lewd flesh in a lewd dance of border blues that has created school, snake as a scarf included.</body>
</review>
