<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Beowulf" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hopefully that Zemeckis completed his technical experimentation and then again we spend good time. Do for the moment, what we get clear with?Beowulf? is that Miss Jolie is still best of cartoon that in flesh and blood? already it is to say.</summary>
	<body>Robert Zemeckis is getting into a spiral of formal Précieuses absent of content is starting to become tiresome. I hope it is just the beginning of a stage, the results of experimentation that lead the director to put all his efforts in the technical part forgetting the fundamental part of a film, the story and I also hope it will solved over time.Something similar happened with the first games in which the desire to create something new gave extremely simple products. So just have to remember the first video game in history, consisting of a pair of bars that move vertically and a square ball. Although now that I think, what was of most addictive.Does not pass the same with the new film based on the technical "Performance capture", than in román paladino comes still record real actors, to then digitally capture your images and create a virtual character. Without any doubt, this mode of animation plus you can see in 3D in some rooms, is best of the film. Everything else, smells to mediocre.Zemeckis technique improves by leaps and bounds. What were simple drawings that resembled faces known here in "Polar express" happens to a new level. Expressions of the actors are very successful and all of them are easily unidentifiable. Ray Winstone, Angelina Jolie, Anthony Hopkins, Robin Wright-Penn and John Malkovich are converted into characters of legend, the Visual details are taken care of to the maximum and images in 3D rallan perfection. All this enables spectacular battles, impossible characters and epic scenarios, but everything blurs by the non-existent rhythm of the film.The story, taken from the most famous Anglo-Saxon epic poem, narrates the adventures of King Beowulf, obsessed hero by going down in history for his exploits &hellip; and that's it. A battle at the beginning, another cortita in the middle and one at the end and the rest are dialogues without depth and pure and hard filled. Nothing makes us draw attention to the adventures of the characters except for the curiosity to see Angelina Jolie in 3D virtual tits.Make an epic movie is not to include a couple of mythological characters or legend, a few well choreographed fights and a hero grips and tormented. A minimum of history must be spinning parts of action if we want to achieve that the viewer he cares what the hero live or die. It may be the English poem which does not give for more, but still, a good writer should know separate the wheat from the chaff and fill, creatively, parties in white. If something has served me "Beowulf" is for realize me how good that I found the trilogy of "The Lord of the rings" or "300".Hopefully Mr Zemeckis completed his technical experimentation and again make us spend the good times of films like "Who framed Roger Rabbit?", "Forrest Gump" or "Back to the future" trilogy. For the moment, what we get clear with "Beowulf" is Miss Jolie even better cartoon that in flesh and blood &hellip; which is already say.</body>
</review>
