<review author="Heitor Pan" title="La brújula dorada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am sure that enough substance is lost in the transition from page to screen, but even so, the film is entertaining and exciting, capable of transporting the viewer into a parallel world.</summary>
	<body>Yes, it seems that they have been in Hollywood to an efficient fellow to find children's literary sagas to adapt to the big screen and they are going like hotcakes. We have had up to now to Harry Potter, "The six signs of light", "The Chronicles of Narnia" and some more that I probably forget and suddenly comes "The Golden Compass", based on the "Dark matter" saga of Phillip Pullman. In addition the package comes with controversy including once more stale and conservative Catholic gritase from the rooftops that this story is a heresy case of great, prompting a further curiosity in me.The starting point has quite a few points in common com many of these youth books. A pre-teen protagonist who lives in a universe parallel to our own, where human beings are accompanied by talking animals, bearers of the soul of the owner, is confronted with a malevolent institution that tries to hide from the world scientific truth to power dominate the reason for people without problems. It thus becomes involved in an adventure that will draw it of his grey life towards other territories and worlds and that will take you to know a lot of peculiar characters along the way.As we can see, the criticism of the Church is not veiled and second reading but direct and slaughter. Even so, although it takes to criticize so openly (and so I understand this will more in subsequent deliveries), Pullman manages to give his fantasy of action to abundance and endearing characters. I am sure that enough substance is lost in the transition from page to screen, but even so, the film is entertaining and exciting, with care special effects, an atmosphere capable of transporting the viewer into a parallel world and some performances that greatly help the development of the adventure.Nicole Kidman in a very bad role in which is moved to taste, Daniel Craig making Aristocrat, Eva Green in the role of witch with broom and all good and the great Sam Elliot, one of my favorite side, which saw in the mediocre "Ghost rider" in a very similar role. In addition, to decide to view it in original version enjoy also the voices of Freddie Highmore (the kid from "Charlie and the chocolate factory" or "Finding Neverland"), Kathy Bates, Ian McKellen or Kristin Scott Thomas. perhaps the negative note is where almost always in these cases. It is very difficult to find a kid to carry the weight of history without clash, the prodigies do not appear like mushrooms. In this case, newcomer Dakota Blue Richards can not cause desire that one bears the clearing, but it certainly is far below the level of the rest of the actors.Anyway, one is soon forgotten of performances and other nonsense is the story that manages to transport us to worlds of fantasy, where a warrior bear friends, can make us be saved by an army of compasses, mounted on escóbulas (sorry, I had to make the joke) or have in our possession a golden compass to be able to gossip to taste on those around us.After a movie like this, you enter one wanting to embark on a new literary adventure and discover the books of Pullman.</body>
</review>
