<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In its attempt to entertain and be bigger and more spectacular than its predecessor, WINS in the visual, to the detriment of originality.</summary>
	<body>Two years ago landed on the charts of half the world of Disney's film, starring the brilliant Johnny Depp, the guaperas of fashion (Orlando Bloom), and a young British woman: Keira Knightley. The result was a magnificent comeback film adventures (do pirates, who would say!), with a mix of action and comedy, took the applause of critics and public, which resulted in an impressive collection at the box office, a merecidísima nomination for Depp, in addition to launching the career of the young Knightley and do Guaperas Bloom had more fans and money.And all so happy.But as the norm in Hollywood is that if you had success, you have to do a sequel. what happened? Therefore that this case is not going to be less. And or so less, because they shot the second and do final? third part of simultaneously. Before reaching Spain, he earned in his first weekend in the us the spectacular figure of $ 132 million, surpassing the record of Spider-man, of 114 million. He was going to destroy the summer box office, and so did (and continues to) pero.¿y the film?Because it turned out to be a small disappointment. Although only halfway. Not for failing to meet its initial to a genuine 'blockbuster' job, which achieves 'grandly' with spectacular battles (being worth mentioning the fight between Kraken, the giant sea bug, and the Black Pearl), as well as pirates and really made a picture that lead to turn the film into a real visual spectacle. As the film progresses, the story gets better and with her entertainment and comical, looking like the pace still already then a certain logic. All this leads me to say that, at least, the second half of the film is superior to the first.But if something was disappointed to leave aside the 'magic' and the originality that he had 'The curse of the Black Pearl'. It is true that in a sequel, one that wait is to see the same thing that you liked the anterior.o see something new while retaining the essence of the original. Then Verbinski (correct director ever there), Bruckheimer (producer ricachón where there) and the writers Ted Elliott &amp; Terry Rossio bet on exaggerate everything what liked of the first, forgetting something so basic and essential as it is the script.The first hour of film is really confusing. Not by difficulties in understanding the historia.sino because one wonders what happened to the previous spark. A top of the most soporific, it takes almost 90 minutes to have history mounted and where the gags are really enforced situations and meaningless. Then when one already sees that the film has no more end to entertain no more (formula that successfully carry out recent films like 'Poseidón'), albeit at the expense of their own valores.¿Es that what was intended? Might be that they were looking for viewers? It is likely, but this small disappointment is still there. And I repeat, not by lack of fun, action, adventure and these visual effects so meritorious, but for lack of genius, at least in the style of its predecessor.One of the most undervalued aspects in the analysis of films, at least in my opinion, is the musical and sound section. And that it is impossible to not finish this review without mentioning anything about the great soundtrack of the film then, still very much in the line of 'The curse of the Black Pearl', the musical pieces that accompany each of the hair-raising scenes allow a greater joy and enjoyment of them. Not in vain, it is one of the pillars of the tape, allowing me to thus appreciate the excellent work done by Hans Zimmer, though in this sense who has to be the merit is his disciple Klaus Badelt, composer of the first part of the trilogy.Photography is an important, almost central point in the 'blockbusters'. And the technical team would not let pass the opportunity to reflect, and even highlight the beauty of the Caribbean landscape, the sea and exotic islands through which pass the adventures of our pirates. Do it is here where the tribute to 'Monkey Island' is obvious, with that bruja-pitonisa that reminds (the swamp scene is practically a copy) to the legendary saga of games of PC.¿Y what about interpretations? Johnny Depp repeated character for the first time in his career, and does so with that much (even more) fame has been reported: Captain Jack Sparrow. While in the first part, his performance was brilliant, this time is a little exaggerated, although I must admit that this may be due in part to the film as a whole has too many aires of greatness and the surprise factor has already lost its meaning. Depp returns to get fully into the role, but perhaps he has betrayed be knowledgeable of what was his previous characterization. Orlando Bloom plays the handsome, loyal and adventurous Will Turner as you can: correct but not never to shine. Keira Knightley, which despite having already certain maturity interpretative, acquired and recognised especially after his work in 'Pride and prejudice', also manages to make a remarkable performance, very in line with his partner on screen. But, despite the fact that his face becomes unrecognisable (almost), who makes a notable performance is Bill Nighy, in its role of Davy Jones, to fill of charisma to his character, coming to instill respect despite the comical (or scary?) of the face.Thus, we have a film that, in its attempt to entertain and be bigger and more spectacular than its predecessor, WINS in the visual, to the detriment of the originality and the script that did the curse of the Black Pearl a success a few years ago.</body>
</review>
