<review author="Estesoyo" title="Death Proof" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The last straw mental Tarantino... another mess that only can be understood under the context of the fortune that has amassed the guy and the desire to go clubbing with his Mexican friend.</summary>
	<body>The last straw mental Tarantino. Another mess that only can be understood under the context of the fortune that has amassed the guy and the little interest to any product quality. I guess that it will have moved it well with his Mexican friend and the girls that come out semi-desnudas and that is the only thing that mattered to him. If that was the goal for puta madre uncle. Mission accomplished. Now, as the film is one of the worst shit I've seen in a long time. 'Death Proof' is like 'To test of death'. something as well as immortal, although as refers to the car not be if very applicable. Well, the nonsense is a specialist of cinema, devoted to crash cars now encorre girls beautiful and light hulls for stamping against them on the road. Pèlícula? It is divided into two parts, the first is get away with killing the girls and the second is with the toebox of the shoe, with a genuine film specialists, giving you what you deserve.That's all. Perhaps shot otherwise would have been able to be well or at least be curious, but thus raised is vomit. To see: supposed that it imitates bad horror, the serie-z films of recent years. Damn, they are much better than this shit. But well, the film has cuts, color changes. all kinds of induced failures (it) trying to imitate the movies before, when they were in rolls before the arrival of the digital image. 80% Of the time also have an ass onscreen. Also imitating these semi-eróticas horror films, but that with Tarantino becomes vulgar and uncouth. Without lower interest unless you are a grain-filled teenager who has not ever seen a butt... No comment. The film becomes long because there's nothing for. but to make matters worse Tarantino makes us to torture with their talks to the Woody Allen drunk. This was his grace in his early films, especially in 'Pulp Fiction' where was curious to hear to that bunch of illiterate spoken ill of their nonsense. But this is already happening in dark brown. hold the two small groups of aunts wrong caradas and worst spoken saying nonsense after another is the task of a genuine freak of Tarantino. I was personally about to turn off the player at least six times. and I held my because I have endured other worst and here I am not going to be less, but it is certainly not worth any trouble. The dialogs are tasteless and boring, not even get cause, which I guess was a target of the film.The thing is very bad in the descending line of Tarantino: each thing that makes is a little worse than the previous. The following is scary to go to see her.Again Tarantino us torture coming out in his film, and is the uncle is not that it is ugly, it's disgusting. Better if he hid behind the camera. Kurt Russell is wrong and it does not hurt, but it is not enough to lift the history. The aunts give grima see them, half naked and dropping a taco after another. Buff, only for trained estomagos.A curious thing: Zoe Bell plays herself in the movie. It really is a specialist which has doubled to Uma Thurman in 'Kill Bill' and a lot of famous. Here's a crazy role (was supposed that she is) and is that at the end gives 'woolly pal' to the smug Kurt Russell. Little more remarkable.Me ashamed to admit that I've seen this shit.</body>
</review>
