<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Encantada: La Historia de Giselle" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The story of Princess Giselle is something as well as the version of Barbie and Ken, a world penetrable and understandable to 100% by those created through the rib of Adam.</summary>
	<body>What is new and arguably original of the film is in the form as trasmutan these beings inanimate to our reality, using New York as scenario, that by the way this year has been the space of several movies like Bee Movie, the Bourne Ultimatum, hard kill 4 among others, with a fairly powerful story with that in addition to fun and trasnportarnos to a magical world planted in ourIt aims to outline the lost innocence, the harshness and our reality cares to deliver us a message of reconciliation and love. And it is that despite transform these characters of fairy tales characters of flesh and blood, the magic retains and becomes a mixture of realism and fantasy between two totally different worlds. The hostile is combined with pure and affectionate feelings of these beings. Who plays Princess Giselle, we are talking about the actress Amy Adams, it makes a really charming and convincing role that in my view takes all the credits of this film. Without doubt, a perfect choice of the director and that it also confirms why has been so acclaimed and award-winning by various associations of film in the United States critics. Especially the highlight to it, because others shortly and some nothing I liked such as James Mardsen who plays Prince Edward. Although some highlights the performance of Susan Sarandon, who plays the evil Narizza, a witch that most excels by its modernism in the makeup and costumes that really liked, that by his interpretation that Sarandon enjoys little Parliament on the tape. On this occasion the evil character is far from being an ugly Witch of more macabre fairy tales and its characterization on this occasion comforting with this character, making it look nice and even beautiful.Another of the work of the director, Kevin Lima with this his fourth animated film and Disney, was the achieve the proper balance between the various genres in which enchanted transits: romantic comedy, comedy-drama, animation and music. All these ingredients with a ágill pace and argued that it manages to keep expectant and entertaining the public in this magical journey.But, Encantada turns out to be a completely white and tender film that becomes limited and worthy to be seen and admired by the female followers of Disney. These features are carried to such an extent, that I really think can get to annoy your audience both child and adult male. The story of Princess Giselle is something as well as the version of Barbie and Ken, a world penetrable and understandable to 100% by those created through the rib of Adam. In this regard, readers I will give or will remove the reason with their comentariosl.Although it has not been my total pleasure, the truth is that this film turned more into a tribute of yesterday, has managed to raise a little more than 105 million dollars in its almost 3 weeks of Billboard with an undetermined budget.</body>
</review>
