<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Death Proof" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Infumable truño about a guy who becomes obsessed with women and them want to kill on Board of your car. Much talk, little action and dialogues that surely many people they encandilen, but they helped me to decide what made the next day for dinner.</summary>
	<body>Director: Quentin Tarantino. duration: hour and a half of talk, 19 moved minutes and 1 minute of show.Release date: August 29, 2007Espectadores: 185.083 beings human according to the Ministry of culture, so you go to know do know by that women do not want is to marry? That to 100 grams each of chorizo are not the whole pig. Embedded within this joke of low estofa is an ancient philosophy that goes on to say "If the duck quacks on the fig tree, the mouse roerá the bowels of the Earth with the sharp fangs of an armadillo died in acts of extreme bravery". Or put another way, go truño movie I've swallowed with a little that seemed that improved but it lasts less than a powder with the Pataki (I would go with haste to tell, of course, is that you do not hesitate my manhood, muahahahaha).The film is about a type who calls specialist Mike or Joe or something like that, which has a black car that makes brrrummmm, bruuummm and with a duckling in the nose. Then leave babes chatting about what out them of her pussy, and are called black shit, bitch white and similar, but they are amiguitas. And it has ass as arenas. And then these crap and skinny white whores black disappear and leave others call including whores, black and white shit but you want to. And suddenly, when it seems that begins the film, goes and finishes.I have to make the synopsis of the film make a tribute to the beginning of every child in school, that when asked a summary tells the whole movie and unconnected horns. If this movie is a tribute to something, is that anything goes. Let's see, that big pain in the ass. I'm equal to be homage, the Tarantino is God for some or what you want to see two women's groups say you basteces that they sonrojarían to plumbers seasoned with raja in the ass in the air, it seems to me interesting. And not pass anything throughout the film rather than see these women say nonsense seems a roll. Only okay, towards the middle of the movie, a scene. I think that they put it to awaken to the staff.In short, infumable truño about a guy who becomes obsessed with women and them want to kill on Board of your car. Much talk, little action and dialogues that surely many people they encandilen, but they helped me to decide what made the next day for dinner. Mental straw.Besitos.P.D: We should have recorded the face that we stayed my half Zucchini and me when suddenly there is an "End". Incredible.</body>
</review>
