<review author="Dragon negro" title="La brújula dorada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The northern lights, the first book in the his Dark Materials trilogy, would have deserved an adaptation to the big screen quite successful and achieved that before us, so seen, I'll buy the two remaining books and I sit to read them on my couch, that insurance I do not decepcionaran both as the planned second and third part.</summary>
	<body>From the outset has wanted us to sell this the Golden Compass as the trilogy was going to pick up the witness of the Lord of the rings, a spectacular trilogy of fantasy that would break ticket and return to amaze us. But there are several factors that may have not taken into account and that jump in sight once seen the film, and the first one is that Chris Weitz is not Peter Jackson or by far and this project is something greet and sought for years as it was ESDLA for him, but it seems rather a film commissioned. Another reason is that you lights of the North (as it is called the book actually), despite being a good and entertaining book of fantasy, fails not even close to the level of epic grandeur of the Golden Compass Tolkien.La work does not put in an alternative world to our own and quite similar except in some things. Humans there van always accompanied of a Dæmon, a sort of personification of the soul in the form of animal and comes to represent the character of each. Our protagonist is Lyra, a small girl to which a great destination awaits you. Everything will begin when someone begins to kidnap children and Lyra have to stop the Oxford School where has raised to spend in the care of Mrs. Coulder, which is who is actually behind the mystery of the disappearances.The northern lights, the first book in the his Dark Materials trilogy, would have deserved an adaptation to the big screen quite successful and achieved before the us. After a year of waiting the film and that her they paint us as well, us they back folded into a film that is not at all at the height of the novel. Although the plot is following the thread of the book, everything seems to happen so fast and accidental way that even seems to hurry by finish or skip at least throughout the first part of the book which is undoubtedly the most heavy, it is not until that begins the journey of Lyra when the thing starts to get really interesting. The film getting going snips of paper here and there leaving aside delve into characters from scene to scene quickly and in a hasty manner, in short too many situations. The final climax happens in the last half hour of film where taken licenses are clearly disturbing and without any sense. SPOILER Ya tell me that pussy looks that the film bears struggle, remove it and the picture stays the same, does not have the slightest sense, on the other hand, in the book is perfectly justified and occurs after saving children, not before, as they are the bears who have retained the uncle of Lyra and where go to rescue him. END of SPOILEREn as to the actors, the main protagonist is Dakota Blue Richards, which can be equally charming than of irritating within minutes of difference, but that generally holds pretty well, Daniel Craig, Eva Green and Sam Elliot are correct on the little paper they have, and Nicole Kidman takes the cake, get to the character of Ms. Coulder which in the book is a beautiful and refined Lady, but the evil Fund and with the power to influence people is completely disfigured and even ridiculous at times.It seems that Chris Weitz not be her has played with the film, as if made Jackson with his trilogy. Not a book as complex and full of nuances can be explained and fantasy elements such as the northern lights in an hour and three quarters, this film with half an hour or more had been better defined. Anyway there is a severe problem of adaptation of script which is the major drawback of all and which I hope will improve in future releases, although seen so I'll buy the two remaining books and I sit to read them on my couch, that insurance I do not decepcionaran both as the planned second and third part.</body>
</review>
