<review author="Kiko de España" title="Thriller: A Cruel Picture" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is the last third where we can see up to where he became the influence of this unknown movie, being part of the universe and the more obvious Matrix Kill Bill.</summary>
	<body>Hold the males because we are dealing with a banned film. I wanted to see Thriller: A cruel picture for several reasons. That if Tarantino was inspired by her for his Kill Bill, that if do not know how many years hidden in a drawer. the case is that the movie doesn't disappoint, but on the contrary: while other 70's movie revenge of in the line of I spit on your grave there is to point a number of rough details to raise to Olympus to this Swedish movie rather than any American cafrada (although always fun) as the "porn touch" or the model scriptsomething that lacked the rest of revenganzas.Thriller is the story of Madeleine, a girl who was fifteen years ago a girl was raped by a tramp viejuno causing a perpetual trauma and the definitive loss of speech.One day fails in good time to the bus and a crappy guy, picked up by a Swedish Malcolm McDowell at the time. And he kidnaps. And it makes addicted to heroin. And it prostituted.We then started to freak out. When the girl is with one of their clients forced the planes leave no imagination: finest first and plans detail of "action" make the movie an instant classic of the porn semi trash.Madeleine be pirar, clear, and while he is lying with the crappy clients will saving for weapons, fighting, shooting and driving classes.Revenge will be slow, but it will be the rehostia.It is the last third where we can see up to where he became the influence of this unknown movie, being part of the universe and the more obvious Matrix Kill Bill. What matters now is to avenge the fuck up and go if there is revenge in the final part, we now have the Peckinpah part of the movie: superslowmotion for each and every one of the shots of the pirate. pure delirium.A final act of street justice so brutal that one cannot help but remember until it came time, probably the best revenge of history. If you haven't seen this "suecada" you are taking.</body>
</review>
