<review author="Bruji" title="Mr Brooks" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps the failure of Bruce Evans has been writing a script over ten weeks to entertain for two hours and be forgotten in five minutes.</summary>
	<body>The particular Doctor Jekyll and Mister Hyde Evans and Gideon is an entertaining thriller tracing intelligent that, low hours, throws hand of three great glories of Hollywood to continue. The experiment works to become one of those stories that inhibit critical sense to not give option to thought. Remember to the Addams?. There was a funny scene in which the great Christina Ricci (Wednesday) attends a costume dance with his usual attire. "I'm dressed as a psychopath," he said, "because all psychopaths have a normal appearance". And this appreciation was not without basis. If we delve in the biography of some of the more "charismatic" serial killers in history, we discover that there is no shortage testimonies that define them as normal, educated and absolutely charming beings. Education and charm, in the hands of the writers of Mr. Brooks, reach unimaginable heights, to the point of making the human and psychological profile of the facet of Dr. Jekyll, which becomes indispensable to personify the conscience to give depth to the dark side as credible. The entrance scene of that personification, - that already appear in some movies by Wim Wenders as the sky above Berlin or Tan Lejos Tan Cerca!-, is so surprising as the rest of events that make up the plot. Sitting the databases and precise with a focus of all its components, is imposed a kind of vertiginous script, frantic, with multiple twists that do not offer concessions or crowds out the reflection. Close to other stories that populate the sky film, since it is easy is sometimes perceive the dramatic intensity of Seven, the light of resurrection passages recreation or the timely phone call in which "the world is more interesting with you inside, Clarice" of the silence of the lambs; many others, far from all of them. For its part, the techniques used in filming and production design enhance the creation narrative, while the profusion of fast planes, impeccable planning in photography, scenic alignment, the own artistic direction and perfection in the Assembly, contribute to enlarge the deceptive final result. To make matters worse, the successful recruitment of Kevin Costner faces a new twist ending in the delirious annulment of the critical sense. At least, on my behalf. And it is that it does not matter the evolution of events, the resolution of the plot or the luck run the characters, while he continues on screen. How difficult to understand is that it is precisely now, in this film, when they begin to recognize their important interpretative qualities, the same as others always had detected and admired. Costner-Brooks is not unlike Jim Garrison, Prosecutor of New Orleans, who jugueteaba with his glasses on the open case of JFK by Oliver Stone; or the untouchable Eliot Ness irresistible; or the controversial fugitive from A perfect world; nor tender lover of message in A bottle; It is even different from the troubled professional who fell in love with to girls of a whole generation with the bodyguard. Kevin Costner has always acted in Kevin Costner, leading to each and every one of their characters to their own land, that where so sure it feels and always lifted blisters among many sectors critical. The perfect riposte to his final performance, can be found in this abstract entity that gives life a William Hurt who may never have this role among the best of his interesting career. Their interventions, many of them collected through the mirror of a car, are kept within the correction more absolute, but far from the magic that used to print his characters in the past. Of course, not forgetting, one of the most camale칩nicas stars of American cinema which, after many vicissitudes and giving the already by lost, again to emerge with such wisdom to make it big in movies such as Striptease or the Lieutenant O'Neill. Together with them, one of the great promises of the contemporary cinema, Dane Cook, in what may be his final takeoff. And after one hundred and twenty intense minutes of footage that does not accommodate the boredom, the nightmare of Mr. Brooks begins to leave the film. It is not the time, recovered from the hypnotic trance in which cleverly has made us fall director, we recall the words of the Mexican Alejandro Gonz치lez I침치rritu, basically they said that "If a story doesn't do a catharsis in the Viewer is that something has failed". Perhaps the failure of Bruce Evans has been writing a script over ten weeks to entertain for two hours and be forgotten in five minutes.</body>
</review>
