<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Mi Hermano Es Hijo Único" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Italian director Daniele Luchetti builds with hand strong, helped by strong performances, both a critique of ideological fanaticism as the vital adventure of a few teens lost in a tide of imperfect ideas.</summary>
	<body>What are the motivations that lead to a teenage kid when his vision of the world is not yet fully formed (perhaps never reach form it entirely) to take some political awareness and choose a few ideals? Family, environment, friends, their experiences, the very nature of the kid &hellip; all these factors together can give us the seeds of radicalism toward any of the possible sides, a moderate or even an ideology of apolitical position. This is what is put on the table the Italian director Daniele Luchetti in "my brother is only son," building with hand strong, helped by strong performances, both a critique of ideological fanaticism as the vital adventure of a few teens lost in a tide of imperfect ideas.In the Italy of the 1960s, in a proletarian and humble family, Accio, the youngest of three brothers, tries to find your site. When he entered the seminary seems to have responded to their questions but the inconsistencies of teachers and priests and the ideas of his brother, convinced Communist, will reconsider the path and to take new directions.The bad relationship with his parents and siblings will make friendship with a neighborhood merchant starts to influence their way of thinking, because this be alien to their day to day is just the opposite of what sees in your family. This evolution will take you to join the Italian fascist party, becoming much more you tense family relations, in where activism and the ideas of his brother make a sort of hero. "my brother is only son" leads us by the life of this kid, showing us his first love, his love-hate relationship with his older brotherits you disappoint and, ultimately, a good part of his life experience and like this influences their political and social ideology.Luchetti is not position itself at any time, without demonizing followers of any of the parties or lionize to others, but by trying to show the inconsistency of the human being, the virtues and defects of each of the groups in which Accius is. This distancing from what surrounds the protagonist and neutrality which tries to shoot is one of the aspects that I liked from a movie that tries to make the public which take party (or not). Luchetti becomes the antithesis of the documentary film by Michael Moore, that take from the beginning and tries to convey their ideas across the screen.The proposal is largely powered by close and totally unfounded interpretations of excesses, approaching the film documentary, as if we were filming with a hidden camera to a family of our own neighborhood, their miseries and their dreams. The actor protagonist, Elio Germano, carries the weight of a large part of the film almost seamlessly, with a naturalness incredible making his character in someone close, a neighbor of life almost from the beginning.The only downside I can find is the excessive ambition of the script, trying to place Accio at all possible situations to raise a full discussion. This causes that towards the end of the footage all are atropelle a little sliding towards a hopeful and almost oneiric, but slightly premature end.It is not bad something social film from time to time between Golden compasses, epic warriors and teenage wizards to deoxidize neurons which, in much of the films, we have been on autopilot.</body>
</review>
