<review author="Kiko de España" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of my favourite books always comes to screens. It is not an unmitigated disaster, but almost.</summary>
	<body>More similar to The Omega man than to the original story by Richard Matheson, I am legend is a forgettable updating that skips lightly the original work so that its director, Francis Lawrence (which prepares a version based on snow white and the seven dwarfs, GLUPS) contribution details cool (or that think he and Mr Warner) and the result is irregular enough to forget about the movie when you're on the subway.Robert Neville is the sole survivor of the planet. A virus has finished with the human race and those who have not died now are vampires (digital, why? what about Rob Bottin, Tom Savini and Greg Nicotero? not to serve?!)Neville was a brilliant scientist who worked on the virus and is now immune and spends time with his dog Sam, "rent" movies at the video store and do push-ups. It also seeks a cure, clear.With an interesting startup (Neville hunting in full Big Apple) and an unnecessary flashback for more inri divided into three segments (the third is Fireworks, it is to repeat a level of Smith crying) the movie forgets the original, self-destructive and decadent, environment to get (with the largest shoehorn I've seen in my life) two or three sequences of action and some impossible to ignore scaremore than anything by the volume.And now a couple of notes to get you to Matheson of the head before entering the cinema. The novel starts such as well: on those cloudy days, Robert Neville could not know when the sun set, and sometimes they were already on the streets before he regresaraEn the film, Neville has alarms that alert you when the sun sets to be able to "cover" well House Windows.Other: Was a tall man of thirty-six years of age, of English and German descent &hellip; and blue eyes and brillantesEs the fresh Prince of Bel Air. And it has a dog. They have changed the sex of the dog and the breed of the protagonist, except that now here come the gañán of Dennis Hopper and let go me the history of the aubergines.Good levels of the deserted city, the best of the movie and little more for a failed attempt of wanting to do something "brainy but box office" because, let us not deceive ourselves, the film nor appears to be a vehicle for mass view once the resolution of the plot, or if?</body>
</review>
