<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Soy leyenda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Francis Lawrence (Constantine) adapted for the big screen the famous novel by Richard Matheson "I am Legend", starring an unstoppable Will Smith that perhaps without prentenderlo it surprises us with one of his best performances.</summary>
	<body>Francis Lawrence (addressed to anteriormenet the fabulous "Constantine") brings the adaptation for the big screen of the famous novel by Richard Matheson, "I am Legend", starring an unstoppable Will Smith that perhaps without prentenderlo it surprises us with one of his best performances. The premiere in theaters will be in a few days."The film is not completely faithful to the book, but the changes that in some cases are successful, in other endearing and other incomprehensible, because it's a novel of vampires while in the film the beings are not defined, are a mix of zombies and vampires.""I am Legend" takes place at a pretty good pace, includes its respective scares and it is very easy to see, is neither heavy nor boring although Yes, obviously predictable. Look that strange that a film where already intuyes what is going to happen, you want so much that not even look at the clock, it is synonymous with good management and therefore a very good rate.I want to highlight the spectacular levels General, decorated and as not the FX, the infected creatures, they are very successful and the entire film is surrounded by a mist to the "Fable" which I liked very much. It is not, nor much less a film that brings something or teach us something new that we have not seen, but it does deserve the penalty see this film, the second for the director already has one fan among his followers, I like directs this man.For fans of Will I have to say that (oh God!) I never had seen so in form as in this film, must acknowledge that boasts a spectacular figure and that the years seem to not pass by him. This versatile actor takes an unstoppable career as as I said at the beginning, coming from the TV and a series as "the fresh Prince of Bell-air" which spent years on the air, was very complicated to get the context to which belonged the character who played without enbargo and with all their eccentricities to slopes, Will has also been a star, geek but not power but star.I believe that Francis Lawrence, wanted to reach the public in such a way that it has eliminated much of magic that emerges from the novel, perhaps by getting the idea clearly. Personally I would prefer to avoid certain turns of history and preserving part of the original confusion of the novel.By true Will, do let's see you somewhere movie making unsuccessful or always gotta be fucking master in all your movies? A little diversity please.</body>
</review>
