<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Deseo, Peligro" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I would like to, danger is a film that peca of pretentious and bombastic, and despite her promotion, is not more than a vulgar, devoid of passion story and some emotion.</summary>
	<body>Ang Lee is a filmmaker who can be considered the antithesis of the prison, as every one of his movies is totally different from the previous. It is capable of doing a romantic drama of time, a film of action and martial arts, the film adaptation of a popular comic or the love story of two men in the deep America.With lust, caution, Ang Lee approached the film noir par excellence, but the environment of spies and war is only a framework for the Taiwanese filmmaker tell the story of the passion arising between an amateur spy and his alleged victim. Entering, desire, danger has to go, to be generous, at least three quarters of an hour, as its excessive length is a burden that the story never recovers. The first half of the film, whose only reason is the present the characters and show the environment of a China occupied by the Japanese during World War II troops, as presentation is too long. Ang Lee recreates with great parsimony in elements entirely unrelated to the plot, as each and every one of the games mahjong. However, this first part is convincing and intense than the second, which should theoretically be wake which more emotions up in the Viewer, as it is the bulk of the story. Unfortunately, the emotional core turns out to be a story that recalls something already seen on many occasions (go no further, in the same year, to the black book), predictable and that offers nothing new. Well, Yes, so promoted sexual encounters between the couple protagonist (whose interpretations are the best of the film), but sincerely resulting free since they do not provide specific weight to the development of the plot.I would like to, danger is a film that peca of pretentious and bombastic, and despite her promotion, is not more than a vulgar, lacking history of passion and emotion some and totally predictable. And if this outside little, its duration ends by exasperate anyone.</body>
</review>
