<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="El bosque del luto" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The mourning forest is a beautiful movie, with some excellent performances and a beautiful photograph that, despite its extreme slowness, make it a true display of feelings and emotions almost visceral.</summary>
	<body>Awarded the Grand Prize of the Festival in Cannes and nominated for the Palme d'Or, the mourning forest has been directed by Naomi Kawase and played by Shigeki Uda Machiko Ono, Makiko Watanabe, Kanako Masuda and Yoichiro Saito.Mogari no mori tells us the story of Shigeki, an old man who lives in a secluded residence. There it feels comfortable and happy with other residents and staff that attends them. Machiko, a social worker that belongs to such equipment, gives special attention, although inside he torments the loss of a child. To celebrate the birthday of Shigeki, Machiko decides to take him for a ride by car by the field. But the car is stopped by the wayside. The elder domestic decisively in the forest, and Machiko has no choice but to accompany him.We could define the forest of mourning with two qualifiers, no doubt, making it totally justice: wonderful and agonizingly slow.Usually documentary Naomi Kawase tells a tender story of acceptance and hope through a makeshift initiatory journey that leads to two people, Machiko and Shigeki, to overcome their own ghosts and accept the death of their loved ones.Depressingly slow pace despite its 97 minutes of footage, always with camera in hand and virtually no dialogue, one should take the viewing of the forest of mourning with philosophy, if you don't want to arrive to exasperate is. Once accepted his apparent monotony, before the viewer opens a truly unforgettable experience, with a strong sentimental burden and a few performances whose symbolism may not be qualified otherwise than as simply brilliant and sweeping.Director Naomi Kawase brings us two seemingly opposing characters but that in the depths of his being, share the same ballasts: Machiko, an introverted young man who is unable to overcome the death of his son, and Shigeki, a cheerful old man obsessed with his deceased wife Mako. Both are linked to a past whose tortuous memory and guilt prevents them from move forward with their lives, facing in different ways. Thus, the young Machiko simply seems to ignore the memories, although can not see his own son in the figure of Shigeki, whose trauma has made him return to a sort of childlike state.This relationship shows us through a daily relationship, without plot twists or apparent melodramatic resources and whose depth lies precisely in its simplicity. Thus, such seemingly vulgar scenes such as the couple protagonist playing hide and seek, or eating watermelon, or the poignant image of Shigeki screaming desperate for the elderly that do not cross the River, seeing in him his own son, certainly remain engraved in the memory of a server for a long time. Overcoming fears and acceptance of death, both own and others, are the principalmensaje of the film, which cannot fail to remind me, especially substance to this wonder of Kim Ki-duk called spring, summer, autumn, winter. and spring.Thus, the mourning forest is a beautiful movie, with some excellent performances and a beautiful photograph that, despite its extreme slowness, make it a true display of feelings and emotions almost visceral.It is Yes, tons of patience.I give a 7'5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
