<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="1408" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With a first half pretty round, but can not remember 'In the mouth of fear' of John Carpernter, '1408' ends up exasperate the viewer under the ineffective formula of the ' harder still '.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Swedish Mikael Hafström and performed almost entirely by John Cusack, 1408 also has interventions of proflífico Samuel l. Jackson, Mary McCormack, Jasmine Jessica Anthony and Tony Shalhoub among others, being projected during this last Festival of Sitges in the closing gala.The film, based on the short story by Stephen King published in our country on the compilation everything is possible, tells the story of a skeptical novelist of terror, researcher of the paranormal, which believes only in what they see their eyes. After devoting himself to discredit Paranormal phenomena throughout the world, Mike begins his new bestseller about haunted hotels. However, everything will change when doubt enters into room 1408 of the Dolphin.Sin Hotel, Stephen King should be the writer, living, dead or undead, more adaptations of his novels has been transferred to both the small and the big screen: Carrie, Salem's Lot, the shining, Creepshow, Cujo, the dead zone, Christine, children of the corn, animal cemeteryMisery, It, the dark half, the store, the Green Mile, this 1408 or the still pending release in our country The mist are some of the titles that filmmakers of the calibre of Brian De Palma, George a. Romero, John Carpenter, Tobe Hooper, David Cronemberg or Stanley Kubrick wanted translated into celluloid.Some I will kill when you say that, personally, the novels of Stephen King not attracted me too (especially my girlfriend XXXD), and is probably that of the four or five books that I have read the copyright, I have not chosen precisely the best. I do not know. I'm staying with Poe and Lovecraft, what going you to do. As well, however, one must recognize that many of its adaptations or screenplays for the small or large screen tend to be fairly decent, good sometimes, and even on time excellent, as it is the case of the recent series Kingdom Hospital, not to mention other more obvious examples.Going to the movie itself, I must say that 1408 could have given much more than Yes, especially if its format is different or, what is the same, yet shorter. I guess turning a short story into a film is what you have. And it is that Mikael Hafström Swedish film is divided into two clearly identifiable but not by them different parts. Do and that what it means? That despite its 94 minutes, 1408 is constiuida hourly quite solvent, bright on time, and a final half-hour of absolute stuffed.The truth is that a room in which strange paranormal events occur gives much of the self and at the same time very soon, because the plot can fall in a permutation that is limited to loop the loop, as is the case with 1408. As usual with this type of film, in the time in which the terror passes suggested to show in all its evil splendor, it ceases to be appealing and disturbing for the Viewer, that without taking into account that the basis of 1408 continues to be the same as that of the shining, the aforementioned Kingdom Hospitalthe genius of John Carpenter entitled at the mouth of the fear and so many other products, in which one space - is a room, a hotel, a hospital, or a city-is cursed for one reason or another, preventing the protagonist to discern between fiction and reality.Thus, 1408 is a product relatively entertaining during its first hour of footage, perhaps less, to then become a bland in crescendo to nor convincing monologue interpretation of John Cusack is able to sustain.I am a 5'5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
