<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Chrysalis" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With a bland and predictable plot, its unique appeal lies in its setting.</summary>
	<body>Chrysalis is a thriller futuristic directed by Julien Leclercq and starring Albert Dupontel, Marie Guillard, Marthe Keller, Mélanie Thierry, Estelle Lefebure and Francis Renaud.Presentada in the official section Premiere in the last edition of the Sitges Festival, Chrysalis tells the story of Lieutenant David Hoffman, who returns to rejoin the service in the European police to trap a dangerous criminalsuspected of the murder of his wife months ago. A complicated investigation just leading him to a mysterious private clinic led by the unflappable Brügen Professor. In a world where the past can be implanted in the nerve center of the brain, the memories have become a very coveted good &hellip; with a quite successful aesthetic halfway of cyberpunk, Chrysalis cannot remind us, at least in terms of aesthetics is concerned, to films like children of men or even the only one. In fact, the similarities between the directorial debut of Julien Leclercq and starring Jet Li nor are so outrageous, although Chrysalis is much more calm, although why not more interesting.The truth is that the fabric of Chrysalis - also relatively similar to the memory of the dead or even, why not, to total challenge - runs very slowly between bluish steel constructions and design furniture, making that a scant hour film and media reaches antojar quite longer. And it is that the alleged complexity of a plot that mixes memories, past, present and future is carried with a tedious simplicity, that history fails to call us at any time the attention, leaving us only specific fighting the Matrix Online and the previously mentioned scenery.Archetypal, and flat characters in dialogues canned and predictable, the atmosphere of film Chrysalis futuristic noir dissipates each minute of footage, producing a growing apathy in the spectator intensified, if possible, by its environmental austerity, because in (almost) any time we can see the real outside world of the near future, so only alleys, laboratories and interiors, which is why even his aesthetic preciosista ends becoming sterile.Thus, Chrysalis no longer a new film set in the near future whose beauty inspired - more or less - in this jewel called Blade runner is his only final attraction, something that has been happening a long with titles as the also French Renaissance, Natural city, Gattaca, children of men, Minority report or Equilibrium, while especially these last four possess a greater background to Julien Leclercq.Algo bland movie, the truth.I give a 4 10plants.</body>
</review>
