<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Negra Navidad" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With joke performances and a dismal script, Black Christmas loses interest after ten minutes of footage, offering us one of the manic with less charisma of recent times.</summary>
	<body>In 1974 Bob Clark directed Black Christmas, a horror film with included psychopath that marked a landmark in what is commonly known as slasher movies, even though that term would begin to be used a few years later, with films such as Halloween night and Friday 13.Pues well, following American rush of remakes, this year reaches the Sitges Festival Black Christmas (or Black x-mas)(, as you prefer), with Glenn Morgan as director and screenwriter, adapted the story and original characters of Roy Moore. The cast features Mary Elisabeth Winstead along with Katie Cassidy, Michelle Trachtenberg, Lacey Chabert, Kristen Cloke, Andrea Martin, Crystal Lowe and Oliver Hudson.Black Christmas puts us on Christmas Eve, in a college fraternity where a group of young people are prepared to return with their families. During the eve, the supervisor of the fraternity will have them the murky history of Billy, a psychopath currently locked up in an insane asylum who grew up in that same House years ago. Thereafter, girls will be receiving strange phone calls and one after another, will disappear.Peñazo often, gentlemen.I must admit that I have not seen the film of 1974, and I breathed deeply when I speak to IMDB to compare scores between original and remake, I found a not inconsiderable 7'2 (6'6 in Filmaffinity) against a sad 4'5. And it is that before films such as Black Christmas, one cannot ask what's necessary to ¿.era?.Totally devoid of order and any appeal, Black Christmas get each one of their frames emanates a stale smell of beans and a bland feeling of déjà vu, with few plot twists, zero tension and the slightest incentive that can offer the viewer a minimally entertaining story. In fact, Glenn Morgan film even is able to give us the comfort of offal, in a film that seems rather a compilation of the American horror film clichés.With rather joke performances and a quite dismal script, Black Christmas loses interest, if at some point peak it, ten minutes of footage, offering us one of the manic with less charisma of recent times and a group of actresses who barely we can differentiate, in a film in which neither his loud music in the supposedly high moments manages to get out of the overall compressor.So therefore, this nonsense called Black Christmas passes directly and in positions of honor, to the growing list of horror films to forget with titles as head of death, White noise 2: the light, or crocodile: a serial killer, clear example of the dearth of ideas that American horror this suffering in recent times.I give it a 2 out of 10, to give something.</body>
</review>
