<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Once" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A fascinating soundtrack, and a few characters who manage to transmit large amount of emotions and feelings, just speechless make eleven a film of great pleasure viewing, that under no circumstances would classify in the musical genre.</summary>
	<body>After obtaining the audience award in the latest edition of the Sundance Festival, the Irish Film Once has become one of the most unexpected phenomena of this year, getting very good reviews by both the public and the press.Directed by John Carney and starring Glen Hansard, Markéta Irglová, Hugh Walsh, Gerry Hendrick, Alastair Foley, Geoff Minogue and Bill Hodnett, the film tells the story of a singer and composer who plays their songs in the streets of Dublin, when he is not working in his father's shop. During the day, to earn some extra money, he interprets known issues for pedestrians, but at night, he plays his own subjects in which speaks of how his girlfriend left him. His talent does not pass unnoticed to an immigrant Czech amateur piano selling flowers on the street, so both will end up working on a demo, the possibility of starting a new life together while hanging over their heads.It is that Once one of those movies that leaves you with a very good taste in mouth after its viewing, despite its bittersweet poso: duration exígua (eighty minutes, think), the film is a simple manifest, more even if we take into account that much of his footage takes place along various musical performances. Once, as I said, is terribly simple at the same time that quite obvious and somewhat sweetened in some respects, but it works. It is simply: there is no complex plots, plot twists, comedy or drama apparent but, in contrast, offers a wide range of feelings and sensations terribly human.And that is probably the formula that makes eleven film, I do not know if memorable, but round: we have two characters worldly, gray and melancholy but not exempt of hope, as the own city of Dublin, linked to a past that is reflected through the music composed. And to join through this, both characters seem to find the reason, the excuse they both needed to leave behind their weights and start a new life together or separately. Eleven offers what a terrible affinity, a mundandad sometimes hurtful, as this perennial feeling round the two protagonists and that makes them wonder with the look and if.?, as probably any of us we will have happened on more than one occasion. And precisely that possibility, hope, makes its players can restart their lives with security that despite all the hits that could give them life from now on, they will always host inside the memory of that person, and that memory will be back to get up and move on.From the delicious introductory scene, until the impossible although hilarious sequence in the Bank looking for a loan, eleven is a song of hope in every rule, next rarely have the opportunity to watch on a screen, and without falling into the clichés of the drama or comedy to the use.A fascinating soundtrack, and a few characters who manage to transmit large amount of emotions and feelings, just speechless make eleven a film of great pleasure viewing, that under no circumstances would classify in the musical genre, and no doubt will be a reference for all those eminently melancholic spirit.Highly recommended, and a pleasant surprise.I give a 7'5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
