<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="The Fall" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A true visual wonder full of symbolism.</summary>
	<body>The fall is the second film directed by Tarsem Singh, known for his excellent career in the world of the music video and his first film, the cell, starring Jennifer Lopez. On this occasion, the Indian director has visited over twenty countries to shoot The fall, film which, according to his own words, was inspired by a Bulgarian film Yo Ho Ho.Tras have been acclaimed in this edition of the festival of Toronto, The fall has been described as the best fairy tale without fairy from the Princess Bride. The film begins with the young Alexandria, a young man with an arm broken at a hospital in Los Angeles in 1920. There you will know Roy, a double for the dangerous scenes, it's commit suicide with morphine. In order to forget their hardships, Roy decides to tell to Alexandria 'the most wonderful story of the world', a tale of dream in which five heroes will travel through space and time to put an end to the evil emperor Odius, who has frustrated their lives.Of all the films that by the time a server has had the opportunity to see in this edition of the Sitges Festival, undoubtedly The fall momentarily, is the big winner. And with difference. Halfway between the Princess Bride and the adventures of Baron Munchausen, The fall is a visual poem, an ode to the fantasy and imagination that captivates the viewer in a way irrremediable.Covert after an alleged account for children, the second feature film by Tarsem Singh maintains this same aesthetic of music video for the cell, in which each sequence is a spectacle of contrasts for the hearing and that the colors seem to exit the screen, thanks largely to the costume design of Eiko Ishioka, acclaimed for his wonderful work both the cell and Coppola's Dracula, by which took the Oscar in 1993.Dejando aside the visual delight which is The fall that, on the other hand, manages to turn every one of their frames in a box of unparalleled beauty, applies that the film could be defined as a beautiful hymn to life and hope, full of symbolism, humor, and so hard as poignant moments starring Lee Pacewho plays the role of the convalescent stuntman Roy Walker in real life, and the masked Bandit in the story, but that he would certainly not have sense without the sweet characterization young Catinca Untaru makes more skeptical Alexandria.Los perhaps to say that The fall touches sometimes ridiculous, that his characters may be joke and that its plot is full of inconsistencies and unexplained temporary jumps, but Tarsem Singh movie manages to bring us both into its history, manages to achieve such affinity between his characters and the Viewer, that any inconsistency or defect is insignificant while history take its course.A true visual wonder full of symbolism, and one of the best placed candidates to win the triumph in Sitges 2007.Le give a 8'5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
