<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="À lintérieur" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He manages to maintain the tension over the orgy gore that we often find in the splatter, thanks to an oppressive atmosphere productions and a few special effects, above the truculence, seeking disturb the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>One of the extreme proposals of this edition of the Sitges Festival has been the French film À l'intérieur, translated into English as Inside. If last year was 13 Tzameti the main gala representative, À l'intérieur already has been named by the press as the bloodiest French film of recent times À l'intérieur is the work of a couple of new directors, Alexandre Bustillo and Julien Maury, who, by the way, already been hired to make a remake of Hellraiser. The film, starring Béatrice Dalle (who can also see in the fantastic drama Cannibal Trouble every day), Alysson Paradis, Nathalie Roussel, François-Régis Marchasson, Jean-Baptiste Tabourin and Dominique Frot, tells the story of a young girl, Sara, pregnant and alone since the car accident that took the life of her husband, that on the eve of Christmas receives the unexpected visit of a womanwhose an itention is snatch her son still unborn. À l'intérieur has been one of the movies that one server has enjoyed in the present edition of the Sitges Festival and, undoubtedly, it is the most extreme difference.With this peculiar style of the most recent French horror film, À l'intérieur could not leave of remember me, especially in the first section of film, high voltage, Alexandre Aja. And is that the initial of both films approach continues to be quite similar: while high voltage we have a young man who is going to spend a few days with a friend and her parents in a hidden rural area, where victims of harassment apparently unjustified from a villager, À l'intérieur ourselves with a young pregnant woman toon the eve of new year's, it is attacked by an enigmatic woman, also no apparent reason.In both films the original tension focuses on the first stretch of film because one of the key premises of all-time horror movies, the lack of justification by the aggressor. And, really, the first steps of the film of Maury and Bustillo are really creepy, at least until the moment in which the lens of the camera begins to dye red.And it is that À l'intérieur, on the other hand, has been able to let remind me also that great jewel of Takashi Miike's Audition name, while Japanese filmmaker gets book with a master's degree without precedent throughout its explicit and overwhelming savagery until the average end times stronger in the history of the cinema, while the novice French directors are certain promiscuityoffering us already the first round a good dose of offal that it will only overcome herself in an anthological crescendo.As well, however, and with the exception of a couple of scenes that, if they had been omitted, would have made À l'intérieur film infinitely more round than it already is, especially if we take into account that it's an opera prima, the film manages to maintain the tension over the typical orgy gore that we often find in the splatter títpicamente productions, above all thanks to an oppressive atmosphere and a few special effects, above the truculence or the desparrame intestinal free, seek to disturb the Viewer.In short, a delight for lovers of extreme cinema, and a really brilliant début.I give it a 8 out of 10.</body>
</review>
