<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Promesas del Este" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cronemberg portrays at the same time the most despicable and instincts laudable human under the instinct of survival as he is only able to do.</summary>
	<body>After having terrified many with films like came from inside of, rabies, Videodrome, Scanners or fly, the Canadian filmmaker David Cronemberg began to change registration already with the naked lunch (or even before), but was not until A history of violence when the dramatic concerns of the director were acclaimed worldwide.With Eastern promises, David Cronemberg returns to work together with Viggo Mortensen, who is accompanied on this occasion by Naomi Watts, Vincent Cassell, Armin Mueller-Stahl, Sinéad Cusack and Donald Sumpter. The film tells the story of the mysterious Nikolai, born in Russia, which works as a driver of one of the most important families of organized crime in Eastern Europe. Headed by Semyon, the charming owner of expensive Russian restaurant hidden behind a brutal and cold nature behind his smile, the fate of the family reeling due to Kirill, his crazy son, which makes more case to Nikolai than to his own father. But the cautious Nikolai life changes suddenly when he meets Anna, a midwife who works at a hospital in London. Anna is very affected by the situation in which was a teenager who dies giving birth, and decides to look for the family of the girl based on the newspaper that left written in Russian. To digging in the diary, Anna inadvertently triggers the wrath of the mafia.It can be that you for many, which I included before leaving to rest this criticism for a few hours before putting me to write it, Eastern promises is something less than A history of violence, much more direct and with fewer concessions. But, after recalling the story and dialogues, after recall certain sequences, some details, a server has chosen to change their minds.A shocking hyperrealism, Eastern promises is, as usual in the work of the Canadian, a sort of manners portrait of a sector of society, unknown to most, at the same time a reflection of the brutality inherent in the human being. With Viggo Mortensen taciturn in contrast with Vincent Cassel rather than convincing and, above all, with an Armin Mueller-Stahl truly superb, Eastern promises naked without any concession the animality of man unleashed by the power and the arrogance.Cronemberg portrays at the same time the most despicable and instincts laudable human under the instinct of survival, showing them under a false appearance reflects, on the one hand, through a bleak Viggo Mortenen capable of performing heinous acts with a terrifying estoicidad at the same time that does not hesitate to bring into play its own integrity in an altruistic Act and, on the other, with an Armin Mueller-Stahl under whose affability hides a capable of killing both by imposing its respect, a respect that is undermined by the acts of his own son and hide their sins ruthless being.On the other hand, can be said that the role of Naomi Watts is perhaps the least attractive of Eastern promises, representing the London citizen (read Western) current who discovers the sordidness of a London slum and unknown, almost marginal, in which a modern revision of the tyranny and slavery to survive under the figure of clans and mafias.Anyway, maybe that Eastern promises finf some slowness in your footage, in which the events occur with a chilling everyday, without excessive shocks or unexpected plot twists. And, as usual in the Filmography of the Canadian, their violence is filmed with an almost hurtful, aberrant harshness in some cases with a hyper-realism, a naturalism, tremendously impressive.Very good film.I give it a 8 out of 10.</body>
</review>
