<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good film despite its many references, but neither much less is the wonder that have tried to sell us with its promotional bombardment.</summary>
	<body>Produced by Guillermo del Toro, the path traveled so far by the orphanage before even of the approval of the public has been truly spectacular. First of all, the film, directed by a novel director as Juan Antonio Bayona and starring Belén Rueda in the title role, accompanied by Fernando Cayo, Géraldine Chaplin, Roger Prince and Mabel Rivera was chosen to inaugurate the present edition of the Sitges Festival, and makes only a few days, named official candidate to the Oscar on behalf of our country.The orphanage tells the story of Laura, a woman who returns with his family to the orphanage in which grew from girl with the intention of opening a residence for disabled children. The new environment arouses the imagination of his son, which begins to be carried away by increasingly intense fantasy games. They are concerned to Laura over its increasingly, to the point where comes to think that there is something in the House is threatening his family. She comes up with something extraordinary and, despite the fact that she is a woman with very clear principles, his universe falters questioning everything in what believed. do both trumpeting deserves the orphanage? The truth is that not.The film, despite having a beautiful Bill, offers absolutely nothing we have not seen since a thousand times, extolling a plot with echoes to movies like Poltergeist, the island of the dead or even, why not, White noise, an aesthetic hitchcockiana and locations on the line of films as The haunting. But, undoubtedly, if there is a film whose comparison is odious with the directorial debut of Juan Antonio Bayona, that is each other. And it is that the orphanage cannot fail to remind us in many ways to the genius of Alejandro Amenábar, because bebe avidly it both aesthetic and arguably.Odious comparisons aside, one must recognize certain merits of the orphanage.As I said, the film has a beautiful Bill, even though it lacks the drama that many had promised and that, supposedly, made it into something more than a simple supernatural horror film. On the other hand, Belén Rueda performed a remarkable performance, eirigiéndose as soul of the film, largely because the rest of interpretations do not cease to be almost anecdotal, as Géraldine Chaplin, who must appear at least in ten minutes of footage in a sequence, joking aside, it appears to be taken from fourth Milenio.Aunque, for a server, the biggest problem of the orphanage is its lack of personality, and is that the movie has been done in a way so academic, as Orthodox, that anyone could have signed the title, especially the own Guillermo del Toro. In addition, add the film of Juan Antonio Bayona fails to create at any time real moments of tension, except in specific occasions thanks to certain usual but always efectistas turns and, as usual with this kind of films, with twenty minutes of footage one already can guess how to finish the story.Finally, a recommended film, but that does not provide anything new.I am a 6'5 sopbre 10.</body>
</review>
