<review author="Javier Saz" title="Naturaleza muerta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The environment is imposed, the beauty of the images, frames, camera, music and sound for a living and indispensable work, movements almost seems it breathe by itself.</summary>
	<body>There are films that seeing them will they catch inevitably, this is the case of "Naturaleza muerta" ('Sanxia haoren', 2006).There are films that after seeing them grow in memory and their images are rooted forever, this is the case of the extraordinary film directed by Jia Zhang-ke.Cercana to the best films of Roberto Rossellini by starting a documentary reality for a fiction, as in "Rome, city abiet" or "Germany, year zero", the environment, the stage always surpasses fiction. "Naturaleza muerta" is a beautiful workstrange, powerful, alive, sad and beautiful. Different readings that do not have a greater or lesser importance in total if not belonging and form part of a single unit of itself as a work.The search for a father of her daughter, the search for a wife of her husband, the search in a dead place, somewhere in the process of disappearance, one goes in search of her past, she to break definitively with his.As the unstoppable advance of the policy of the Chinese Government with the creation of the three Gorges Dam condemning entire neighbourhoods, (reordenadas) ripped people from their lives. destruction to progress? And the consequences? No longer the consequences following the destruction if not the consequences during the destruction. Fiction to show a untold reality. A pervertidamente Westernized and materialistic culture. UFOs appearing on the horizon and buildings that take off from the ground.Made in high definition video, "Naturaleza muerta" is structured in three parts for telling us two simultaneous but not converging stories. The environment is imposed, the beauty of the images, frames, camera, music and sound for a living and indispensable work, movements almost seems it breathe by itself. (4 +)</body>
</review>
