<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Mr Brooks" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mr. Brooks manages to be above the average of thrillers that have been premiering during the last years, and just very entertaining and burning result, above all, for a Sunday afternoon.</summary>
	<body>Mr. Brooks is one of those movies whose plot premise is really good; Moreover, this uneven film by Bruce a. Evans begins in a masterful way, to become a simple entertainment, but equally interesting. The star is Kevin Costner, whose consciousness (played by a superb William Hurt) pursues him during the footage, and you will be warning of all the facts "should" be. You can say that this part of the film is the most interesting and best carried out, but unfortunately, with an intention to nothing rather than commercial, Evans chooses to add the effect police thriller, with a correct Demi Moore at the helm, and with a rather disappointing result, since it has little to do with the story and also too topical. So I would call this Mr. Brooks as a film very entertaining, with some dialogue and interpretations that surprise and, despite everything, irregular in its storyline.Somehow, could be a return to the genre of the psychokillers, either by its classical form of being told by his noventera aesthetic (very typical of the costume), and this is, for my taste, a real success. We are not tired, already, the typical modern thriller with cutting-edge technology and empty characters? As I said, Kevin Costner and his alter ego are those who carry the Palm, with some great interpretations, will undoubtedly make a style elegant and at the same time sadistic. But Mr. Brooks contains a huge and aforementioned bug, and the have added a police plot even more complicated (not complex) than the of the killer protagonist that little is beside the point. This, undoubtedly, makes waver the irregular script and losing interest to the main story, whose content is much more work. Unfortunately, a clumsy and unnecessary character appears in the middle of a painful Dane Cook, and makes the work of writer will end up being lousy. Thus, this is a film with a screenplay with interbedded absurd and a truly interesting initial plot. A film really irregular, but not entirely failed.However, Mr. Brooks manages to be above the average of thrillers that have been premiering during the last years, and just result very entertaining and adiente, especially for a Sunday afternoon. Before all, recommended.</body>
</review>
