<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Rec" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hyperrealism, if they want to, but it matters little: matter is pure cinema, new movies, movies fact to last in the memory, but then (temperate) know what's deceit, what marketing and, above all, how much of what seen here is certainly new.</summary>
	<body>'[REC]' is based on a plot premise viscerally away from any film pattern: not fiction, there is a gradual and adrenalítica immersion in the pure terror. The fear may be lacking arguments so the Ribbon offers a mcguffin lengthened until the last five minutes (where there is a slight explanation for what we have referred to) and a coherent crescendo of scares and Visual atrocities filmed with an undeniable sense of the show, although cheater because puts us in direct a Spain verismo anyone when in reality (Plaza and Balagueró) makers are making movies, and also not insignificant. '[REC]' is physical film, a corporeality so tangible that hurts: its protagonists are not characters, though they are ontologically, but people and except some actor who note that it is, all away (and has its merit) force a diction or impostar a few gestures. The sensation of watching television (and not film) occupies almost all of the footage. What looks like a televised document makes that we feel as credible what we see. Cinema always deceives us, and we accept the deception as a payment for the happiness that we reported, but the effort of the writers (the cited Plaza and Balagueró more Luis Alejandro Berdejo) approaches the Vertigo and hyperrealist everyday reality shows and videos to the youtube to the big screen and breaks the innocence of Viewer. We are voyeurs, voyeurs with pedigree, if you want to, they have paid an entry and eat popcorn and drinking cola while they ametrallan us misery and vices, textures of the real that sometimes seem to fiction and matters of fiction resembling beauties of the real times, I would say Machado.El format here is the success, the success: are so accustomed to television we shape and positioned to the reality that we do not consider that cinema can also do so. At least, not as instantly. The film makes us better or worse people, gives us culture us dumbs, we enlisted in the army of the people trained and responsible, sensitive and human or makes us mercenaries of the foolish, robotized instruments of mediocrity. '[REC]' has the merit outstanding transfer formats, light film where before there was scattered bits of life that a clever editor has assembled for the benefit of the artistic innovation. Because the film is, above all, a prodigy of pure art. The Blair Witch Project breakthrough, but was a simplistic film--in its complexity - and devoid of hook, even though the idea (foundational) was remarkable. Perceive in '[REC]' what film in its very purest form, and I don't know exactly what I mean by that, but thus I felt. There is a kind of accountability before the small Magisterium of his workers, who handle with a priceless respect terror, which has been trampled, ignored, frivolizado, instrumentalizado and, finally, deformed until the parody by the recent film of masses and now get a rewarding injection of verve and coherence. '[REC]' must be the terror of the twenty-first century tape, or at least one that serve as reference to illustrate the modes of production in line with the times that we live. Shooting, imagine that nothing conventional da for a making of anthological, but is that the tape is in itself a making off of himself, a prodigious display of metacine asking to be referred to in a very strict context. The same must not be see the movie in large room in house. The movie theater is a wonderful place for many reasons. One of them is the ability that has to transform the spectator into true spectator. At home, the film is almost always an extra that sneaks into the relationship of domestic activities. I can prepare dinner and then sit on my high definition screen to watch a movie. Until I can stop it and dispense with all what I offer and return to what it was. Going to the cinema is to participate in a kind of invisible communion with the astonishment and the ritual. '[REC]' requests shouts be seen with more people.In fact, there are forums on the network reported on the reaction of the public with more detail and prose that opinion on the film itself.The mockumentary taken to the extreme of 1809–1865 fiction carries more than one hoax. The absence of a formal and elaborate script is excusable because what matters (and how) is that this deranged alembic of hatches and gloomy corridors we entertained for an hour and a half without, at any time, want to end of the hallucination.The zombie subgenre has found a key that will open new doors: there are already remake USA, apparently. Plaza and Balagueró are doing much for the Spanish film and are (mostly) dignifying a type of film usually cornered on the shelves of video shops, capable of delivering bazofias of the size of a planetary orbit more easily than any other genre, including bird melodrama, which is more reliably where the embarrassment, the misery and the falsity of those who seek to make art and found only a roll of tape which should impress with images.</body>
</review>
