<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="187" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hard film about a teacher with strong educational ideals that should channel a few students of Institute. Rather it tense, hard and with a very emotional ending, although it is a little heavy. To see one time and no more.</summary>
	<body>Director: Kevin Reynolds. duration: does not reach the two short hours.Release date: November 17, 1997.Espectadores: 31.468 human beings.There is a film genre that I encadila although, fortunately, does not exist a real number of films of the same, and it is the porfesor who wants to save students descarriados in troubled neighborhoods of U.S.. I am not referring to the kind of "The boys of the choir" (that pretty, and what soundtrack), or even to "The club of dead poets" (oh, my captain, my Captain), if not the type "Rector" (with James Belushi defending their school). The hairs as escarpias and have not yet started or to talk about the movie of the day, which is none other than "One Eight Seven" a code the police which means homicide (not me are super legs and you read cientoocheta and seven as I).The film is about a timorous professor who works in the Institute more hard in the U.S. giving science classes. A small incident with a student that catea takes him to ask for a 15-month low, as well as losing his job. So what, past this period, enters another Institute to make a replacement. At first, the memories crowd you and feels loose, but little by little is achieving that this cluster of present and future criminals learn a little.Let's start by saying that nothing else finish the film caught the sword and I went to liberate Scotland, which take a chalk and go to teach oafs is much less poetic. What finalón more lagrimógeno, as gozé. I have already warned that this genre I like, right? Well, the argument is that more or less know, except that some conflicting students are beginning to have accidents and soars over Trevor Gardfield (the Professor) the shadow that he may be taking justice into their own hands. The role of the teacher assumes it Samuel L Jackson and I believe that does not end it embroidery, not be if movies or what, but you do not get in their flesh. On the other hand if you get do you charge of the situation, so you spend a tense time and at the same time enjoy the history.In short, hard film about a teacher with strong educational ideals that should channel a few students of Institute. Rather it tense, hard and with a very emotional ending, although it is a little heavy. To see one time and no more.Can steal us the chalk, but never will they remove us the pizaaaarraaaaa!Besitos.P.D: The average age of the American institutes is 28 and the minimum height 1.75, Amen have biceps like legs of gorrino, that you may not know.Pd2: The scene move the Phalanx is a total hijoputismo, I loved it.</body>
</review>
