<review author="Berto" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One continuation rather than worthy of that great film which is the first part, entertaining equal or more than its predecessor, although this falls much more in sensationalism than in the old regustillo of the old movies.</summary>
	<body>Jack Sparrow has returned to sailing the seas. Continuing the success that took part in around the world in 2003, Disney decided to exploit the goose that lays the golden eggs with a return to the old films of pirates and was released to record the second and third part at a stretch, to thus cut costs and problems of compatibility with the main actors in the film. It is in this summer of 2006 which comes Pirates of the Caribbean: the chest of the dead man, continuing exactly where we left off Pirates of the Caribbean: the curse of the Black Pearl. Will and Elizabeth are about to marry, but for having helped the escape of Jack Sparrow are imprisoned and sentenced to death. This is sufficient for Will Turner, commanded by Lord Beckett, go in search of Jack Sparrow, which is sufficiently busy trying to save his soul because of an ancient Pact with the pirate Davy Jones. From here, and as expected, thousand and one adventures and journeys throughout all Caribbean Spanish. in this second part take precedence and much incredible situations. If the first part of what made it a success that was around the films of Errol Flynn with duels of swords, approaches and other pirates classic situations, in this second part pulling in excess of special effects, removing a part of the magic and that old taste of great adventure film that distilled the first. Why not the film loses strength, the scenes are the most spectacular, but make it a too visual spectacle when the best would have been to have remained in the same style. That if, despite this change from the classical to the special effect adventure, history does not lose too, remains a pure entertainment of two hours and half in which the major protagonist, separate special effects, is Captain Jack Sparrow. Here Johnny Depp leaves bring still more back in the pirate half amanerado, without feelings and totally rogue, constructing a totally overloaded interpretation in relation to the first part, and but the scenes in which runs in this second part I refer. A real enjoyment to see it on screen, because when the sale removes the leading role the rest of actors, which are more or less correctillos.Orlando Bloom repeats his role of Will Turner, and in this second part sees a Will Turner much more charismatic than in the first part, though still not even remotely to the packing and personality that distills Jack Sparrow. As for Keira Knightley, she if going to worse, dedicating himself to put the same face of horny throughout the film and doing the worst role for my taste of the entire film. Note well that this change of personality are things of the script plan more independent woman who does not fear anything to go in search of his beloved, but is becoming repellent in some scenes, and but for the beach scene I refer, for anyone who has already seen the film.The rest of side are in his line. Bill Nighty, is everything it rather than special effects leave work with that makeup/prosthesis which makes it completely unrecognisable, being his eyes the only thing that can bring the actor for his portrayal of the evil Pirate/Squid Davy Jones. Attentive incidentally to the acentillo that have put you in the Spanish version, the truth that has its charms. Stellan Skarsgård, correct in his role as Bill the boots, Will Turner's father, and repeated again all the former crew of the Black Pearl, incorporating the very booming lately Naomie Harris in the role of aunt Dalma, very inspired character in my opinion in the video game series also pirate Monkey Island and this September 8 will be able to see her sharing poster with Colin Farrell and Jamie Foxx in Miami Vice.La so very discretita address by Gore Verbinsky. Plans comprehensive teaching pretty good action, thing welcome in times videocliperos in which we find ourselves, although with a great failure, because still do not understand account that comes this horrible initial level to slow that stretches unnecessarily and that still did not I've found sense.Of the script can little comment either. Typical phrases, and more of it than the first of the parties, that links in history with many of the things in the first part, leaving the comic part above all to the character of Jack Sparrow. Ultimately, a continuation rather than worthy of that great film which is the first part, entertaining equal or more than its predecessor, although in this falls a lot more in sensationalism than in the old regustillo of the old movies. As it could not be otherwise, they leave an ending that you makes you want to kill them, the style of the two towers, and leaving us with the question of which will be the end of the adventure for Jack, Elizabeth and Will in this third installment it premiered in May 2007 and at present only we know that it developed in the South seas.</body>
</review>
