<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La Luna en Botella" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not only we have the more risky project of the Spanish film so far this year; It is that most personal of recent times is one of the films.</summary>
	<body>Brave was the first word that came to mind when I saw the first trailer of the Moon in the bottle, a film by a director that I, in my ignorance, it had never heard at the time. Brave because the aforementioned teaser gave to understand that we live to a different tape in the Spanish scene although some questions about whether it would not be a cheater announcement left open or if it would not respond to an attempt to imitate other directors ("Delicatessen" came to mind) rather than an own vision.Now that I've seen the movie, if someone asks me what I thought to leave the screening you have to answer frankly: Grojo, you are a brave man!Because not only we have the more risky project of the Spanish film so far this year; It is that most personal of recent times is one of the films. If only for that reason, they already deserve much applause Grojo as screenwriter and director as producers who put money for that dream possible.And dreams, is precisely what is the movie. Those impossible dreams we all have. Or should I say almost everyone there in the film, as in life, who no longer dream. It is faith in the impossible, in the cosmic utopia, which moves the hearts of the protagonists of the film and which moved, I have no doubt, to Grojo to write the screenplay and fight to bring forward against all odds. Dreams must be pursued them and no matter the amount of times and ways that tell you "NO", because sometimes only occasionally, the stars are placed in a row, the miracle occurs and you hear a redemptive and final "Yes".At this point already you you may have noticed that is a film by and for dreamers. Therein lies its strength and hence, in part, also its weakness. Because the tape has a dot of innocence that is appreciated in times they run but that, at the time, can move her from certain types of public more given to "realism". The film is Yes, innocent because innocent is dream in a world which strives to topple utopias every day. If you are not willing to believe in the impossible you should not see this film.Unfortunately the tape is not perfect. I think it would have needed more spending when it comes to filming because I have the feeling that there are ideas that have been in the dark and others that have not been all the well that could have had more time/money. Of course, money in the promotion has been missing but that, in addition to endemic Spanish film is also due to the economic problems of Sogecine currently.Nor I am convinced all the resolution of the story of Rossignol (Dominique Pinon) and his two comrades. I could not explain it but despite seem to me a good ending, there is something in the gear that I finished fit. Speaking of late, also of the history of Zeta (Edu Soto) is for me something rushed and helpings.Edu Soto is in fact, one of the things that I do not like because, although their factions fit with the character and follow to his personality, his interpretation does not convince me and seems loose most of the function. I do not know if it is by him or not but its history with Alicia (Bárbara Goenaga) is somewhat ñoña, but to me I won't be annoying.On the other hand the actors are good and especially the side as Leigh Zimmerman (Irene), who sings a beautiful song, Michael Jenn (Kurt), Federico Luppi (Rubén Cumplido), Usun Yoon (Michelle) or a Dominique Pinon which is especially brilliant.I also like and, above all, amuses me the vision of art and famous artists offered the tape. Details malicious as of the profession of the protagonist (writes great books that have signed authors famous and uninspired) or the artist who makes a giant egg for a city square and wondered if he should not have done a cube &hellip; but if something would remind you of the film, in addition to its beautiful and utopian history and the tremendous courage to have brought forward a project like thisIt is its visual brilliance and their ability to create a personal world in which Grojo manages to convince us that everything is possible and that maybe, someday, we also can put the Moon in a bottle.Final rating: 7 out of 10.</body>
</review>
