<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Francis Lawrence terjiversa altogether the Matheson message for the benefit of a hopeful palomitero blockbuster that loses its charm in the middle of footage.</summary>
	<body>Here is the Christmas blockbuster.Directed by Francis Lawrence, responsible for entertaining Constantine, almost entirely by Will Smith with Alice Braga, Charlie Tahan, Salli Richardson, Paradox Pollack and a cameo of Emma Thompson included, finally reaches our screens of the third film adaptation of I am legend, Richard Matheson novel in 1954.La film puts us in 2012. Robert Neville is the last man alive on the face of the Earth, although he is not alone. The other men, women and children have become vampires, and are all thirsty for the blood of Neville. During the Hunter, looking for the living dead while sleeping, but at night you must hide waiting for dawn.The truth is that a server had a terrible desire to this film, but apparently not have been able to feel more than a remarkable disappointment; not by the product itself, but rather by what I am Legend could have been and is not. But, for better or for worse, this blog has always defended the fact of having read a novel prior to the screening of a film, and we will not make an exception now.Lasting little more than an hour and a half, I am legend is divided into two distinct parts, along which we are witnessing various flashbacks - not very fortunate usually - intended to put in background. The first half, certainly the most interesting, is only and exclusively performed by a solvent Will Smith accompanied by his dog Sam and Francis Lawrence delights us with a succession of spectacular panoramic images of a New York devastated and seriously affected by the undisturbed advance of mother nature: buildings in ruins, abandoned vehicles, dirt everywhere. The Big Apple is now a vetigio of the past, a ghost town inhabited only by Robert Neville, which seeks to maintain the codura through habit and custom, either with a disciplined daily order, with the search for a cure, or desperate interaction with his dog, on radio, or sets with mannequinsasking to beats of silence various moral dilemmas both the protagonist and our own society.Unfortunately, as the plot of I am Legend ceases to delight with its approach to begin to develop, the myth is crumbling steps agitantados: on the one hand we are with the terrible disappointment involving vampires, not by appearances - on the other hand, based on topical effect-coups, but by its own reconstruction digital, quite far from the refinement of the CGI we have seen in several productions throughout this final 2007.Enthey are poorly made.On the other hand, the identity crisis which should lead to the emergence of Anna and his son in the far monotonous life of Neville although Yes we is raised, for the benefit of the persecutions and the shootings of rigour, though not badly shot nor posed no wonder, that without taking into account the various inconsistencies that raise. As if this were little, the outcome I am legend - that I will not reveal - is dotted with a hopeful pseudoreligiosa moralina, beyond being radically opposed to the original intention of Richard Matheson, simply is insultingly dogmatic.Ultimately, a server so just highlight the first half of the film, as Smith should begin to interact, I am legend is lost by palomiteros paths which, despite being (relatively) required throughout blockbuster raised otherwise would have given foot to a completely different film and, probably, quite round.Maybe the dog Sam.Le am a 6 out of 10, even if if I would compare the conba film the original novel, the note descended sharply to a 3'5 or 4.</body>
</review>
