<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Pepito piscinas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is very bad, but the appearances of Tip and Coll are essential viewing.</summary>
	<body>As a child I wanted to see this film, not because me it fascinase the argument nor the big players, not even by the suggestive poster, much less. If not to discover what referred my family when in closed circles, while we were in pools or beaches commented by the bajini mira to pepito pools goes out there and everyone is dying of laughter at the sight of a bathing suit type cojón - outside and a man more cool than an eight. That time, my mother.The film is a man (don Fernando Esteso) which is a well-known car salesman. Its scope of action are the swimming pools and the boités with surprising results, especially that can't swim. By accidents of fate, one day discovers launched seductive networks a girl to run a rallie on the Costa del Sol. That more you want? If we have cars, women, beach, erostismo, Estesismo and more.So yes, I would like to a little more, that the thing is too weak. And it is that the script is very, very flojote, with a criminal outcome. In positive terms, it has a soundtrack of the caspismo Summit, created exclusively for the film. From time to time appear Tip and Coll, without having nothing to do with development and come to mind, giving you a great point that saves the bonfire to the final product. Special attention to the scene which Tip sell you a car to Coll, masterful. And look at that boy didn't understand the humor of these gentlemen, but when I saw this movie almost I fall of the Chair.In short, the film is very bad, but the appearances of Tip and Coll are essential viewing. It has more myth than film.PS: "give me cream in the buttocks says Tip to Coll both sausages in their black suits".Pd2: I do not understand by that if they wanted to make a special Tip and Coll, put you all the roll of film of adorno.P.D.3: Fuck in the scene driving a Mercedes, what you see is the national I, which has changed slightly, specifically at the edges which is now full of homes. Things.</body>
</review>
