<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am legend is the new producto-espectáculo which offers Hollywood for winning the battle in the Christmas box office, but despite his good start, turns out to be a predictable and sleeping more film.</summary>
	<body>Approaching the holiday season, and if not enough with the constant bombardment of ads, the hustle and bustle that is created day if and day also in the shopping areas, and the night lighting in each city, the Billboard arrive which plague the big betting Hollywood by the box office.After the failures (always speaking in language Hollywood) of Beowulf and the Golden Compass, arrives to us I am legend, introduces us to Will Smith as the last human alive on the face of the Earth. With a very encouraging approach, in which up to the cinema of catastrophes already through our country (albeit only the appearance of a Madrid devastated in a poster in Seoul theaters I am Legend), starts a film unsuitable for most staunch critics of Will Smith as he appears in almost all of the frames. In honor of the truth, the film has a few minutes that hooked by its intensity, largely thanks to well boulders are a soulless New York City levels. Unfortunately, the intensity will falling as the story becomes monotonous and repetitive, and is that you have as protagonist the last living man on the planet does not give much game for a film of entertainment. And at the moment they appear infected, by the screen parade a series of persecutions and several shootings that will only cause one to those viewers who had fallen victims of the sleepy show. All this ends in a final filled with American morality and with a strong religious emphasis.I am legend is the new producto-espectáculo which offers Hollywood for winning the battle in the Christmas box office, but despite his good start, turns out to be a predictable and sleeping more film. Ideal for a warm afternoon in the film and take a good NAP to the health of a long-suffering Will Smith.</body>
</review>
