<review author="Jesus Lens" title="La noche de los girasoles" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I have been fascinated, causing me the mixture of repulsion and attraction that carries the look, face to face, the more murky, complex and contradictory status (in) human.</summary>
	<body>If this film, instead of passing in a village of Castile-León, aconteciese in places of Iowa or Wisconsin and instead of by civil guards, the criminal investigation was carried out by a sheriff tripudo and his young Assistant, we would be hearing and reading thousand and one magnificent film of black gender absolutely model and book critics.If, rather than come signed by an unknown Jorge Sánchez-Cabezudo, carry the signature of the Coen brothers, we would be talking about a new enduring classic of the noir genre. Because "The night of the sunflowers" is an excellent black and crime genre film, based on a prodigious script that signs the same Jorge Sánchez. where has gone this type? What round in his head? Now, just a few hours after suffering and enjoy with his film, I don't know anything of him. But I think hear and, from now on, make a close monitoring. Because "The night of the sunflowers" has fascinated me, causing me the mixture of repulsion and attraction that carries the look, face to face, the more murky, complex and contradictory status (in) human.Let us in history: some young cavers reach a village, to investigate whether newly discovered caves may have some appeal from the turístico-arqueológico point of view - scientific. At the same time, a traveling salesman is teaching its showcase of industrial vacuum cleaners in the area. The only two survivors of a deserted village are still fighting and after the civil guard and one of his subordinates, which at the same time is his son-in-law, dine in House how to get, with these twigs, an excellent film of black gender? Such is the greatness of the indent of Sánchez-Cabezudo. Using resources tarantinianos, playing with time and space, by concatenating the cross stories of characters so private as simple and ordinary, having swallowed dry and brutal violence of Sam Peckimpah "straw dogs"; We have a film without concessions, exciting, hard, devastating.During the two hours of footage, there is little time to take a deep breath. -What is this?, you ask yourself continually. And this is. What Jorge pleases. And what want you is to change registration, surprise and enchant the Viewer every quarter of an hour. And you get it. "Because, as in the exquisite corpses that both liked our surrealists, each segment of the film is linked to the previous one, but only to give a brutal twist to a story which, however, ends up having a total and absolute, without leaving not an only coherence loose.""The night of the sunflowers" is a film of multiple viewings, calling voices a Deluxe Edition DVD that allows us to recreate in a puzzle so ingenious as well shot. If had to put a but. the music. Sometimes it becomes too obvious and charisma. But hey, you already see the but that we put to an extraordinary and colossal film that I'm already looking forward to see again.</body>
</review>
