<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Charlie y la fábrica de Chocolate" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>more applause.</summary>
	<body>Applause please. Thanks a lot.The film is about a child of those that do not exist in an imaginary world with an amazing script. This child lives with his parents and four grandparents in a House any pillar or wall remain vertical. Willy Wonka is the owner of largest Chocolatier Empire in the world, where manufactures the best chocolates that exist. But it takes years without leaving the factory and has, apparently, no worker therein. One day, a mysterious posters announced that it will open its factory for five children who find a ticket gold in the interior of a Wonka candy bar... and come about very little gentlemen, and rivers of chocolate, cocoa palaces, magic lifts, incredible events and impossible characters; and more stuff that I've loved.Tim Burton has made plagiarism. Have you got the dreams that we all have and has put them on a film. I have no words, and look that is rare, to describe what I just saw. It may seem exaggerated, that probably, but for many years he enjoyed not taaaaaanto with a film. Everything I loved, absolutely everything. I laughed, I cried, I am excited, I have suffered. I have lived, and I have not bored in no time. Increible.TODO in this film is care to detail. Characters have faces full of expressiveness, clearly indicating what its role. The sets are amazing, mixing digital effects with the purest papier-mache. The scenes are implausible and at the same time perfectly credible, safe to we have dreamed them. The color, impressive, care until the last point of light. The dialogues, embroidered by hand, Word for Word, are perfect. Each word is where it should be. And the musical scenes, watching I usually them hate, are great. The scene of technological child is completely out of the film and at the same time fits to perfection. EU Nice, my mother. Already takes me to go buy the DVD with the version of collector, that my child is going to say that the Remove of the times that I think the see.In short, more applause.Essential. He was going to say that I want a squirrel, but almost that not. And a Lunga Upa, safe or heard. I've eaten half box of Belgian chocolates, this must see it with chocolate, not with the shit that the popcorn which cracks the lips and give them heartburn.</body>
</review>
