<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La Novia Cadaver" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although it is not the style of film that is often seen in these parts, I have to say that it is a very good movie and every time I like more the animation. Highly recommended, although perhaps for children is somewhat harsh.</summary>
	<body>It must be acknowledged that the title of the film coincides fully with it, does not leave an iota. And I can't think of more introductory nonsense.The film is a boy son of a family of newly rich to marry a girl of noble family without a penny. Of course, these two are unknown, although as soon as they are, remain fond (slightly) and the wedding does not seem too bad. By own clumsiness of the boy, this House with a corpse, causing some headaches to everyone. And it is that you have to see how badly it bury people.The type of drawings used Tum Burton in this film I do not end like. It goes without saying that they are real good, but used some colors and some sketches too dark, too dark, too dead. Perhaps that what I am not convinced it is the argument, but the drawings I do not end call. The love story that is seen in the film is quite moralistic, but I have to say that I really liked. The principle, that come to be the first 50 minutes, I did not finish like. But the final half-hour is sublime, especially the last 10, which I greatly enternecieron ('ll be pregnant?). And cerradito that remains throughout the script, without failures anywhere or anything of anything. I liked.In short, although it is not the style of film that is often seen in these parts, I have to say that it is a very good movie and that each time I like more the animation. Highly recommended, although perhaps for children is somewhat harsh.Besitos.P.D: The bride dropped the eye from time to time and get a very funny worm. Mola.P.D.2: Both parents are very well characterized.P.D.3: And the cosas who sings from time to time are not bad. "Do the pulse?" "Sobrevalorado" je, je.</body>
</review>
