<review author="Yojimbo" title="Muerte de un Presidente" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Unfortunately this outburst of originality in the idea does not transform the work in a fascinating documentary.</summary>
	<body>The title and the introduction of this post imitate the provocative intention of the film. The proposal certainly original. Dangerous for some. Highly desired by others. In any case, a product that unleashes the curious to know what would be the time. Come on, one of the ingredients that would need to make a film in box office or very downloaded over the internet.Unfortunately this outburst of originality in the idea does not transform the work in a fascinating documentary. The main attraction of this documentary would be to see how the world is following the assassination of the President more donkey and powerful of the time. But is dedicated exclusively to invent a theory of the murderer.American cinema has been a turnaround significant when looking for enemies in their plots and wars. If previously the Stallones and Schwarzzeneggers which killed Iraqi and other ethnic groups that hated America, now the bad guys are always at home. A traitor. Some crazy considered patriotic. Some unconscious that trains barbarians which then undermine them.The documentary feeds and closes based on the figure of President Bush: his murderer is a soldier who returned traumatised war of Iraq and wanted to settle accounts the culprit. However, as the American intelligence services are not so smart, they blame a Muslim with a somewhat dark history of the assassination of the President.The main attraction for this documentary would be the impact of that murder in USA and the world. It would cease or continue the war of Iraq? Is it would expand to other countries? How it would affect the rest of the world? They honor and ensalzarían Americans a murdered Bush which Kennedy? This documentary does not get wet and does not answer to any of these questions. A pity.</body>
</review>
