<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Antes del atardecer" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Strange conversations, smell of summer, smiles, caresses, kisses... A moment to remember that you don't want to ever escape of fleeting glances of brief moments, accompanied by laughter, gimmicky conversations, gestures.</summary>
	<body>I find it difficult after seeing this film analyzing with coldness, although it would be easy, it is at the same time an exercise which seems to me difficult, let's see, this that analyze these fleeting love, on the one hand people that she pass by your life of obliquely and perhaps, if the destination (curious paradox) would have put them more time (corrido) in your life, perhaps everything would now be different, warm, sincere, people of those with which the mere fact of a coffee on a terrace and share a few minutes of supposed banality leave a huge mark on your interior, sweet moments, that as Ethan Hawke says in the film, remember better than many of your best moments of life.Strange conversations, smell of summer, smiles, caresses, kisses. A moment to remember that you don't want to ever escape of fleeting glances of brief moments, accompanied by laughter, gimmicky conversations, gestures. A lifetime precipitated in a "brief encounter".It is difficult to talk about an hour and twenty projection that leaves a footprint, which although it is easily removable in one fell swoop, the brand there is in you. A great film, that while suffers from an open ending is open? Cone, abiertísimo! Let "I posed" (as usually say from time to time). Especially recommended for all the "hardened romantic" for all those who enjoyed an afternoon of a morning, a few hours of their time accompanied by someone already not this beside her (and you go to knowing where to walk.)Richard Linklater magnifico in the direction, photography perfectly Paris, the city of love, tremendous Hanke and Delpy, in fact sometimes look to the face does not need to see the words how in a simple movie can exist as much magic?In short, without a doubt. You have to see it!</body>
</review>
