<review author="Bruji" title="1408" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do Mikael Hafström demonstrates with facts that? make movies is to know the camera?.</summary>
	<body>Dignísima adaptation of a Stephen King, of remarkable invoice and impeccable direction short story. Mikael Hafström demonstrates with facts that "filmmaking is know the camera", the wise conclusion reached by Martin Scorsese and an essential aspect to bring to fruition the present script. 1408 Always promising are the stories that start in the middle of a rainy night. A study in this regard, trying to figure out fascination engaged in this type of planes of opening should undertake. Of course, find the face of John Cusack in the following, with their notches shirts and his eternal cigarette in the shelter of the ear may presage one of these adventures, which winner horse boot, often lead to stop ass. Just have to remember the famous identity (2003), some even come to understand after the twenty-fourth viewing. On this occasion, the room 1408 (which, if they have not set, sum 13) of a Kafkaesque New York hotel, the Dolphin, located in the 45 with Lexington, proposes a macabre game to the Jumanji where paintings come to life, extreme weather events occur and the different dimensions temporary space are interrelated, without the possibility of finding the dice to try and control the situation. A repeated argument, with vices of Haunted House, which is synthesized in an episode of fourth Millenium in which the mystery ship team performed a recount of our country happy and charming hotels. From the famous room 510 of true Zaragoza hotel to newspapers of the fear experienced by Madrid journalists in an alleged pension of Sabadell. So, obviously it did not mentioned and faithful report, was with the visual aesthetic in which supports tape Hafström, nor with the photograph in pastel shades responsible for Show friendly spaces even in the midst of the most absolute chaos, incorporating the unmistakable red Scorsese in open spaces. And that, above all, 1408, that - either by the ineffectiveness of his award-winning writers, either by own limitations of the story of King-holds an uncertain message, yes that gives an invaluable cinematographic exercise of excellent leadership. Among many other factors, in a film that makes passing most of its footage between four walls, being subject to the incentives and clichés of the genre, it is essential the timely location of the camera. In this sense, very few references that are in the path of the unknown Swedish director. He himself admits that the use of special effects meant you "a learning experience", very well exploited judging by the results that it offers the demonic stay. Nominated for the Oscar for Evil in the best foreign film section, his first American film, without Control, starring by attractive Clive Owen and Jennifer Aniston sosa, transformed the brief meeting, David Lane in a thriller as unexpected as interesting. In 1408, his virtuosity with the camera, brings us to the good movie fan memory make two great directors that always made their presence felt after them. Contra-planos flat troop established between the two main characters: the search of ghosts and the own room, and the travelling of round-trip it runs along the corridor of the 1400 to the 1430, reminiscent of the legendary and extraordinary way of directing that raised Max Ophüls at many of his dramas. The German filmmaker used this technique to accentuate the impeccable structure of his screenplays; While Hafström, in the absence of a solid narrative, used to wisely, achieve the introduction of the plot. On the other hand, the extensive level sequence that it flies by the hall and its tendency toward the creation of flat impossible, bring us closer to the film style of another of the large, Brian de Palma. In both cases, this attitude intelligent, after a careful mimo to recreate the most insignificant details that put to the test the photographic memory, ensures widespread cold sensation when the thermostat marks five degrees below zero, "taponados ears" at the time in which decides to dispense with the sound of anguish to be bound to mentally tell the eighteen steps that occur by the cornice. Or what is the same, manage to envelop the viewer in an intriguing approach that brings depth to such brief story; shuffling, at all times, the double possibility of reaching different alternative outcomes that will be offered in the DVD version. Therefore, and for all tastes, hallucinations may - or may not - be true paranormal effects, with the belief that personal ghosts that attack to each of us are as dangerous as the esperpénticos beings of the most there. Thus, it is not true that the great mistake of the film may be at the chosen end. The best novels of King of hundreds of pages, are settled in way rarely satisfying and always surprising, in the last five. 1408, In its final stretch, satisfies and is not surprising. That Yes, leaves a good sentences for collectors, and makes the genre lovers sing that old song of Mecano: "during an hour and a half I could be happy, eating chocolate and popcorn". In the end, what is if not the film?</body>
</review>
