<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Next" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There is no way possible term, there is no bondado; one of the most demoledoramente "bad" movies this chronicler of his vices could be seen in their few years of cinematic experience. Are you clear?</summary>
	<body>Being rigorous, Next lays some of the more harmful vices that plague the current cinema or, moving away for once defeatist tone that will substantiate this Misty review, film checked into the Hollywood and prevented in the company of sweeping to victory at box office, contribute little or nothing to the memory of any moderately intelligent film lover and above allEnter the market of the DVD so much or more than the proceeds in movie theaters. I do not know the cause and maybe me not strive too much in search for her, but strikes me as very complicated task to write about what amazes me and me trying to pleasure (write about the pure Excellence) and instead, I go the fingers as nerve lizards when I touch (today is the pleasant day) heaping abuse on a product of obvious or already direct and nauseabundamente bad mediocrity. Infected by all possible evils and any more than my NAP Wednesday laziness makes me not reach now, Next plays with the advantage of not be breaking any cultural law, but should skirt the crime and the case that in the future some public quality inspection agency (CPI, ja) Decides to veto or warning on the cover of the terrible evil that can cause your consumptionNext is the formidable Golden Palm of absolute chaos and the bear of platinum in terms of annihilation of everything that smacks of simplicity, clairvoyance, quality, in short, those things that make life journeys through most soft paths and all us put hair on end and the soul assertive when we see nice things on a screen. The like, common sense and beauty, abstract concepts absent in this embarrassing hodgepodge as an anal intercourse in a farce of the brothers Alvarez Quintero.Podemos to fine-tune the configuration of the Colt of linguistic torture by recourse to a topic or two hundred, but for once it will be a topic (or 200) convenient: our friend Nicolas Cage is already-fondón, can spare you four films per year and that of young and still has reaños and capacity to lift flight and redirect a career that has had interesting moments (Leaving Las Vegas) or even any indisimuladamente good (Adaptation). You lack the man a role which redeems it, but will cost much erase our memory, so sweet, so bombastic when wants to, disasters motorized with burning skull or fortune-tellers to trial as the here of clumsy and dimwitted portrait.Next despreocupa of narrative coherence and attends a very laughable argument, so fragilísimo without blushing and mild, so to bad post, one thinks, armed with a bag of good intentions, that Lee Tamahori (Warriors of yore, his best film); Mulholland Falls, the Brigade of the hat, on the good side and XXX: State of emergency or in disaster muladar) wished with all his neozelandesas forces fall as low enough as to take off there and do something decent. Ah, the height of the blunder is to leave my beloved Julianne Moore. There already unraveled me all the purposes of Temperance and I thought seriously not expose me too much, give death certificate and not to attend a function of such vilification. Everything is by the good times that has given me this wonderful actress, also - like many - casualty of this worldly Vice which are the bitches and the stable job.Next is not even bad by itself, but that precise pecados ajenos contest to formulate the already muscular his own. The diviner who sees the near future (two absurd minutes of precognition) persists in not being a hero to the use and recites adages of zen transcendence for Buttering- and carried halfway the cot - compulsory Lady, which do not need us to emphasise that it is concupiscible moza, carita mona and more dazed in the roll of film as a seminarian in a bang gang at Cannes (Jessica Biel). It must be difficult to make the gallant you around, while sticky and delicate, attentive and overflowing in mimes, a magician of supernatural powers in whose hand is to save the world (us included) or - let me semantic excess - send everything to the Holy shit. Parentheses: I have to open my page - neglected lately — a corner in which you click the worst films of the history of cinema: the efforts made and turned into pure churro.Next (still digging) has already submitted credentials and it is postulated in all nominations more grenades. The spectacle of the cinema - noble art, noble art - has taken this intriguing path: becomes disgusted to serious industry and embraces with freshness of brothel to the occasionally decent mercantislismo disguised as art, adult or teen entertainment, delivering a generous dose of tedium. You could have written a brief authorities bla bla warn of the dangers associated with the consumption of this product., but it can not go one hand and just as well. The video shops live, after all, this: of trash, of remnants of palomitero balance which only shows the progress of technology and the quality of the new TVs, with its colorínes and its assorted pack of connections. I, at the time, I'm thinking about my self-esteem, I open wide the Windows of the chest and leave out the demon of masochism. He sneaks and has been remoloneando by my soul since I started to face such nonsense. Go, bastard</body>
</review>
