<review author="José A. Peig" title="Soy leyenda" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Anyway, after scares and intelligent management of suspense we find the greater simplicity in a regrettable final concentration of clichés to all levels of narration. This is certainly to fall back and not be able to lift ever, hear.</summary>
	<body>And back again with the zombie theme. The first deliberate waste of Robert Rodriguez, then "invasion" (we have not yet seen but we have been told that it is very bad), and could then fun with plagiarism of realistic terror in REC, and now this religious dyes scheme set in an apocalyptic context. And is that nothing there is worse for a film that be just that: a scheme. It will Smith embodies a scientist obsessed with his desire to be the Savior of civilization. The portrait of his solitude among the remains of a decrepit New York becomes claim to delve into topics as the involution to barbarism and our sacred vulnerability before the death of God in a world of assassins, although its resources stagnate in a schematic expression of such solitude (depth of field in flat long that isolate the central character)(, more the sensationalism of the sound tricks). It is also true that the Mise en scène, aided by a cloudy picture and in accordance with the psychological state of the protagonist, gets at times capturing the attention of the Viewer to create a stifling atmosphere.It was difficult that a film with a very brilliant realization could decline as it does from the second segment, concluding the most predictable way. The portrait of loneliness becomes a messianic moral conclusion that we have seen many times in much more suggestive that this stories. Digitisation of humans and infected animals is a mistake, because computer graphics drowns the human dimension of the same, more resembling a herd of creatures of the underworld that humans stripped of his soul and destined to the abyss of madness (that was the best material to talk about isolation to two bands and the context appropriate for its marked link to science fiction).Anyway, after scares and intelligent management of suspense we find the greater simplicity in a regrettable final concentration of clichés to all levels of narration. This is certainly to fall back and not be able to lift ever, hear.</body>
</review>
