<review author="JLO" title="Caja negra" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ortega surprises us with a film at times baffling, intimate, minimalist, almost without a script visible but always vital to demonstrating that with few words or even gestures, you can say too.</summary>
	<body>Say to start the debutant director Luis Ortega is the son of the cantante-actor - political Palito Ortega and also brother of the also singer Emanuel want to set aside prejudices and put us squarely in his directorial debut, which seems by intention and tone, to break away from his family clan.What we say because his particular look does not accept any kind of fussiness, addressing something crude such as old age and the complex father/daughter relationships, grandmother/granddaughter. Ortega surprises us with a film at times baffling, intimate, minimalist, almost without a script visible but always vital to demonstrating that with few words or even gestures, you can say too. Dorotea (Dolores Fonzi, couple at the time of the director) must care alone for her grandmother and at the same time to rebuild the relationship with his father that just came out of prison and is a character seldom seen in our cinema. A weak person to the edge of the disabilities portrayed by Eduardo Couget (of aspect cacariturezco) director found through the streets of San Telmo begging and both in the film and in real life, living in the neighborhood Salvation Army. Without issuing judgment nor condemn the characters and with slow pace but fluid, portrays the suffering and solitary confinement, degradation and destitution in a natural way and at the same time, as if you were slightly Manus. Manners, without defined direction and even ambiguous repetitions of scenes, the video footage pales a little good successful photography. Punto y aparte for the lead role of the grandmother, a salient feature of the film played by Eugenia Bassi 99 years - not actress - owner of a lúcidez and humor enviable for its age, died five months after finishing the shooting, with a senile warmth who was remembered in the film year-end balance sheets.Luis Ortega then is another representative of new independent cinema Argentino, in the stylistic line of the Caetano, Perrone and Trapero, in a surprising and promising debut (22 years!) and with a second film (Monoblock, 2007) to explore on my part.</body>
</review>
