<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Arma Fatal (Hot Fuzz)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is comedy to every bullet, recommended to anyone who enjoys with innovative, creative and English humor taken to extremes.</summary>
	<body>Comedy is certainly a difficult genus. They can already be made great films of this genre that never will be recognized as they should. Fatal weapon (Yes, Hot Fuzz is the original title) is the comedy of the year and probably one of the best that was made in the 20th century. I guess it is time for her to recognize as such.The film focuses on a policeman whose life is exclusively dedicated to his work. When they amount, is sent to a seemingly quiet town where, subsequently, you have to discover what mysteries according to &hellip; initial proposal is very simple, even too much; but, however, it's a total nut back to all action comedy that has been done. Just have to see how the story (his screenplay is prodigious) or the myriad of gags that are perfectly added. Everything about fatal weapon is impeccable, since your technical Bill until a few memorable performances (especially that of the protagonist, a superb Simon Pegg). No, it is not easy to do a comedy like this, and that is why I admire deeply íncreible work of its director, Edgar Wright.Empezando by his hilarious dialogues, there is no doubt that we are facing a risky and personal proposal. They get to laugh with and of these, a fundamental fact in a comedy of this caliber. It has brilliant moments, others somewhat predictable (perhaps the greater failure of the film) and vibrant action sequences. It is very elaborate, fitting is extraordinary, and there is no moment in the movie where you bored. From an excellent home with many cameos to a denouement, predictable, but shocking, there is no time in fatal weapon which gives you time to breathe. It is comedy to every bullet, recommended to anyone who enjoys with innovative, creative and English humor taken to extremes.A brilliant, efficient, fast, incredibly fun film. Undoubtedly, the best comedy of the year. But, above all, for lovers of intelligent parodies. A ferocious satire on the apparently shocking action movies. This is an action movie! The others are nonsense.</body>
</review>
