<review author="JLO" title="Blade II" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entertaining, with some interesting back of script to not be so obvious, good topics tecnos/hip-hop, finally... a fun guaranteed for lovers of fights and weapons. Long leather, much blood and cinema itself, are talking about another day...</summary>
	<body>Comics in celluloid and know that it is a negoción. After the sagas of Batman, Spiderman, Superman and X-Men, also Blade noted which have sequels, being the Hunter day another creation of the master writer Stan Lee, producer and capo total of the influential Marvel Comics (X-Men, Daredevil, Hulk, Spiderman, etc). Blade in addition to being one of the few heroes of black comic, lacks the "weakness" required of the Marvel characters that makes these interesting. His invulnerability and omnipresence more emparientan it to a Terminator or Rambo as the romantic Dracula also have points in common. With Blade one knows in advance that beyond some that another passenger danger, not going to go so wrong. Oriented towards the public of video games, the film appears to be built to simulating levels of these where as difficulties are dodging, are added rivals and armament. In this second part Blade (Wesley Snipes) is ally of his enemies to together to try to defeat the Reapers, a new breed of Super vampires trying to destroy both humans and sucks them bloods common, having to stop their leader Jared Nomak (villain achieved good) creator of these nearly immortal beings. Many good action scenes with videoclipero and special effects worthy of a blockbuster of its kind pace. For those who saw the first there will be many new features except a more meticulous aesthetic and an address from the Toro with more pace and craft, which raises the level of its predecessor. Del Toro already play in the major leagues and loves this fantasy genre (Hellboy, El laberinto del fauno). As for Wesley Snipes, is his best character of action since Simon Phoenix of the demolition - including brings some tics than that - but also giving you plenty of room for the brightness to the not to deal him a single gesture, being sentenced to use lenses black 90% of the film and with a huge leather coat. That Yes: know that it looks a good physical condition and a good haircut. Entertaining, with some interesting back of script to not be so obvious, good topics tecnos/hip-hop, finally. a fun guaranteed for lovers of fights and weapons. Long leather, much blood and cinema itself, are talking about another day.</body>
</review>
