<review author="JLO" title="Luca vive" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Music - and Sumo - had its own characteristics: strong, powerful, visceral neighborhood poetry, harshness. Unfortunately, all things this film suffers.</summary>
	<body>Always say that when a fact deeply affect one remember exactly where, with whom and what was done. The death of Luca Prodan produced this effect in me and of course I remember where and I was doing. As I did with the deaths of other artists such as Alberto Olmedo, Freddy Mercury and other great rock rebel as it was don Kurt Cobain.Luca and his band (the legendary Sumo, germ of much of what you hear today on Argentina) were pillars with the Redonditos of ricotta, an underground movement of early eighties that changed all the previously established national music. Music - and Sumo - had its own characteristics: strong, powerful, visceral neighborhood poetry, harshness. Unfortunately, all things this film suffers. It is true that it did not want to review life linearly or is intended to be an accurate bio, but sins remain only in anecdotes, in fragments interlaced by their relationships of dubious likelihood and does not help a montage furious, with an animation trying to show the travel and poetry of Luca with excessive slowness of the musical films of the 70's to The Wall or Tommy. decision equally riskyalways will be enough for the fan and too chaotic for the unsuspecting Viewer. The most interesting aspects of his personality are just outlined: rebelliousness, animal force on stage, his depressive melancholy, its mix of genius and insanity. Yes they are Tom Lupo, the infamous today Omar Chabán and local cement. Its Geneva, bulín Alsina Street, their ira attacks. Not so a key detail of this story: his music. For only rights problems appear covers permitted and sung by the actor know little, despite the good achieved sound (years, night of peace, Fever). Daniel Ritto already accustomed to the character to represent for more than five years in theatre (and also responsible for the screenplay) strives to both phonetically in the interpretation, doing a credible Luca and without unrest. Jorge Coscia (jets, Sepoys, Comix) stands far away give us a pasteurized or cartoon, image without solemnity and showing their love and admiration for Luca, escapes his essence and we agree that it is quite difficult to achieve talking about this character. Too much lyricism by times, chaotic, film ambiguous to one of our greatest myths of rock. A be unique, ahead in life saying: "I am in the right, turned are you."</body>
</review>
