<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Un funeral de muerte" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is more intense than that "In & Out" and rather more interesting than "Perfect women".</summary>
	<body>As Zach Helm spoke on "Mr Magorium and his magic shop" of death in an easy manner and quasi - child, here, the legendary Frank Oz (not just famous for the Muppets and Yoda in Star Wars), tells us in a fun way what can happen at a funeral in any part of the world; the takes as a reference (and also as humor) to a British family, but apparently the tape well can occur from in Spain up in any part of the planet.Oz creates situations hilarious but not power, all of them from the first minute from a Prism daily comicamente, which, again, may be as common as fun, without falling into the casquivano or unpleasant, and using all the resources that are in his hand, to make fun and enjoyable development of the tape.In the roster of players, a group of British acquaintances of those that we all know, but we don't remember their names, people like Alan Tudyk (secondary in plenty of movies), Ewen Bremner (the mythical "Trainspotting" Spud) and so to complete this deal. The idea of Oz include little-known (but recognizable) faces was likelihood provide the film, in the wider and comic of the word sense.In the script, are devoted to perform, as already mentioned, any type of barrabasada at the funeral, always looking for the fun of the Viewer, on the other hand, some gags are a bit forced and are brutally recherché, and is that while there are a hundred of situations that one can know or feel identified, others are too little credible, hence fetched them.The score of Murray Gold is enjoyable and fun with these touches of guitar, they do comedy even more funny if possible, with a few notes that are repeated to greater or lesser intensity as the plot progresses.In short, it is more intense than that "In &amp; Out" and rather more interesting than "Perfect women".</body>
</review>
