<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Mr Magorium y su tienda mágica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Strange and extravagant film fantasy genre, something boring in general.</summary>
	<body>Film from the fantastic genre, but absolutely fantastic in terms of entertainment and good pastime.Perhaps what I am about to say is no more than the opinion of an adult referred to a movie aimed primarily at children and therefore should not be taken into much consideration, but the truth is that it is one of the most boring films that I remember seeing in recent times (and I've seen a few already).The thing frankly begins well, with imagination even or the less enough originality. I refer to the initial credit titles, where we are seeing to the components of the facets technical without that put they are assemblers or musicians or photography. We simply see their names along with animated obejtos give us to understand in what apartao are included, but we should be very attentive to perceive it. It is frankly good this way to display them.But when the story begins, everything changes something I do not know how to qualify. It is a film from the fantastic genre, but very strange, bizarre, extravagant, so I've not caught you the point or the comma. I have failed where to take her, the truth.It is a cluster of scenes animated (the store) that are displayed randomly, forming an amalgam of situations that are immersed in a whole, but something inenteligible.The dialogues, the characters, the message, the original, escape me as water between your toes. Much sentimentality, in my view quite cheap: that if you don't go (die) please. Yes, that I do so, it is my time, look in your interior. In short, Sanctimony butt in my opinion. Perhaps we must persevere in our dreams, to achieve them, perhaps all must not lose the illusions of childhood, perhaps... But what does, the truth is that, as the argument is represented, nor do I know or I imported a cumin, as it demonstrated that I can even say that I slept on one occasion. I guess they were two minutes only or so (when enter you Magorium in a hospital) .and was a break for me.No, I did not like this film, it has seemed very well fotografíado but no I was interested in no time, seeming to me a peñazo, by very good intentions you have.</body>
</review>
