<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Mr Magorium y su tienda mágica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tape to be see as a child and then is possible to have a good time. A fable with a careful aesthetic sense and a moral (and moralina, everything is said incidentally) hackneyed but effective.</summary>
	<body>Honestly it did not have the slightest intention of viewing this film but as I am a person of principles and me peak easily pick up the ball and very dutifully reported on it. With the terrible tagline of "inspired by Imaginarium" all adult Spanish Viewer will have so many prejudices that it is possible to lose a good Christmas divertimento. More in the tone of Hamleys, London, this magic Toyshop has a peculiarity is that not only the own shop is delighted and their toys come to life if not that people that they enter it just somehow changed by persistent boldness of owner of the same. This must be because having the experience of two hundred and thirty-four years to your back like the toy entrepreneur helps. The figure of Mr Magorium, Hoffman, is a delicious incentive for children, the hook for adults is their store manager Mahoney, played by Natalie Portman with certain boorishness and sosez will have to face the departure of Magorium, to assume their responsibilities and return to find the magic. In this larduo way will feature Eric, a child prodigy of nine collector of hats and asocial; and Henry, the accounting officer, or as affectionately call him "mutant" that it will also have to forget about their numbers and to see life with children's eyes again.It is obvious that we have a film you must see with as a child and in this case it is possible to have a good time. Perhaps that's the problem of Americans, where both critique and public did not understand the proposal and ensañaron with the tape off of child boring. If, for an adult falls into each and every one of the insurmountable topics suitable for all the public tapes but children enjoy, and even an adult to see the forced need to accompany his son can let his imagination fly and end up in places that never would have imagined &hellip; is that we are a generation with great films of toy stores to our credit. Who not daydream with playing the Big piano? Or lock with Macaulay Culkin in the second part of Solo at home in the great toys? Perhaps if Mr Magorium would have formed part of our childhood now would be on this list as it is a fable with a careful aesthetic sense and a moral (and moralina, everything is said incidentally) hackneyed but effective. Away from other proposals more unsatisfactory as the magical nanny or A series of catastrophic misfortunes with the same wrapper but less premium Mr Magorium matter can be seen. It falls on many rookie mistakes and skips to the Bullfighter narrative logic but when one is 8 years old is not important. Only one concern. What would have happened if this tape fell into the hands of Tim Burton?</body>
</review>
