<review author="Jack Torrance" title="Soy leyenda" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is a post-apocalyptic story that some want to see a copy of 28 days later but that it hides inside a sediment of sorrow and deseperanza as few tapes of fantasy have never had.</summary>
	<body>Before you begin, a few preliminary words for those who opine that the film before us is not a good adaptation of the novel by Richard Matheson. They don't know what they are talking about. "Lose the sense of the I am Legend of the novel" may argue some, and indeed, in this regard the film not opts for placing Neville as a legend for the vampires. But is it film gentlemen, that possibility does not exist, the fact that the novel was a bidisección of the myth of the vampire as legendary Monster and as highlight of this, the human ends up being the monster, the legend that vampires have been created. The premise of the film, adapted to the times, leaves little room for such a possibility, however here Neville remains the monster at the end and after. But faithful to the novel is not based on the repetition of the argument or the recreation of classic passages of the material original(como_la_primera_versión_The_last_man_on_Earth) or in the reiteration of Neville as a monster for the vampiros(Motor_principal_de_The_Omega_man) if not in the very essence of the story: the day to day of Neville, and the effects of loneliness on the human mind. In this respect I am Legend not only picks up perfectly the feelings of Neville if not that recreates them emotional, unique shape and form fideligna to the original material.I am legend also adapted the script for the second version with Charlton Heston, but its structure is quite similar to the novel. Thus, the third Act, very spectacular and without great force, is at the bottom, similar to the book (in its own way) finishing a bit abruptly and leaving no doubt with wanting more. But overall, there is one more than notable film. In no time the tape is felt as a Blockbuster, but a small and intimate, story except few action scenes, effects are put at the service of the story or the stage, music is little hyperbolic, rather minimalistic, sad and used at specific moments. A pity that the design and finish of the creatures, completely created by a pobretón CGI, are not at the height of a very high budget. Removing these problems, the film is a post-apocalyptic story that some want to see a copy of 28 days later but that it hides inside a sediment of sorrow and deseperanza as few tapes of fantasy have never had. Who expect a tape of action is very disappointed because instead there are empty spaces and melancholic images, without just lines of script, showing a world without humans as a film had ever shown before. That, gentlemen, it is at least worthy of mention is. It will Smith does, undoubtedly his best performance to date, only showing gestures all the pain and nihilism that Matheson described with words, being very significant for just a moment, choosing their reactions to relate the survivors: an example of fidelity to certain passages of the novel. The use of the flashback explaining how Neville lost his family, while the way of doing it is not like the book, if there are passages of memory and here, like that, help to understand the importance of his family and his pain for the loss because of the pandemic is also a success. I am legend is almost an independent film disguised as a blockbuster. It is not boasting in the majority of footage shot without emphasis and the absence of any other free fright maintains a tone of film rare intimate in the current fantastic cinematography. However, it has its bad parts, some of the class "what could have been and was not" as the wastage of the locations and scenarios for some moments of action, suspense or tension.Others fall into that "it should have been and was not" as the inexplicable choice of zombies made by computer. Finally, the great flaws are that weak climax with a somewhat messianic script and out of place. and, in general, decaffeinated conclusion. Despite this, the truth is that it is not a significant adaptation of the original material and is, without doubt, a rare bird in what usually offer the factory of hollywood in recent years.</body>
</review>
