<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Calle Mayor" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Manners film about the Spain of mid-20th century, where a group of friends thresh us the past miseries. Unless you're a scholar of film or born in that time do not recommend seeing her. It is not bad, simply outdated.</summary>
	<body>Director: Juan Antonio Bardem. duration: 80 minutilla.Release date: 5 December 1956 Barcelona Windsor, on January 7, 1957 Madrid Gran Via.Espectadores: 6,207 human beings.At the end of the film, in which the medium Zucchini slept in the third frame in black and white, I reminded my father with nostalgia. In particular those trips by car, laden with tapes of Eugenio and the great Marianico the short. And it is there to much like a father to not strangle him after four hours of "Know that than diú.". I remembered just a joke Marianico, saying that modern music groups complete the songs as if they were no forces, and the orchestras before ended with a chim pum (hear laughter from the audience). Because this film ends like, when most interesting seems the thing, it ends. It seems that some scene, lack you even.The film is about the life of a type which has a few chums of bar and House of whores. Involved, as well as to the interests mentioned above, to make jokes to people (such as carrying a coffin to one who nearly died of fright). As sympathetic bromazo in a depressed and sexist society which was the Spanish in 55, they decide to a girl that is going to be drier than the mojama to his 35 years without marrying, do believe that one of them we want to marry with her. Step film shows us the sad thing that was Spain from the middle of the century, at least in the medium-sized populations.I'm not critical of put me in these pools, but it is that this express recommendation of my mother-in-law me bored to the point of not sleep me by not having to return to see another day. And it is that over the years ago that certain films are not for everyone. I.e., the film will be a marvel, a cruel portrait of a vile and sexist society, where the ruindad and the lack of morality leads people to unusual extremes. But vista is now a very large suckling pig. The dialogues are not understood, fewer situations, and women now have children with more than 35 and nobody excoriated them for that reason. On the positive side, it is very curious to see small details, such as the plates they used, how cooked, the eternal raincoats and tie for men, etc. Much better than the "Cuentamé".In short, costumbrista film about the Spain of mid-20th century, where a group of friends thresh us the past miseries. Unless you're a scholar of cinema, was born in that time, or scholar of the subject, I recommend not seeing her. It is not bad, simply outdated.Besitos.P.D: Recalling another joke, now of Gila, the joke that you want to do would be as "Mabeis killed a child, but what I laughed" or "Look, if you don't put up a better joke going on the people" after booting an arm to one.</body>
</review>
