<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Búsqueda: El Diario Secreto" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The search: The secret diary is an entertaining adventure unpretentious film provided that the viewer decides to take her a joke, because seriously judged, you have so many inconsistencies and barbaric acts that would not be where take it.</summary>
	<body>When we talk about an adventurer, a search of treasures, everyone comes to the memory the figure of a man with a whip and a hat. From this idea, we are now to a Nicolas Cage which seems to always go with a brush, and which is capable of anything without his studied quiff lose consistency.Ben Gates is back, and for all those that this name does not tell them anything, it is the character of the search (fortunately in Disney Spain are aware that the title of the first part here national treasure have liked nothing). This time our hero starts a crusade by returning his family the good name, retrieve his girl, demonstrate the maloso which is the character of Ed Harris, all without disheveled or lose that so supposedly youth air. The best thing you can do to go see the search is minded to take her to messing, in order to thus spend a fun time, rather than the film itself, by the number of atrocities being committed. Only brief appearances of the character of Helen Mirren given to the movie moments of genuine humor, more than all the antics of a Nicolas Cage last thread (regrettable the argument with Diane Kruger at Buckingham Palace). What most annoying of the tape (apart from your script riddled with errors and brabuconerías) is the patriotic exaltation that makes Americans, with some esperpénticos and surreal moments of values, history and spirit. We know that anyone with two fingers of forehead and a vase in the hands can go through the Office of the Queen of England as Peter by his house.The search: The secret diary is an entertaining adventure unpretentious film provided that the viewer decides to take her a joke, because seriously judged, you have so many inconsistencies and barbaric acts that would not be where take it.</body>
</review>
