<review author="José A. Peig" title="La ardilla roja" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Being a product too schematic, stands out above all the synthetic work of Medem to configure his particular universe of emotions and paranoia that is displayed and the contempt to certain conventions governing life in society.</summary>
	<body>The film by Julio Medem sins - or enjoy - wanting to create dreamlike abstraction from the costumbrist shade, leaving his work in a position which makes it vulnerable to several considerations. La ardilla roja reads a social critique or a unrealistic catharsis in which the reality of the people and the squirrels are part of a same psychic construct. His cinema is symbolic, the resources used for this purpose is not to have too much talent, but in the case that we are now discussing (as in the recent Caótica Ana) there is a line of development and a thematic Centre exposed with some fluency. The filmmaker uses speech to discuss himself surroundings on two characters, Jota and Felix, in absolutely antithetical but representatives of a same obsession lived in two intensities. Film about disturbed, and behold one of most obvious weaknesses, to use cloudy personality of the girl that radiates magnetism that disturbs and manipulates her two suitors, who respond equally to a Machiavellian profile and paranoid. The most striking of his theme is that it is so conventional as twisted in its submission, that speaks to us from the basic axis of a teenage love type "boy finds girl" motivated by unattainable women, that girl that always goes ahead with his bike and his two lovers desperate unsuccessfully to because she is (as opposed to the initial appearance) which takes the frying pan by the handlethe same squirrel that always win the game, as corretea over the heads of male characters. The use of the animal as Totem of femininity is a recurring theme in the author, this being a fairly simple resource. In any case, if we let take by the intuitive process that proposes (the only way to understand most of the cinema) discovered the obsessive soul of Medem, with the burden of love frustrations, a vital experience synthesized in a triangular game about love and sex.Being a product too schematic, stresses primarily the synthetic work of Medem to configure his particular universe of emotions and paranoia that unfolds between lyric tonality and the sordid harshness of human relations, sexual-amorosa obsession, and contempt to certain conventions governing life in society.</body>
</review>
