<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Café solo... o con ellas" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spend 2 hours of your time to read anything, from a Kafka to the mark last week, but!God don't waste their time in such crappy! (let case for once in his life).</summary>
	<body>Complain about how bad that works Spanish cinema, us tear vestments before harsh receptions at the box office of the patriotic film, and yet again and again produce a thousand clunkers that don't deserve the penalty and spend 2 min. on view them but as noses will run something like? On the one hand we have the actors always seen in Teleseryes (as for example the serrano) or any work of Theatre (or music), we put one argument saw that the TBO, with a current soundtrack, themes of any group of fashion, and try to sell it to teenagers, which are, more than anything, people are going to go by box office to pay the entry; but don't we realize that, before this movie or any "americanada" self-respecting, the spanish teenager, is going to leave their &euro; in the film "Made in USA". Lords Spanish film, producers take a tape to fruition is complicated, expensive and in some cases even a mission impossible, hundreds of movies are left in the dark, or sleep "sleep of the righteous" in some drawer of a top executive, gentlemen, we want to film us excited, do us spend a good or bad time, but not these clunkers, where one smiles (slightly) for a couple of moments and then continues to something else butterfly, as if nothing happened. You have the decency, kindness, or whatever, in not drain us a thousand times the same film; look as things like "The orphanage", "El laberinto del Fauno", "[·REC], or even the more quirky cinema of Santiago Segura (with that the quota of casposidad is covered), they fill halls, I need not say more right?" Of the film, let me you speak little, to say nothing, since the few min. in which one smiles are thanks to a Lady of the Spanish scene as it is the illustrious Terele Pavez, the rest is a succession of gags more seen than the comic book, of inheritance eschatological, silly to the more not power, and tits and ass, ah! And poop, ass, fart, pis. That this love to the chavalería. And finally, well, frankly, spend 2 hours of your time to read anything, from a Kafka to the mark last week, but!God don't waste their time in such crappy! (let case for once in his life).</body>
</review>
