<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Deseo, Peligro" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great movie that consolidates Ang Lee as one of the most interesting of the current global film scene and libérrimos directors.</summary>
	<body>Importantly, the comma in the title. If not, "Desire, danger" would otherwise. How important is seeing a movie in good condition! Just what viewers last Sunday we went to the Granada Center multiplex can not say. Film blurred, cut and rebobinada, lights and dialogues lost for the sake of a nefarious projection. And as the movie lasts about three hours, this type of accidents, as they fuck especially. So, if I say that the film seemed somewhat long and that for my taste sobrarían you 30 minutes, many staunch defenders of the last film by Ang Lee could tell me that no, that was the culprit of both Court and so much discomfort. Really, the film seemed excellent. An example of special classic film, film in the old style of cinema of spies in distant and exotic landscapes. And that "I would like to, danger" is another very serious risk: of that talk of the warm their sexual sequences and the censorship that has been mutilated in native China of the director, this enigmatic and surprising Ang Lee. Because while we have an exercise in classicism at old-fashioned, Lee has foregone the moral false that prevented to Cary Grant and Ingrid Bergman wallow as descosidos, giving free rein to his tormented love. And, thus, the protagonist of "Desire, danger" uses not only their seduction skills, but the benefits of his splendid body and the fogosidad of his youthful soul to achieve woo the Chinese collaborationist with aspect of hard, insensitive and undaunted. But each frame of this film distills the classic breath which, unfortunately, is no longer the style. We speak of a classicism in the best sense of the word, well managed and not this pantomime that starred George Clooney in "The good German". Classicism as aesthetic choice, with a Shanghai that, in comparison with the postmodern city today, seems a more distant antiquity people. And a story, at the same time, very simple and very complex. The story of an infiltrator and the risks that it entails, challenges, dangers, the anxieties and sorrows. Is funny, the amount of excellent recent films that have an infiltrator as protagonist, from the eponymous film from Scorsese to one of the great masterpieces of 2007: "Eastern promises". Perhaps because we live in an age of simulation, deception and double faces in which nothing is what it seems. I like the melancholy of the games play the Précieuses of their suits and dresses, women, throughout the film's production design and, above all, the interpretation of the two protagonists, searching, avoiding indulging, loving it, repelling. A great movie that consolidates Ang Lee as one of the most interesting of the current global film scene and libérrimos directors.</body>
</review>
