<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Battle for Haditha" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film necessary about the war of Iraq, but not convincing at all.</summary>
	<body>"Haditha (Iraq), November 19, 2005." Iraqi insurgents bombed a convoy of us marines and kill the officer most appreciated by his comrades. Incensed by this loss, his young companions carried out a brutal reprisal. Their violent house searches have as a result the massacre of 24 people, many of whom are women and children, tragic victims of war who are unable to control. The marines are also victims: are attacked, injured and forced to respond the way you have taught them. But, when events occur at high speed and in circumstances of extreme stress, one can accuse assassination to the marines who were in the line of fire? "."Interesting film of Nick Broomfield, which is worth seeing, above all, for its undeniable documentary value on a true, sadly remembered fact and which still colea, given the similarities between this fact narrated and many others that are repeating in the war of Iraq, from November 2005 until today.Therefore has the value of the current, because still the human being has not learned to value human life, or to be able to curb barbarity which nests in the hearts of people, at least in certain emotional strés, or superseded by the more Miraflores situations circumstances where morals, ethics or other positive emotional connotations, merman to violence that is palpable and even lives in the environment.However, and beyond all this, I repeat you cannot be denied, we are witnessing, in general terms to a film not many strictly cinematographic virtues.The technique employed in many scenes, the camera on his shoulder, aims to empower the tape of a documentary stamp, to make everything more credible, more realistic. I'm not saying that it fails, but there isn't a good staging and the script lacks depth, being all too evident.The interpreters, real marines who fought at Iraq, do quite well, especially which plays simpar Cape Ramirez. But given her, at least, moral and psychological complexity would have been better that carried you out a professional actor, as seen in the scene that, finally, speaking evil of war, their superiores.un little late for what is ago and orders do men at his command. Hero, killer? This question in the film is. It can be trying to answer this question with a dilemma, to a controversy, but as it looks great in the beautiful final sequence, the man, as individual, equipped with rationing, is ultimately responsible for what you do. It almost always has the door open to act in one way or another. There are some good action scenes, as the key moment of the explosion of the vehicle of the marines and the immediate response, but also others that are not understood very well, been quite false, as when the aforementioned Cape Ramirez le tends hand a woman who, because of his responsibility, you just become a widow.Anyway, that very well and laudable the pretension of denunciation of some embarrassments, which hopefully not repeat never, but not is a good film, it is much improved in all aspects. I don't know if the general public will convince you.</body>
</review>
