<review author="Luna" title="30 días de oscuridad" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>New vampire gore film and expendable. You will like if you're a lover of the genre without prejudices and her detestarás you if you are looking for something more than entertainment in it.</summary>
	<body>The cinema of vampires and monsters back fashion. In this case we return to talk about the adptación of a comic, written by Niles and Ben Templesmith and Sam Raimise has been responsible for taking the paper to celluloid.This film tells the history of a city of Alaska in which during the winter, there are 30 days in those who do not see the light of the Sun. With this starting premise it is not strange that a group of vampires "accidentally" discover this small village lost in the middle of nowhere and they decide to bleed all its inhabitants to give the great feast. Happen to survive any of its inhabitants? You'll have to go to the movies to find out because I so I will not tell.Personally found me a movie boring and predictable. He had hopes placed in this film as its director, David Slade, was also the architect of the disturbing "Hard Candy" sweet and relied on its good do after the cameras. However, the script uses many topics on the subject, in this case without delve into the psychology of the aggressors. It does not explain where leaving the vampires really nor what aim with this action.The action is advancing by leaps and free and from the point of view of carrying out there nothing really remarkable. The actors are correct in some papers with little dramatic depth. The most notable of the film, the 4,000 gallons of artificial blood, 280 tons of snow and five tons of propane gas employed. To these figures, the avizado Viewer knows that we we have one of these products a little gores and facts for quick consumption which will not pass to the annals of the history of cinema, even gender.You will like if you're a lover of the genre without prejudices and her detestarás you if you are looking for something more than entertainment in it.</body>
</review>
