<review author="Raccord" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Possibly open the way for new Court Hollywood blockbusters that sell many popcorn. But as a film, it is boring, slow and monotonous.</summary>
	<body>"Alatriste is for many reasons a film failed, mainly because the most expensive film in the history of the Spanish film from a bad script can do.""Alatriste" is based on the successful series of novels by Arturo Pérez Reverte to recreate the life of a swordsman in the pay of the Siglo de Oro. The logical thing would have been adapting a book, or make a new story, but with the keys and the spirit of the series. Instead, they prefer to adapt all the books in a single film, offering a rehash of scenes taken from the context of the work in which are found, placed one after another and without a common thread that hilvane. This produces that many are characters that parade throughout the two hours of film, while none leave a special sediment or having excessive importance in the plot.Both "Alatriste" fails miserably when trying to create a history consistent (with its introduction, knot and ending) and with a minimum of tension or intrigue. Simply see the captain Alatriste in three types of scenes that are repeated several times in the movie: war stories, conversations with people, and duels in a dark alley, and almost with the feeling that were arranged at random, until the end of the film. But it is up action sequences, by the lack of interest in the plot, lack sufficient claw to draw attention and are below standards of the adventure film. Special mention deserves the battle of the Spades, probably the most stupid war scene of the seventh art.It is a pity that a poor script, tape the quality of the cast, full of names of first row of our industry as well as the meritorious work of make-up, costumes, decorated etc. Photography and montage are good; but a little stiff in the action scenes, especially compared to some static frames more paused sequences, that seem taken from a book of Baroque art.Needed a project so ambitious in our cinema. Possibly "Alatriste" open the way for new Court Hollywood blockbusters that sell many popcorn. But as a film, it is boring, slow and monotonous. And that in the adventure genre is unforgivable.</body>
</review>
