<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Once" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is a film, in short, that you will enjoy all over the world, but will be much more, for anyone that really enjoy the music, all that are able to simply sit down, close your eyes and listen to paladeada.</summary>
	<body>I am of those people who like to listen to a whole album. From time to time, you find an LP which has a meaning as it is made, whose order saves a logic and whole, heard from beginning to end, manages to convey a feeling, an idea, or a State of mind is not able to, say, a compilation album. Does not happen always, in fact, very few albums that I keep in my memory of this form, as a book, should that not be read a loose chapter since, if it did, it would lose much of its magic, but when it is one of these works, it is almost certain that you will save with zeal until that one is deaf &hellip; and even more beyond.Watch the movie "Once", I had a similar feeling, rather than a film to use, is more a good disk to which you have been images so that you can follow more easily, or to complement those feelings that the music alone, is capable of touching but him harder to remove. One exercise that, in another form attempted to Disney in the incredible "fantasy", although at that time he tried to to the style of compilation albums. In this case, we have music filmed with soul, with a story that shocked, amused and thrilled in equal parts.The degree of emotion that manages to convey the film is directly proportional to the frankness with which is filmed and performed and this succeeds, largely thanks to the main actors, both musicians that had worked together on a disk. Glen Hansard and Markéta Irglová composed songs that serve as a thread that the argument goes sliding and offer a simple interpretation that manages to cause that we identify with what they are going from the first moment.The story is that of a street musician who performs known songs during the day and at night, sings his own compositions that revolve, almost all around a loving disappointment. One day he meets a saleswoman of flowers that stops to listen to a song and they begin a friendly relationship in which music will be its point of attachment.The film talks about music as an integral part of our lives in a very powerful way. The images of the guitar of the protagonist, old, broken, a guitar that has lived and suffered the songs coming out of their strings, or when she goes to practice with the piano at a music store, testing every day a different keyboard while the owner listen pleased, or in the recording of the album, when a sound technician who has seen too many bad groups is surprised with the quality of what you have ahead. Everything that happens, every change, every feeling comes forward by a beat changed.A film, in short, that you will enjoy worldwide for his friendly face, a story that leaves marked is this a smile on the face and an enviable soundtrack, but it will be much more, for anyone that really enjoy the music, all that are able to simply sit down, close your eyes and listen to paladeada.</body>
</review>
