<review author="Andrés Pons" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What happens with the artistic part? Because at any time you try to do justice to the large text that adapts, important thing here is entertain the audience, something very different in earlier versions far more faithful to the novel.</summary>
	<body>As you build a secure success? Good first one of the most outstanding science fiction novels of all time, written by the great RICHARD MATHESON I mix masterfully adapts the horror with the apocalyptic genre. The virtues of the work is echoed in the last man on Earth with VINCENT PRICE and hereinafter referred to as the best-known version with CHARLTON HESTON, THE OMEGA MAN.Taking the good mimbres in a well-known story next thing is to find a competent director to dispatch a BLOCKBUSTER action, then appears the figure of FRANCIS LAWRENCE who proved their prowess in CONSTANTINE.Taking the Director, a good distribution, which along with a MARKETING work to support a major star of the action or sci-fi film. It must be someone young, attractive with stunning physicist to look at the scenes of action with the delight of the fans, no doubt WILL SMITH is appropriate with great experience in the genre after I robot or INDEPENDENCE DAY among others.Now a budget of several thousand dollars so the machine begins to work hoping to raise a monumental taquillaza that allows large gains to all parties involved. What happens with the artistic part? Because at any time you try to do justice to the large text that adapts, important thing here is entertain the audience, something very different in earlier versions far more faithful to the novel.It is not that force in the first part of the film which shows a desert city lack you. Even an emboldened SMITH shows some dramatic skills in a character that oscillates between the line of sanity and madness.The first appearance of those infected is really terrifying. But little by little it starts to fail the concert, the surprise factor influences such as commented in the first attack of the humanos-vampiros while the other appearances are no longer novel discovering a few mediocre digital effects that make not as fearsome as they should be.The FLASBACKS in time is not convincing, a religious end does not know very well it comes. Well actually I think that if, is a nod to the audience so that everyone cheered the courage of the hero.Another point in favour is the prominence of the German Shepherd that almost overshadows the star of the function.Ultimately a film entertaining with good technical aspects except for some digital effect with a WILL SMITH that at times manages to be credible but in others is not removed the tagline of comedian being his little proper interpretation for the drama that should make his character.</body>
</review>
