<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="La brújula dorada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Of time, and with only the first piece of the puzzle have the obligation to suspend this Christmas experiment that I have no doubt copará movie billboards and the gifts of the child menus of all fast food restaurant which boasts.</summary>
	<body>Perhaps me back older and already I do not like the infantiles-juveniles films of adventures. I was all praise for the Goonies, I who knew the dialogues of the Prodigioso Chip of memory, I I went to film the day of the premiere of the Lord of the rings, I I'm going disguised to all event self-respecting Star Wars, book I that I look forward to wield my wand when exit the next Harry Potter &hellip; do something has happened between all this which has made losing perspective on fantasy films? I recognize that the Chronicles of Narnia seemed peñazo n (James McAvoy, excluding of course) and this new trilogy seem to absolutely follow the same steps.The Golden Compass is the first book of the dark matter, as they call the series of books about a world where humans coexist with their spirits that shaped animals called Dæmon (Yes, I also thought that the next step was to Picacho come out for a corner). Mysterious disappearances of children and the existence of a subject called "Dust" trigger the protector of Lyra Belacqua to leave to investigate phenomena in the highlands while the girl will travel with a mysterious and powerful woman. Everything portends a great adventure gets &hellip; and say this is coming because it clearly does not have an end if that isn't a long prologue to the next adventure.I admit that I am a little upset before the brief and dull appearance of Bond, James Bond this tape and simultaneously intrigued about the decision to take Nicole Kidman as random roles after winning his Oscar. Now not you can trust a film with her in the cast as a guarantee of quality because it seems that your agent has taken a vacation to advise. The result is a long and boring movie but with a sensitive and precocious photography that leads from Oxford to the pole. It can not put you any formal hits the tape and do not dare to wear to the script without having read the novel that perhaps seen as a whole will have a certain grace. Of time, and with only the first piece of the puzzle have the obligation to suspend this Christmas experiment that I have no doubt copará movie billboards and the gifts of the child menus of all fast food restaurant which boasts.</body>
</review>
