<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="La vida es bella" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A gem that the longer is more enjoy.</summary>
	<body>I like to say that Roberto Benigni is the Italian Tom Hanks. I guess it may sound crazy but if we start to analyze it coldly the thing makes sense. Both were the real precursors of comedy in their countries, were tapes of success which marked a whole generation and were imitated by comedians coming. With the 1990s decided to become serious and Hanks found papers that would give prestige and Oscars and Benigni played along by also placing behind the camera. I.e. life is Bella is the Forest Gump of Begnini.En Europe we laughed not of war. They say that to see things in perspective there must be many years and while on World War II dramas and action tapes are well seen and enjoyed some popularity by making fun of Jews massacred by the Holocaust seemed very risky.Life is Bella is a species of fairy tale with a moral. It's a comedy sui generis which Guido tries to stay in the field of concentration for his son, Giouse, pass much lighter inventing games and stories. I admit that there are few things that I love in life is beautiful. It is a tape that distills some magic in overwhelming of any alleged guerra.por realism and the brutality his wife Nicoletta Braschi plays Dora, or Principessa as the flame affectionately.And clear the awards did not wait. There is still marked on the retinae the face of terror of the poor Steven Spielberg that was little fortunate to sit in the seat prior to the Italian comic when it decided to celebrate her Oscar for best actor jumping on the public. An Oscar deserved but controversial because Benigni portraying if same as demonstrated in his subsequent speech where many gave thanks for our mediocre and moderate English.The penalty is after life is beautiful decided plagiarizing himself, and of course, the public is stupid but there is a limit and about Pinochio (never released in Spain) and the Tiger and the snow we ended up convince that perhaps the Italian Tom Hanks going big this filmmaking with uppercase. At least left us this gem that the longer is more enjoyable.PS. I will not fail to tell an anecdote about the germ of the idea of Begnini. At the press conference for the presentation of the "EL train DE LA VIDA", released several years despupero that came out the same year 98. He is a French Jewish people that with the imminent arrival of the nazis decide to do pass by Germans and cross Europe to a safe place. Oddly does not have much that see the tone, the action and narrated adventure if they have mucos commonalities with La Vida es Bella. When asked about the similarities its director explained that in his attempt to get funding sent his screenplay to Begnini and even offered a role in the film, this turned him down, two years wrote, starred in and directed the life is beautiful. If you enjoyed the work of Benigni, please, I encourage you to seek this French production which is equally fun but also corrects errors of Sanctimony and floral ornaments of the Italian. I believe that you will enjoy.</body>
</review>
