<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Rec" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In short, a waste of time, money and above a sense of scam by wanting to be like people of the announcement when in fact I've bored as an oyster.</summary>
	<body>I am in favor of using the system, on the other hand illegal for the Viewer, protect the Spanish cinema at any cost. That sometimes translates into subtly decorate the virtues of a tape and a little to hide their mistakes rounding to the stands, as if it were the euro, the general outcome of the same.In this case I will betray this agreement not written with the Spanish film industry to tell all those avid spectators who have been dazzled by the unique and intelligent promotional trailer for Rec that will not see her to the movies, or at least that lowering their expectations. Being one of the most misleading campaigns of the season the subtlety of teach the faces of terrified viewers watching film in a movie theater and not talking about nor average word of his argument have hordes of teenagers go to see homeland terror and shame to summarize in two minutes a film without feet or head that also has four numbered scares that had surely been gutted in its promotion have spared.A couple of reporters will follow a group of firefighters in their overnight trips. Spineless reporter and her camera start their interviews to the purest style Spain direct portends a roll of story unless something to happen. Finally they receive a notice and people in a building where accompanied by some policemen enter the House of an old woman alerted by neighbors on the strange noises. The aggressiveness of this and subsequent events they think that in that building something very serious is happening. So reporters, policemen, firemen and neighbors will see trapped and sealed inside along with a mysterious virus that become "zombies" to all those who are infected by him.The Ribbon is a kind of surreal cross between the project of the Witch of Blair (by the subjective nature of recording and blatant theft of planes), and best and worst tapes of zombies in the history of cinema (including the head of plagiarism to 28 days later). It would not be bad if it were not for the inability to make coherent what happens from the first minute. It is a nonsense. Against more try to explain this more they roll and contradict each other, more sensible against wants to appear more ridiculous is the explanation, and if not me I belong to the final scene in the attic and challenge any son of neighbor to tell me how, where and why started the infección-posesión.Three numbered scares adorn the narration. Also sees all of them are so obvious that even a child of two years them come. None of anguish or printing, everything comes on the screen and does not give time to process any feeling, part of hatred toward the Lord of the toupee you want to be the next victim as soon as possible to put an end to that vision. To finish the play think Manuela Velasco is possibly one of the actresses more lumps, heavy and ñoñas that has left on the big screen. In short, a waste of time, money and above a sense of scam by wanting to be like people of the announcement when in fact I've bored as an oyster.</body>
</review>
