<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Soy leyenda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film of extermination of humanity, where a man with his dog wants to find a cure for infected survivors. It is not like any of the genre, and I see, is not popcorn film. It has a little more.</summary>
	<body>Director: Francis Lawrence. duration: hour and a half well served.Release date: December 19, 2007Ayer told my cuñao "Let's see Rec" as well as very embrabuconado. When I said yes I saw at his side, clutching him and telling him that I wanted to go and that almost did not convince me. That is my cuñao me as a courageous type Sandokan shaving to sword. Thanks movies allied himself with me and as the meeting was of those who call themselves whores told him that two hairy men entering a cinema at these times was suspected, because that does not. So today I said to see this, that had been my sister-in-law and the other going to give am. My manhood has been injured, but still alive, heh, heh.The film is of a near future in which a researcher with crappy aspect discovers a cure against cancer. The girl that he was right, because of cancer, since then nothing at all. Well, now infected humanity with a virús kills almost everyone. And which not, they become creatures of darkness. Only Willy Smith and his dog survive and are dedicated to finding a cure for the virus.The two frame, if I had been the protagonist, I would suicide. I was not born to be legend, even a small review in the annexes of the history. This film is a little roll of always, with humanity extinct, bugs to eat the survivors, I never understand as not is suicidad. The peculiarity, in my view, that the survivor is only, with which it entered much his role, even more distressed than him. Instead of escaping, he decides to seek a cure. The action scenes are not many, say that they are well distributed, and the spectacular lies in see desert Manhathan, which gives much bad feeling. In the flat negative is that it leaves a little cold, but I think that the culprit of this is thinking it is an action film, when it is not exactly that. It has left me a strange aftertaste.In short, film of extermination of humanity, where a man with his dog wants to find a cure for infected survivors. It is not like any of the genre, and I see, is not popcorn film. It has a little more that may mislead the public.Harrowing, very distressing for my fragile and child mind.Besitos.P.D: My sister-in-law is has "transposed" a few frames, while my brother-in-law looked at askance thinking if had not deceived you for not going to see Rec. Not to say that they do not like.Pd2: A man alone, a young bitch. Suspect, dear Watson, suspicious;-) P.D.3: is apparently based on a book (those who have read have emerged from the film saying "it was best the book") and made two movies before, and the rumored of Charlon Heston. You save the search in Google.</body>
</review>
