<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Alatriste" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I liked, but isn't that masterpiece than expected and I would have liked it</summary>
	<body>I liked, but. So I want to start this review, especially because that "but" represents the overall feel that I saw in the majority of the people out of the film, while it is stretched, after two and a half hours sitting in the cinema.I liked, Yes, but I made something long. And it is 241 minutes do not pass in vain. In fact, there are who had removed long half-hour to the footage of this "Alatriste", that Yes, it is technically impeccable.I liked, but Viggo Mortessen speaks somewhat rare. Normal. He is an American who speaks Spanish porteño accent. Much is that it has not been necessary to fold it, as it would have been logical, with a big star of world cinema.The actors are great. Both the main Mortessen and the side. If Noriega is fine, Eduard Fernández is better and, above all, Echanove, camera and Dechent are fable. To make them a tribute. However, Únax Ugalde me continues to fall fat and, above all, the female characters out ostensibly harmed in the Division of roles. They have the characters less grateful, the less gracefully and more uncomfortable. That Yes, the magnetism of Ariadna Gil remains always.I liked personally, this "Alatriste", but I miss a storyline that you coherence in a concatenation of powerful and well resolved images. That is to say, do now why go to war? What happens with the gold ingots? Why Iñigo ends in galleys? Okay that life, sometimes, takes you by unexpected, unimagined and unimaginable ways. Okay that life, at times, does not follow a predetermined script and that things pass, simply. But "Alatriste" is a movie, not life.There is an argument or a story that you hook and you inmovilice against the seat. There is a script that you excited, there is not a simple story that makes you pay attention to what happens on screen. There is a story of astonishing love, nor a unnerving rivalry, a dream, a challenge or an exciting challenge. And, therefore, "Alatriste" just something cold and soulless.I would like to say that I liked, but that I have missed something a more classical narrative, with his approach, knot and outcome. It is technically perfect. The high budget is well spent and looks like the jets of the gold. Suits and dresses, historical reenactment and battles are perfectly achieved. Pero.Cuando Alatriste and Perez Reverte words appeared, finally and at long last, on screen, I realized that I had moved much during the film, he had looked at the hour a couple of times on the phone and the truth, did not have excessive anxiety by ask the lockers about when possible part II premiered.Or that "Alatriste" I liked, but isn't that masterpiece than expected and I would have liked it to be. I do not regret having gone to see her, but I have no scheduled reserve in the video club of the corner when comes out on DVD. That okay. That it is not wrong. But it is not the vibrant and intense film that, even with the grief and darkness was supposed to him, I was expecting.</body>
</review>
