<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Soy leyenda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To make simple vampire monsters, betrays the subject spirit of the novel by Richard Matheson, but as action film is ambitious enough to make it worthwhile viewing.</summary>
	<body>I am legend (2007) credits include, the foundations of his screenplay, not only to the Richard Matheson novel, but also to John William Corrington and Joyce Hooper Corrington, the couple of writers architects of the Omega Man (1971). This is an unequivocal sign where Iran shots in the film, that while the argument quite away from the film starring Charlton Heston, yes it shares with her his desire for action film, high clear is at its maximum power to become the blockbuster that, finally, finished by razing this Christmas. Let us remember that this project leads in particular be brewing more than one decade, and finally we have been without the promised version of Ridley Scott starring Arnold Schwarzenegger. Fortunately, director Francis Lawrence has managed to offer a spectacle worthy about Will Smith star status, and although I am legend is far from being the adaptation of Matheson we both waited, has enough hits to merit a viewing.The story is already known to everyone at this point: a military scientist Robert Neville is the last man remaining in the devastated and lonely New York City (a geographical change of this story to date had always developed in Los Angeles). During the day round the streets in search of supplies and during the night is entrenched in his house to resist the embites of the hordes of vampires / mutants that inhabit the ruins of the city. Vampires are the result of a mutation caused by a viral cure against cancer has finally turn against its creators and ruined the human race. Neville, however, continues to search for a vaccine at the same time struggling to survive in the city who refused to leave.This city is, certainly, the greatest success of I am legend; In addition to the already proven reality that an empty city is something that hits in full context, the desolate New York of this version is perhaps the most impressive ever seen in cinema, and a test of the true scope of this version. The shots of the solitary City (which, in an unusual windfall for our time, are devoid of all music) are so appalling that I cannot even imagine how must have been seeing this movie version of IMAX, which unfortunately we won't have this side of the pond. Throughout the first half of the film goes in the recreation of this atmosphere of solitude in which we only see Neville and Sam, his German Shepherd Dog and only companion. Funny thing is not only that Will Smith succeeds in making a convincing Neville (in spite of those who complained that the protagonist was, unlike what happens in the novel, black race, an opinion which I do not know to think), but that the dog is also a major character whose interaction with the prota provides the most effective drama of the film. The relationship between the two is perfectly credible, and during this first hour the public reached a real connection with Neville, in spite of the flashbacks that explain the origin of the plague and which, for me at least, were not necessary, with the exception, perhaps, of the the escape sequence of Manhattan, a scene that seems deplorable recent version of Spielberg's war of the worlds (2005).But despite its spectacular nature, I am Legend fails the most important paragraph: Vampires are facing Neville. While the first time that we see them succeed in creating one of the most successful and tense of the footage, sequences dead once the surprise are technically disappointing, creatures made digitally and that they seem to exits of some mummies film directed by Stephen Sommers. But worst of all is that, inexplicably, have decided to display them as simple monsters entirely devoid of humanity, with which they directly uploaded the thematic Center of Matheson novel to a level that none of the other two versions had reached. To make matters worse, the end of the film shows a pseudo-religioso twist completely out of place and that somehow ends up altering even the meaning of the title of the novel (something I cannot explain without spoilers).Literary betrayals aside, what we have is a very good film with a first half highly recommended. Essential to see her in a movie theater to appreciate his spectacular and maintain the hope that a future adaptation of the novel that meets our expectations.</body>
</review>
