<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="El silencio antes de Bach" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The silence before Bach belongs to that kind of film of freely expressive, very rare nowadays, which through long and suggestive planes teaches us more than with an eternal dialogue. A work of art.</summary>
	<body>The Thursday night was fortunate to attend the preview of the silence before Bach (Die Stille vor Bach), the new film by Pere Portabella. Seventeen years ago celebrated filmmaker (which was rewarding to greet him) not placed after the cameras to make a feature film, and one wondered what would have done after so long. As well, this new project is a personal view on the influence of music in society over the years, taking as a reference to the composer Johann Sebastian Bach, the real teacher that you marked a before and an after. Lacks in any film, Portabella, a storyline: relies mainly on a succession of images to the rhythm of the music (this, certainly, is not a simple accompaniment: is the true protagonist). It's an approximation to a Europe marked by the culture and pure beauty. His memorable images delve us into a world known to all, but portrayed, here, impeccable and elegantly, as only few filmmakers could do. Portabella gives us a completely atypical cultural lesson, marked by a slow pulse (doom9), recreated with a no less common argument, with Interwoven stories, which the filmmaker little cares that they have any sense. The silence before Bach belongs to this type of cinema of freely expressive, to a very rare movies nowadays, which through long and suggestive planes teaches us more than with an eternal dialogue. And that is the unique and suggestive dialogue from the film which takes place in a bar of road, probably one of the many strengths of this magnificent work.The film opens with an image on white extremely risky, which is preceded by a tour by an empty room. We see, once finished traveling, a player piano that moves with an air of freedom throughout the room, who plays and "dances" single. Without doubt, a great start that indicates perfectly what we find: a free tour of several places that have the music as a point in common, sensuality expressed in images. It has a special starting point, which starts as just, blank. We assume, then, that this table aims to show us all this wonder, a set full of expressiveness and feelings. This is certainly a film to enjoy and be carried away, a trip that probably not carried anywhere, but in which you've had a tremendous time. Within its apparent inconexión, the various stories that occur, in addition to having the music in common, have the same slow when it comes to be counted, a delicacy and beauty that exceed the limits of the current film.This is a totally anti-commercialism proposal, a real demonstration that current Spanish film can give much more than itself, leaving orphanages in band. Possibly one of the projects, not only most daring and beautiful year-round, also of the best. Portabella's isn't exactly where everyone goes to see; Moreover, it is exclusively dedicated to minority audiences, then understand or want to understand the film as something more than a simple story with argument with three distinct parts. As I said, the silence before Bach doesn't have a clear beginning or a development highlighted nor a final like any other. It has none of these characteristics, and why I think it is a work of genuine courage, based on the power of images and music.A wonderful film not suitable for the incodicionales of popcorn and who enjoy with American nonsense: is intended, no doubt, those who want to witness something very new, adult, distant everything what they are accustomed to seeing. A real achievement that will remain in my memory over the years, due to its incredible sensuality and beauty of its contents. We must thank to Pere Portabella by leaving us take on such huge, risky, mysterious and extraordinary work of art.</body>
</review>
