<review author="José A. Peig" title="1408" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting and at times fascinating horror film, with a display of imaginative and absorbent, but unfortunately is check the terrible imbalance: so brilliant in its form, but as unfinished and indefinite in its background.</summary>
	<body>With 1408 return to the damn place to taste a supposedly Kafkaesque tale in the tradition of horror film based on the introspective look: or terror from within outward (i.e., on the basis of the psychology of the or of the central characters), alternative to the tradition of the terror induced by manifestly external phenomena. From this point we can realize the incongruity that throws rushing one of the best visual work that we have seen in recent months.Surprisingly, this is a film to discuss plans, framing and focus of the entire visual field. His mise en scène is imaginative and take advantage of every angle and the room object to create the atmosphere in which the central character defines his delirium. As a work of horror, goes beyond the feeling to entangle a paranoia of contours oniric and often sentimental (and often, also, childish). The first thirty minutes are a virguería narrative in which synthesizes and defines the time of the central character, writer descreído on Paranormal subjects that conceals a murky past and which is dominated by the family drama. John Cusak prepares a fresh and versatile performance with the accompaniment of Samuel l. Jackson, and the relationship established between both characters reaches a remarkable ease thanks to the good work of the writers. In fact, the best of this movie - what home looked like it was going to be the best - is its ability to address profiles and stereotypical situations of the clichés of the horror film without stagnate in clichés.The relationship described between the Manager of the hotel and the skeptical writer, for its credibility and versatile sketching, showed great promise in this story. And on the other hand, as the narration goes into terrifying dream that shapes their dream the psychological trauma of the protagonist, everything is confuses towards the ground of the dramatic, or a mere display of visual virtuosity without internal consistency, without specify the tone or the thematic thread that offers us a defining idea and, hence, a raison d ' être of the product. Worst of all is that, as regards the content, is limited to passing on two levels of meaning without reaching any port: when ends the first segment (with John Cusak unconscious after the crash on the beach) narration, explicitly noted the psychic nature of everything that has happened, something that, on the other hand, was already implicit - because of the Kafkaesque pulse that inspires - in the same exhibition of history (this bland redundancy that both) (us it bothers and that nothing brings to the set, but simplifies). And then takes longer, ends the movie in the worst way possible: recording on magnetic tape that shows that what we have seen - and that the character has lived - has a literal meaning, and not psychic or symbolic. This final contradiction - which aims to be a plot twist - is too free to be the defining range that must be the last image, so even is a turning point in the argument, but a resolution, to put it in some way, aborted.Ultimately, interesting and at times fascinating horror film, with a display of imaginative and absorbent, but unfortunately is check the terrible imbalance: so brilliant in its form, but as unfinished and indefinite in its background. And not angry you: If this were a tale of terror "to dry" the rating of this film could have uploaded a couple of points. The problem is that he wants to be too many things at the same time.</body>
</review>
