<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Best taken I am legend as a more popcorn, but without girl showing curves (the dog Sam lacks). And to follow all the same. When you enter the cinema, it leaves the brain out.</summary>
	<body>The generation of Matheson (novelist) and Lawrence (director and producer) read books, and watch movies. Both, which writes these lines, inoculaba in his spare disturbing tales of horror and science fiction, and B-movies today - many of them - are recognized as relating cultural. In those stories we found good times of action and fear, as well as suggestive metaphors about the world and ourselves. However, the generation for which the history of I am legend is told is a generation already not read (or barely), but that devours frames of film made in uses wherever you can. And it shows in the pace and lack of courage to handle scripts for productions such as this which we are talking about.I am legend is an efficient production, as many many more which we will make live a more bearable Christmas. So a literary claim who knows the viewer taken as regards, and if you don't know who was Richard Matheson then don't worry, add as bait advertising the presence of Smith (in new plan American hero) and his estilazo hiphopero, sliding his great guy gym by a New York apocalyptic but dignified, accompanied by his dog Sam. The rest do a few special effects that life to the more skeptical. And it is already. Guaranteed success.I am legend will not be a lasting product in the memory of the Spanish Viewer, and much less in contributions to the genre of horror or science fiction. But this not worthy a matchless technical work, some disturbing scenes, and ceases to count. If we try to rely on his literary comparisons are revealed more than hateful. There is no or hero scientific or more survivors support the plot, nor vampires where used with brain, nor end made in the Matheson Novella. Matheson underlines the solitude of the character, without political metaphors post 9 / 11. It focuses on the psychological aspects of Neville and takes the vampire icon to give it more scientific realism and suggest a juicy reflection on the concept of social normalcy and its perverse effects.In the version of Lawrence there is little psychological approach, despite the fact that the script starts suggesting otherwise. The scene of the video store is notable in that regard. But the action soon becomes what it must never have to pretend to not be: pure excessively seasoned spectacle of a cheat political propaganda with a nothing lightweight colorful conservative.Is true that the director could have tapped the potential of the book by Matheson to suggest a powerful metaphor for the acceptance of the other in situations of fears or socially accepted prejudice. But not. Is more than the Bush era end up managing to all vermin living vaccine of liberalism conservative. where is then the novelty of I am legend? Because nothing less in the strange relationship that established the indent between alleged skepticism of New York citizens after the attacks of the 11-S and a history of terror and conventional science fiction. "My name is Robert Neville." I am a survivor in New York City. If there is someone there, please. "You are not alone". This is the desperate message released by radio the protagonist who could stay alive. Dr. Neville survives in a ghost town, bleak, a zone zero perpetua, threatened by beings infected, dehumanized. "I am here to bring light to the darkness," says a promotional spot.And at the very least lets give the secondary (by way of announcing Angel of hope) role to a Brazilian character (do a diplomatic nod to Lula?), that while it will serve Friday to a Crusoe depressed by loneliness, it remains mere recipient of the blessings of the sacrificed American friend.The director, Francis Lawrence, drawn with this a not so faint (and of course a political correctness that puts hairs as hooks to all attentive spectator) metaphor on the State assumption of mind of every American self-respecting as such (patriotic, to be exact), threatened by the hopelessness of terrorism in his own House. And in turn plays for the umpteenth time the megalomaniacal iconicidad of the American redeeming hero, always ready to give their last breath for a free world.Do not be afraid, American. Science and our abiding faith in our lifestyle will help us to resist and ultimately win the war to this virus. For this company we have the best, a hero that despite being human, not allowed to carry by discouragement and their efforts at the end will give its fruit. The objective is to morale to one America disenchanted by both critical discourse, more that help generate discontent and apathy. Let us stop Communist fabrications and hope dad State, which ensures the designs of a country was born to succeed (with God's help, of course) with loving justice.But what can import us European viewers a political reading of what is mere spectacle! Best taken I am legend as a more popcorn, but without girl showing curves (the dog Sam lacks). And to follow all the same, that's what we have USA protecting the free world and offering our evenings of Christmas fun. When you enter the cinema, it leaves the brain out.Finally, we will always remain the great novels of Matheson. For those who have not read this emblematic author of science fiction of the 1950s, them maybe interested to know that many of his works have been adapted to cinema with greater or less success. Note the devil on wheels (Spielberg, 1971) - both short format but eternal in the memory, the incredible shrinking man (Arnold, 1957) - perhaps the most suggestive of all and the closest to the theme of I am legend-, the final step (Koepp, 2000) - a film disturbing, but absorbed by the phenomenon the sixth sense-, beyond dreams (Ward)(1998), Somewhere in time (Szwarc, 1980).</body>
</review>
