<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Deseo, Peligro" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Estimable Ang Lee film, linking thriller and Eroticism in an attractive and suffocating peculiar love story.</summary>
	<body>Good Ang Lee film, returns to demonstrate his heterodoxy in genres, changing from one to another as likes the story you want to tell in pictures.On this occasion, get a good product thanks to a measured and studied screenplay, fruit of Eileen Chang and James Schamus.La story, superbly manufactured from the formal point of view, with a perfect atmosphere thanks to a commendable and easy task for make-up, costumes, hairdresser, a surround soundtrack conducted by Alexandre Desplat and art direction, both indoors and outdoorsIt has a classic and at the same time modern taste. Classic on the modus narrative, taking his time to show the various characters and their psychological evolution through the past and modern time as regards the steamy sex scenes, amazing in a conventional Asian cinematography.All this leads to a footage that could brand of excessive, not in vain lasts longer than two hours and a half. But it must be said that it not tired at all and interest not only not lapses over the footage but is on the rise. But it is true that the final part stretches a poquillo more thing due, but not too.Interpretations are vital in this more than estimable film which, let us remember, won the Golden Lion in Venice last. Both Tony Leung, as introverted as we usually see him and Wei Tang, in a role that no doubt it brings them, very demanding in all aspects.Without a doubt, "I, danger" is not the masterpiece that any / as they say, but it is an important work, which is completely worthwhile and has excellent scenes, hard to forget, as frank with Hsiao floor, the former friend of the Chief of the command, so to speak. "Scene which is not original as much drink of the most remembered"Curtain Rasgada", master Hitchock.""Desire, danger", an estimable thriller with juicy scenes of sex, perhaps at the end may be disappointing to some viewers and say at the end of the same as "then go for it". And is that the end is the most realistic as possible, but not the taste of the majority, probably.</body>
</review>
