<review author="JLO" title="Cerdos salvajes" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Incredible by you where look. Not for the surprise of their unexpected achievements, but because it is impossible that a script so poor and with ideas for the comedy behind decades will filming.</summary>
	<body>Incredible movie where you look. Not for the surprise of their unexpected achievements, but because it is impossible that a script so poor and with ideas for the comedy behind decades will filming. And no doubt that the fact that it is realizable is because actors of the stature of John Travolta, Tim Allen, Martin Lawrence and exquisite secondary William H. Macy decided to make it.If we talk only about Travolta is worse, already a case apart. An actor who seems determined to accept everything that will pass nearby, roundly. More skinny, fat, fat again, that they seem to be interpretative variants. Choose a film well and three evil. Tarantino will be repentant of his revival? An artistic agent here!.Four fifties friends decide to leave their daily routines and venturing into bike by the roads Yankees to see it what them the destiny. His argument that is simplistically. But there is another way to exemplify it either.In this "film" education is not that one in the beginning of old age may their dreams despite the look escrutadora from the outside, if not that everything can be resolved. shock. And still losing fights. Do incredible mentioned above?.The salvageable are these amazing custom motorcycles, these beauties are the dream of anyone who ever has gone on two wheels. The true protagonists of the film. Some side well resolved, good gags (Marisa Tomei, Ray Liotta), the sympathy of the leading, good end crèditos, isn't enough to take off from mediocrity.The only salvageable joke is that the friend of actor Tim Allen (voice of the unforgettable Buzz Lighthyear) is called. Woody. Film that if oneself is not humor, is to launch to infinity and beyond.</body>
</review>
