<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the good, or very good remakes of those who do have something to say and contribute to the original. If not for its excessive length, almost two hours, we would talk about a round film.</summary>
	<body>The alarming lack of ideas Hollywood remakes makes one constant increasing weekly releases. If you visit this page, you can get an idea of how things are, but as a good example suffice it to say that it has already been announced the American revision of "[Rec]" (1).Most times, the remake is usually a pretty and sweetened, version forgets the identity of the original and becomes a product of mass consumption for all jovencillos more willing to throw popcorn each other than to enjoy a film session in conditions. However, sometimes the movie Yes worth, as demonstrated Aja, Snyder, or Nispel. On this occasion, has the turn it to "Halloween", carried out by semi-novato Rob Zombie. But he has not limited itself to tell us the same story which in its day was attended by Carpenter.Para present as God commands, Michael Myers has opted to split the film into two parts of almost equal length (one hour each). The second does not have too many plot developments over the previous version (note, I'm not saying that it is a bad thing), and is the first that we find the largest number of news. Because "Halloween" is rather a kind of prequel, which focuses on developing what the other was left in the attic. With his usual style, dirty and badass, Zombie writes and directs the early years of Michael Myers, in an attempt to justify this unhealthy behavior that led to so many deaths. Thus, the first hour is an oppressive atmosphere, full of negativity, heat, and flies, and is in this type of environment we grow and mature the young man obsessed with masks that will end up killing his sister and stepfather, to then be locked in the mental Institute of Richmon for fifteen years. But the thing it does not end there. During the next half hour, continue assisting the formation of the monster, through the interviews that Dr. Loomis (played by a chameleonic and - heroic (2)-Malcolm McDowell) is doing it. Everything until suddenly, in a bloody act of rebellion, Myers escapes after ending all resistance that occurs, and returns to his hometown, Haddonfield.A starting from here the low film a little its up impeccable point level, since the history is the same as the "Halloween" by Carpenter, and a couple of victims more and more blood and sex are not an excuse to extend one extra hour his (already itself pretty) (long) footage. For very well done that everything, that it is.And it is that Zombie manages to give a physical change to Myers, becoming a forzuda mole of two meters high, long, dirty hair and undone mask by the passage of the years. Thus, better accepted the fact that it is so animal and don't show any mercy with their victims. Because deaths are quite extreme, in the case of production which is (remember that behind all this are the fearsome Weinstein = easy money and censorship to the singing), and as with his previous two films, the director does not cut in showing close-ups and blood to GLUGs. Good for Rob!So, together we talk about one of the good, or very good remakes of those who do have something to say and contribute to the original. If not for its excessive length, almost two hours, we would talk about a round film, but that problem distance something to the Viewer, which it just seeing their final minutes with some coldness and impair their proper enjoyment. Even so, it is worth much. Look at the several cameos in the film. From Forest Whitaker ("the rogue of the devil"), Danny Trejo ("Machete"), Sid Haig (Captain Spaulding), or the historic Ken Foree ("zombie").7,5/10 (1) that Yes, not everything is bad news: between the long list of remakes, some promise. The creators of "À L 'Intérieur" are doing a revision of the classic "Hellraiser" charge, and Aja continues rolling "Mirrors", with Kiefer Sutherland in the lead role.(2) Those who continue the series "Heroes" associate you immediately to Linderman, because in the second part of the film it is going with the same Court of beard.</body>
</review>
