<review author="Andrés Pons" title="La cólera del infierno" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Trying to sneak an argument to the Romeo and Juliet, go to know what were the writers to create such parida, the minimum budget is evident in a few technical effects that resemble the amateur, is again destroys a small classic as on previous occasions.</summary>
	<body>At the end of the 1980s one of the great magicians of the effects of make-up and special STAN WILSON I collaborate in countless films of success "CONSTANTINE, TERMINATOR 3, BIG FISH" among so many others, performed his greatest success as a director in a bit prolific career in that branch.I am referring to Covenant of blood which had one of the big players of serie b and the fantastic LANCE HENRIKSEN who reached great popularity with his work in the alien series or television with MILENNIUN which continues to work piece in small productions.Without being a wonder an attractive film for its great atmosphere and above all by the appearance of PUMPKINHEAD turned out one of the most bloody bugs of the unforgettable ALIEN-like GORE.All the virtues of that small success were ruined with several continuations of video-club meat. Carried out in any way they are typical sagas that are created in an attempt to get four peel using the name of a cult film.We arrived at the 2007 with the release on DVD of a new party, the fourth if I not wrong directed by the horrible HURST MICHAEL author among other barbarities of the dawn of the ZOMBIES. Repeat LANCE Henriksen as commercial insert surrounded by pseudo-actores coming out of small series.Trying to sneak an argument to the Romeo and Juliet, go to know what were the writers to create such parida, the minimum budget is evident in a few technical effects that resemble the amateur, is again destroys a small classic as on previous occasions. See examples of howls and HELLRAISER who were notable works of the most visceral horror played to lose in its subsequent sequels.</body>
</review>
