<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Bee movie" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Extremely entertaining, with clear-cut characters and more hilarious situations. A divertimento ensured, aimed more at higher than children.</summary>
	<body>Barry B. Benson is a bee concerned about their future. The idea of honey every day for the rest of his life without any rest terrifies him, so decides to risk and leave their hive inside to see the world outside before being forced to deal with the inevitable. In his particular crossing, it manages to keep healthy and except thanks to Vanessa, a human who saves a terrible death by crushing. Barry feels suddenly attracted to her, and would give whatever thank you gesture, but to do so it should break the first law of the hive: is strictly forbidden to speak with humans. Difficult task asking him to the new proposal for Dreamworks. After seven years of exploitation of the flagship of the producer, it begins to already notable signs of exhaustion. Therefore, Simon j. Smith and Steve Hickner, directors of "Bee Movie", had to demonstrate that there is life most of the blatant green OGRE. To do so, that certainly had an important ACE up the sleeve, as it is Jerry Seinfeld in the tasks of screenwriter and dubber. While the end result still does not get too close to the level of Pixar productions, the truth is that they have far exceeded the goal, creating a film (and a character) that nothing has to envy to the trilogy of "Shrek". The main difference between bee and OGRE is that the creators of "Bee Movie" is not limited to offer us a succession of gags based on making fun of other films. Here they build a script around the characters and the situation in which do, and the jokes are interwoven in dialogues and actions of the same, resulting in very little forced. So much so, that even the (few) jokes that referred to the references of the viewer work perfectly. Although much of the success of these perhaps lies in that it focused on characters or less obvious programs which could fear (no there is not a single nod to the scenes with stop-motion of "Matrix", I would say that for the first time in the history of the Dreamworks). It is worth as an example the characterization that make an actor Ray Liotta is unusual. But what makes a different film of "Bee Movie" is what counts. Because what begins as another substitute of "Monsters, S.A.", that is, two co-workers in a parallel world to the humans, with a single company in which all the bees work (includes too similar scenes even visually, as the arrival to work by car by the two main characters), little by little is distancing himself and acquiring its own personality, creating a real mountain of little foreseeable events ending with crashes of through beginning of a grain of sand such as the output of their hive bee (indeed that its top also can remember quite "Buscando a Nemo", now that I think). In addition, throughout the central part of "Bee Movie" belongs to legal genre, something in total contrast with the cinema of child Court that will achieve more entertain adult, tired public because that these films are limited only to parody scenes from other films. And as mentioned above, Barry is charismatic, dynamic and is very well defined. It is be somewhat stereotyped, but never come to bother with your mordientes comments, strokes his actor gives him and they get that the bee is truly hilarious. Everything would seem to indicate that we are discussing short film animation, or the victory of Dreamworks Pixar. Sadly, it is not the case. Because where "Bee Movie" innova not an iota is in your background. Despite the originality of situations (bees talking with men, judges and courts, companies of honey with clear references - this time Yes - to the human hives of "Matrix", Ray Liotta and Sting.), the film follows a path as predictable as his watered-down end, what causes you to lose many integers on numerous occasions. Thus, to the minimum that the bee does no good la manga no comments of their own, or that there is no any other plot twist, rhythm get stuck, and the film becomes something melosa because it concentrates too much on a script that is not always at the height. Even so, is a film very entertaining, with clear-cut (and well bent) characters and more hilarious situations. A divertimento ensured, aimed more at greater than children (which will become bored by not having too many action scenes visual spectacular), and beautiful invoice. This should be the correct way forward of the producer, which however remained committed to resort to the goose that lays golden eggs and has already announced the fourth part of "Shrek". 7.5/10</body>
</review>
