<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Beowulf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Beowulf" is a beautiful and striking, film with a simple and entertaining story loaded with the slab of a script that seems to take too seriously the proposal</summary>
	<body>Robert Zemeckis is increasingly closer to his goal. I.e. make the animated film with actors perfect, arduous task that unless it fails can bring more than one disappointment.Since it began to implement the use of new technologies in the film, many have been attempts to innovate in an industry not for anything defined as a factory of dreams. One of the busiest directors in this regard has been precisely Zemeckis, who with "Back to the future" composed one of the best films of science fiction of all time (surprising even today, both at the plot level as visual and technical), which followed experiments like "Who framed Roger Rabbit?", or "Death I feel so fine". Squarely in the technique of scanning of actors, something which has tried with little success some case "Final Fantasy" was released with "Polar Express". Zemeckis is a film Christmas, positive and tender, that while it pales before any of the Pixar productions, is undeniable as both visually (unforgivable not to see it in 3-D, is worth as an example this unbridled race to the train by a real roller coaster which empties into a frozen pond) as to any other. As much as impress in destroy her. And it is one of the problems with those who depart the films who drink of new technologies is contempt for the criticism. Committed to making to prevail the classic cinema, that of always, the "good", baited against any innovative proposal. "Polar Express" is a bullshit just for children (then go and "Shrek 3" leave it in the clouds), or "Sky Captain and the world of tomorrow" is so silly and soda, or "300" is so bad to dry. Stay with the film Garci and Redford, and already you can see how well will go you to the sector. A little bit of please, man.Downloads and claims to part, the problem that did "Polar Express" was the excessive coldness of the facial expressions of the characters (most of them played by Tom Hanks). Looked like dolls, without a soul, and that is something that the director wanted to avoid for its new immersion in the genre. To avoid repeating the same mistakes with "Beowulf", Zemeckis was surrounded by a large number of professionals and technical resources, tripling the efforts invested in his previous film. The result is undeniably better in general. Now, the faces of the actors do seem to more alive, with all luxury of details (wrinkles, freckles, passage of time, beard.), and the quality of the scenarios is overwhelming, as well as the details of various blood spills, a constant in the action scenes. But still failing in others, being its main ballast true acartonamiento in the movements of the characters, which sometimes are unrealistic and robotic gestures. In reality, little imported these defects if you see the movie in three dimensions (1) spectacular is guaranteed, and if not attentive to the final stretch, the fight against the Golden Dragon. In fact, many of the levels are designed only for this format, taken from too much up, or down, so what you seeing in 2-D can lead to think that it's a garrafal bug, 3-d is one of the fundamental pillars to achieve a superb impact on the Viewer.Curiously, the qualitative decompensation technically serves as a ring to the finger to describe the film itself, because its second problem is surprisingly in the script, which seems fun and spectacular at times, but tedious and pretentious in others.The response of all ills is surely Neil Gaiman, screenwriter of the boring series of comics "The Sandman", which together with the fearsome Roger Avary (capable of adapting brilliantly Ellis as well as load - and see that was easy - the mythical video game "Silent Hill" series) is responsible for writing this new adaptation of the epic Anglo-Saxon history. As it could not be less, the screenplay is a too relamida and pretentious, composition with infinite dialogues that cause too many slippages of pace. Nor is it a boredom on the order of "Matrix: Reloaded" (that same leg limp). The overall taste is sweeter than anything else, because the movie is quite funny. The problem therefore it is that basically He entertains, but not everything that it should. And that is a pity, because the action scenes are absolutely exquisite, and no doubt we would be talking about a masterpiece in all its senses for an excessive duration consisting of empty and awkward dialogue, failed attempts to give the characters of a moral duality that was clear from the beginning and does not need so many explanations."Beowulf" is thus a striking, beautiful film with a simple and entertaining story loaded with the slab of a script that seems to take too seriously the proposal. But despite everything, Robert Zemeckis (or co-workers) moves with ever more ease in this new format, and the evolutionary leap of "Polar Express" this is more than notable. Spectacular on all four sides, a wide distribution and attractive (highlight to Crispin Glover making an even more disgusting than Tolkien's Gollum), and an impressive display of technical resources. (Almost) all a gozada.7/10 (1) in Barcelona there are to go to the driver to do so. A pity that they do not also in the Imax.</body>
</review>
