<review author="Alex Largo" title="Ratatouille" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Altogether a great animated film (from beginning to end) that will delight all those who are dignen to take a look.</summary>
	<body>The downside of not having time is that, one day, as who does not want the thing, you are writing the critique of a movie you saw in August. That sad is the world.What went, "Ratatouille", the movie about a rat called Remy and his funny goal in life: be Cocinero.La film usa its asset have a crazy starting point, fresh and perfect throughout the film and without abuse, because every minute that passes it surprises us with a scene that makes us twist in the seat (of laughter)(refers).Without a doubt the movie is a great "made in Pixar" joy after Cars. Film that although accurate and entertaining kept from being a pure visual product completely hollow to telling the same story we have been listening to for years.But good. Let's go by parts: the address: it is more than obvious that Brad Bird passes as a dwarf, and what is more admirable, that makes the public what happens as a dwarf.Screenplay: round, although not brilliant (but little lacking) reinvents himself and try not to fall (and almost succeeds) in some stupid clichés and trite jokes.Characters: (say the characters because server has not been able to do a fair assessment of the voices in the original version) are perhaps those more salsa give the tape, they congenian very fast with the viewer making has this enjoy as nice.Soundtrack: without a doubt a great soundtrack of always correct Michael Giacchino that accompanies the film without stridency and without removing protagonism to the images.Animation: is responsible for both the characters and the story are as good as they are. Undoubtedly the Pixar is exceeded (although in a less spectacular way) with this tape with the most impressive scenes (Cars was pure consumption shitty fast) have seen in relation to animation in recent years. From this magnificent and funny principle on the farm, through the flight by pipes to all and each one of the scenes that we are witnessing in Paris. altogether a great animated film (from beginning to end) that will delight all those who are dignen to take a look.</body>
</review>
