<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="À lintérieur" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good horror film bloody pure and simple, with a Béatrice Dalle really unbalanced and relentless as the bad very bad and undoubted dyes of cult film that is well worth highlighting.</summary>
	<body>Much excitement for this bloody French thriller that already garnered critical acclaim at the Cannes Film Festival past. What begins as a thriller uncovers the half an hour as a brutal orgy gore who plays to beat records in deadly stunts, double jump with ringlet and triple amputation with spillage of gut. The plot of the thriller is quite silly and predictable, but one realizes immediately that the intention of the film actually goes another thing and not care too much. No matter because bloody scenes are fantastically executed and go in a rhythm and a realistic increscendo in c major truly terrifying and because they are also shot with an admirable talent. The makeup effects are great and insistent music manages to freeze us blood. The picture is quite interesting but strikes a unforgivable detail: the use of artificial smoke to create atmosphere in the House is horribly managed and rather gives the impression that will appear behind the curtain of a moment to another the grandfather of the protagonist fumandose pure. The truth is that there seems to be a fire in the House during much of the footage without it and this if that is to shoot the director of photography without any mercy and to include it in the footage. Even though this problem and that the carousel of sadistic exaggerations of the end will fully mother's, the film leaves be taken somewhat seriously if it and thanks to this the film leaves to fully enjoy as entertainment of terror, albeit sometimes with hands covering us a little eyes by the sickly and brutal scenes or covering us the mouth by nervous laughter.In short, a good horror film bloody pure and hard, with a Béatrice Dalle really unbalanced and relentless embodying the bad very bad and undoubted-tinged cult film that is well worth highlighting.</body>
</review>
