<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Soy leyenda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Curious, for the reflective and not very spectacular, film, which I hope, for the sake of humanity, is not of the genus in advance.</summary>
	<body>Curious and quite competent, in my opinion, adaptation of the famous work of Richard Matheson, already on two other occasions prior to the film.Here, against what you would expect, and more with the oscuras way of making action films today, the film is quite thoughtful, quiet and has moments righteous action, very spectacular and something terrifying, always distressing, but displayed progressively, account drops, when should it be done, never free and dramatic way.With few characters and a high profile of Will Smith, which is splendid, Martin Lawrence, director, achieved an estimable science film fiction or anticipation, who knows, banked at certain moments to pure horror movies."With great planning, where we see the immensity of certain completely deserted streets of New York, is conveys perfectly the solitude of the protagonist, increased in scenes like that of the C-Dclub mannequins, with whom tries to keep a minimal conversation.""I am Legend" could have been more spectacular, but the script going in other directions, more intimate, more human, and get, I believe, convince in its more realistic proposal of a world with human beings about to disappear from the face of the Tierra.Pero also, those intimate scenes, complemented with other superb as the attack dogs of the protagonist and his faithful Sam, long scene (second frame), transmitting anguish, fear and emotion in equal parts.By what I have heard and read out there, it seems that the film fails to convince readers of the original novel, but in my opinion is a good movie such as it is designed to be number 1 in the United States of North America, wonder but Will Smith has personality and history is appealing, achieving a very entertaining and interesting film that leaves a good taste in mouth.</body>
</review>
