<review author="Jokin García " title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Omega Man is faced with a horde of infected and the reality of being a bad remake.</summary>
	<body>Imagine that an Apocalypse decimated humanity and you are the only human being left on the face of the Earth. Now imagine that you're not alone at all, you're only human, Yes, but that you get to share space with a race of mutant vampires, and that day you head-on at your leisure, but at night you have to ocutlarte of them, that does not give you hunting.This is the premise of the novel "I am Legend", carried to the film previously on 2 occasions, being possibly the most famous "Omega Man", starring Charlton Heston, titled as "The Omega Man".One could say that this film is a remake of one, although it could also be said that it is a remake of "Harry Potter", "Snakes on a plane" or a documentary about the alignment of Manchester United in 1998, since all you have in common is that a certain get Neville.Un Neville, also suffered from kingpinismo, something that quite meets the personality of the protagonist of the novel, but in the end. If that were the worst.In this film the vampires are substituted by infected (that not zombies) enrabietados and through, very different from the afro-setentera sect of the Charlton Heston film roll, involved attacking wild form and mandada, with assault on the included Neville mansión-arsenal. Look, yes it shows this is a remake of a movie of Heston, insofar as it is to have weapons up below the carpet.But while there are a many things that grind, the film manages to be entertaining, until that hour and film media, the writers decide, in a completely anticlimática way to end the film in a final of the of "I want the money back", and an explanation of why the film is called "I am Legend" stuck with shoehornpetroleum jelly and many shoving.Ultimately, that they have caught a license, is they have smoked, her have changed from ariba to below and with the excuse they made a bad movie (sorry of infected) zombies and are loaded the fundamental premise of "I am Legend" is not the "I am a black man that shoots the zombies" but of "I'm a monster and they fear those that I fear"", since for them, I am legend."</body>
</review>
