<review author="Jokin García " title="Bee movie" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fun, which is what can ask you for a film of this genre. Suitable for consumption by both children and adults.</summary>
	<body>Bee Movie, a comedy is about. bees. An incongruous and funny film, with final moral on the vital importance of these yellow insects in the ecosystem and the catastrophic consequences that would have his disappearance on the planet.In the purest style of these films, the protagonist fights against the system, resisting to be one more and give good fate that preasigna you (as already happened for example in Antz) and in this case the protagonist is Barry B. Benson, a young bee that newly graduate refuses to a boring life of worker bee and decides to join the squadron of elite of foragers to see the outside world, and there meets a human, Vanessa, which became a pretty friendly. Yes, the bees speak and read, ye seek not sense.But not everything is beautiful on the outside, and Barry discovers a terrifying truth: humans enslave bees for stealing honey and gasean them. (And you know who gaseaban people, isn't it?) And there is where happens one of the events of the film, when Barry decides to bring a lawsuit against humanity, a hilarious and absurd trial, Cup much of the film and some truly subtility moments, especially the totally autoparódicas appearances of Sting and Ray Liotta as well as the winks to talk show host Larry King and to the teddy bear Winnie the Pooh.Sin doubt the best of the film is the absurdity of their situationswith totally impossible scenes but at the service of the laugh or at least smile, and even if it does not reach the level of classics like Shrek or Finding Nemo, is a choice of entertaining to spend the afternoon and to establish some comparison, the would over Madagascar or fun Robots.Muy also that brutal hack through the mosquito, typical secondary comedianthe movie gets to the Group of lawyers. Kidding, for obvious reasons, made that I broke out in a laugh.</body>
</review>
