<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="The Nanny Diaries (Diario de una Niñera)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Soft and acidic, at the time, lyrical and prose, at the same time, diary of a nanny is a more than decent exercise of adult film made with elements of teen comedy or, if you like, teen movies with adult material...</summary>
	<body>Satire of anthropological inspiration, tell fairy in Manhattan, listened and soft composition of topics, diary of a nanny is a nice effort to satisfy a very broad sector of public and not upsetting in excess, none. Less acid that one would like to, the development of the tape goes more to less, but even thus contains traces of high comedy, notes field sociology and, finally, in its more pedestrian charm, adolescent gender ingredients with plot custom jargon and a very exaggerated sense of his own character hinge between film of the Disney (gentle through to the delight of the chiquillada paid for the heroes) and Disney initiative, intelligent report, Declaration of principles strictly urbanites. In this sense, these nanny diaries pivoting between how wonderful and the weakling.It seems a modern reworking of some snobbish hood, lost in the city, atribulada by the circumstances, comply with the Wolf hinque el morro in the ass, but severe in its considerations on the capricious nature of the human being and his frivolous machinations. In fact, everything embadurna a kind of end of career project where this formidable Mary Poppins (Scarlett Johansson makes a magnificent recreation of the babysitter full - time class C which sacrifices the soul for the sake of the purpose of their study) delights us with his innocent adventures, frankly fun (occasionally) and written a remarkable sense of the plot with primorthat sinuously, moving with grace and desparpajo, without that at any time you get tired or overwhelm or wake up suspicions that, ultimately, we are brewing some creeping poisonous populist message, markedly centrifuge for the clichés of the hundreds of comedies as similar to this that the offer (Christmas or not) pushes us to go to the cinema and offer us the prodigious ceremony of deception.However, the joy is not so much and one admits that the end result suffers from one greater scope: all agree to the simplicity, especially in its predictable outcome. The saves and gives her a corner in the memory of small films that manage to be the surprising boot - these revealing diadoramas, true index of the film and intelligent way to tell us what we see and how is going to be cash - large and very compelling interpretations of its interpreters (Laura Linney is a huge actress;) Paul Giamatti is untapped, but offers a recital; (and even the child Nicholas Reese Art gives the counterpoint desired infante, to be contrary to Hitchcock). Nor the Symphony of blessings left us the scoundrels that we often and decide, for pleasure to seek three feet to the best of cats, undo any hint of excessive praise and express that anthropology that wants to be a debtor becomes later boba clichés prose very stylized, that Yes, that without falling in the romantic or the chic nor melts - as it should - that plot mortgagethat it is well advised and had case of acquiring, desastrado the effort altogether. Robert Pulcini and Shari Springer Berman, directors of the acclaimed American splendor, that I have not seen, sign a good proposal, a fun, carefree, original, white tape despite everything said.</body>
</review>
