<review author="Robgordon" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Anything worth caring both for this design, if you forget the most important thing; caring for your story and give it a minimal film interest.  Slow and eternal. Ultimately, a waste of 24 million euros, to achieve well little.</summary>
	<body>Often sopor I meant the viewing of which was called to be the great savior of the Spanish film, "Alatriste" production.Also, modorra, numbness, heaviness, lethargy, boredom, it hastió or I tedio? as you want to call. And it was not something personal, judging by the views and faces of the rest of the spectators out of the projection.There is no doubt, what is that "Alatriste" is a blockbuster. One of the few who dare to make the Spanish cinema. And this time, view the formal invoice, we could think that finally our film had achieved what he had never done; come to Hollywood with a Ribbon of adventure and action, spared expenses, with an international protagonist and an ambitious production.Because as for production design is concerned, "Alatriste" has nothing to envy to the American blockbusters, or without having to cross the pond, to the French, which also take care with great success the visual aspect in their most expensive works.The Spanish 17TH century, is beautifully recreated in "Alatriste". Their scenarios, locations, his costume design, this Madrid of the Siglo de Oro, of capa y espada, with the valid of the Kings and monarchs themselves. This is the best "Alatriste" and the only thing that is a step forward for the Spanish film.But that is not enough. Anything worth caring so much for that design, dressing to the film with a plasticity characteristic of a painting by Velázquez, if you forget the most important thing; caring for your story and give it a minimal film interest. "Alatriste" is excellent in the formal, but simply null in the background, which ends up being a dramatic failure, a major disappointment and a sovereign boredom.The director of the event is Agustín Díaz Yanes, "Tano" for friends, a director who stayed in promise. Was pleasantly surprised with "Nobody will speak of us when we have died" but evidenced by serious doubts about his talent on the unclassifiable "without news of God" in which, the best was the Bob Dylan song that opened the initial titles.In "Alatriste", Díaz Yanes is unable to provide narrative coherence in the tape. It does more than wander. It presents sequences, characters and contexts and close them, not to open them again. He then does the same thing. And thus it is running time, unless we have received nothing in particular. There is an alarming lack of storyline. It gives the feeling of Yanes (director, and at the same time, screenwriter of the event) just wanted to do a 17TH century fresco and not to move Pérez Reverte stories to a cinematic context, which is what most are missing in this work. The viewer of "Alatriste" will wait for 2 hours and 20 minutes to display the action, arising the adventures, and all, is expected of an overproduction of this style. I'm still waiting.And now look at actors? that's another story. All them are great costumes, but only Javier camera as count Duke of Olivares and Juan Echanove as Quevedo, are able to take advantage of them. Yours, are the best interpretations of the tape. Something difficult to achieve in a movie in which your director strives to make you appear as soon as make you disappear.An important gibberish characters come together in "Alatriste". It is true that all belonged to that time. But? they were all needed?, perhaps adds something to the development of the story Fray Emilio Bocanegra? And it was necessary to make the poor Blanca Portillo rapase hair and play a man? Barely appears endos sequences. Eduardo Noriega? has someone said he is not good actor? What transmits not absolutely nothing? Does he painted something mildly momentous, his character, the count of Guadalmedina?And better nor speak of Ariadna Gil to which I have always considered "a deadpan concrete block".Antonio Dechent and Eduard Fernández, save their small roles. Pilar López de Ayala has two sentences. And Enrico Lo Verso, is the closest thing to a villain in this movie. Not to mention the romantic relationship between Iñigo Balboa and Angelica. Abrupt, nothing credible. Why is it so bad? It gives me the feeling that the moments in which both have fallen in love and have shared time together, have been left in the editing room. That if Diaz Yanes puts you two seconds of each of these mutilated sequences so you know that you among so much cut and swordsmen are the two enamoradizos pipiolos. Lamentable.Y on Viggo Mortensen, a good actor as well demonstrated in "A history of violence" and a magnetic hero's adventures ("Lord of the rings") is, in appearance, a perfect Diego Alatriste. "But its Spanish forced at times incomprehensible cancels all his good work in the composition of the character.""Alatriste" is a blockbuster without epic without adventures, with a multitude of unnecessary sequences, zero contribution to the plot development. With poorly treated characters. And few action scenes. Slow and eternal. Ultimately, a waste of 24 million euros, to achieve well little. Spanish overproduction is the worst of the American blockbusters light years.Much hype is being given to "Alatriste" (there are many people involved to share the cake) something that in the short term will be counterproductive for the Spanish film. Which boasted as a possible hope for our film, is not but another sign of the deep creative crisis facing our country. Frankly tape desilusionante. The nth disappointment of Spanish film.</body>
</review>
