<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="1408" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After a momentous start, it drops to a desenlance awkward, hopelessly untapped. Even so, entertains. Or my movie buff corazoncito, steeped in Christmas, ho ho ho, have been light and is porous as a Magdalene in a cafe.</summary>
	<body>Stephen King is an inexhaustible hotbed of arguments. In a sense, King makes the demanding reader of literature forgive its (often smear of rush and poorly refined) form in style and logistical resources and gives up without hesitation in the background to this formidable barque of stories that we are well accustomed. Why 1408 is Stephen King to 100%: because the film inherits the vices and the successes of the master of horror short narrative and proposed, in a format more television than film, an orgiastic and recommended income in fear, in the certainty that everything that surrounds us can conjure up against us and make us suffer the most intolerable hell.Order fantastic entertainment has been severely strained by the quality of the products it intended to recover as a genre worthy and relevant. It is not that this room 1408 is going to substantially change this evidence, but helps greening a style of doing things which made it more wisely than anything else while we not contemplábamos. More consistent to the story to what Hitchcock or an episode of midnight Twilight Zone to the feature film that can come very long tape entertains a lot, teaches his letters as soon as start and never stealing the spectator the feeling to be attending an entertaining and intriguing tour de force between a screenwriter (King) overheated imagination(, background) and reality, always plumbate, always paid to the routine and lukewarm to manipulate, alter, decompose, sometimes rot.It is not, despite what was written, an outstanding film. We even give a remarkable. Convinces the innocence of his proposal, with its precious metalwork domestic, for his indisimulado effort to open new chapter in the hypothetical Manual of Terror in the 21st century, book forcibly reviled, enfangado Hostel, Saw, and other chabacanas inquiries in the morbid and the lust of the stump and the entrails hanging from a chandelier lamp. Why 1408 produces us that Nice blushing cheeks: by not resorting to clichés and return to the classics, to the Nice - and we are talking about terror - tape that we left cheerful while we delivered.When everything could enlist in the parody, the movie takes flight and takes really seriously. The story of the writer in low hours who decides to specialize in disassemble esoteric renditions of haunted rooms, urban legends sound difficult to digest and several spells and discovers that the religion which denies has sanctuary, altar and up rigorous officiating (a measured here John Cusack) is nothing more than the history of the priest King, used when you want the writer as alter ego, as passion of his irregular but attractive hero work. Mikael Hafstrom runs without frills, without establishing a personal way and without falling into clichés that could have burdened the end result being at all times an aseptic worker, an efficient Manager of the material that has fallen between hands and is not at all negligible.Armed of good intentions, is lost in traps that angry gourmet of these rare dishes between the dreams and the Kafkaesque fantasy, seen what skill should be to get out of these three parameters something that hook and does not fall in frivolities, cursiladas or poor exercise of teen horror coated transcendence. Until the end removes any possibility of ambiguity - blessed, sometimes - and disarm us the fabulation to which we have been subjected for eighty minutes. He comes to tell that Milton has truly been in paradise and to prove it he has brought a rose.How naive we believe.How nice that is the cinema.</body>
</review>
