<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La Búsqueda: El Diario Secreto" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More of the same, but at worst. Already.</summary>
	<body>To say of those who look forward with stories as counted here, search 1.0 (delivery Disney affiliate fashion of Templars, treasures and various Rosicrucians) meant a fresh air in the languid picture of teen movies with pretensions of liven up the eventual adult. I agree with that the the one point zero left me a pleasing impression because I recognized an interest in renewing the genre and produce something always desirable: that people go to the movies and leave with the deep feeling that has not been misled and that the time, among the many that disfigure us life, has been pleasant and even advisable. I understand that sometimes just what I say to that film, understood as pure evasion, hold itself only the fragile building of leisure in this our age of Plenipotentiary gadgets, broadband in the pocket of the jacket and downloads of speed adrenalítica another effortlessly than a desultory click. So I went to see this two zero point delivery with a sincere enthusiasm saca. I knew that they could give me cat for a ride, as it is; I knew that the savvy geniuses of the Disney could ride a theme in the form of frame Park, a kind of Shrine of the loop: everything that has been tested and has given results should not be changed. In the absence of lavish treasures (which there are, how not) it was to find an unexpected twist, an ACE in the jewelled manga of the chieftains of the producer, which did not hesitate to throw checkbook to bring Helen Mirren or Ed Harris, who along with Jon Voight or Nicolas Cage collaborating to movie buff package (Oh, what hyperbole) the then provable engendrillo. What, ultimately, is check a free family film of folds, well packaged and adorned with a livianísimo Fund enciclópedico of cultured aftertaste and, ultimately, easily removable. What was once a passion for archaeology, mixture of Kipling, London, the better Verne and up a blade of Indiana Jones urbanite, here is a Christmas filler not completely negligible, but repeated ad nauseam and lacking, behold the true pain of the sanísimo spirit of adventure of the first franchise. They have failed or have not wanted to give a stronger dramatic body and have conformed with present situations that do not differ little from those already referred to in the work which opens the series (since there are more searches, was please this) and that are also based on pillars of very weak credibility (that seek the lost honour and restore the name to the place it deserves in the history)(this is what has to be, that there cannot be enter in this domestic review).The patriotic stench does not leave the sensitive spectator to be swayed by the mere fascination of the ups and downs of the adventure: there is an excess of montuno nationalism that threatens a minimum sense of that story which push us as if it were a chapter from the diary of session of the Congress of the United States of America. In the absence of several centuries of history, the American people amplifies title of show that theirs, yet succinct, has to deal with pages in school text books. There is in this film a unbearable (at times) hodgepodge of chapters, to engage, creaking in excess and disorient the reasonable monitoring of the only truly important thing: entertain without handle, offer a decent show (nor is it is not) without offending who, apart from the necessary dose of evasion, want the required training. It is one thing to not tell the truth and another, quite different, symbolically punishable carried to its extreme, seeking to sneak us butterflies in flight when what is perched on the ground is a advises and nothing orchestrated mob of flies. Deception, the little effort of the managers of the plot, is also the fragility that confront us the tracks, keys, secrets revealed and leading to the final pirotecnica, not tell here, but that solves Turteltaub with the same aquatic and Baroque texture with that finiquitaba the previous delivery. Jerry Bruckheimer, the new Midas visual pirotecnica and the greedy box office, has put his eye divine on a product of proven acceptance between the épila and even the sometimes little demanding section adult. It is unforgivable that the movie purchase vigor and get contaminated by the same excellent sins when we already have an hour of footage from the first: up there all bored, everything gets carried away by a not knowing what to do that it exacerbates the avid action public and it helps to forget this misleading Christmas candy of family spirit and commercial breath until boredom ahead of schedule. Only (repeat) the concoction becomes a lasting taste when the action runs and the characters (lacking a real link, pushed to move in the plot as soldiers, as vapid puppets) enter in caves (Mount Rushmore) that hidden passageways, traps, keys and - ultimately - the Opera and guignolesca retahila of archetypes that usually adorn all films of the genre. The entering the oval office for the face and reckless daring walk by Buckhingham Palace without the witless police machinery of his Majesty alert of the mess sounds like excess, it take a Parliament of you to you with the President of the United States and abduct him for three minutes for him to become entangled in a viscous matter sounds to roll the House brand Disney. Hence this modestly sensation (one is good, basically) to feel disappointed, reasonably disappointed. Read more: all the treasures that appear in these films, friendly and patient reader, are in caves. Up there everything perfect. Mother nature cela basements unfathomable, others to the intrusion of curious citizens to the casual managed of an inspired treasure hunter, and scale all the treasures (repeat) are for centuries the uncomfortable eye safe and waiting to Nicolas Cage, what hair, what gestures, and that everything crumbles. Up the ad hoc in a wonderful well since oil and it enlightens the roost sounds added formidably animated fantasy of yesterday and today. I can not help (a couple of days ago I saw) remember laughter (I just, without that nobody backed me) gave when Indians gold illuminated the room screen. What fill. What appalling tired. What grotesque. Do want to make money and what effort justify the ganancia.addenda: and I have had none of the 47 page, but that is already part of the 3.0 delivery and that will come with the next polvorones.</body>
</review>
