<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="American Gangster" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>American gangster gift us with both points of view, both worlds, so close yet so distant in reality. For me, one of the best films of this year.</summary>
	<body>Directed by the now Sir Ridley Scott, able to gift us with real director wonders (the duellists, Alien, Blade runner, Thelma and Louise) or infumables clunkers (the Lieutenant O'Neil, Gladiator, Hannibal, the Kingdom of the heavens), US American Gangster, movie co-starring Russell Crowe and Denzel Washington, which also boasts some side luxury such as Josh BrolinChiwetel Ejiofor and Jon Polito among others.The film we located in the Harlem of the seventies, where the driver of the main mobster of the area decided to monopolize the market for heroin in the neighborhood, extending their networks to the length and breadth of United States making it one of the older history drug traffickers. For its part, a not too popular police will seek to discover of desenmascaralo, and thus uncover the network of police corruption that makes impossible any attempt to put an end to the traffic of drugs in the country.With a length of just over two hours and a half, American gangster is the second foray of Ridley Scott in the dark and profitable world of the mafia after Black rain. And is that American gangster is a mixture of the big titles of the genre, as if Tony Montana from the price of power turn out to become Michael Corleane of the Godfather, in a game of the policeman and the thief in which the characters of Heat and Sérpico recreate French Connection. Thus, can that after saying this American gansgster may sound like a rehash, but señor@s, beans often. In the absence of watch movies as No country for old or Sweeney Todd, I believe that on this occasion the British deserve once and for all the statuette.Going to the movie itself, applies to American gangster covers from the origins of the mafioso Josh Lucas until his arrest, covering a period of fairly broad time, perhaps not so much in Zodiac, but substantial enough to justify its mammoth length. Thus, a server barely dare to eliminate a couple of inconsequential scenes, taking into account that the Assembly of the film is simply perfect.On the other hand, the interpretative duel between Denzel Washington and Russell Crowe is worthy of mention, while the main scourge of the Ridley Scott film lie precisely there, in a possible lack of nerve, in the lack of peak moments over a marathon footage, but thus and everything at any time American gangster allows us take us off of the screen. With a taste of cinema of gangsters between classic and setentero, the movie takes its time to show us both mental and professional evolution of both characters until finally intercrossing their destinations, although, as in Heat, will be fairly complex to see them sharing level.Thus, American gangster gift us with both points of view, both worlds, so close yet so distant indeed, constantly playing with this inherent duality, offering us a duel, so to speak, between Tony Montana and Frank Serpico in a single film. A wonderful film that, as I said, perhaps you lack some nerve (read bad milk), something of Sidney Lumet or, why not, Sam Peckinpah, but by no means less round.For me, one of the best films of this year.I give a 8'5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
