<review author="Andrés Pons" title="El hombre de mimbre" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I just remember the reason for my love of Padre this genus with one of the masterpieces not only British horror but the film in general.</summary>
	<body>Do you know? Sometimes one can lose perspective of what is true horror film, you go to the film premieres where you have the same approach over and over again. Direct releases to DVD are the most often copies of recent successes where taught four tits something Gore bad miss and so classified us in horror film when it is not or film of any kind.I just remember the because of my perpetual love this not only genre with one of the masterpieces of British horror cinema in general if not.ROBIN HARDY is one of those strange cases of an author that performs a Magnum Opus to disappear without a trace except for some small TV as for example the otherworldly.A sensational cast at all times helps the plot with the Dracula CHRISTOPHER LEE or the SEX SIMBOL BRITT EKLAND who at that time lived stardom in work featured in the genus with macabre refuge or night without end. Without forgetting the great actor protagonist that his role as religious man in the face of EDWARD WOODWARD seen in young WINSTON or the current outboard fatal weapon.This is one of those films that his debut did not deserved being the passage of time that ultimately impact her placed in the large jewel which is today. Unclassifiable moments where it is mixed intrigue, terror and even the music with an elegance rarely seen. Also be reflex masterfully Pagan beliefs and HIPPIES communities helped with a mammoth soundtrack reminiscent to CORAL records.Adoradoras naked nymphs of sex, cruelty at all times with a duel between the superstitions and Christian faith, its enormous photography is another claim into a feature film that no doubt is left marked to fire in the retina of the Viewer.The Remake of the same name starring NICOLAS CAGE is a joke, the director ROBIN HARDY will again count on CHRISTOPHER LEE in 2008 with COMBOYS FOR CHRIST.</body>
</review>
