<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Soy leyenda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good, good film, which could have been very good and even wonderful if it had not fallen into misfortune of wanting to twinning undeniable success in box office and exclusively goer taste. As if it were impossible to twinning quality and pasta.</summary>
	<body>The apocalyptic story often adorn messianic prose biblical passages and iconography medievalist. Even the eschatological story, the book of the end of times long-caressed by all enlightened literature since the Apostles until this betrayed Matheson, requires a component mystical, religious or spiritual than war. And here, in this poetic sense, is where I am Legend displays their best weapons, their heightened respect for the beauty of a few absolutely hypnotic images, shot to the memory of a fed enough of enduring scenes spectator to be very critical when it comes to expand the hard disk and allow some few megs more plasticity. To I am Legend spare you plasticity, him too much honesty and have too you melancholy. Lacks it perhaps everything else. Francis Lawrence film is not much less a round work. Lacks an internal order that justified: there are sections of scandalous tedium, episodes credited to apathy, blunt boasts of pure nihilism. Who go to the cinema to see a display of special effects, a lesson in action with bottom of popcorn cinema will not find what you want. Hollywood has gone by the tangent with this installment of minimalist cinema, indie almost, amateur, although charged with the necessary budget and marketing seasonings to give the pitch at the box office, but neither this I have it clear after having enjoyed (and reviled in equal parts) commitment. Or dreadful action or psychological Interior, and Lawrence has drawn a fine middle way not just convince those that opt for these two vertices in a way difficult to converge. The devastated New York City shot like never before: that perhaps the claim that hunt the unsuspecting Viewer, who (like me) it has not hurgado in the literature, hagiography, in the milestone in science fiction intrahistoria, conducted (appears for the third time, I'm not definitely put in the subject) to the big screen. The film fails in the recreation of the action you want to uniquely link to be the blockbuster of bells. Vampiric creatures are only a start in the already if decelerada plot. These zombies smell lab too much: as if those responsible for the technical side had decided to downplay any possibility of credible, of humanity, say. In fact therein lies, in my opinion, the most unacceptable missteps: abandonment (I have no doubt that intentional) of the reasons of evil, of the reasons for the Wolf, as you would say the classic tale. I am legend is a story about loneliness of man. Gives equal which is represented on the rubble of Manhattan that in half of a carpeted Avenue of pedestrians. Loneliness considered an instrument of madness, loneliness even as a perversion of the modern society which has produced the evil which has demolished their strongest moral and civic principles. Neville (an immeasurable Will Smith) scientist has created a universe around his crusade: going to the video store and executes with impeccable rigor mechanical acts all do when we go to the video store. The mannequins are disturbing and anticipate the true image of the world: a huge chessboard where an adversary has been reduced to a single piece. There are no metaphors beyond the strictly permissible: the film scales among its commercial vocation and its undeniable intimate pull between certain open-minded moviegoers who will come to the film to devour images, digest them later and not be contaminated by any current of opinion that steal them formidable have discovered pleasure (themselves), the misery and the glorythe pain and the joy. All that there is in this ambitious (and ambitious, failed) modern horrors and psychologies of apocalyptic avant-garde film. Intermediate politically correct: Papa Bush sail by our dreams. His heroes filmed at 24 frames per second and even dare, in the solitude of a cellar, in the grim certainty of a dismembered world, to come up with the definitive antidote, a kind of masterful multicultural Coca-Cola formula. It will Smith contributes to the purpose with good manners that often lately and seems fantastic demiurge of a world made up to suit. To say of those who adore the book by Richard Matheson I am legend is a fiasco. Probably. I have not had the pleasure of reading it. I have known of its existence after the usual fire of artifice of advertising and its unstoppable propaganda machine. And I saw her on notice, aware my purity of spirit and a complete lack of expectations. Perhaps the best way to watch movies. A to which not always we pay when we went to the room and we give to the miracle of the figurative representation of life. Then left perplexed: halfway between the fascination of images and the boredom of a plot Misty, devotee of a cumbersome specific of what could have been counted in much less time. As is a television episode of quality on a cable channel. There is light outside.</body>
</review>
