<review author="Estesoyo" title="Juegos secretos" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A dramatic film of that time in when get to see... and that in the end you have an aftertaste they bitter, of the type: why milk habré had to see this thing? It was not more happy for a couple of hours?.</summary>
	<body>A drama film, which plays from time to time see. and that in the end you have left a bitter aftertaste, of the type: ' why milk habré had to see this thing? It was not happy for a couple of hours?'. In fact, it's another shitty movie that we have crept in through the back door.History us torture during more than two hours by mixing three miserable people's lives: a bitter husband is responsible for the care of his son while his wife works, a wife mother of a girl leading a bitter life and a pederast (without comments).The thing is that 'normal' fathers are lian by pure boredom (such as which has produced me this story) and almost just fugando, while the child molester just auto-castrando on the death of his mother. Joie de vivre, are going. So then say that al gore lovers are sick. ill will that has enjoyed with this story, I say.Well, the original title is 'Little Children' and I guess that it is a game on both parents to have a child, there is a pederast of means and that in the end, the real kid is the husband who stays at home with his son, it is unable to make a decision (and when making stays enbobado watching play teenagers and forget it)(go stupidity). Here is translated as "Secret games" to mislead a bit and see if you get something more public. I personally thought it would go with spies and why I swallowed her. Go slip, pardiéz.Kate Winslet is well in her role as bitter and wealthy housewife. because these fulanos not lack anything. It will bunch of scoundrels. Too bad that the story does not give more than Yes. The uncle, Patrick Wilson, I just do not fit, too similar to Paul Newman in a role of galán quite bland and repellent. The rest spend out there.As a curiosity, the film was nominated for 3 Academy, which demonstrates how different are the criteria of these Lords of mine. I will not bother to look if he won any.The director, Todd Field, has done a lot of things, so much as an actor as director. He has worked for television shooting many series, combining his task of director, actor and producer. I Fortunately, do not remember seeing any of their work.In short, another film amargante, sad and disgusting, that 'serious' criticisms tend to say that they are good movies, but here are zero stars.</body>
</review>
