<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="El espía" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The end result is, therefore, rather sweet and sour, that while the feeling of déjà vu is too explicit, and the television aspect of the film becomes even annoying, can neither deny that it makes you have a fun one...</summary>
	<body>Billy Ray, which debuted several years ago with little luck with "The price of truth", now directs "The spy" ("Breach"), which tells the true story of Robert Hansen, agent of the FBI religious and exemplary family guy that however was the most dangerous of the U.S., and how spy the also Eric Neill (Ryan Philippe) managed to unmask him posing as his employeehaving followed orders from the highest positions of a FBI wearing years followed the track.It all starts reasonably well. Interested in the script, Chris Cooper (Hansen) is excellent, winning the game by a landslide to Phillippe (as it was expected), and the presence of Laura Linney is, as always, a real pleasure for the senses rather than his character is completely flat and predictable. The address is not anything like the other world and peca too impersonality, turning the film into something that hardly stands out in a tv movie, but still are not heavy because it is always at the mercy of the script. Let the thing promises.The penalty is that everything stays there. It is not to fall the level, is simply not cares less for uploading it. When the character of Hansen is presented, offers very good expectations, and begins to break down in a very interesting way (comments of more coercive does on women at work just before entering a chapel are a clear example of the moral duality - or not - which proposes). In the same way, doubts that assail the character of Phillippe on the veracity of the complaint of the FBI to him come to convey to the Viewer, which though to know in advance how this will all end (the film opens with real after scenes of a spy arrest) cannot help but feel uncomfortable. But from there the equipment stops dry. We are witnessing something repetitive and stereotypical situations which continue outlining the obsessive religiosity of the suspect, and ultimately are only a rhythm of one already obstacle per se paused movie.Is true that also occur situations of tension, in that it seems that Hansen is about to discover the lid, but they are too predictable, and, as I say, they do not lead to anything. In the end, everything turns into a cluster of somewhat repetitive scenes that go slowly down the interest (without to lose at all, that Yes). Even the (rather cameo) presence of Dennis - President Palmer - Haysbert saves the furniture, because again we are talking about a completely untapped and flat, stereotyped character.At the end, it seems that someone will realize that there are already enough spent footage, for becomes it a rather hasty conclusion (not explain one of the aspects most critical of the real character, as it is his knowledge of the existence of a tunnel through which you could access with ease to the White House) that despite everything the Viewer it is rather a reliefwell then you already know that the film will not give more than Yes, and therefore he adds absolutely nothing new.The end result is, therefore, rather bittersweet, that while the feeling of déjà vu is too explicit, and the television movie aspect becomes even annoying, neither can deny that it makes you have a fun one, because it is solvent and sober, and contains a couple of scenes even worthy of mention. 5/10</body>
</review>
