<review author="Vsancha" title="Alatriste" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Alatriste is one of the saddest shows that one has seen in a movie theater. A heavy, very long and very expensive joke. At least now they may not say that that if money and media could do good cinema.</summary>
	<body>It is this something more than any premiere, days before, you can check with the news connecting live at the door of the cinema to see that you going there, the "President" of the Government and other authorities going to see the movie. And above all it shows when one goes to the movies and above is the premiere, isn't one film, there you find all kinds of viewers, fans of the books, making a truncheon on his favorite character, that moments before those we have seen in the section of literature of the same mall chatting about them. Do you can find even a "famous" local journalist, normal people who go alone, as a couple, with friends, in family with grandparents, grandchildren? There there is nobody. No one wanted to lose the umpteenth attempt to Spanish film.It had prepared the critique of "The girl in the water" but seeing what I saw last night I I could not resist to outline which is the most expensive movie in the history of the Spanish cinema. Alatriste is nonsense from beginning to end, without any kind of storyline, where witness scenes one after other, by which worst shot, and by which they appear, a long cast of well-known interpreters Spanish, and there has been great part of the grace of the film, see that actors make it worse. And in the meantime loose mamarracho and although the election has been difficult, the worst has been Eduardo Noriega that follows, and is not the only one, with its serious problem of diction, not be as pussy manages delivers it all the same uncle, but the funny thing is when we see his statements in the press conference of presentation of this disturbing filmin which she said that to know that his character had few words he decided to try to express it through its presence, its forms, and that it were these factors which define. A port and an expressiveness that has Eduardo or Marlon Brando.Eduardo has had stiff competition with Unax Ugalde, the poor, not be who will be told what actor. If I even putting desire he performed better. We also, I could not miss, free nude, appearing in every movie Spanish who boasts, this time by Elena Anaya which is to be welcomed. A chapter apart deserves the performance of Viggo Mortensen, whose election deal to portray Captain Alatriste seems very misguided, only understandable by marketing as claim abroad, the poor try but the character does not transmit a shit, not to create or him, he looks very content to Taming their Argentine accent, and at times, everytime I get on screenIt seems that he is drunk when he speaks. It was really unfortunate, more of one laugh managed to boot the spectators sitting in the Hall, that when understand you clearly is. Not be that work would have cost to bend him because his performance is really diminished by their accent, which makes it quite unnatural.The address is not that it is bad, is that it is non-existent, you need something more than personality behind a camera for a production of this caliber, what did Agustín Díaz Yanes, it seems that he has shot a trailer for 2 hours. A soundtrack of penalty, this soundtrack that seems you've already heard before in thousand movies, while above this very poorly integrated, many scenes where missing and others where spare. The battles are of penalty, there are No specialists in Spain?, but battles are those with four cats and very bad shot. And the picture, without being bad, comes to tire with both painting by Velázquez and both still life. To all this, already half of footage, you look for the thirtieth time clockwise and you think it cannot be, you think that you have stopped the clock, you take away and you save it to not suffer more.Both Alatriste is one of the saddest shows that one has seen in a movie theater. And it makes you ask me the reason for both compliment between the author of the work, Arturo Pérez Reverte, and responsible for "directing" this monstrosity, Agustín Díaz Yanes, and can only respond to a communion of interests. Alatriste is a heavy, very long and very expensive joke. At least now they may not say that that if money and media could do good cinema. Show.</body>
</review>
