<review author="Renegado" title="Beowulf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An entertaining story that bored, with good moments of action, not enough blood, and much heroic fantasy. Recommended as experience to see a different format on the big screen.</summary>
	<body>After a reasonable time of non-assistance to the cinemas because I am a person very very busy and, most importantly, that had not released anything to my liking (actually I wanted to go see "Halloween: the beginning", but my wife decided not to accompany me more when are films of the horror genre because, in his own words)(, "Enters into panic", and I do not I like going to the cinema only), I'm back in the ring.The film chosen in this case was, as says it in the title of the post that says there (read the title &hellip; top &hellip; there. eeeesa &hellip;).First and foremost (why is in the first place), should be noted that this film has no actors. I.e. it has, but they are not there. No, it is not a cachada. Of truth.Real actors only provided its physiognomy and their voices for, then, using a technique called "motion capture" (or "Performance capture" &hellip; in inglish, bicos ai spik inglish very guel okay?), be digitized, i.e. converted into virtual si figures themselves. Is it understood? Those who are on the screen are not real types, but some digital animations of the types. Seriously. I swear. It's crazy thing. The result of all this was a visually interesting product, big savings for producers with regard to costumes, set design, catering, life insurance and other things, and a way to original and distinct from presenting a classical epic story.Personally, it is not be hinchapelotas or anything of the sort, but I would have preferred a thousand times see her starring actors of flesh and blood.It is not be bad animation, on the contrary, it has a level of detail really so extraordinary that at times you forget what is actually being there; but on the other hand, and at other times, if one turns in fucking, get all the impression that back of a table will appear Shrek and the donkey and are going to make a joke.The issue with digital animation is that, without a doubt, it has become an essential tool in order to create magnificent scenery, impossible scenes or inconceivable creatures, but in their ability to grasp in its entirety the essence of the human figure, still you long way to go and in a production entirely done thus, it shows and pretty.Expressions, subtle gestures, texture and brightness of the skin and, fundamentally, the brightness of "life" of the eyes, are still far from both resemble reality as to get to the point of imitating to perfection (for my noted especially in the face of the Queen).With regard to the story itself, is based on an old English epic poem of over 3000 verses (one thing well half crappy type "El Cid Campeador" but there), written more or less for the first half of the century sees stick stick DC (after eating).It's a classical legend, sung from generation to generation, which chronicles the heroic adventures of the brave warrior Beowulf, a type so re pulenta, camorrero, egocentric and swaggering as the single, reaching the lands of King Hrothgar to liberate them from a monster rompebolas that walked out there killing people.The thing was more or less like this: is that he was King Hrothgar dele DELE celebrate with the bar of chums in a bolichón that had armed (with public funds, such as here) exclusively for use of quilombo and have fun in private there sucking, eating with the hand, burping with his mouth full, and voleteándose mines of airy life.In a moment, in any meeting of drunks, are put into singing and hitting the tables, which terribly annoying to Grendel, a deformed, slimy and ugly monster who lived in a cave as at 30 km. of distance but was more fussy than the shit with the subject of loud noises and people who sings. So much so that the bug this hot re sends to bowling to see if you can do them shut up a little.When he arrives, the door patova tells that it cannot let it pass because it's a private party, because it has no brand clothing and also because a type of more than two metres, deform, unclean, and it is falling to pieces does not fit the profile of the local Grendel responds to what descuartizando of a handshake.There just kicks the door, is sent to inside screaming (because shouts constantly in a very annoying way) and comes to kill, devour, gutting, and dismember the majority of those present, less to the King, to retire after making pasito murga.Hrothgar, when it recovers more or less of the fart that had and cagazo that stuck, offers half of the gold of his Kingdom to anyone that can free them of the cortamambo of Grendel. There is when Beowulf arrives (it is known that he is because all the time shouts "I am Beowulf!") with his boys, all hooligans equal to him, ready to fulfill the Mission (and incidentally suck free and make a tirito to the Queen which is girl) (and it looks eager).The thing is, indeed, at night a jodita arman, turn to suck as goats and made to sing again.Grendel listens to them and said "good Ah.!" But these guys are taking me to the chacota. Will now see! ", and get the farts willing to break everything again."Arriving, again begins to kill anyone who crosses, unless confronted with Beowulf which had been balls because it was very hot and, incidentally, to introduce you to the friend to the Queen. Are they interwoven in combat (in a clear insinuation of homosexual and that both are unnecessarily into balls, while Grendel does not have), and pineapple is, pineapple comes almost middle of fart, Beowulf defeats the monster and he also starts an arm (could make the horrible joke then Grendel is running for Governor of the region more important of the Kingdom, but I'm not going to do).Thanks to this fact, he is considered a hero and the King, in person, gives you award a species of chopp gold re lindo with a figure of a dragon and all.And if me are whoring up in Aramaic, that them recontra and withstand, because the film does not end there.The monster all shit sticks, manco and dying, returns to the cave tells everything to MOM and stretch the leg.The old, which apparently is a fucking recontra demonia, gets like crazy, because although had gone you for the ass like it was his only son, and flies to avenge covered at night and taking advantage of that they are all sleeping the mona.Dawn found the bowling of the King become a butcher, all covered in blood and guts.As a result, namely that the curse of the Kingdom will still persist while the mother of Grendel remains alive, the King tells Beowulf must go to confront it directly to his Lair, because but that he was going to look half bad for having received the award even without having completed their mission.Beowulf he complains:-crazy Eh, me cagaste! It was to kill one only. This is another dad-good price - says the King - if terminás with everything I leave the Kingdom, the Queen and the writing of my house in Punta. Do Ta well? - Dale - says Beowulf - Quedamo' machine as well.Spit the Palm and join hands to seal the deal.And up there, just the review.I do not follow that then walk not saying I tell the end and that.Anyway, isn't complicated taaaaaaan a plot that one not be account to the touch which comes hand in hand, but hey, just in case, veanlo for yourselves.As I said at the beginning, there is no action to analyze all the characters are generated by computer, but even so they were actors which is prestsaron to give them life and voice, be referred to by what you deserve (and incidentally to make identifiable them to see the movie).To Beowulf used it to Ray Winstone; the great Anthony Hopkins was King Hrothgar (sometimes it shows, sometimes not); John Malkovich was Unferth (although sometimes thought it was William Dafoe); Brendan Gleeson was Wiglaf, Crispin Hellion Glover made Grendel's (although well could have been either because to digitally create such deformed monster of the actor is not much), and finally, as a grand finale, as the dessert frutillita, to create the beautiful demoiníacamente Grendel mother, used to Angelina Jolie, who is so but so beautiful that even drawn is to give.The film was directed by Robert Zemeckis, that was her quite played to decide to do it in this format, but again, if the hubeira made with real actors would have been much better.Rating: 3 virtual forsaken (good.) An entertaining story that bored, with good moments of action, not enough blood, and much heroic fantasy. (Recommended as experience to see a different format on the big screen.)Recommendations: If you are half nerd and loves the medieval fantasy and video games, this is your movie. Don't miss her.If you don't like the film with many computer-generated special effects, no go. This whole movie is a great effect generated by computer.If you don't understand why the actors move medium rare and they appear with little life, it is because he does not pay attention, do not read the criticism and lives in a cloud of farts.If you are a man (or woman, some are also recorded) and when it comes on screen the OGRE mother based on Angelina Jolie, felt a true tingling and had morbid thoughts even knowing that it was a virtual character created in a computer, don't worry; We went to all.</body>
</review>
