<review author="Javier Martínez" title="La quimera del oro" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do Chaplin said that he would like to be remembered for this film, was his girl pampered above possibly best and most revolutionary tapes as?Modern times? or more emotional as?Limelight?.</summary>
	<body>What is true for a type that was not only a great director, but also a great actor, a great producer, a great musician, a great writer, &hellip;.? I do not believe that there has been no comprehensive one in the history of cinema. The only can do you shadow (and distance) is the great Orson Welles. This film cost a fortune at the time and almost ruins to Chaplin. It was perfectionist until sickly ends, what did they had to shoot shots over and over again until they were to their liking. But the truth is that you worth. Chaplin said that he would like to be remembered for this film, was his Darling above possibly best and most revolutionary as "Modern times" or more emotional as "Limelight" tapes.Charlie contracted the fever of gold and part to Alaska in search of a future better. When it is found that not all the mountain is oregano is trapped in a cabin in the middle of nothing with a murderer and a Hunter hungry Size XXL. I don't want to tell more, see it, your eyes become accustomed to the purity of the film in black and white, enjoy all these gags, the banquet-based, the dancing shoes of the rolls of the hurricane, the bear, everything. It is a comic epic, this man dressed as a tramp made the misfortunes of his time humor, people went to the Chambers and forgot of wars, famines, of dolores. Incarnate in him, in that poor Devil incapable of harming anyone, at the bubbler in the hands of fate were.I don't know if I do well to qualify "The gold rush" as humorous. It has adventures, romances, crying, philosophy, &hellip; it is simply perfect and made practically only.Finally I leave the scene where dinner his boots, masterful parody of a time where so many wars managed to almost 80% of the world's population thought imitate it.</body>
</review>
