<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Mr Brooks" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Correct thriller double personalities and hunt down the killer, that despite its flaws does not let be a relatively atypical entertainment given the times.</summary>
	<body>Kevin Costner returns with a dark thriller that plays the role of a successful businessman and family guy night giving vent to their terrible desires of blood and death. Demi Moore will be the inspector responsible for attempting to stem the tide of evil crimes which leads to this Mr Brooks.Bruce a. Evans proposal cannot draw attention for several reasons. First and foremost, because it assumed the reunion of Costner and Moore with the public (in recent years, it is difficult to see films in which one of the two to be protagonist, and they usually do not have much success at the box office), but also because the concept that the film seemed to offer a priori wanted original, very different from the thrillers that have been released in recent years.When it comes to the truth, that originality is true only in part, is ultimately what "Mr. Brooks" not more than a two-hour series "Dexter" chapter. But it does not mean necessarily something negative.If you take a look at the latest films of this genre, it is not difficult to see how same pattern is has been repeated with increasingly more emphasis, both visually and mounting. I am referring to the "CSI" series. So great is the success of this, that the nearly all film premieres drink with increasingly more brazenness of it.However "Mr. Brooks" chooses to completely change the tone, which is why in advance already represents a breath of fresh air among so overused gender. Visual sobriety and the rejection of the videocliperos mounts already mean major progress, but it is that also likened to something so much quality as "Dexter" does not imply more downside than the consequent lack of personality. But although Evans constantly plays with falling into a bland plagiarism, manages to avoid it by providing his film of a basic element to distinguish it, which is also a great success for the same. I am referring to Marshall, character played by William Hurt an excellent which is the incarnation of the madness of the protagonist, a kind of demonic guardian angel, alter ego who is calling him to continue killing. Dialogues between him (cynical and stinging) and Costner are certainly the best of the film, then give this Ribbon of distinction much-needed.It is mainly through these dialogues (and any more that it maintains with other side) understand the mentality of Mr Brooks, tormented man (by some, rather than correct interpretation of Costner) which recognizes addicted to murder. You don't like, but you can not stop by far that I try dismay is increasing while trying to avoid symptoms of weakness to their loved ones.At a more general level, the script maintains a fluid and constant pace, and manages to entertain despite its slow development. It can accuse him, that Yes, the inclusion of a cluster of secondary stories stretched in excess that, ultimately, bring absolutely nothing to the history major and only serve to hinder the pace and not finish developing the personality of the protagonist.What we have, because it is a proper thriller double personalities and hunt down the killer, that despite its flaws of being a relatively atypical entertainment given the timing that they run, and therefore none negligible. The question that leaves around me by the head is if "Mr. Brooks" existed do not "Dexter".</body>
</review>
