<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="La Búsqueda: El Diario Secreto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Epic action-adventure that keeps the pulse at all times and catch any viewer who knows to appreciate films of rapid consumption.</summary>
	<body>After the overwhelming success that was "The search", it was hoped that the Almighty Jerry Bruckheimer put hands to work on a sequel. And so, three years later, comes to our screens "La search 2: the book secret", in which not only repeats the entire team of the first part, if not who will be joining the poster names of the recently born Helen Mirren and the versatile Ed Harris.Esta time, Ben Gates (Cage) shall wash the name of one of his ancestorsaccused of being one of the conspirators in the assassination of President Lincoln. To do this, you must discover what secret behind the newspaper owned by the real killer, John Wilkes Booth, which speaks of a treasure of unheard proportions.If something works, why change it? This must have thought Bruckheimer, Turteltaub (director, again, of the function) and company, because they repeated this blockbuster adrenalítico and enhance both the strengths and the weaknesses of the first search. Starting with a completely absurd script (special mention for the impossible encounter of Gates with the President of the United States), is presented to us as an impressive whirlwind of crazy situations in constant ascending rhythm, that while the mere idea of take it seriously seems quite far-fetched, not less true is posed by little more than two hours of pure fun.Exciting action scenes translated in persecutions, shootings or floods encourage at all times the footage, making it inevitable not immerse himself in the adventure, by very reluctant to try and be one position.And that reasons for this are not lacking. The bizarre script should add some performances well below expected that only save the correct Harris and John Voight, which seem to be the only person who really knows where have gotten. Nicolas Cage returns to prove that his Oscar was a mere coincidence and gives a deplorable work as the main character. Its already usual grimaces rises to the nth, to be too unnerving (see his face after having been photographed by a video surveillance camera). And the same is true with Helen Mirren, which reduces their performance to a succession of shouts and exorbitant looks, as well as the rest of the side.In addition, "The book secret" fails to want to resemble too (especially in its final stretch) Indiana Jones trilogy because it pales before the superb masterpieces that once parieron Spielberg and Lucas.Pero as I said at the beginning, are details that remain hopelessly in the background, in pursuit of an epic action-adventure that keeps the pulse at all times and catch any viewer who knows to appreciate films of rapid consumption. Doesn't matter the nonsense of plot based (America continues Carlton Europe's history), if in return they offer us scenes as spectacular as the persecution by the alleys of England, or which he confronts his characters to a hanging platform.Scenes, these, who enjoy in detail, that Turteltab shows that gender and wheel known in elegant and strong, without complicating life with confusing montajesLa second part of "The search" comes well prepared to become the Christmas movie, which achieved with astonishing ease, something that translates in a continuous visual delight extremely entertaining. Refrain anyone wait a minimum of plot or acting quality, that Yes.</body>
</review>
