<review author="Luna" title="Irina Palm" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mariane Faithfull, the grandmother who does everything by his grandson in Irina Palm.</summary>
	<body>The second movie of Sam Garbarski had a good reception in the Berlin Festival in 2007 (a standing ovation after its projection predicted the best for this film) but in the end failed to do with the bear of gold against all odds.Its protagonist, Mariane Faithfull, has also garnered critical acclaim in his role of grandmother, as well as to be nominated as best actress for this role in the last edition of the European film awards, he also got.And is that in spite of the benefits of the film, as the correct direction of Garbarski or sober interpretation of Mariane, there are certain elements that does not leave you with a taste of "film round". For starters, the soundtrack does not help at all to the fluidity of the frame and impede, rather than facilitate, the passage of a sequence to another. Ghinzu fails to create a memorable soundtrack, in his debut as a composer of film soundtracks, and all that achieves is a reprise of the main theme that tires and hastia the viewer that it hinders the narration.In addition, the tape ends somewhat abruptly and with the typical "happy ending" so typical of American commercial films. The written script to 6 hands by Philippe Blasband, Sam Garbarski and Martin Herron begins with force but loses intensity and interest in the latter half to conclude, as I have already mentioned, of too sharply.Undeniably the film grabs the acting float of Mariane Faithful, who bears the weight of history, as the grandmother who sacrifices himself to get money for his sick grandson and so will do anything, even work in a sex-shop. He is the only character that the plot allows to develop as a whole, because of the other characters only have short sketches.In short, it's a nice movie about filial love that, despite its faults, will leave a good taste for those who dare to see it.</body>
</review>
