<review author="José A. Peig" title="Hook" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Synthesizing, the irregularity predominates in this film at all levels, while being an interesting magical tale about innocence lost and recovered, a product of entertainment that drinks from the musical and the disneyano universe.</summary>
	<body>Peter Banning is the model of the materialistic and stressed man who only lives for his work. In our society today there is much talk of children abandoned by irresponsible parents who have forgotten childhood, and implying having children and care for their needs. His son Jack reminds him that his problem is fear to fly, which goes beyond the literal interpretation in the filmic text (fear to go flying out of the window of the plane), as was already implicit in the original work of James Barrie; fly means to break the shackles with schemes, obligations and conventions of adults. Be a child does not mean to be irresponsible, but free, innocent and a bit malicious. Peter asks his son Jack to stop being a child and when the family comes to London to visit the home of Wendy, this requires a unique condition:!Children, let grow.! For Peter Banning it is already too late, even recalls his childhood and, moreover, the Wendy grandmother tells us one of the central themes: Peter, you've become a pirate. The pirate is a symbol of aggressive man that eyebrow not reaching their financial benefits at the expense of whatever. The subsequent sequence emphasizes that connection with a marked dream-like tone. London becomes a sinister city and nestled in the past, while Peter Banning ascends the stairs that lead up to the fourth child, - the old room of Wendy, John and Michael - and once inside he meets the image of the pirate ship and Captain Hook profile drawn on the walls of the room. Now, Peter and hook are one only. Banning is that kind of men that builds a wall of isolation to its around to ensure the material success, losing part of their humanity and deteriorating relations with his wife and children. The viewing of Spielberg is direct and concise, and not devoid of dramatic intensity from a circumstantial elements in appearance: Banning, in the Hall of the House, talking on the phone with one of his co-workers, whose profile is situated on the left side of the image, and in the background his wife and children running around and trying to encourage Peter to play with them. But Peter does not know to play, only interested in the money. A mild contrapicado emphasizes the isolation of Peter with regard to his family the shadow Jack projected onto the wall grows in tune with the irritation of Peter, unless the situation explodes in the final reprimand. After the revelation of Wendy (you are Peter Pan!) and the subsequent appearance of the fairy Tinker Bell, Banning travel to the country of Neverland, where will soon encounter a captain hook that is expressed with continuous laughing and ironies, isolated from his men, depressed and tired himself and live in Neverland, and obsessed with meet the child who did not want to growonly that it can return to give a raison d ' être (here there is no adventure). Hook pain is worse when he discovers that Peter has become something very similar to himself; Cod!. You do not are not the shadow of Peter Pan. In the country of Neverland, hook is a character so pathetic, as flatulent and so cartoonish as it was Banning in the real world. There is the antithesis between Peter and hook, that is why many people say: that is not Peter Pan!, as also says the own Banning. If you want to recover their children, Peter needs to learn to play, to sleep in the trees, to fight with the sword, to use the imagination, Crow and fly. But lost, insensitive and innocent, children recognize the enemy: all adults are pirates. Death to the lawyer!. Indeed, for them, there is not much difference between a lawyer and a pirate. This cannot be Peter Pan!.!! However, when one of the children playing with the face of Banning, stretching with the hands the contours of his rigid face, appears in the face of Banning the magic and insolent grin of the eternal child. Hence these, Peter!.!! But it was an image held hands, forced to the skepticism of Banning. There to help him recover the spontaneity. For its part, hook discovers that the best way to take revenge and attract to Peter Pan is to make children of Peter want you, that the children will forget his family, that they understand that their parents hate their children. Hook does nothing more than make explicit and carried its maximum impact Banning isolation with regard to his family. The misfortune of a father is, in fact, have had children, statement that reflects an attitude which hook and Banning share an affinity. In the imaginary dinner, and motivated by the leader of the lost boys (Rufio), Peter is learning to play, use the imagination, forget about "good manners" and freedom from the conventions of the well educated and bored adult who had become. Going slowly recovering the insolence and freedom, while hook comes with the small Jack to the Museum of broken clocks, place where hook aims to stop time and invites Jack to destroy all the clocks that enslaves the conscience of the adult represented the father: for not letting me do bubbles in chocolate! for not letting me jump in bed! do never anything with me!. In short, hook, as analogous to Banning character, uses his knowledge on the slavery of adults to exorcise and free Jack's influence and bad memories associated with his father. The better know your opponent better know where must attack him. This is how hook culminates its plan to manipulate the mind of Jack. The pirate baseball game, Banning discovers that hook has supplanted him as Jack's father. This causes a reaction in the consciousness of Banning, seeing that he has lost his son. You do not value what you have until you lose them. I have to learn to fly!.!! Find out when the consequences of the bad father who has been - and what supposed to be an adult who has completely lost its connection with the original innocence - is when it feels real need to change and to recover all lost. An accidental blow to the head, Banning is approaching a bed and contemplates with amazement, reflected in the waters, the image of the child who did not want to grow (and much attention to how the music of John Williams highlights the magic of that moment, one of the best melodies of this great composer, perfect evocation of nostalgia and childhood recovered). In this film, the innocence contained - and is thus symbolized - in a cup (as in the original work of J.) (Barrie). In the interior of the tree that was built to Wendy, Banning placed the Cup on his finger. Wendy. A Cup is a kiss. The innocence. I remember!. And once more the music of Williams immerses us in the nostalgia (Wendy sat in the rocking chair while he burst socks and told us stories) and even for a few seconds, Banning children is the children of all. Banning relive the past to understand the present. Peter Pan wanted to grow because the granddaughter of Wendy, he met and fell in love with her, and wanted to give him a kiss, but a kiss of truth. When the lips of Peter include Moyra, the finger of Peter loses his Cup, and is rolling on the ground, as the lost innocence. Peter wanted to grow and be a father, and that happy thinking that will make you fly and be free. Contrary to the established handling by hook and reinforced hitherto in the attitude of Banning, paternity - assumed aware and responsibly - can be a source of freedom. I found my happy thought!. Banning, even under the guise of pirate, contradicts to hook, and then is drawn on his face, the smile of the child happy and insolent (looking directly at the camera), and begins to rise, and flies, and, in a burst of magic that accompanies the revival of youth and adventure, the gesture and the unmistakable silhouette of Peter Pan appears emerging from the branches of the tree (with its suit freshly made juices of tree leaves)(, symbol of freedom and innocence, shedding the guise of pirate that symbolized the corruption of the adult man who hates her children), the blue of the sea bottom, and Peter rises towards the Sun. Again, in this sequence that begins with Peter emerging from the branches of the tree and until his arrival in the Sun, the soundtrack of Williams reinforces the significance of the image with emotion and although alone they are three few seconds, by the magnificent visual execution and what it means in relation to the narrated above, the image of the reborn Peter Pan that rises with its cheerful flight towards the Sun of NeverlandIt is one of the best Visual moments of entire Filmography of Steven Spielberg, in collaboration with the piece of music that accompanies it. Peter Pan is back!. The analogy between Peter and hook becomes the traditional antithesis, which hook may not use their knowledge of himself to disrupt the world of Peter and his family. In a way, hook always has represented a dark reflection of the same Peter Pan, noting the duality in the personality of Barrie, as they have claimed many analysts of the literary work. But Peter - and here we have an apparent internal inconsistency problem and in the speech - you have forgotten that his next adventure is to save them and their children. When Bell asks a kiss, Peter returns to resort to the Cup as a sign of innocence. But Bell calls a kiss of truth, and that Kiss returns to awaken the memories of Moyra and his paternity. Ran your adventures, Peter. It does not matter. However, to make clear that Hook is a film failed, and one of the most imperfect and frustrating of Spielberg, who attempted and intended to offer us a crepuscular Peter Pan to be the definitive Peter Pan for the history of cinema. The idea was good, a masterpiece potential, discover the child who did not want to grow from a decadent optics, and its revival after the understanding of the need to mature and be responsible. With this libérrima vision with respect to the original, Spielberg could speak of himself as updating the themes and designs that give way to the country of Neverland, being this one of his films more personal in which human being, so much that he wanted to offer, slipped her hands. And that it was not only intended to be intimate insight and a somewhat sinister re-reading the classic, but also a total spectacle. All this does not exclude the fact that - seventeen years after its premiere - remains a misunderstood and film, in part, underestimated, ignored by much of the public, tasted with nostalgia by others who saw in it the best possible Peter Pan update. In any case, Hook has two facets: family film entertainment and dense in concepts work. As film entertainment, although irregular, works pretty well. When it fails the Mise en scène, the soundtrack by John Williams guarantees the fun with a varied musical record which, at times, reach a few levels of adequacy to the image, the rhythms and bombastic sense that Spielberg intends to give to its history, exceeding everything imaginable. Apart from the examples mentioned in preceding paragraphs, is indispensable cited the sequence in which Smee (Bob Hoskins), followed by Peter Banning (Robin Williams) and an Entourage of pirates (Yes, Yes, the hook is here), carries the hook from the pirate village, passing through the gateway that ascends up to the ship and the room in which Captain Hook (Dustin Hoffman) expects to announce the news of the abduction of children. The score of Williams is a huge boost to the already on their enormous sense of the show showing Spielberg, taking maximum advantage of the bombast of the decor, especially in the case of a scene of pure transit. As work of introspection and personal analysis of the author, often critics noted internal inconsistencies, which, in the light of what I have already said, are quite relative, and that kind of trials they are rather fruit of errors in reading and interpretation of the text. Hook, indeed, is a film that has many objectives, and often the narration loses the fluidity, it stretches and will espesando into a megalomaniac story in which, especially in its final stretch, predominates the kitsch of the worst Spielberg. But the backbone that gives shape and meaning to history, under an eye attentive, comprehensive and freed from the prejudices caused by the desire to see a story true to the original work of J. Barrie, presents one more than acceptable development, as we have already explained in detail. And it should not be forgotten that Hook, as indicated by the title, is more a film about Captain hook that on Peter Pan. We insist: Peter Banning and hook are the same, and this analogy dominates most of the footage. Interestingly, the film loses much interest from the moment in which it appears Peter Pan, that thereafter he hoped a circus rather bland and insubstantial. Let us turn now to mention their most obvious defects; There are clear - and high-profile - errors of casting, as the election of Julia Roberts to play Bell. It is not only regrettable action actress, they the Bell character is virtually out of the story and this is an error in which the writers have part of the responsibility. And speaking of the script, in a work who walks among the lyrical fantasy and humor, dialogues and description of situations do not always keep the proper balance of tones, being very clever in some parts, and others are absolutely childish. But the more serious problem of Hook - and this would have been unthinkable, trying to Spielberg - is its irregularity in the Mise en scène. In certain passages, we run into a staging cold and empty, a default very well disguised - as we have already said - with energy, the bombast and the magic of the music of John Williams. In the first segment of the film, which takes place in London and the home of Wendy, impeccable Spielberg narrative fits into a dark atmosphere that implies the imminent arrival of hook. The mess starts when we arrived at Neverland and we find ourselves with a photograph of Dean Cundey. Photography is a crucial element for achieving the narrative quality, and is not otherwise used properly according to a meaning or a narrative intention lighting. It is important that a natural lighting filmmaker will create an abstraction depending on what you want to express. Unfortunately, in the scenes filmed in the pirate village and on the deck of the ship from hook, apparently the photographic work is limited to illuminate the scene with light, with which we have a world of impersonal Neverland, a spectacular and excessive decor without the abstraction characteristic to the worlds of fantasy and magic. This error damages especially in the final leg of the story, in the overwhelming battle between the pirates and the lost boys, and the subsequent duel between Peter and hook sword, but lacks meaning and dramatic force because of a colourful and absolutely banal image processing. Synthesizing, the irregularity predominates in this film at all levels, while being an interesting magical tale about innocence lost and recovered, a product of entertainment that drinks from the musical and the universe disneyano, a modernized vision of the original work that inspires, capable of significant things to say both to the mind of a child as an adult. Ideal in any case for Preparatoria - possibly with the heat of a fire - on dates Christmas, so conducive to return to our origins, to visit parents and grandparents, and remind the child that we were. </body>
</review>
