<review author="Rafa Marin" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Where there could be five films or series of interesting television we exhibited a showcase of scenes full of holes that might fill one day.</summary>
	<body>Let us recall once again the first law of William Goldman: the films are structure, and that structure is different and independent to the structure of a novel or a play. This structure must be above the literal adaptation of a book, that that is the style now, with the mania of being faithful to points and commas and minor characters and actions of filling, or, as it is done upstream in Alatriste, adapting in one movie several books at the same time (, I nor I do not understand why kills thus the goose that lays the golden eggs).And that is the great defect has, like movie, Alatriste. He fails the structure, and to fail the structure, the pieces do not intermarry as they should. Storytelling is, thus, deslavazada, suggesting too and telling little: we skip of the highlights of a book to the next, and leave you hanging scenes that are key to understanding the motivations of the characters, the historic surroundings, court intrigue: is a ride by the most emotive moments of the books, but full of holes which is whyThey lowered the great everyday gestures than the own Alatriste or wars colleagues and misfortunes are living: the suicide of the Portuguese, stabbing aboard the ship, economic sacrifice of Sebastian, the inability to release the accused sentenced to death, charges of Spy to Iñigo. In that look to the novels, we are also left with the desire to know something more of all these historical characters that appear as padding, making cameos of themselves and cameos of actors (too popular) that embody: the great camera Javier making count-Duke of Olivares (a point to admit that I always had seen him in the role of Góngora)(, who looks more), and the no less large Juanjo Echanove portraying a bitter and quarrelsome Quevedo, characterized so excessively that it seems almost a caricature of the poet.Therefore, neither Malatesta has the strength which should, nor the episode with the Duke of Buckingham importance later in the plot (as long as you cut the development of that episode). Angelica is practically well in the film, as long as it does not convey any idea of femme fatale and Elena Anaya performance not puts it above any pilinguilla number of institutes. Ariadna Gil makes Maria de Castro, a role that in another time would have fallen in Ana Belén. but Ariadna is not Ana Belén, I fear.They say that Arturo Pérez-Reverte, happy father, demanded that the film was shot in Spanish, for what that no one imagined Quevedo or own Alatriste speaking in another language. Interesting proposal which, from the outset, closes the doors to the export of the film more expensive cinema Spanish, as they have stressed us by active and passive since it began shooting, and perhaps even some nomination to the Oscar to the great Viggo Mortensen, which outboard his role (remedando poses of the own Pérez-Reverte?) Although his character does not dominate many times history as it shouldboth times the film becomes too much coral and steals too many minutes of prominence. Mortensen makes what can, and do well, hiding his South American accent, but unfortunately can not say the same damn direct sound and the declamativa capacity of the actresses, who does not understand half the time and it recite everything with the same College tonillo: is shameful that the beautiful Pilar López de Ayala has just four lines of dialogue and the four tell them evil. Nor means that the Inquisitor Bocanegra is interpreted by a woman who is recognized as Blanca Portillo at all times and whose voice is not camouflaged.The film thus becomes long because it is giving stumbled. The great moments (that is) are very diluted in a narrative that stretches: is an episodic film where the narrative jumps, paradoxically, fill her deadlocks. Despite its cost, noticeable gaps: the assault on the ship has already on deck, without that let us look at the boats climb aboard; the galleys with little conviction rema Iñigo are a closed set that even ranges and whose boat also obscures. Impeccable, historical reconstruction and lighting, suffer from the lack of a general plan to show us from the air the Madrid of the time. Very well choreographed and quite realistic to sword duels, although perhaps it has an excess of degüellos throughout the film (follow you account, because I lost).I said: that where there could be five films or series of interesting television we displayed a sample of scenes full of holes that might fill one day, as saying, "look what we do if stop us doing so". I am curious to see how the film at the Spanish box office and, above all, beyond our borders, which will be the only place where the pasta invested in this project can be recovered.</body>
</review>
