<review author="F. José Lorite" title="Réquiem por un sueño" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Stark dramatization of the fall to hell, where involving the spectator, making to produce havoc on the stronger stomachs, where squeezed them to fall with the characters.</summary>
	<body>Darren Aronofsky film based on the novel by Hubert Selby Jr. Aronofsky was the creator of the opera prima Pi, cult film for many that chronicles the neurotic life of a mathematician, and which won the prize for best direction at the Sundance Festival. We found a Director with concern to forge her own universe, he is considered one of the last masters of film tension, able to engulf the viewer and make it to grip to seat, as well as that you experience everything that feel the characters on their journey to self-destruction, and personal mutilamiénto, is an author able to the modern post avant-garde cinemacreating the aforementioned, his own universe.The work take on wheels flawless performances by actors many times in State of grace. Ellen Burstyn (Sara Goldfarb), represents the journey more complete and with which the viewer suffers, by embodying innocence consumed by it to say and be someone out in his means of personal liberation, television. He accompanies Jared Leto (Harry Goldfarb), son of Sara which already this hooked to drugs and who is representing the spiritual guide in the fall to hell, where he accompanies Jennifer Connelly (Marion Silver) pair of Harry, which represents an independent dressmaker who plays the abyss to sell his body to get drugs, losing part of their human condition to becoming like his fellow slaves of magical substancenext to them is also flawless interpretation friend Marlon Wayans (Tyrone C. Love).Together represent the history of Sara Goldfarb a greater, lonely and widowed women and that of Harry, his addicted and opportunistic son. Sara is suddenly nominated to compete in a television program. Excited at the prospect of becoming "someone" for appearing on TV, decides to do a strict diet. That is the only alternative if you want to attend the program with his old and lovely red dress, because their weight goes beyond measures of the dress. Meanwhile, Harry and the delicious Marion begin a relationship based on love, drugs and a life project away from the poor and abandoned semi of Coney Island beaches. To speed up the processes of "increase" of capital, Harry and his friend Tyronne C. Love become small dealers of hard drugs. The problem is that the product apart from sell it, they consume. Suddenly, the fate which had promised them another opportunity is belies and take another path away from their lives.The overwhelming pace increchento of the film introduces us to the world of drugs, which feels before and after having consumed using optical effects such as acceleration or deceleration of the image to your liking to create the environment and the sensations of consumption. Aronofsky raised an avant-garde realization that uses many daunting parallel mounts and mounts upward and rapid preparation and consumption of drugs that accompanied with a magnificent sound installation at certain moments almost musical that involves the Viewer to the maximum.Uses previously unused resources and above all not used so brilliantly, as the fact that divide in two the image to show us characters often separated by few centimetres and it gives you great emotional load, or the placement of the esteady cam, in the body of the character to represent the confusion of these. The overwhelming pace of Requiem for a dream is probably a strong indication of what he feels before the prick and what continues. It is not a film that promotes the use of drugs, as they were not Trainspotting, panic in Las Vegas or Drugstore Cowboy. Aronofsky, simply wants to convey the feeling that impacts on the human body before a dose of drug.The dizzying succession of images can deplete the unsuspecting Viewer. The speed in the Assembly, could transform into a nightmare or a migraine. If the viewer can overcome certain sequences of schizophrenic Court, enjoy a film, frantic, surprising and above all, uninhibited. Although those with sensitive stomach will have to abstain because that on many occasion it may offend sensibilities.</body>
</review>
