<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="1408" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With these credentials, it was impossible that this supernatural horror blockbuster fail, right? Then go if did it.</summary>
	<body>John Cusack often choose relatively well his films. More or less all his filmography is fumable, counting with small (or large) jewels as "High fidelity" or "Being John Malkovich", and when to choose productions of rapid consumption. well, there is "Con Air", which much to many people, mola cacho.Samuel l. Jackson is somewhat lost lately, but also tends to be an actor of those "if it goes on it, something has to have the movie".We go beyond. Stephen King is an author that despite not knowing how to write, tells stories that can hook, and most importantly, they sometimes get a movie more than acceptable ("La mile green", "The shining").And, Yes, the producers are the Weinstein, but still the director chosen for "1408" is Mikael Håfström, has a fucking great name that is valued him as "author", and that in the United States debuted with the (say) mediocre-but-well-done "without Control".With these credentials, it was impossible that this supernatural horror blockbuster fail, right? Then go if did it.We are in Los Angeles, where Mike Enslin (Cusack) wins the life writing books of terror on hotels or haunted houses. To make its work more realistic, the writer is installed one night in every damn room who discovers (through advertisements) and her looks with all kinds of objects. To date never happened anything supernatural or ghostly acojonante in general, until that discover that in New York the Dolphin hotel has a room "not available" for years. Despite the attempts at persuasion by the Manager of the hotel (Jackson), Enslin ends up doing with the key of the 1408, that hold you all sorts of scares and hallucinations.On this not too original premise, should recognize that the film has some graciosilla situation (mainly thanks to the dialogues between the two actors), and some other entertaining no more entering the room. The thing promises exactly what one is expected, a film of popcorn to see and forget instantly, that may be a good way to pass the time. However, after the first half hour, interest is lost completely, and the film just becoming a soporific game no feet or head that fails to convince even the most enthusiastic of the genre.There are many problems that lead to the film the most absolute collapse, although perhaps the most important and critical of all of them is that people change. I am thinking that a few years ago, when he started the boom of the terror of ghosts, apparitions, or comings of pot mental of the protagonist in general, the easier to get the sure shock was upload the music decibels and add them to a fast zoom or close-up of something shocking (either side of pale girl, or a giant snake). It worked so well that the movies that make use and abuse of this have multiplied like ants, and that has ended up creating an impassive public before this, that needs some encouragement that it compensated the cost of a ticket. Here, the stimulus does not exist. The only thing hidden is a double final twist, which is not only quite predictable, if not worth you the same problem I have just explained. Perhaps we are not tired already of the protagonist's dead from the beginning, is locked in an insane asylum and everything is fruit of his imagination, or that the murderer is the son who returns from the dead? According to King, Weinstein, and Håfström, seems that not.If it wasn't enough, another big problem that lastra all footage is that it comes from mother the twenty minutes, and delves into a spiral of impossibilities as gimmicky and rocambolescas changing abruptly the intimate tone of the film to put it squarely in catastrophism, from scenes of psychological horror to genuine natural carnage (always in the room)(eye). The idea seems a priori good, a pace in crescendo to generate increasingly difficult situations for the protagonist, but is everything so clumsily resolved that there literally is no where catch it.And also too hard for what it is. Avoid at all costs, he is without a doubt one of the great deceptions of the season.</body>
</review>
