<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="La Búsqueda: El Diario Secreto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>My advice: If you enjoyed the first it is possible that you repeat this. If you are absolute fan of the toupee of Cage, forward, happens without calling. If you want to see good movies look to see that they throw in Conference Room 3, possibly better.</summary>
	<body>I have to admit that the first part of the film was cinematically pretty bad not is surprising that the thing does not improve in the second. The script that tries to be a little more elaborate than its predecessor is even more bizarre and nonsensical but for an adventure film the thing is not very important. That Yes, while you may doubt the ability to film both can not lie and say that it has not in the first part of a tape because when you go to see films of adventures the thing is simple, there is action, there is humor, there is a certain plot and you spend a nice time. The search I was a surprise from the hands of the Disney (as pirates of the Caribbean but in smaller proportions) who clearly had to be continued. Benjamin Franklin Gates and his father after the first "treasure hunt" have managed to make a name in the scene and full conference one of the spectators accuses his grandfather to be part of the plot to kill Lincoln. Of course, one may have a toupee but family it is not touched. Why the first art equipment (including the funny companion) launches the adventure to assemble the pieces to unmask the real murderers and step, and if it arises, find fantastic treasures. So give back to the world making stop in the capitals of Europe and in some historic landscape of USA. Nicolas Cage, Diane Kruger, Jon Voight and Justin Bartha repeat, adds Ed Harris as bad malísimo, Harvey Keitel loose and off is the poly Tracker and Helen Mirren is the tape which alma en pena in search of some brilliant point that never comes. Bruce Greenwood plays the President, again, and it seems that with a view to staying with a role in the next installment.The Ribbon is loose, really tightly follows the scheme of each film of Jerry Bruckheimer, track after track, persecution, action, shooting, simpleton humor, spectacular levels, any explosion, &hellip; a formula has furthermore managed to get to the palomitero public in the Pocket. Obviously nothing seems real or realistic, is fanciful in excess and leaves you with a feeling of pride for being American, &hellip; wait, I'm not American, &hellip; what disgust!My advice: If you enjoyed the first it is possible that you repeat this. If you are absolute fan of the toupee of Cage, forward, happens without calling. If you want to see good movies look to see that they throw in Conference Room 3, possibly better. If you think that Cage always acts with the face of chard, the thing does not change this.</body>
</review>
