<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Los Cien Pasos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I Cento Passi is almost a political pamphlet and a declaration of intent mixed with a reality of Italian culture that still nowadays seek to fight.</summary>
	<body>I Cento Passi reflects the Sicilian idiosyncrasy. If think that the regions in Spain have marked differences go to Italy is a parallel world. The first thing that comes to mind when we say Sicily is "mafia" as to not disappoint us this story it has their dose of mafia, the Communists and their opposing ideologies. It is another worthy work of political and historical film narrated once more similarly to the view in other recent tapes as "My brother is only son", children, young and idealistic. Peppino Impastato at young age realizes that political thoughts and the fighting of their elders have a direct impact in the society that surrounds him. The death of his uncle takes him to meet the Communist ideas of a painter to mark his future. Already an adult in the 1970s being Communist and convinced activist founded publications and a radio as a main vehicle for propaganda. Lives in Cinisi, a small town in the province of Palermo, known for the airport of Punta Raisi is in their vicinity and the powerful local mafia bosses use to their businesses. The hundred steps referred to in its title are separating his house of Tano Badalamenti. The greater the area boss and with which his family retains good relations based on silence and consent. Peppino with your revolutionary ideas and their way of making them public will get not only disturb the Mafiosi local if not to endanger his family and himself when finally decides to run in the election by Democrazia Proletaria.Los facts of the're film based on a true story and once again the death of Aldo Moro will mark the fate of the main characters of the same. It would be lying if not that of all Italian films on the subject is recognized that perhaps more extreme is shown and that as a result its effectiveness decreases. While others worry of finding a point means to express political concerns of its protagonists I Cento Passi take the figure of Giuseppe (Peppino is if diminutive in Italian) and her extols both their successes and their mistakes. Not to blame this weakness to director, writers or actors that for better or for worse in the late 1970s Italy were so raw and pronounced.I Cento Passi is almost a political pamphlet and a declaration of intent mixed with a reality of Italian culture that still nowadays seek to fight. While we conceive the mafia as her showed us American filmmakers in the country of the boot is something markedly different. Gangs are nothing more than families that little by little they have accumulated money from the time where nobody had neither to eat and have finally opted to keep his empire with the same methods of yesteryear while maintaining the smuggling and illegal to protect loved ones. I Cento Passi is the idea of Mafia as family, as protection and as a way of life in few tapes. For that reason alone already worth the viewing of their hundred fourteen minutes.Its judgement on the contrary is support from the middle of the tape in his political thinking stagnating to their characters and storytelling.</body>
</review>
