<review author="Silvia Giner" title="1408" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Scares, intrigue, and a thread of suspense that is maintained throughout the film and not that ironic comedy so original that only King point know give to their stories. Few horror movies get me in tension until the end.</summary>
	<body>The fact that this film is based on a Stephen King story "1408", is synonymous with that for very badly adapted the book, the film is going to be good, because let's be clear, no one as King to fill us with the minds of terror. And it is precisely with what plays this film with the mind.Before proceeding with the critics want to say (because I read other reviews) that seems absurdísimo the commentary that the film "is loaded with topic of horror movies", for God's sake. first is the adaptation of a book, i.e. to the clichés of having them because I honestly do not see them, they are given by the book not for the film based on this.Continued. scares, intrigue, and a thread of suspense that is keeping throughout the film and as that point of ironic comedy so original that only King can't give to their stories. Few horror movies manage to be in tension from the beginning until the end.Mike Enslin the protagonist this brilliantly-intrpretado by John Cusack, an excellent actor who we saw not long since in Spain almost none of his films have been released. Pre-production has 8 titles to be released in 2008, the quality of this actor is undisputed, is an actor who is autodirige, reason why probably Swedish director Mikael Håfström chose him as protagonist and experience for both has had satisfactory since both repeated in 2009 with SHANGHAI showing us a period of the ' 40s that revolves around an American expat who return to Shanghai in the months prior to the facts which occurred Pearl port, due to the death of his friend. So I look forward to this title, I believe that I deserve punishment see this couple together again.Mikael, has proven to be a director novell but with lots of talent and good operation of the camera.</body>
</review>
