<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="El Club de los Suicidas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One more, that it is more of the same, and that, following my boycott to the Spanish movies in theaters, I have done right thing leaving her DVD.</summary>
	<body>As I've said a couple of times on this blog, and it is that, we tear us vestments stating categorically how badly that works Spanish cinema, no wonder if what comes to screens is always bad, poorly shot movies worse planned and with arguments that (although surprising) fail to be consistent with what is finally displayed by the Viewer.Myself long ago I threw the towel, and reserve 90% of the Spanish film that opens directly to the DVD (alkyl, I see and appreciate), long decided to that if they (except for things like "The orphanage" "REC" and similar), not decide to risk, not I who leave the &euro; uros in similar patochadas.After my complaint number. I don't know, I've lost count, I commented a bit the movie (that's what I paid), say both Fernando Tejero and Lucía Jimenez have pointed out this kind of films, and that kind of characters, Lucia repeats the same role that we have seen it perform in the vast majority of the strips appearing and three quarters of the same can be said of Fernando Tejero, which, although as person I think a type of exceptional, as actor seems that he was going for big and that he stayed on the road, since that is the fourth or fifth time that I see do the same, okay, here cries sometimes, but it seems that from one moment to another will escape the "A little bit of please.".As regards secondary have Luis Callejo (who saw in "Princesses" of Aranoa) and Juanma Cifuentes television, perhaps the only tape that I have come to touch with his character, close the cast Cristina Alcázar (which we have seen in "Tell me") and the young Clara Lake, another who always repeated the role of troubled young.Something I always put special interest is soundtracks, and, as happens in much of the Spanish film, as follows!GENTLEMEN, a soundtrack for a Spanish film is not to put 2 or three known issues! (and ball point), I know that Roque baths must have calluses in the hands of make themes for movies, but I bet that in this country there are hundred of composers that could make themes for movies (and surely at a good price), do not always fall into the same mistakes.Anyway, that one more, that it is more of the same, and that, following my boycott to the Spanish movies in theaters, I have done right thing leaving her DVD.</body>
</review>
