<review author="Heitor Pan" title="The Nanny Diaries (Diario de una Niñera)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A study of the customs of the upper-class New Yorker serving principals to dissect a family where not working mothers are unable to take time for a child that grows in the arms of the nannies.</summary>
	<body>I believed that I was going to see a romantic comedy and is that no, advertisers, the creators of trailers or my own prejudices, I had cheated. Everything seemed that he wore until the genre: Scarlett Johansson in his most lovable version, cares for the child of a wealthy family while he falls in love with the good guy on duty, in this case Chris Evans, the human torch of "fantastic four". All this out of a novel usamericana written by females, the type of which parieron to Bridget Jones and the protagonists of "sex in New York". But all this was going a little further. Perhaps not too, but it is enough to have "A nanny diaries" more into account than in principle thought.Annie Braddock just graduating in anthropology and about to dive into the world of work, it is somewhat lost. His mother pushes her to you to succeed in life and become a woman powerful and self-sufficient, without making the mistakes that she has been able to fall and this is to abandon the utopian idea of anthropology and entering the business world.By chance Annie is an easy road, that passes by postponing any drastic decision about their future while performs a job easy and very well-paid, the nanny for one of the shoots of the typical wealthy family of the Upper East Side. So begins a study of the customs of the upper class New York serving the directors Shari Springer Berman and Robert Pulcini to dissect a family (it seems that) typical in these environments, with no working mothers who are unable to take time for a child that grows in the arms of the babysitter, while trying to please a husband that divides their interests between absorbent work and the lovers who are falling by the way.So the film is flowing between the situation comedy and family drama, aided by a few actors in absolute State of grace. Paul Giamatti and Laura Linney embody precisely this couple desencantada with life, which lives in the face of the Gallery, discusses cries at home while it exhibits the perfect smile at parties of society and becomes completely from a child with obvious emotional shortcomings. Linney outboard to the cool, elegant and neurotic Madam X and Paul Giamatti comes to be much more scary than many psychopaths of axe in hand in the role of Mr X, a cynical, distant and paid type of himself. Incredible camaleónica ability of this actor, which is revealing steady as one of the best side in recent times.Resultonas and comic scenes are alternating with social denunciation of this aseptically so that only the usamericanos are capable of achieving. Both the protagonist, a Scarlett Johansson that moves well in almost any environment, like the rest of side, read the aforementioned Chris Evans, singer Alicia Keys or the Donna Murphy television carry out their duties, making that the outcome will be very entertaining to perfection.So the film passes without a single but until the end, where the strange gland prevents American filmmakers finish off an argument with a bittersweet ending, returns to act. Walt Disney syndrome strikes again and it seems that the Yankee Viewer will suffer severe seizures if a movie left some storyline without his desired happy ending or if in a movie of science fiction or intrigue left something without explaining. So, finally, everyone learns the lesson and the lives of all pass by much more yellow tiles than when they started.Pity that they do not apply this to reality.</body>
</review>
