<review author="Illaq" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The problem of the film, in my opinion, is that you have to condense too many incidents in a very limited time</summary>
	<body>Just as who says, see Alatriste, a film that I liked and, at the same time, I was disappointed. I am not an expert in the art of "watching movies", but, rather, a voyeur film and, therefore, although this is, inevitably, a critique, it must be taken, preferably, as mere opinion and I believe that it would be desirable to see reflected other views, probably more expert in this field. In fact, it is difficult to conceptualize a production of this type, especially when one has read the literary work that serves as a basis, that is compressed in 147 minutes of film narration that, basically, is staying true to that. Naturally, the result is complex and controversial. As I see it (and as I see the literary work), Alatriste is a subterfuge to present the Spain of the 17TH century from the perspective of Diego Alatriste, far removed from the bubble of power while at the same time, linked to that bubble for a thousand reasons, giving it a special interest because diving in reality sociopolíticoculturalreligiosa of the timetrying to approaching it from the position of the Plebs of the time, although, inevitably, filter the view of someone today in the Maremagnum. Seems to me that Diego Alatriste, made of flesh and blood in Viggo Mortensen, is a reflection of Arturo Pérez-Reverte, father of the literary creature and, therefore, "grandfather" of the film, whose face court reminds me of Mortensen (obviously this is absolutely subjective). On the other hand, from my point of view, a film adaptation always a major problem to the viewer who has read the literary work which has served basis, because this is influencing the reader through the text to recreate it, imagining them, characters, scenes, situations and places, while the film narrative removes that step of the imagination of the viewer and, in return, aims to introduce it in the same action through the images. This problem is also the Director of the film and, logically, of all those who are involved in it. But we split. For starters, the atmosphere. Found me simply impressive. It should bear in mind that it is a film of many different actions which link is the main character and that this not only does not remain in one place, they changed places, times and situations. As well, every place, every time and every situation has its setting itself, in my view, very wise. See, if not, these samples: photography, Paco Femenia, perhaps the most prominent element of the film. I do not think that any donkey is say that you give the film an impressive wealth of different atmospheres, according to the times, situations and places. Extraordinary countless games with light, which introduce the viewer in situations as varied as the blows of hand in Flanders, Madrid intrigues or the heat of the battles. On the music of Roque Baños gives me the feeling that integrates seamlessly into the work, which, in my view, is a success. For its part, Agustín Díaz Yanes, as screenwriter, has opted to offer a view of the life of Alatriste, for a few years, to the end, perhaps, of portraying the character in its multiple facets, while never being who is and who has been, which summarizes in his presentation Pérez-Reverte: wasn't the most honest man or the pious, but was a courageous man. Diego Alatriste and Tenorio was called, and he had fought as a soldier of the old thirds in the wars in Flanders. In my view, is in principle a merit, therein lies the fundamental problem of the film. In his role as director, Díaz Yanes outboard work: shots long, appropriate to the situations that presented and with the tone you want to print his story; measured camera movements, stunning scenery, hyperrealistic sequences, a set which conveys perfectly the harshness of the life of the soldier and the people, his tiny price, the existence of the powerful, tensions between them for their struggle for power, the street life, tavern, the Francos, the Inquisition, the fear, the tension of cavalry charges, the life of the (not so distant from today) infantryman... Even duels, that perhaps are short when we think of other movies, it is easy to respond more to the reality. What about the players? Obviously, there is talk of Viggo Mortensen: his performance is impeccable, because I think it conveys perfectly the "being" of Alatriste. At the beginning, you can "confuse" a little his diction (perhaps by the effect of the imagination of the exlector.), but fails to defacing the character. I would also highlight the performance of Blanca Portillo (fray Emilio Bocanegra, Inquisitor general), whose diction also me "despistó" and yet manages to convey, I believe that to perfection, the sinister character that represents. Very good performances by Antonio Pérez Dechent (partner of Alatriste), Nacho Pérez (Íñigo Balboa young), Unax Ugalde (Íñigo Balboa), Juan Echanove (Quevedo), Ariadna Gil (María de Castro), Elena Anaya (Alquézar Angelica), Javier Cámara (count-Duke of Olivares), Enrico Lo Verso (Malatesta). Somewhat blurred is Eduardo Noriega (count of Guadalmedina), although you may owe to the role. Maybe I forgot some characters, but these are those who remember better. Then, with so many virtues, is I why am disappointed? I have already mentioned that the problem of the film, in my opinion, is that you have to condense too many incidents in a very limited time. Changes in situation imposed by this excess break the pace and, in certain cases, I understand that they can get bored (not to me, certainly) and, of course, cannot hold the viewer in a vacuum (hence Yes). And that is a pity, because the effort is worthy of applause, but the end result was not, in my opinion, that would have liked. I have read some "very critical" criticism and not I who say that its author is not right. However, to me only I have to say that here. Ultimately, each viewer becomes his input and, together, are the spectators who have the last word.</body>
</review>
