<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Michael Clayton" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Absorbent, told simmered, intelligent and quite adult, debut as director Tony Gilroy is, above all, very correct, although it does not reach the level we all had hoped.</summary>
	<body>Absorbent, told simmered, intelligent and quite adult, debut as director Tony Gilroy is, above all, very correct, although it does not reach the level we all had hoped. Its effective script and two master interpretations of Clooney and Wilkinson make Michael Clayton another entertaining and contained proposal on human consciousness, the decisions we make in risky situations, the status of the current policy, etc. It sounds like a cliché nowadays, and it is, but its apparent tranquility that turns into a frenetic and wonderful final scenes is first and foremost, the most personal of this film.The film is presents us with a series of images that have little in common, which do confuse the viewer and at the same time going to this dark world of the advocacy and business corruption. Michael Clayton, a truly dark tone and expressive slow than the difference from all the other similar experiences that had hayámos has. Just has action scenes (a couple, if you count them) and everything that happens is overwhelming, a voltage camouflaged by its leisurely pace. The characters, very well written, change as the film progresses, suffer from an internal development that makes them more human and not so monotonous. The lawyer who makes drastic decisions as the accused who wants to freedom and truth above all are two fascinating portraits (somewhat similar) personality human, like the character of Tilda Swinton, although this will be the representative of the evil.After writing good scripts Tony Gilroy is placed after the cameras with a potent staging, although not too personal, managing to create a very entertaining movie, played incredibly well written and, however, contradictory, because to be produced by a downs as the Warner Brothers, one feels a bit of confusion to see what actual complaint Michael Clayton is the power of these companies in our society. Therefore, we have no doubt that money rules.</body>
</review>
