<review author="Kiko de España" title="Indiana Jones y el Reino de la Calavera de Cristal" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull is probably the best film which will provide us with the year that is dot to start.</summary>
	<body>I must admit that Indiana Jones and the last crusade, seen just before the latest installment. It is not aging well. It is the unique adventure of the doctor Jones with downtime and not tedious minutes but little busy. I remember that while revised could not stop thinking in this fourth part, give the stop to the dvd and plug this new adventure. that it discovers as the better and more authentic in the series.Let me: I love the search for the Ark and the damn Temple is megadivertida, but is that the very essence of adventure is concentrated in the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull. An (unexpected and majestic) Sean Connery prostrate in a wheelchair, drooling (but classy) puts us in a situation: 1951, Dr. Jones is prejubilado and amateur butt to beekeeping because he believes that can preserve the life of insects in the honey.One day, while the doctor take a NAP in your garden with the foot supported by a strange trunk, Mutt Williams, a musical representative of three to the fourth with a ridiculous mustache, it sneaks into the House to steal a microphone of gold, possession of the doctor, in an attempt to record a catchy single, the song of the summer, with his new signing.Indy has the dream lightweight he wakes and Williams flees on motorcycles until Indy, whip in hand, and with a few f/x left in his underwear to the Transformers, is mounted in the back seat. Then come the tributes and surprise: slope down and without brakes reach the 14th km/h and where they now had trams occurs a leafy pine forest. and a mysterious cave where attempts to hide the bird of prey. Once inside unleashes Madness: aliens, women malvadísimas as you've never seen and a final twist that you could never imagine that you read out there.Full of scatological humor (thought that eschatological linkearía at what Yes?) and without the usual moralina to which we are accustomed to its director, Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull is probably the best film which will provide us with the year that is dot to start.A 9'5, innocent! (see the day of publication of this criticism)</body>
</review>
