<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="El precio de la verdad" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you like the world of journalism and want to see something (based on a true story), it is worth keep an eye.</summary>
	<body>To which we are dedicated to a greater or lesser extent to this "write" this film, virtually unknown tells one of the things that we often face, you feel to the keyboard to write something (collaborated on a film page, another of monologues and a couple where I send some other news loose) and sometimes you like to "disguise the reality" to give another approachHow many times one has stopped before the keyboard thinking, perhaps, that the news was writing should not have happened so, that it had to have happened differently and that, unfortunately, you can not do anything to change it. !So is life! Every month as I have to submit different articles for the sites where work I think so what would happen if he completely changed the article I am writing? What would happen without rather than rely on accurate and concise information do so inventing me? This is what makes the protagonist of this film, played by Hayden Christensen "Anakin", in this film and we see how the thing goes from being a brilliant editor to be a pringao. It has seemed curious to see in the film criteria that are a priori not always respected when it comes to make a magazine in the light, not always checks if the information is true, the articles presented are not always read, and NI DE COÑA director defends death to drafters, rather click them to get of them 200% of what they publish. Bad times in this era of information. I know that it would have to give my opinion on the film and yet here I am releasing of what little I know of this scene, where is squeezed much staff and where few (if not none) are given opportunity to people who know, leaving than if do you the dropping of duty or the "sons of the." Once I I desquitado pleasure, I'll see if I can speak a little of the film, brilliantly shot and so pleasant, that the hour and 28 minutes of footage spent flying, perhaps as this negative note the drudgery of the soundtrack that accompanies almost the best moments and scenes of the same. The performances by the actors are excellent and the direction seems sober and at the same time effective, with a perfect picture. Anyway, if you like the world of journalism and want to see something (based on a true story), it is worthwhile to take a look. For me, without a doubt one of the biggest surprises of the year.</body>
</review>
