<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I would advise I am legend because, despite the rare occasions where the tape suggests ways with their dose of mystery and the balance with scenes of action, in the end always just deshinchando is not.</summary>
	<body>It is hard sometimes to elucidate the quality of a film based on the good or bad press received. In this case and after hearing their views on the last film of the fresh Prince of Bel Air buddies expected a hodgepodge of overwhelming dimensions, so perhaps did not seem so bad.I am legend is the title of a novel by Richard Matheson in 1954. It's about the last man alive in Los Angeles, after an epidemic which has transformed all humans into a species of vampires. It is a magnificent exercise quasi scientific that explains the progress of the only living man to kill the virus and its daily routine. If there is something funny is that as every science fiction book his distant future is already distant and that his work ambientaba a pandemic during the 1970s. Two films before the blockbuster dared to adapt this peculiar vampire film: The Last Man on Earth in 1964 with Vincent Price and the own Matheson script (but signed under pseudonym by disagreements with the producer; in 1971, the last living man only takes small threads of the original novel and Charlton Heston leaves the arduous task of fighting against the "mutant photosensitive" and to finish this new version that could have been done in) 90 with agarrense this is going to hurt, Arnold Schwarzenegger of protagonist and director Ridley Scott. Thanks to the stinginess of the producer not could carry out and thus Will Smith a decade later took over the role and starred in another taquillazo.In I am legend, Will Smith gives life to Robert Neville, a doctor and member of the army that it survives the mutation that occurs after the failed attempt of a cancer vaccine developed by the very same Emma Thompson which does not appear either in the credits. Those infected develop an allergy to the Sun that forces them to live at night and have authentic attraction to human blood. Neville in this case is not only a number of people who are immune to the virus (thing which never appears in the book). Besides their routine is more scientific than anything else, is not dedicated to go to hunt vampires as their counterparts in books or films if not that stays on the sidelines (and sober because now we all very politically correct) renting movies in his video store and radiating offer of help messages if someone drops by the film.If it is true that make a serious film with material of series B is risky. It is also true that the mutant "vampiros-zombies" - is not that they are holy in my devotion (especially if they resemble Lord Voldemort) and much less recycling of mutant dogs to the Resident Evil &hellip; but since then no one in the room who could resist the wonderful interpretation of Oscar (of the dog, of course). That Yes, I create a bit of uncertainty to know how people are able to enter and exit from Manhattan when they have destroyed bridges with as much joy and ease when at the beginning of the evacuation of all trapped although, of course, is not the only incongruity of the script. Otherwise Francis Lawrence does not bad bearing in mind that the only time that he has picked up a camera for something longer that to make a video clip of Britney Spears has been to Constantine but the truth the idea that could have fallen into the hands of Guillermo del Toro seemed much more appealing.Why a sense of "neither cold nor heat" will let you. The first part is much more exciting than the second when it focuses on the daily routine, in the anguish of spend the days glued to a clock escaping from the shadows. When the vampires make Act of presence and insinuating that they learn, risk and begin to be desperados begins a crash dive in the narrative even bored.I would advise I am legend because, despite the rare occasions where the tape suggests ways with their dose of mystery and the balance with scenes of action, in the end always just deshinchando is not.</body>
</review>
