<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Fred Claus: El Hermano Gamberro de Santa Claus" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fred Claus is expendable but possibly less annoying than the thirteenth part that wants to present Disney this Christmas.</summary>
	<body>The Christmas tinker are quite disappointing. And to the poster appear Vince Vaughn, Paul Giamatti, Rachel Weisz, Kevin Spacey, Kathy Bates, Miranda Richardson, or John Michael Higgins, is a hook that few film buffs can let go but is really like these traps for rabbits. You know that if you get to eat the carrot the door will fall and you will be locked in a cage waiting to receive the coup de grace. Fred is the older brother of Santa. As we all know the Saints remain frozen in time and all their relatives and spouses are benefited by this divine prerogative. But as el gordo San Nicolas is a good guy his older brother who has lived in its shadow from an early age has dedicated itself to spend hundreds of years malviviendo and wheeling and dealing while his younger brother earned the respect from the American base to leave gifts on Christmas Eve. But in the times or the Christmas business is safe and very bad bad Kevin Spacey person to make an inspection at the pole and close the snack bar. The happy event coincides with the forced Fred visit in search of money putting on silver platter the head of the fat man dressed in red.If we compare Fred Claus with the rest of the genre films possibly it come out well in some form despite his childish and white humor has what few others, i.e. this roster of actors that can make it more enjoyable and solvent. I must admit that there are three very entertaining moviegoers moments who managed to get me a sincere smile: the ninguneados brothers support group (self-criticism Baldwininana and the moment layer red himself Lex Luthor and a favorite for all antinavideños: the physical assault towards the figure of Santa Claus with uprooting of included head.)In short, Fred Claus is expendable but possibly less annoying than the thirteenth part that wants to present Disney this Christmas.</body>
</review>
