<review author="Bruji" title="Soy leyenda" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>?While New York sleeps?, Will Smith stands out in an innovative overproduction which gives emblematic images to the seventh art.</summary>
	<body>"While New York sleeps," Will Smith stresses in an innovative overproduction which gives emblematic images to the seventh art. A thriller of action and special effects, in perfect harmony with the script, and in any case recommended for owners and friends of German shepherds.In recent years, half of Europe has been suffering from the barbarian invasions of all kinds of viruses and retroviruses, of various origins, responsible for transforming into little recommended neighbors to the almost all of the population. Front of them, a small group of survivors trying to resist in places such as Germany (Resident Evil 1, 2, 3.), Great Britain (28 days later, 28 weeks later, do 28 years later?) or Spain ([Rec], the next day), in which health authorities, to activate the famous anti-terrorism Protocol, forgot that the father of the angelic snapper criaturita remained outside the sealed building. In each and every case, has to be understood "resist" in the literal sense of the word, by putting the effects of the technique of the script, making sure the box-office success of its thousands of followers in a critical and chronic situation in which an emergency plan B was never screened. The infected-in other times, human beings-are only a goal to break down within an argument clear in unusual message: none. Come the moment in which "We must enlighten the darkness", American cinema will be able to do so, much to us though, with greater intensity. Specifically, with something known as "overproduction", which doesn't hurt in clothes get special dispensation, unprecedented, to stop traffic in New York, recruiting members of the very same army as extras, and plan an actual evacuation of the island, with advice and supervision after cameras highest levels that make up the State security forces. This is America! As little money is still in the coffers, is does not hesitate to hire the best technical team of recent times: the Director of photography of the Lord of the Rings trilogy, the Director of special effects of Matrix, the writer of A wonderful mind. This is cinema! The excuse of such elaborate project, which gives a definitive solution to the pandemic that came to plague Europe unless it is able to lift head, found in a novel, I am Legend, 1954, signed by the writer Richard Matheson, who has two previous film adaptations. It is at this point that would make no sense compare and collate the final result of I am legend with its predecessors, history today discussed, disguised as hateful commercial cinema, being called, from the moment of its conception, to enter into the history of cinema by the front door. That nobody is RIP vestments still, because the explanation is easy to understand. The spectacular deployment of means which strengthens the multimillion-dollar production, excellent picture showing a Fifth Avenue, never seen, flooded vegetation, achieved air intakes that run the ghostly deserted city, the concentration of levels short increasing the anguished feeling of loneliness, the inestimable artistic direction based on the most chaotic of the anarquismos, successful flashback that brings consistency to the story; they would be written on the wind if the entirety of the footage did not have the livelihood of a solid script. Even more, if the synchronization between the images and the plot not rallara perfectly. Us continues to weigh, but we have to recognise that there the Americans know to illuminate the darkness. They are specialists in the genre of disasters, in situations to the limit, in atmospheres of real danger that can only be resolved by individual actions that characterize its own personality. Is not enough to combat the infected, we must heal them, you have to risk the physical integrity of the super hero, that - how could it be otherwise-, is a prestigious scientist, military expert, perfect father and husband and, as if all this were little, exemplary lover of animals. Can you ask something else?. Yes, and we have. An involution in the world of feelings, the special inner journey that any human being experiences after a cathartic process in his life. "God not has done this, but us", and not they scared us monsters cry hipohuracando coming out of a bad version of the Mummy, but the fact of knowing that there are no days off for the thugs that are not persuaded by the power of a song. Despite us or not, it is necessary to admit that, among the many virtues of American cinema, is also that of knowing rummaging in the hearts, be able provide a ridiculous post-apocalyptic story of zombies in a revealing message. If something missing, the direction of casting stake by Will Smith, surrendering to his detractors (including myself) with a memorable performance. All this leads me to recall few times I have dared to recommend a film, but, in this case, what I would like to invite the reader movie buff to repair this. Do not be swayed by the refusal to produce the words "American blockbuster", thinking that paradise lost proposed Truffaut in Fahrenheit 451, and provide an opportunity to draw their own conclusions. Personally, I like to belong to the minority that is immune to the virus of hatred, xenophobia and racism. I like Shrek, and know that people just be them measured on the inside.</body>
</review>
