<review author="Andrés Pons" title="American Gangster" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that could be a masterpiece but lacks a couple of revolutions, a nerve in the realization that fails, emotion is conspicuous by its absence.</summary>
	<body>The friendship between two major HOLLYWOOD the great actor RUSSELL CROWE and director RIDLEY SCOTT irregular. He gave the spectacular than not great movie GLADIATOR and that nonsense called a good year.After that I guess that both had thought well a next collaboration. To not fail made sure to surround himself of other great actors, the always brilliant DENZEL WASHINGTON which has already demonstrated its great worth playing the villain with his escarizado role in day of training, the ascendant JOSH BROLIN that this year we saw in PLANET TERROR, or also by JERRY MAGUIRE CUBA GOODING JR oscar winner.A well-constructed script that recounts in a meticulous manner the gangsters operations to pass the goods on the one hand and on the other hand the police investigation a honest police bearing their motto up situations that border the surreal. The production of the film note of luxury in your invoice, the locker room, photography, music, everything helps beautifully recreate the era of the 70.Con all those means, a good director after the cameras, some of the best performers of the time giving the gift of chest, one of those epic stories of Ascension to power that both like in HOLLYWOODthe result should be touching the outstanding. Because neither approaches, by the topic has many points in common with the Godfather saga, there was the Sicilian mafia and here the greatest gangster color. Gentlemen; RIDLEY SCOTT is not COPPOLA nor did get to the soles of the shoes as much at the beginning of his career signed two of the greatest masterpieces of science fiction in Alien and Blade Runner. Because his later filmography has disasters of the caliber of the Grifters, a good year GI JANE. By all these titles showed that this man is a great distance from the best teachers.Obviously a pardillo is not and know when it wants to offer a great wrapper but occasionally when unfolds the wrapper there is inside it is not for both.A film that could be a masterpiece but lacks a couple of revolutions, a nerve in the realization that fails, emotion is conspicuous by its absence. In a few words it takes more courage to tell something so hard and it impact of truth, since no scene of this correct film comes to knock out the viewer being his greater sin the boredom that takes over in the room as it progresses the footage.Ultimately a film deslumbrantemente submitted that it lacks the necessary to become great epic and that is not bought with money.</body>
</review>
