<review author="Andrés Pons" title="August Underground" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are other two continuations you miss by the same team and the third is the best because the delayed learned that it should leave the still camera so that at least we know what happens.</summary>
	<body>Sometimes I say, why not me along with four crackpots and shoot something? Do not I have no idea of directing? So what?I could shit on top of a type and then force him to eat her own shit, also we get if the situation so requires in a residence. We violaríamos some elderly women, we vomitamos them above, also eaten the vomiting.Since then nothing of script, so noticeable that it is amateur apparently gives very bad feeling neither assemble and distribution or anything at all. The camera will move as if fastened by a lame monkey.After some Nutter network will discover you, then I encumbrará author of cult, a type that without a budget and with other psychopaths to made a work of art.That is what happens with FRED VOGEL and his colleagues, not disgusts me the mutilation, shit, vomiting or violations of the film, the nene has already seen mondos of all kinds, sagas GORES as GUINEA PIG, swallow me and no need to bicarbonate. Maybe this quite sick or simply not it impresses me as nothing, but I am still not so bad to do this and believe me director.¿Saben what really disgusts me? What really shocked me and made me vomit? As a piece of meat with brain filled with shit say director if same as some talk of these terrorists and regarded as them filmmakers.It is not film, it has no script or anything to grab, it has no actors, it has no music and has not the slightest glimmer of human intelligence, that is shot by a few animals wanting to give the note, precisely this kind of people are what give bad name Al Gore because the garbage with a head does not give them to think that in that genre also occasionally you need to have something to tell.There are other two continuations you miss by the same team and the third is the best because the delayed learned that it should leave the still camera so that at least we know that pasa.¿Saben? They are considered authors of worship, some things are still beyond my mind.</body>
</review>
