<review author="Caty" title="Silent Hill" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another new fiasco in the conduct of a video game to the big screen</summary>
	<body>The day I found out, makes some years, who were going to make a film about the famous video game "Silent Hill" series have to confess something made me extremely alert: saga being that one of my favorites, with four games to everyone better and with a philosophy which had nothing to envy to many books or films, had the strange feeling of being before a new fiasco in the attempt once (up to exit something mildly decent) to try to bring a video game to the big screen. He spent with two deliveries of Resident Evil made for showcasing the "actress" Mila Jovovich, and looking backwards, with the infumables "Street Fighter", "Mario Bros", not to mention of course those monsters called "Mortal Kombat" or "Alone in the Dark". Curiously, these films come from games with reputed quality, anyone who knows a little bit about the consolero scene will know that they are renowned titles. But my friend, in films since then, are another story. Perhaps, the only honorable exception is "Final Fantasy", but of course, that saves this title is precisely it isn't based on even one only 12 games, and I think there was merit to save at least the muebles(mi_cuerpo_se_convulsiona_ael_saber_que_se_va_a_adaptar_tambien_"Metal_Gear_Solid"). On that basis, in my total and absolute subjectivity when speaking of the latest film from Christophe Gans(ael_que_tengo_algo_estigmatizado_,no,_no_me_gustó_nada_"El_pacto_de_los_lobos"), I am to talk about the film itself. Although, as I mentioned in the previous paragraph, the director did not give me much confidence, was not the case the name of screenwriter Roger Avary, co-creator of one of the undoubtedly most brilliant scripts in the history of the seventh art: Pulp Fiction, always correct (although not brilliant) Sean Bean and the fantastic musical work carried out by Akira Yamaoka(que_lleva_la_música_de_los_juegos_directamente_a_la_pantalla), I thought "what the hell, let's give it a vote of confidence to this". Basically the movie takes more or less approximate based the plot of the first game though it mixes concepts of all of them, in which a mother (Rose, played by Radha Mitchell) comes to Silent Hill, the people that his daughter not to appoint in dreams, hoping to find answers to certain strange behavior of his daughter. Once at the entrance of the village, everything seems to shift and Rose's car lost control, leaving our unconscious protagonist.When he awakes, his daughter Sharon has disappeared, what comes out of the vehicle and goes walking towards the town, the expectation of what you can find. Silent Hill, on the other hand, is totally deserted, and a sort of mist covers the people unless you can see much around. From this moment and broadly, the argument stays interesting, to the expectation of what might happen, and when it happens, one is surprised one of the few successes of the film: the good work in shaping the strange creatures that populate the city, so it could be argued that the first half of the film seems pretty decent. Thereafter, the argument falls sharply to making an excellent idea - that of the first game, which if had been such that the screen would have been a pitch - becomes a hodgepodge of ideas, in the poor attempt to condense the incondensable: 4 totally different arguments each other into one. So you do an idea, it is as if we condensáramos throughout the Star Wars saga in one tape drive (that would be there?) (Nothing good, safe). I strongly recommend that if you want to and can, will you give an opportunity to the games, they have nothing to do with the tape and are small works of art. Perhaps people who not know anything games can minimally interested, but even so I am afraid that do not get nor approved.</body>
</review>
