<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="The Fall" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A magical, beautiful film and whose positive message is able to encourage him to one day. We need more movies like this in the rooms.</summary>
	<body>He has won the award for best film at the Sitges festival, ahead even of the masterpiece "[Rec]" (which, Yes, has won the great general of the year). Its director, Tarsem Singh, was unveiled with "The cell", endless beautiful invoice pestiño, in addition to having shot video clips as incredible as "Losing my Religion", rem. With "The Fall" has remedied his mistakes, convincing with an attractive, and emotional story that hooks and falls in love with, and again, an infinite formal beauty.The premise is simple. A girl is recovering in a hospital. There, he meets a double actor, also entered and forced to save bed, tells a series of stories of adventurous Court, which they unleashed the imagination of the protagonist, and make dream awake and let fly his mind towards these magical places to listen to.Read the summary, it is hard not to think in other similar films that always have been appearing on the screens of film, with greater or lesser success. The most recent, "Big Fish" and "El Laberinto de el Fauno", are almost the same, but luckily, the two pale (especially the second) before "The Fall".And it is that where these fail, by the excessive weight of the imaginary aspect ("Big Fish") or realistic ("the labyrinth."), Tarsem achieves a balance more than remarkable, preventing his film fall into the shallowness of the previous. And harder still, despite its two-hour, "The Fall" does not fall never in the tedium, becoming an entertainment from beginning to end. I don't want to say that your pace is endiablado, he is not an epic movie or anything. But yes administered doses of drama and adventure with intelligence, exciting or fun when the situation requires and avoiding the Viewer to take any look at your watch.This task (the lower the gaze) extremely complicated, because as I say, the beauty of each of its levels, from the most intimate to the most overwhelming, is infinite. Tarsem runs as if paint paintings, for him there cannot be anything that clash on the canvas. "Beautiful photographs of impossible landscapes are interspersed as well with the colorful costumes of the various characters, melting in a tremendously addictive, almost perfect harmony.""The Fall" is therefore an incredible Ode to the joy of living. A magical, beautiful to the eye and rewarding movie in the soul, whose positive message is able to encourage him to one day. I do not want to say much more because I believe that I have already unveiled quite its charm, and think that it is a film of these that is worthwhile to discover during your viewing. I will only say that they need more like this in theaters</body>
</review>
