<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Across The universe" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For all those who have lived the era of The Fab Four, for the nostalgic sesenteros and declared to be pacifists is compulsory viewing.</summary>
	<body>There are two types of people in the world, those who are fans of the Beatles and "the rest". Why was matter of time before someone decided that it was a brilliant idea to make a musical that used the best songs of the best musical group of history as a thread of a film that takes its title from a 1968 recording made for charity. Obviously and how it could be otherwise is set in the 1960s. Jude, a young worker in the shipyards of Liverpool decides to leave his native England to seek a better life in United States. Since then the music will be a key part of his new life in New York. You will find their ideals, will face with the ghosts of the time: Vietnam, drugs, love, life,... those items which are always much better behind a veil of psychotropic substances.The film is delicious and risky. Virtually unknown actors accompanied on screen by major music committed, what would a film for peace and dialogue without Bono singing in it?, what greater pleasure that Joe Cocker singing in the subway?, what man has not fantasized with Salma Hayek to the Pin up multiplied by six?, &hellip; all of them are well seasoned da Across The Universe a vibrating base and an explosive start. Possibly that pace will be broken with the psychedelic trip in the bus and in the surrealist aesthetics of the circus (from my point of view the only totally dispensable point).Across The Universe I loved because the conciliator from the epoch spirit intact and gives a personal touch to the songs of the legendary group. The actors are simply magnificent and Jim Sturgess is the revelation of the year with a delicious accent and a warm and enthusiastic voice jumping from directly below the first division category television productions.For all those who have lived the era of The Fab Four, for the nostalgic sesenteros and declared to be pacifists is compulsory viewing.</body>
</review>
