<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="El Destino de Nunik" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The destination of Nunik is a sober film that excites and moves by the narration makes an outrageousness almost unknown to most of us</summary>
	<body>The international career of Paz Vega could not qualify with another word other than that of extraordinary. Praised by American critics on its first steps in Hollywood, as well as by co-stars of the stature of Morgan Freeman, the Sevillian actress has achieved a more than interesting series of films, which has first trabajao on the orders of prestigious filmmakers such as the Taviani.La brothers thinking next to one at the top to see the destination of Nunik is unfair is the film industry. It will happen without penalty or glory by Spanish movies (and what little that is due to the presence of Paz Vega), but if it were an American production impact and impact would be huge. The new film of the Taviani brothers, are not Holy devotion that subscribes to these lines, narrates the genocide carried out by the Turkish army during the first world war against the Armenian minority. The main drawback of the film is that it takes to boot. The first minutes is quite slow, and therein the Taviani are entertained with the small details and small stories, remaining intensity and drama as a whole. As soon as the film progresses, the story is gaining a higher category and packaging, and to the Taviani not shakes them the pulse to show the horror, hatred and the resentment accumulated a crude form but without losing elegance. But the destination of Nunik makes no sense without the magnificent interpretation of Paz Vega, whose work in the final moments of the film puts the willies.The destination of Nunik is a sober film that excites and moves by the narration makes an outrageousness almost unknown to most of us. And it is a new opportunity to see a great Paz Vega film to film growing in leaps as intérpete. The pity is that Spanish Cinema loses, at least for a season, so good actress.</body>
</review>
