<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Zoo" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Zoo does not judge, does not pose ideas, does not give options to the Viewer, the director assumes the normality of what it tells. It is long, boring and somewhat heavy because it does not create sympathy nor hatred for none of what appears on the screen. I'm staying with Equus.</summary>
	<body>Zoo is a rare film. It is not only the pseudo documentary format or disturbing topic which is, rather is the complete package.This small newspaper on a zoophilic (or group of them for is more correct terminológicamente speaking) explained with disturbing voices in off where, how and why is the love for animals born after the terrible death of one of them. Kenneth Pinyan died shortly after being brought to the emergency room of a hospital in Enumclaw, Washington, where traveling is one of the few States where crime is not considered. According to death certificates, he succumbed to internal injuries resulting from a perforation of colon. Began a police investigation that led to a farm. There were revealed videocassettes and DVD in which several men claimed sex with horses. The documentary, based on the testimony of one of the participants, has novice players to rebuild the vision of these practice account with much material of the events which occurred in 2005 as interviews of radio or television which helped to give the account entity and to accompany resource images which tend to aim at the lyric and poetic rather than the chabacano Act specifically zoophilic.The main problem of the narrative is that it is quite complicated to connect with the spectator despite trying to show the concerns of each of the protagonists of the story. It is difficult to justify or understand the bestiality or that encourages a person to change State to maintain relations with a horse. While in the tapes on adolescents or in the hands of Kevin Smith the thing may seem up fun take it seriously costs a little more. Comparing it with Peter Shaffer's Equus, play written in the 1970s revolutionized in due course to the public (and even still gave a couple of blows in the Assembly of this year) Zoo seems an exercise in college more carnal than anything else. Sex explicit appears little on screen but no one has objections in talk about it. En la obra de Shaffer made into a film by Sydney Lumet its protagonist prefers hurting animals aware of the relationship (which never comes to be carnal) is amoral. All the work is understood to the young man and his inner struggle coming to the end to understand his anguish. In Zoo never raises the possibility that stakeholders recognize that his behavior is questionable, it defends the difference and its freedom and motivation to go ahead because its director envisages that the existence of these practices is real and reasonable.Zoo does not judge, does not pose ideas, does not give options to the Viewer, the director assumes the normality of what it tells and precisely therein lies the controversy surrounding the film and its main Achilles heel. It is long (despite last an hour and ten minutes), boring and somewhat heavy because it does not create sympathy nor hate for anything of what appears on the screen. I'm staying with Equus.</body>
</review>
