<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="La Huella" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is quite mediocre, unoriginal but it has fantastic actors in the leading roles. Despite his strenuous efforts in few moments get attract viewers that they end up losing the interest.</summary>
	<body>I read on one occasion when they were shooting the film that Michael Caine confessed that he was tired of that Jude Law won the pan base to destroy his films playing him. Therefore agreed with the eyes closed the Remake of the footprint in which reserved the role had earlier played Sir Lawrence Olivier as dignity in 1972 production directed by Joseph l. Mankiewicz and leaving the address common friend Kenneth Branagh. It seemed to be a perfect plan, more if it should be that which is at the beginning of the tape.The footprint is not so fresh, so round and as entertaining as the original. Normally the remakes tend to have these glitches that seem so fantastic to the public that is unknown to them, in this case even the public to know the original has managed to get bored. The penalty is the new, pseudo alopécico Jude this intends to be a serious actor after the fiasco of the last years but seems to be that either the box office or critical have not the slightest intention to grant him the benefit of the doubt &hellip; while watching the latest movies presented can not culpr anyone from the disaster that isn't himself. Modest fund-raising in the film both in England and in Spain. Not only by the stench of several remakes that tirelessly stars if not for the unquestionable theatrical mood of the same. A young actor, hairdresser person in the mansion of an illustrious writer of success to negotiate with him the divorce from his wife is now loving. Soon the handsome suitor will be tempted by the old man to get money at the expense of faking a robbery, this will start a terrible game where each will have to figure out how to win his peculiar sets and where the money, ambition and ambiguity will have a predominant role.The film is quite mediocre, unoriginal but it has fantastic actors in the leading roles. Despite his strenuous efforts in few moments get attract viewers that they end up losing interest in a story that becomes slow, unoriginal and quite predictable.At least this was a good thing, Kenneth Branagh decided that next year his Hamlet in the West End has the face of Mr Law, perhaps thanks to the theatre get lift head and recover the interpretation and the attraction that had a day.</body>
</review>
