<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Roma Ciudad Abierta" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If there is a film that is recognized as the home of the Italian neorealism that is Rome Cittá Aperta of Rosellini, from my point of view is essential to understand the film's quality.</summary>
	<body>If there is a film that is recognized as the beginning of the Italian neorealism that is Rome Cittá Aperta of Rosellini (and the bicycle thief of De Sicca).(The terrible relevance of the tape is that is almost contemporary acts recounts was recorded in 1945 on facts of the 43-44). While in Europe and United States defend the need to spend time to assess historical events the Italians dared to denounce recent and cruel stories of a regime that still had many adherents. Why tapes like this suffered censorship, not only in Italy. In United States was her it shortened, reducing its duration in a quarter of an hour. In Argentina it was inexplicably removed from display by an anonymous Government order in 1947. In the Western Germany it was banned from 1951 until 1960. But none of this prevented that you won the Palme d'Or in Cannes in 1948.Sobre a screenplay by Rossellini, Sergio Amidei, Federico Fellini and Celeste Negarville, the film is loosely based on the true story of Fr. Luigi Morosini, tortured and murdered by the nazis to help the resistance. In the Rome of the 43-44, Interweave the stories of several people related with the anti-Nazi resistance. The stages of the devastated city are authentic so no one can deny the realism of the same. Especially sad and shocking is the story of Pina masterfully performed by Anna Magnani who takes over the screen at each level and leads one of the most striking scenes of Italian cinema. Part of the successes of the tape is the ability to display a city devastated, hungry and terrified in the temporary period of just three days that are dramatically truncated with a RAID for the arrest of father Piero destroying the life of several of its neighbours.There are no concessions in Rome Cittá Aperta. All the fear, tension and violence. Not hide betrayals, the motivations or the reality of a people torn apart by a totalitarian regime and its filmmakers, honest and courageous dare to put it on the screen. Rosellini worked in a company of cinematographer and they managed to steal some plans and footage used in his film is said in the history books to portray the desolation of the city which is actually the main protagonist.With the passage of time may question whether the quality of the tape or the taken options are the most appropriate and many valuing Rome Cittá Aperta as a correct exercise but overrated. However all will agree that mastery of the script and the film and historical conditions are, without a doubt, what makes it a masterpiece of the time which remains captivating to friends and strangers.From my point of view, it is essential to understand the film's quality.THE movie data: Won the Palme d'Or in Cannes in 1948. suffered censorship in almost all countries that was brand new.</body>
</review>
