<review author="Red Stovall" title="Alatriste" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Alatriste is the tangible demonstration that in this country already we go dedicating us to do something else, I don't know, it calceta for example.</summary>
	<body>It is the Spanish of the year movie, as in 2005 was 'Torrente 3'. I am talking about the box office, of course. And if we talk about its quality as film because little better is that the messing of Santiago Segura, and no, not kidding. I would already like. The alleged crisis of Spanish Cinema is going to save two truño there is no where catch them. Because readers mine, 'Alatriste' is palpable proof that in this country already we go dedicating us to do something else, I don't know, sock for example. This film is not only a clear exponent of zero quality of our cinema. It is an invitation to any viewer with two fingers in front again not stepping over a movie theater to see a patriotic product. It is also an invitation for all those engaged workforce in this film in our country are thinking about change pofesión and not waste more time doing silly. what I'm being too hard? What will! What happens is that if the movie were American, I would therefore give birth without more and point, and what is best, I care a damn. But as it is ours (and of our will with second) I can not stay silent no more and confine myself to make a critique of the film without entering certain considerations that I think important. So much time complaining that in our country not we dare to make a blockbuster to the American with many media and such and which, with all the history we have and blah blah blah. and when is that there is the possibility of doing so (a good possibility I would say) and separate us put in tray an actor of the likes of Viggo Mortensen and some 22 million euros, over a minimally acceptable literary basis, I wonder how is it possible that made such shit?On his argument I won't talk. OS cogeis books that Arturo Pérez-Reverte has devoted to the character and comprobareis that something everyone has got to tell the story told in the film. A greatly confusing history never progresses and what is worse: isn't interesting at any time. What does Alatriste? What do the other characters? what it unites them? These and other questions may have answer but only halfway, because never ya que nunca queda is perfectly defined or explained what makes each character and its role in the film. Many come out, or rather because known actors interpret and so the public can say: "look, Pilar López de Ayala" (my daughter, who recommended you that you metieras here?).That little definition affects not only characters but the history. The central plot is quite diluted, either by the overwhelming artistic direction by the excess of characters or secondary frames radically hindering the narrative, as for example the love affairs between some of the characters. Apart from wasting time, they are not well displayed. Also I should say that the film is lost in historical data relating to famous paintings, which matter to us a cumin, because even the fact of wanting to convey the feeling that we have something big just in time to be carried out is achieved. This glut of information ends up getting tired of us, is how if policymakers thought that we weren't going to give an account of the exact time in which the film takes place. But vamoa see, if already at the beginning tells the year, and we repeat every few minutes: "one year later", "ten years later" and so on.Agustín Díaz Yanes it is not that the film is great, it is that there is still enormous. Unable to infer the correct rhythm, is more, sometimes gives the impression that there is no or rhythm; hold the entire film is truly soporific and ends deranging. There is no or slippages of rhythm, that is to say no. And when it comes time to be spectacular, the director shows that he can't shoot or a single battle or fight of swords. Everything is confusion and is very wildly displayed. The film can not boast of having many spectacular scenes, which continues to be a mistake, because when it focuses on their characters is total chaos. If I at least had more action, and would not be stopped both in useless, we would be talking about another movie without a doubt. But it is not.The actors work there for all tastes. Who takes the cake is obviously Viggo Mortensen, who only have to accuse him of a form of talking really strange and slightly damaging his interpretation. However, endorses the character and is used throughout the film by filling the screen, perhaps too, because of which there is no doubt is that the film is a vehicle for his showcasing integer, that everyone knows that this actor has come to work with us and focus on much, won't be the only time you approach here. The rest of the cast really passes straws to keep up. On the good side we have Javier House, actor who earn a lot over the years; Will Blanca Portillo, that if does not take Goya, do for 'Back'; Juan Echanove as an excellent Quevedo; Ariadna Gil, not because it is well, but because I to this actress forgive you all and it is always a joy seeing her on screen. And how not, Eduard Fernández, magnificent off-road actor that outboard what throw you.On the side of the bad guys we have to Eduardo Noriega, think anytime that we will say that we drink Schweppes; Elena Anaya, is not credible never; and on all Unax Ugalde, who at this point I already qualify as one of the worst actors of the Universal history. His character, vital in history, does not have the slightest entity in the hands of Ugalde, does not exist. The actor who only knows to put a face, yours is truly pathetic and ends round the general disaster.Good actors must add what was spent in production, to design there Yes the movie is perfect. Every penny of your budget is reflected on the screen, something is something. But obviously not arrived, that the rest are nothing more than a bunch of characters coming out left and right and reciting phrases which at times are ridiculous.A very bad film once again putting highlight and exposed the enormous artistic shortcomings of our film, which should be defending tooth and nail (never better said), but with films like this is impossible. To see what it takes to make fun of us in how much the movie is exported. At the moment the sense is of absolute casting, tomorrow will be sadness, because I repeat once again that the opportunity to do something big was unique and they have squandered her. And incidentally, it does not seem to be to make a series about the character, which would be the logical thing. Of course, they have been without money there this, there for a continuation.</body>
</review>
