<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Encantada: La Historia de Giselle" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Disney laughs at itself in an elegant way, entertaining and fun, without disheveled, and with great modesty.</summary>
	<body>Best thing is to laugh at oneself. That thought the Disney when they decided to make Encantada: the history of Giselle. And that they did, because the saying is true, it was needed. What they have done in an elegant way, without disheveled and with much modesty, since it meets all the clichés of fairy tales that has been doing the factory for more than seventy years of history, and mocks them, but without the nasty.Thus, we can find references and parodies in the form of small winks, jokes, gags and even songs (how not) of snow white and the seven dwarfs, Cinderella, the Little Mermaid, sleeping beauty and beauty and the beast (level tracing to the dance of the final level, the best moment in the film). The villain on duty, without going further, is a mix between the Queen of snow white and the best villain of all time Disney, maleficent, from sleeping beauty. Only in appearance, of course, because it is the Coca Cola light mixed with a zero of the evil.In addition to the more or less modestita autoparodia best of the film are actors: Amy Adams is perfect, playing Giselle, a Princess typically Disney, corny, flower-power and defender until the nausea of true love with Prince charming on duty. Nails all tics and movements, falls in love with, and love (je.), the camera and the Viewer, and also sings wonderfully well; something that does not appreciate in the dubbed version, because the songs are interpetadas by Gisela triunfita (forgive the redundancy) that everything must be said, does it not nothing evil (Disney: specialist in which all the songs in his films perfectly den the pego in all countries where Premiere). Also have to James Marsden, who we saw him in Hairspray, and which remains committed to ask shouts a nomination Oscar for the best supporting actor, given that, for a change, it is in its passing it pipe playing typical, topical and cheesy Prince charming.On the other hand are Patrick Dempsey, Timothy Spall and Susan Sarandon, but one is a sosainas of care (Dempsey), the other overload (Spall), and the other has a role as anecdotal that not enough time to appreciate what it does (Sarandon).Another highlight is the typical animation of the factory, which is her missed enough, and it seems that it follows in full form. There are levels that are a true wonder. When viewers will see the final round of Disney to these 2D (but without neglecting the 3D) both us marveled with his sense of musical entertainment during the past decade?All this make Encantada minimally enjoyable product (sometimes boring) and adopted, since the story is typical of the romantic comedies, and is predictable (and incoherent) even say enough, since it is thousand times vista. And no, is not entirely true that to make a film work, he has to work history: REC directly has no history, and works. D</body>
</review>
