<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Saw 4" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lords of Lions Gate, not bludgeon his saga franchise nor his goose eggs of gold, disappointing and without contributing anything to the saga, or to the development of the same, without motivation, empty... it can tell more negative words in so little space?</summary>
	<body>As said at the time when I saw both "Saw" as "Saw 2" as the third installment "Saw 3", while the first seemed like an excellent film, who saved the ass and current accounts to a small producer as Lions Gate had thinking about launching it directly to DVD for rental and that avatars of fate decided to release in the 2004 theatrical Halloween, the rest have been shifting thanks to the good reputation (and excellent taquillaje), and while the first was an experiment that was excellent (as already mentioned), the rest have been order to its predecessor, and demonstrating that with little, you can make (or raise) far without great efforts, neither actors nor effects, leaving, I might add, to the audience with the mouth open with a final very style that likes to get mNight Shyamalan (but in shabby), and making the mouth of the teenagers who would do the rest.Sincerely did not have any type of bet towards this fourth installment, especially when I started to read and verify that criticism her put as the worst in the series, so I waited for DVD and!Voila! an evening without having nothing better to do I I started to see her; and once more my opinion joins the most, while the film delves into the aspects of the life of Jigsaw, as if of a vulgar Hannibal Lecter tell the reasons that led him to become the murderous serial killer that today they tell us their films, after explaining these reasons the film is lost in a thousand byways without sensewhich they do not serve anything, and where a "anyone can be the murderer of the Puzzle" seems the leitmotif of the same, on the other hand, traps, which in the early tapes were not only curious but rightly cruel, are transformed into mere crap, which ever is easier to RID, and left again to the viewer with very bad taste in mouth (for the time lost in viewing) and few wanting more.In terms of actors, all unknown and side of multitude of series, none are seen delivered, all lost, without providing, without expecting anything, and without showing the "bad feeling" that is supposed to move on screen, mention besides that show in some moments to Jigsaw, as a sort of avenging hero, and not as a cursed and bloody murderer.Finally, if the saga continues down this path, for my part is the last film that I see, already has happened with other deliveries in the horror film, where I parked movies and I refused in round to keep watching for new releases. Lords of Lions Gate, not bludgeon his saga franchise nor his goose eggs of gold, disappointing and without contributing anything to the saga, or to the development of the same, without motivation, empty. can one say more negative words in so little space?</body>
</review>
