<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Resident Evil Extincion" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It matters little that the script is not Oscar, or actors sank without remission. You are looking for is fun, and that is neither more nor less what offers "Resident Evil: extinction"</summary>
	<body>Mila Jovovich gets involved again in the skin of Alice in the third part of "Resident Evil", which presents an apocalyptic world in which the undead campan at ease and that the few survivors must tread with very careful to keep alive. Accompany the cast the spectacular Ali Larter (Nikki in "Heroes"), Oded Fehr, and Mike Epps, and directs the Russell Mulcahy.Sin semidesconocido doubt the ship insignia of the adaptations of video games to the big screen, the "Resident Evil" series has always differentiated from the rest by having that drive and gripper which both missing productions such as "Alone in the Dark", "House of the Dead", or "Silent Hill". And above all, great virtue, especially in the first part, is that it entertains like few, regardless of the quality of the final result.Because if "Resident Evil" is a more than correct film of horror and action, part two, "Apocalypse", left something to be desired becoming nonsense seemed not to know what string cling, lurching between action scenes precitipitadas and dramatic moments of non-existent consistency.Fortunately, the third is much more compensated, and while the introduction of fantastic and supernatural elements subtract you the little credibility that he had the character and therefore the argument in general, the script is much more focused on a dynamic and fast-paced, story which just leaves one minute pause Meanwhile shot and fight live against zombies. And references. Because a new constant for this occasion are clear references to other films of the genre. Will not be at all difficult to recognize almost kidnapping sequences "The hills have eyes", "Birds", "Jurassic Park", and especially to "The day of the dead" by Romero, which until may feel insulted to see how bebe Paul W.S. Anderson (writer of the trilogy and director as well as the first) of their ideas.In another order of things, for this occasion the film style changes, breaks with the characteristic precocious and dark lighting of the previous two installments, which were situated inside the complex first Umbrella and a destroyed city later. Now it's been five years, the land is completely dominated by an infinite number of undead, and large cities like Las Vegas had been overdue and buried by the sands of the desert. For this reason, the film is (apparently) ugly and dirty, empolvada and warm, placing nearly all of the action in full light of day. But that no one be fooled, because everything is calculated to the millimetre: only in this way can be enjoyed throughout his scenes as the cuervos-zombie attack on the convoy of the protagonists, or scenarios as the impressive desert covering Las Vegas. And why not, the choreography so spectacular that it is composed Jovovich to eliminate his enemies.Because ultimately that is the major asset on which it counts Mulcahy film, the spectacular constant action scenes throughout the film. As it is the case with this kind of movies, it matters little that the script is not Oscar, actors sank without remission, or that the address is not precisely Scorsese. You are looking for is fun, and that is no less than what gives "Resident Evil: extinction". That Yes, to starting the end credits, one already is has almost completely forgotten what you have just seen.</body>
</review>
