<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Matrimonio Compulsivo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is hilarious and extremely entertaining, with some absolutely unforgettable jokes that soon be forgotten. Impossible not laugh.</summary>
	<body>The Farrelly Brothers return to the fray with a hilarious film less sweetened than we are accustomed, starring one of the current Kings of comedy, Ben Stiller, who accompanied his father and actor Jerry Stiller, and Michelle Monaghan ("mission: impossible 3").Eddie Cantrow is increasingly more overwhelmed: fails to find a woman to lay his head, and his forty years still unmarried while all his to the rededor pairs and House. Why, who believes finding the ideal girl (Malin Akerman), so no doubt even a moment and decides to take the big step a few weeks of knowing. Decision that turns out to be more reckless, because during the honeymoon discovers that the perfect woman so perhaps not so much. And certainly does not help in any way the appearance of the dazzling Miranda.Que Brothers directors have lost the pulse which at the time had no doubt no one. From "Something happens with Mary" little by little they have gone down the bar, his films becoming increasingly commercial products and therefore adapting his personal humor to a broader style, in order to reach a greater number of viewers. Thus, products such as "Love blind" or "Love in game" replaced "Two fools very stupid" or "I, I, and Irene", to the disappointment of many. However, with "The Heartbreak Kid" (original title of his latest film) seems to have been given a turning point.Is not that they have returned to their origins, since the scheme that follows "Compulsive marriage" is the same as in "Pretty Woman",".""And then she came", or many other romantic comedies, and is still abusing certain somewhat unnerving empalagosismo. And it is precisely in the scenes and moments more to use when the film loses long bellows, coming to do something heavy, taking into account the excessive length (almost two hours).But yes begin to see again gags delirious, harsh and painful, a kid and thick brush, characters of the best humor freak. all elements allowing to distinguish a film of the Farrelly from the rest. There is still a long way to rebuild, but the first stone is already set. "In addition, despite the predictability that stains in general all the footage, the film hides a couple of twists coming surprise a viewer that already accommodated in your sofa believing that he knew how things would end.""Compulsive marriage" is a film that is far from being "Something happens with Mary", and peca still of some plot schematic prevents him to mark the difference. But it is hilarious and extremely entertaining, with some absolutely unforgettable jokes that will it take to be forgotten (the scene with the medusa, solar protection, of the Mexican "folklore"). Ben Stiller is in top form and with its schizophrenic performance shows that it remains a reference in the world of humor, and both Michelle Monaghan as the other side (in particular Jerry Stiller and the Miranda family) are charming.Impossible not laugh.P.s. recommended stay to see the final titles.</body>
</review>
