<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Dragon Wars" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>They are only saved the twenty minutes of spectacular struggle in L.A., which although quite remind "Tranformers", still working a charm, having fun like few. Too bad that it is completely insufficient.</summary>
	<body>Hyung-rae Shim writes and directs an epic story in which everything has a place: a curse, dragons and giant snakes, and the U.S. Army.Journalist Ethan discovers one of his recordings it seems a giant reptile scales. He is immediately family, remember how small saw something similar in an antiques shop, in which its owner explained that the same Ethan was the protagonist of a myth which is repeated every five hundred years. According to legend, two giant snakes, a good and another bad, leave their caches to catch up with a girl that generation after generation is born a dragon mark on his shoulder. She contains the necessary element for the snake to find earlier is transformed into a dragon and reach the Kingdom of heaven where he remained for the next five hundred years. or something like that.The idea of placing a struggle between dragons and army in a city so impressive as it is Los Angeles in advance was a stimulating proposal. Feeling that he confirmed to watch spectacular trailers circulating in the network, where cuttings as reflected in some special effects, eye-catching and very careful. Even the argument might be, how much less, curious, to adapt a legend of sur-coreana culture to the present day. Unfortunately, the end result is a real disappointment, because there is no where to take "D-War".There are many bugs that embrutecen the film, in the majority of its aspects. The actions are all deplorable, with special reference to Jason Behr (Ethan) and Robert Forster (who plays the owner of the antiquarian and mentor of the protagonist). I don't know what would be thinking of casting directors, although well is true in a movie so neither is seeking work oscarizables. Another important burden is the entire Assembly. Flat cut meaningless, flash-backs of flash-backs (at the beginning especially) that are not only ridiculous, if not making it one to lose the head, are just a couple of examples of the visual gibberish that we are witnessing. They are only saved a couple of shots in which, through clumsy zooms and quivering filming, you get some (impossible) realism, as if it were a documentary.But where is more emponzoña "Dragon Wars" in his script. Empty and little stimulant, moves around all the clichés of popcorn cinema by resorting to absurd situations that have no feet or head (see the time that boy and girl Kiss, having known only few hours before and with a giant snake chasing them) and constant references to "Jurassic Park" or "King Kong". It is impossible to take this movie seriously, but is that even without doing so, we cannot accept such absurdities.The truth is that this film both promised, at the end only are they saved the twenty minutes of spectacular struggle in L.A., which although quite remind "Tranformers", still working a charm, having fun like few. Too bad that it is completely insufficient. Do not lose time.</body>
</review>
