<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The result is the dreaded, at the end you've seen a hodgepodge of ideas which is very difficult to stay with nothing, except with the performance of a Will Smith who had already demonstrated that it is able to load a movie on their backs.</summary>
	<body>Good ideas abound in the film. In fact just have to take a look at the films circulating in the world, a good example of good ideas, many of them very well carried out. If above, the idea out of a known novel, read by millions of people and made into a film on two previous occasions, one ensures almost altogether that the essential part of the story will not be bad. The problem often occur around the nucleus of an attractive story.In this case part of the novel bestseller by Richard Matheson "I am Legend", with substantial changes, relates how an army scientist becomes the last man on Earth, being the only human immune virus turns men into a kind of rabid vampires without other committed in its existence than the eat their healthy peers.Also the history of a catastrophic interesting halo and warning you can confer to attribute the spread of the virus to the man himself, telling that this is in principle a mutation of a deadly virus which in principle is going to win the battle against cancer. The premise is not bad for a discussion of the struggle of man against nature or the eternal quest for immortality.The problem comes when everything falls halfway between genres and is at this time when one leaves the film convinced that he has not seen absolutely nothing. The plot begins observing the life of Robert Neville alone with his dog in a way that reminds us of Castaway, the struggle of a type trying to not go crazy with his solitude. From time to time they assail us flash-backs of the attempt of Neville save your family in a vertiginous drama. We also assist the efforts of the protagonist to find the cure for the virus and fix all the desagisado which has caused. The genus is changing towards the Middle, turning to terror when you must escape the zombies to settle towards the end in the pure action and once again the drama in the last bars.The result is the dreaded, at the end you've seen a hodgepodge of ideas which is very difficult to stay with nothing, except with the performance of a Will Smith who had already demonstrated that it is able to load a movie on their backs, but that does not have an eye too clinical when choosing scripts other than comedy.For his part, Francis Lawrence, the director who had already brought the entertaining "Constantine", shows at times that it is capable of filming with good pulse, but is very difficult to do something worthwhile with a script that does not know what he wants to have more moments that fill of history.Finally, a point for managers seeking to acongojar staff (as if it were to read). The lawyer decided to come with me despite the fact that vampires were characters in the film and she was rather more scared in the parts in which Will Smith travels through empty houses and dark rooms in which in the end turn vampire looks over his computer-generated fronted (excluding the classic scare-based rise in volume and rapid emergence of bug on screen)(it works even if the bug of turn is Bambi). Do even they haven't learned that the terror of quality works in this way?Although, as in the end I did not no conclusion of the genus in which the movie was installed, maybe not this was what was intended.</body>
</review>
