<review author="El vengador toxico" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the films of adventures more entertaining and fun of the past years.</summary>
	<body>Finally we have here the continuation of the adventures of Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp). The great taquillazo of 2006 is on the screens. I guess that almost everything that read this her there will be seen, so I'm going to avoid putting the synopsis.The first thing I have to say is that Pirates of the Caribbean seemed to me one of the films of adventures more entertaining and fun of the past years. To give you an idea, I could give on this blog of 4 star 4 and a half if catches me good. Making this clear, I have to say that this is much lower. It is not a bad film, but it is that the bar was very high.The movie is entertaining. I have heard people at the beginning has been heavy. No, I think need to try to draw an argument and that not everything is action and shots. It is true that the part of the cannibals may be totally unnecessary, but me you are booted smiles who have then there.But well, then comes action, in spades. I've also seen in an interview that not have been used many digital special effects for what gets used. Because I do not know who can believe that, by computer effects abound everywhere. You know, one of those movies that you think should see it on the big screen.Also I like to walk a lot of topicazos of the stories of pirates and adventures of childhood stuff when you were not looking for a meaning to everything: appear cannibals, witches (there are moments in which thought it was within the game of Monkey Island), the profundidades(os_dejo_aquí_la_reseña_deel_kraken_en_la_wikipedia) monsters, the Dutch Errante (with his review review of wikipedia), the patent of corso. All mixed to the good random.Now the comparisons with the first, i.e., what weakens. The bad guys are bad and already, where is the sense of humor that makes a memorable adventures bad? Nothing, or a little bit. The first Captain Barbosa had wonderful moments (or all the credit was Geoffrey Rush?). At least it seems that we will see in the third.The special effects were not so perfect as other times. I do not know if it is due to that the water is always more difficult, but the scenes of the kraken, when they were fast did not believe them me. Moving the tentacles to all milk and what seemed to me is. that they were not real. Also the destruction of ships, the more fast, less credible. However when the action was human speed (tentacles moving slowly, cautiously) Yes it seemed more real, except for the confrontation with Sparrow.En the first film, the action scenes often were at that point so hard that he is staying in a light (light) credibility bordering ridicule, but without transferring it. It is that that may not be true but you not squeaking. Here are a few scrapes Tales: the escape of the bonfire of Sparrow, the duel between Will Turner (Orlando Bloom) and the ex-comodoro on the Ferris wheel, when the Dutch Errante dives with Will Turner hidden in the figurehead. It's like the struggles of Elizabeth (Keira Knightley) crewed Jones. I think that he has learned to fight and keeps them at Bay, even with the changes of flying swords, but why has to kill two pirates backs nailing them swords below the armpits, so to the remangillé?Jack Sparrow was the King of the first, mysterious, enigmatic, ambiguous moral, with those andares, its entry into the port at the beginning was glorious. But it was more, was Captain Jack Sparrow, with resources amazing, ingenuity and skill to leave more TThe situations. In this we have the gait, ambiguous morality (the hero Fund), the humor. but we have lost the ingenuity and cunning out of desperate situations. The flight of the bonfire is a slapstick, not a plan. And the escape from jail, which implies an ingenious plan, us is not shown.As a note to please, here Elizabeth proves not a noble soul, and this ambiguity I like. You give party in the next.And I have spoken several times of the next. The first was a movie with a beginning and an end. It has a beginning, but not an end. stays halfway (missing "continuará"). And it has bothered me enough, I expected a full movie, that lasts two and a half hours. One last thing, after the closing credits there is a scene of seconds, but is not very significant. As well as the first that was to see the live monkey (which by the way, is present in this)</body>
</review>
