<review author="Javier Martínez" title="El acorazado Potemkin" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It never said so much in so little time behind a camera. A catharsis continuous based on frames.</summary>
	<body>I do not know if it is thing of spontaneous generation or a specific alignment of the planets, but the fact is that in a particular territory is turned on a spark and they begin to sprout geniuses. The great Greek list (Sócrates-Platón - Aristóteles), del Siglo de Oro Spanish or the Renaissance are the most significant examples. Probably the last great boom occurred in Russia between mid-19th century and early 20th. The list is long and includes all Arts: Tolstoy Dostoievski, Chejov, Stanislavski, Mayakovsky, Kandinsky, Turgenev, Gorky, Vertov, Pudovkin, Nijinsky, Pasternak, &hellip; curious verify that it matches the most turbulent era in the country, as well said Orson Welles on "The third man" and published Socioapatía ago poco:http://socioapatia.wordpress.com/2007/12/13/posters-polacos-de-cine/De between them appears Sergei Eisenstein, disciple of another theatrical genius (Meyerhold) and that would change forever the structure of the film. He and Griffith we owe them the epic blockbusters and have become to the seventh art rather than entertainment. You don't have to be communist to enjoy with this movie. In fact, even the Goebbels himself admired it. That Yes, we must warn that it was commissioned by the dome of the Bolshevik Party (with recently deceased Lenin), who is extremely partisan and even distorts the true facts of the popular revolts of 1905. Eisenstein was the "Leni Riefenstahl" red, although it ended (does and who does not?) in the sights of Comrade side Stalin.Dejando these trifles I have rather than kneel before what this man did in 1925. Well, he and the great Eduard Tissé on the picture. Convert to a crowd in a film possibly is crazy, sweet folly that elevates this work to the category of immortal. I do not think that there is an only critic that does not include her in your list of favorites. There is only a character with their own name, Vakulinchuk, incarnation of the courage and suffering of the people in a person, very of taste Soviet under the amount of iconography of Heads of State that they produced (and later destroyed). From the meat agusanada until the twinning with the fleet of the army everything are shock effect, a continuous catharsis to base frames. The panoramic and foregrounds are happening while the music guide emotions. And there are of all colors: indignation, rage, hope, joy, bitterness, terror. All this will be parading in front of the eyes, which surrenders. I have already said it before but it can not be forgotten; not only Eisenstein is the magician, what makes Eduard Tissé with the picture is out of reach for anyone. Impossible angles of the battleship, the penumbra of the ship at dusk, multiple approaches to the persecution by the stairs of Odessa, the burial of Vakulinchuk, &hellip; colossal close-up as the of the mother, the falling roof, the barrel pointing at the camera, crucifix and &hellip; course, if you like the things related to the technique of cinemaThis is your movie.And as Colophon makes my favorite scene of all time, the massacre of Cossacks to the population of Odessa when it welcomed the mutineers and said goodbye with honors the fallen hero. The mother, the chariot of the baby, the lame, the aligned passage of the Cossacks and thousand more scenes take place in just a few frantic minutes, minutes that contain the essence of what the film is, or what should be. It never said so much in so little time behind a camera.There was a time in which he wanted to be a filmmaker, and all this blame "The Battleship Potemkin". Anyway, I would need a million pages to tell everything that comes to mind when I think in this film, which is why I put end and that each one to see and draw their own conclusions. I attached the Odessa steps scene.</body>
</review>
