<review author="Luna" title="No es país para viejos" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bardem or the psychotic gunman of the Coen brothers. No country for old men, or as they have translated it here, it is not a country for old men, will become one of the movies that we should not lose sight of the Spanish chart of 2008.</summary>
	<body>Dir: Joel and Ethan CoenInt: Tommy Lee Jones, Javier Bardem, Josh Brolin, Woody Harrelson, Kelly Macdonald violence begets violence and no matter where I try to hide, the weight of your actions will always return to give you a kick in the ass. This could summarize the plot of the last film by the Coen brothers. After finding the remains of a shooting by chance, an average American (Josh Brolin), of those living in a caravan in the country of the bars and stars, find a Briefcase full of money and decides what it. But as no action remains unpunished, he discovered and sent to a psychotic gunman (Javier Bardem) to hunting.From the first frame we discovered cinema in its purest form and a story, written by the own directors, who you will be catching more and more. It is not what you have, it's a story that you've probably seen more than once, but how have. A reflective look at revenge, violence, through a deliberate, thoughtful and fast-paced rhythm at the same time.In addition to his good work from the point of view of the realization, the Coen brothers have genuine talent for the direction of actors and achieve some impeccable interpretations that undoubtedly will reap many awards (not in vain Javier Bardem is nominated to Golden Globe for the role). The Coen brothers we discover a more visceral Bardem than of custom and highlight that this actor has many nuances, because in their role as we discover a dark and stinky background that we had not seen him on screen. Behind a mask of inexpressiveness, are the eyes of Bardem which tell us about the character. With a great expressive economy Bardem composed one of the most memorable roles, that without a doubt, will be a gap in the history of cinema.It is not the only one which is superb in its interpretation. All manage to compose credible characters through the expressive restraint. I would like to highlight also the interpretation of Tommy Lee Jones in the role of police and voice of experience, which provides the viewer the narration of the story from another point of view.The picture an ochre, red and brown tones of Roger Deakins (usual picture of the Coen director) and the music by Carter Burwell (another of the usual Coen) conform as ring to the finger at this story, becoming perfect tools to provide the same greatest echoes of verismo and depth.No country for old men, or as they have translated it here, it is not a country for old men, will become one of the movies that we should not lose sight of the Spanish chart of 2008.</body>
</review>
