<review author="Bruji" title="American Gangster" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The favorite actors of the Scott brothers delight with separate master interpretations in that it could be the movie of the year.</summary>
	<body>The proven expertise of the best director in the world makes a complex plot of the American underworld bosses for beginners manual. For its part, the favorite actors of the Scott brothers delight with separate master interpretations in that it could be the movie of the year.Make the difficult easy is tremendously more laborious to make the simple complicated. Perhaps that is why proliferate films that enjoy the blessing of this sector of the criticism that should be called "transgression" to everything that no one understands. Perhaps for the same reason, the less learned, that we never see bread where there is wine, found in the trend of Ridley Scott flee the half-hearted, the guarantee of an almost always safe bet.Which was considered "best director in the world" in the 1980s with titles such as Alien and Blade Runner, with a style - moments-comparable to Stanley Kubrick in the Duelists, expert Narrator of locations (Black Rain), undisputed master of aesthetics and forceful director of actors, able to extract better performances than those who have worked under his command (Thelma and Louise)(, Lieutenant O'Neil), still seeks the recognition of a prize Oscar. After sound failures as 1492: the conquest of paradise and the Kingdom of heaven, has been able to go back in the direction of films like Gladiator (funny remake of the fall of the Roman Empire) or Los impostors; to provide, recently, a new dimension to the traditional romantic comedies, transforming the bland script for A good year in a pleasant viewing footage.American Gangster is where Scott of best time to recover.The story of powerful home and confusing approach that makes honour to one of his phrases: "this is a chaos, every bully acts on their own," soon will be normalized into a powerful development of an apotheosis outcome. Shoot in one hundred fifty and two decorations different alternating with natural spaces, in a country of political instability such as Thailand, in the five boroughs of New York City, in emblematic mansions located in the place of residence of billionaires as Rockefeller, which give way to low income apartments built by the City Council; It was a challenge that only a "director of environments" would be able to solve. Scott, with his "style of shooting guerilla" camera in hand, expanded the system of multicameras in the action scenes, and with a spectacular variety of wide shots, transports the Viewer from Viet Nam until the Harlem 116th Street without him shaking the pulse, in a feat that is not always reciprocated with the Director of photography.On the other hand, the complex network that holds the American underworld world in the 1970s, shown with the profusion of strokes ranging from 1013 police until the attainment of the blue magic, since a security system that does not hesitate to intercept a cache of heroin which will be cut and resold to the honesty of who returns a Briefcase of banknotes unnumbered; It will masterfully reconducido towards the creation of a simple story of Lords for beginners. A story of narration fluid and careful passing, failure by the edges, proving inadequate measurement of time, result of an abrupt mounting, with total safety, suffered the revision of the producer, adapting the length of the footage with a view to their distribution.Without fear of being wrong, can ensure that the major asset of this film, sometimes, as irregular as the professional career of the director on his latest projects, lies in the choice of the main actors very capable of solving action in solo, immersed in a contradictory but accurate description of characters.Thus, while the role played by the eternally deadpan Russell Crowe seems to have been removed from a "black takeover" of a prefabricated common history to perfect policemen facing members of his Department, unable to keep his private life because of their continuous love affairs (do not reminded to Clint Eastwood's performance clear?), with the extension of incorruptibility we knew in Serpico; the back story of drug dealer opts for the peculiarities of the gangster genuinely American willing to upset the balance between the families of the lower depths. And as there are no benefits or the absolute evils, and those who remain on our side not always are "one of ours"; the adulterer aware to clean his conscience without receding a bit in their longing for Justice; directly responsible for thousands of deaths, with the appearance of business that must be defended, will prove to be an exemplary son, brother and husband, that does not neglect the mass on Sundays; and life, by one of those strange coincidences of "synchronicity", will bring together both destinations to uncover one of the biggest scandals ever written in the history of the United States of America. In a final balance sheet, we are left with the soul of the footage, which is none other than the priceless performance that got moved to the real Frank Lucas, Denzel Washington; with the irresistible image of Richie Roberts in jeans, with the great moments glued with bullets and perseverance. We are left with the devastating scene of the Thanksgiving giving way to the ravages among consumers of a city covered in white powder, with the retime the stairs that lead to the heart of the New York police, the arrest produced in Harlem, with a memorable vis รก vis, and with the conviction that the typically American resolution that culminates the life trajectory of the characters can turn it in the best film of the year. A year in which those who claimed that Ridley Scott was the best director in the world should be right.</body>
</review>
