<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="American Gangster" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excellent example of film noir today. It will be, without a doubt, one of the films that are in the list for the next ceremony of the Hollywood Oscars.</summary>
	<body>Excellent film Ridley Scott that, even if the tape is custom, achieves a very interesting Chronicle of the late sixties and early Harlem of the seventies, when the heroin came in the country and with it great corruption to all levels it, made shake the American society.Scott get a fascinating portrait of a time and two antagonistic men, the best professionals in their own. It does so thanks to a rich script by Steven Zaillian, who always withdraws all common, and an agile direction, with a wonderful montage, brilliant performances and a bright, clear and concise narrative energy.While it lasts two and a half hours, or you find out, being entretenidísima at any time. There is not a single plane over and downtime or little interesting simplemennte not exist.A thriller of gangsters and policemen, which will delight the most demanding Viewer.There perhaps the level of ethics is something controversial, if you want, because it is true that, despite the fact that the prologue may not be more clarifier on the personality of the protagonist, at all times get, if not sympathy, yes the admiration or respect for his person. Being a lethal criminal, who did so much damage in reality, it can be this wrong fact. But in toto moment seems to me that things are clear and not fool anyone here.In his short epilogue, that has been said enough, maybe it's true. It could have been cut perfectly, but Scott and screenwriter have shown for, I say, we can see that progress, what represented the protagonist in his profession is presented in all its ferocity, after almost twenty years. "An irony, or simply evidence.""American Gangster" will, undoubtedly, one of the films that are in the list for the next ceremony of the Hollywood Oscars.</body>
</review>
