<review author="Moebius" title="El hombre invisible" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>So please, ladies and gentlemen. Pass and "see" one of the strangest phenomena arising from Universal Studios. But beware, watch: the next time that they have "a breath in his barn", be cautious. Perhaps Claude Rains is there ready to make your own!</summary>
	<body>The stranger walking moves in the middle of a strong snowfall in search of refuge. With all that snow falling barely we can distinguish a coat and a hat. At a nearby Inn, the patrons chatting, drink, sing to the sound of the piano, are spent jokes. In short, have fun in the heat of the fire. However, to enter the strange everything changes. Covered with gloves, a scarf and a strange dark glasses, his face is hidden to the prying. While it is not tourist season, the owner of the Inn accepts prepare a room for the disturbing traveller. Little could imagine that angry his new hidden host a great secret.The invisible man, based on the immortal eponymous work of writer h. g. Wells, is another title emerged the new policy adopted by Carl Laemmle Jr. in the Universal to shoot big-budget films based on classics of fantasy and terror. At the head of the project was placed to James Whale, the wizard of the gothic horror and the light comedy which had provided his greatest success, the adaptation of the invisible man Frankenstein.En studies still have a scientist playing God, although on this occasion the terrible consequences turn forward to glory chemist in his own Monster. However, the Gothic atmosphere gives way to a sort of threat as invisible as a virus, causing a more characteristic of science movies horror fiction of the 1950s: top messages, collective panic, police mobilized. On the other hand, the hunting man and the distraught Lady and other elements of the film are a mere continuation of the already treated in Frankenstein.Por other side, view today, never ceases to be curious blend of horror and humor that used to build Whale in their work. I imagine that it would be to relieve some tension to a spectator bit accustomed to so many emotions, to then take it again to the paroxysm of horror. Anyway these small interspersed jokes do not harm anything to the tape and are quite endearing, and the almost magical sense of the pace of Whale is one glued to the screen for little more than an hour of film that anyone could say that they are just a few minutes.Of course the most spectacular moments of the film come hand in hand with really sublime special effects for the time. Never ceases to be fascinating to see how under such heavy clothes only there is a vacuum worrisome. How many spectators chillarían to such show?Considering that his face remains hidden during most of the film, see the dubbed version of the film (which has been my case) probably subtract much to the performance of the great Claude Rains; without going far James Whale chose him for the role by his voice, so if they have the chance they won't see the invisible man in its original version.Among the rest of the cast include Henry Travers (the Angel of how beautiful it is to live!) as the Chief Scientist and friend of the character of Rains and a sosa Gloria Stuart (the snowing of Titanic) as desperate girlfriend of the invisible chemical and daughter of the undaunted Travers, it seems that he treats every day with invisible men. Among the side is undoubtedly Una O'Connor, the homemade Grump married the innkeeper calzonazos. Your profile means halfway between Witch and Miss Rottenmeier, one is them enough alone to generate good comedic moments, as it would demonstrate later in what would be his last film, witness for the prosecution. Villagers suffering from the heavy jokes of the invisible Rains include character actors like Walter Brennan and John Carradine, although I have hardly been able to come to recognize none of them. Who I have been able to identify is the charismatic Dwight Frye as a journalist to interview the Chief of police.So please, ladies and gentlemen. Pass and "see" one of the strangest phenomena arising from Universal Studios. But beware, watch: the next time that they have "a breath in his barn", be cautious. Perhaps Claude Rains is there ready to make your own!</body>
</review>
