<review author="Dragon negro" title="Monster house" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good movie that can enjoy both children and adults and is one pleasant entertainment, another animated film that surprises.</summary>
	<body>Recently digital animation film is that more pleasant surprises comes giving fun, entertaining films and with consistency, exceptions clear. But Monster House is another proof of that, the second film of animation from the hand of Robert Zemeckis, this time only performs tasks of executive producer, with the invaluable help of Steven Spielberg, leaving the direction the rookie Gil Kenan, will have more luck than the failed Polar Express Christmas story, as its theme is by far much more appealing than its previous.We are Monster House in the typical neighborhood of American houses, but one of these houses is not what appears in reality and its owner is an old Grump that does not allow anyone approaching or even to your garden. D.J. is the boy who lives in front of the mysterious House, and obsessed with her, gets the day observing and pointing every detail that happens. An accident will the old man disappears and the House is single, it is when D.J. and his friend Chowder will have to face seriously to the House, which seems to come alive at times.We could classify the horror film for children, but it is really a funny story that perfectly combines the history of fear with loaded with humor moments. There are scenes and notable moments as the first time that the two friends are with the girl and the two want to impress her or the couple of policemen that are the most surreal, for highlighting one.Monster House improvement at the level of animation results with Polar Express using the same technique, with real actors that should be every day a suit and special shoes and then makeup is them put a rubber head and a reflective points on the face to capture each of body movements and facial expressionsthen acting in a kind of set that was a totally empty box where developed its roles. Then would have step the process of animation and decorated. The characters are much more cartoony this time I even dare to say Burtonianos, and we have actors of the stature of Steve Buscemi giving life to the grumpy old haunted house or Jasón Lee making friends with the babysitter, but without doubt the most notable performance is that of Kathleen Turner giving life to the House.A good movie that can enjoy both children and adults and is one pleasant entertainment, another animated film that surprises, one of the best proposals for this weekend if we are going to the cinema.</body>
</review>
