<review author="Javier Martínez" title="Roma Ciudad Abierta" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The fact is that this film never leaves indifferent, gives equal that the you've ever seen one, seven or a thousand times. Still tearing apart me the screams and the personality of the Magnani, the interrogation to the engineer, the monstrous coldness of the nazi leadership and, above all, father Pietro.</summary>
	<body>Sometimes a cry more than language, becomes a symbol of such force that there are no words to describe it. Anna Magnani gave the film the best of all (see below), is like the Munch made film. It is curious that the owners of the two most famous shouts of classic cinema, and I forgive purists if I left any, die halfway through the film, both Magnani here as Janet Leigh in "Psychosis".But there is much more than the heartbreaking "!"Francesco, Francesco! "." The performance of Aldo Fabrizi as father Pietro (based on a real event) trembles almost as much as the cry of Anna Magnani. None of what he says in the film is priceless, they should get a book only of their phrases written ex aequo by two geniuses such as Rossellini and Fellini. When see you in any comedy, more or less 90% of his filmography, may understand that piece of actor was this man.I know that the world has known heroes with cassock but, as he himself says, it is his duty to help the downtrodden. Perhaps instead of so many demonstrations to the family, tinsel, commissaries, encyclicals and dirty people like Rouco Varela maneuvers should export more the image of those living in the midst of the horrors of famine, disease, war and suffering. Others, that vadean it and move onto dogmatizing without knowing what is the world real do not more that denigrate the ideals of unsung heroes and encourage every day fewer people take them seriously. I am sorry to say this, gentlemen of the top brass of the clergy, but did more Aldo Fabrizi in an hour and a half to you in twenty centuries. You continue sucking of the udders of power; and those who belong to "the Church", which really helps people, forgive me if I have offended them. It was not my intention to offend them neither you nor your creed.Leaving the extraterrestrial issues, it is essential to point out this film as the pioneer (along with "the shoeshiner" by Vittorio de Sica) a film that put the camera to ground level, depicting reality and suffering and setting aside any hint of glamour and sophistication. Here was born the neorealism, even today continues to draw the best movies, Yes, those who nobody sees of Iran, of India, of Russia, &hellip; films to avoid film us suicide dandruff and producers more interested in his collection of Cadillacs to do something useful. Certainly, the world would be worse if there had been the same Neorrealismo.Al that almost all Italian neorealist films the actors aren't professionals (except Magnani and Fabrizi), that also should be ashamed a lot star media of their time both now. When I saw "Bicycle thief" I could not believe that they were not professional, really. Perhaps it's true the Italian theatrical character, who knows.The fact is that this film never leaves indifferent, gives equal that the you've ever seen one, seven or a thousand times. Still tearing apart me the shouts and the personality of the Magnani, the interrogation to the engineer, the monstrous coldness of the nazi leadership, the revelations of alcohol of the general throwing Earth the ideals of the Aryan race and, above all, the father Pietro after seeing this movie, Ingrid Bergman wrote to Rossellini: "Dear Mr Rossellini: I have seen his films"Rome""", open city" and "Paisà" and I have really enjoyed. "If you need a Swedish actress who speaks very well English, which has not forgotten the German, which can be made to understand in French and in Italian only know say you love, I am determined to come to Italy to work with you". Too much modesty for an actress that was on top after having triumphed with "Light that is dying", "Casablanca", "remember", "Chained", or "Do for whom tolls bells".The rest of the story already know: end of era Magnani, global scandal and Bergman as muse and wife of the great filmmaker did more to the height of "Rome, open city" (was almost impossible), left masterpieces such as "Stromboli" or "You querré always".</body>
</review>
