<review author="Silvia Giner" title="American Gangster" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the "supposedly" country of opportunities where you can be who you want and at a historic moment where the mafia is facing major changes, "modernization" runs this story that transforms the dreams.</summary>
	<body>The 2007 closes with one of the best games of this year. American Gangster, directed by Ridley Scott master one of my favorite directors and one of the most loyal to his actors are turned in fetishes of the interpretation by repeating experiences in his various films. And if there is an actor that Ridley is addict that is Russell Crowe. This actor that is like good wine (the older is better is), has an admirable ability to create an authentic universe within each character. Each character has their tiks, way of speaking, andar.este man is one of the greats. What about their co-stars Denzel Washington is an authentic animal before the camera and Chiwetel Ejiofor begins to solidify his career, all these players have something in common and is "what have achieved" cinematically speaking is the product of many years of effort and withstand recondition on the face. Ridley has consecrated as they deserve through of several of his films and now returns them to unite with a truly spectacular interpretive result. A 10 for all stakeholders; Side, transfigurations special, are all sobervios. The interesting thing about this story is not what tells us about the gangsters, but as you can get to reach and to truncate the American dream. In the "Supposedly" country of opportunities where you can be who you want and at a historic moment where the mafia is facing the biggest changes "Modernization" runs this story that actually transforms personal dreams and realities in nightmares. In this film as in the Filmography of the director, his magical form of the story is full of magic in every one of their frames and that is precisely what has your interest from beginning to end. Fair dose of action, impoverished photography and a horrifyingly ugly miss Puerto Rico are some of the notable things negatively of the film. It is true hell, as it can be a Miss Puerto Rico with this skin and that face, in short it is very ugly. In conclusion highly recommended movie. Churchill at War, Body of Lies, and Factor X are the films that Ridley premiering in 2008 and you can guess who are sharing?</body>
</review>
