<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="August Rush (El Triunfo de un Sueño)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It could be defined as a simple and emotional musical story suitable for all audiences.</summary>
	<body>As a lover of music, nearly so much as the film, any proposal that is able to unify both arts seems very attractive why, despite the terrible poster who used distributors in Spain for August Rush, could not pass the opportunity to see things so shocking as the guitar shock or delight me with songs performed by the selfsame Jonathan Rhys Meyers (that same thing put you Henry VIII of grunge with equal) (success) Freddie Highmore, is Evan (aka August Rush) an orphan who is able to see and hear music everywhere. In addition to the music he argues that you listen to the voices of their parents and therefore decides to escape to fetch them. Will soon discover a special talent to play instruments, inherited, even without knowing it, of their parents, that will develop as a way to find them.The film actually does not enjoy an exceptional quality and possibly if we remove the musical numbers would be little more than a pleasant chapter of a children's series (very frame looking for his mother) but the combination it really alluring and magical in equal parts by the three protagonists: Freddie Highmore (seen in finding Neverland and Charlie and the Chocolate Factory)Keri Russell (which finally lifts head very decently) and Jonathan Rhys Meyers (which I will not add anything else because it would clearly sound biased). It could be defined as a simple and emotional musical story suitable for all audiences.The major slump of the film comes from the hand of the unclassifiable Robin Williams as always sobreactuado and unbearable in a sort of pseudo trip to Oliver Twist as "the magician" an exploitative child musical eccentric (because of course, a child prodigy of eleven had put an end to a troubadour of fair) who teaches him to exploit the musical talent playing in the street. This part of the story is absolutely and even get to do heavy (not only by the presence of the said actor) not worthy a final result correct and quite entertaining.Attention to Terrence Howard, who plays the wizard of minors because everything portends that she will be his year cinematically speaking.</body>
</review>
