<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Possibly the best product of the Spanish film of the year and the closest thing to a blockbuster that can shoot today in Spain. The problem is that the story is very light and is quite predictable.</summary>
	<body>Released two months ago and converted almost to the moment in the great success of the Spanish film of 2007, it is high time that comment here my opinion on a film that I took me to see for lack of time and took to comment on due to lack of enthusiasm. "The orphanage" is, I want to make that clear, possibly the best product of the Spanish film of the year. A type of commercial cinema that we should do more in our country: directed by Juan Antonio Bayona (that you predict a great future), with one camera more active than usual in our cinema, a wonderful sound, effective art direction, a good soundtrack, good performances and some really disturbing moments, that manages to maintain the interest of the viewer during the slide. Put another way, the Ribbon is the closest thing to a blockbuster that can shoot today in Spain. In fact, it has nothing to envy to the American blockbusters that burst ticket offices around the world. Every euro invested in the making of the film is seen on screen and it shows, I repeat, the high level of production of the film. The problem, for me, is another. The problem is that the story is very light and is quite predictable. Already been made so many movies of supernatural terror in the history of the film and so many and so many years there already, just, to the surprise of all. By that when the final moments, superbly directed on the other hand, one cannot avoid a disappointment. For example, and without leaving the Spanish film, I have to say that I've found more than one resemblance to "The room of the child", the episode directed by Alex de la Iglesia to the series of tv-movies "Films not sleeping". For this reason, who ends up becoming owner of the function and prove once and for all that she is a good actress that must be taken very seriously is Belen Rueda, able to suffer on screen as few and worthy of all the praise it has received and could be extended, to a lesser extent by having less weight in the final result, to almost all his co-stars. In short, a film that is well, a perfectly topped product but it offers nothing particularly novel and that, in my opinion and despite what they say many, is not the best of the Spanish film of this year. Final rating: 6.5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
