<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Michael Clayton" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>George Clooney and his co-stars are the best of a film that sails half way between the legal thriller and drama without reaching opt for either of the two options and what could have been a tad shorter.</summary>
	<body>Five minutes to start the projection of "Michael Clayton", we see the central character climbing a hill and sit staring at a few horses. In that scene, George Clooney shows us the great actor is and how, without histrionics, may show the internal collapse of a character. Until the final part of the film we will not know what is what has led to a man as he so painful situation but just by looking at their eyes is clear to us that he is a character in a position limit. As clear as the interpretative height of a Clooney we have that many, until recently, considered little more than a guaperas.He and his co-stars are in my opinion, the best of a film that sails half way between the legal thriller and drama without reaching opt for either of the two options. Indeed, both Tom Wilkinson and a wonderful Tilda Swinton are worthy of all the praise and his works are perfectly nominables to the oscars this year, as it also, course of Clooney.En the other side of the balance would be the correct work of the director, Tony Gilroy, that while deserves some credit for the good performancesIt must be said that hand in hand goes it with the pace that could have been more successful.So much footage was not necessary to tell this story, I lengthened 20 minutes more than necessary, possibly due to the current idea that the films "with a conscience" have to be long to feel important.The film boasts a well bound script (by the own Gilroy) and requiring to be attentive to small details, as some book that demonstrate a respect for the unusual Viewer.That and the performances, especially that of Clooney, are the highlights of a film that will not go down in history but that turns out to be a quite right entertainment.Final rating: 6 out of 10.</body>
</review>
