<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Viaje a Darjeeling" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What was great films of Anderson was the combination of his prodigious imagination and his acid sense of humor, and Darjeeling Limited marks first but not second</summary>
	<body>Very few times a short film has given so much that speak in a festival as Wes Anderson's Hotel Chevalier in the Mostra of Venice. And all, because it appeared an integral naked Natalie Portman. Naked when the truth is anything but a nude film, and that Israeli actress quickly repent. At least this time not demanded that it eliminated the final Assembly, as it did in short Closer.Dicho form part of the Darjeeling Limited film, in fact is his prelude, which introduces the character of Jason Schwartzman. After the brilliant Tenembaums Los and Life Aquatic, Wes Anderson gives us a trip to his new personal universe. On this occasion, Anderson intended to parody the spiritual and internal discovery trips are fashionable, but always makes it from the greatest of respect. Perhaps an overly respectful way, that after the first minutes in which one feels fascinated by so delusional and fearless trip, discovered the absence of irony and biting sense of humour of Anderson. As usual in the film, all the characters are more eccentric and marciano, but are at the same time pathetically endearing, and it is impossible to not catch them great affection. However, what was great films of Anderson was the combination of his prodigious imagination and his acid sense of humor, and Darjeeling Limited marks first, but not the second. And although the trio protagonist is fine, no actor has been able to better represent the characters of Anderson as Bill Murray, whose cameo is the best of the film, and Gene Hackman.Viaje Darjeeling Limited is a film failed twice, and is so personal Anderson world leaves no one indifferent. However, on this occasion, even his staunchest supporters will be disappointed.</body>
</review>
