<review author="Silvia Giner" title="La brújula dorada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Infumable product for children takes Christmas to ensure a place in the market of the Trilogies.</summary>
	<body>With a budget of us$ S 205 million, this film is convirtie in some of the most expensive productions of the producer New Line Cinema.Este film is an adaptation of the famous and award-winning book lights North of Philip Pullman. The Golden Compass is the first part of the trilogy dark matter. I very much fear that we are going to have to endure next installments as the producer wants to make your particular August thanks to the novels of Philip.A my sincerely so much history impersonator of "Narnia" already I tired. Besides that it is adapted horrosamente, the novel itself is already loaded with incruencias, for instance, the figure of the Gipsios (Gipsios = Gipsy = Gypsy = bone that it is as say Gitanoide this is not offensive? whatever it is is unoriginal) bear skins to dress up. but let's see, if all animals are Dimons (human souls) and when it dies the human the Dimon evaporates from where her pussy take the skins?. In summary the story sucks on all sides.We have everything, lack of pace, failures of racord, which well well disaster.Nicole, Daniel! How you convinced?. I imagine that the poor, think of the producer would paste the taquillazo as they did when they adapted the successful trilogy of the Lord of the rings. But the truth is that it has been a real truño. I have to qualify that both Nicole and Daniel, get all the juice possible their characters "the script is that it does not give for more". Eva Green (very pretty) is also involved in the film, in principle his character has too much relevance but her it is winning over the following deliveries. The protagonist Lyra Belacqua, played by Dakota Blue Richards (born on April 11, 1994) is a British actress, born in South Kensington was chosen from among more than 10,000 girls in various cities of the United Kingdom: Oxford, Cambridge, Exeter, and Kendal. The director has said of it that fully illuminates the camera with his face. Dakota has no experiences in the film above and has already signed the 2nd and 3rd installment of this series. (Please see if for the sequels can whiten you teeth because any yellow and is a shame.) This is perhaps the most notable of the film.If you want to see Nicole, Daniel, Eva and the new hollywood Dakota Blue boom, you can go to see it, but if you expect to find a sort of Harry Potter "or by hint" you go to see her. Although you can always enjoy the FX and costumes.</body>
</review>
