<review author="JLO" title="Mi gran casamiento griego" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A minor but sympathetic film achieved its purpose of being an entertainment perhaps by subtracting you points, an exaggerated expectation in advance.</summary>
	<body>Unknown Canadian actress Nia Vardalos never imagined that Tom Hanks and Mrs her tentarían to finance a film based on his own theatrical monologue, on own experiences (she is of Greek descent and her husband, who does not here the role of friend of the protagonist) without being someone fairly known in their own country.Less thought that they would accept it as a main character and that its screenplay became in the independent film highest grossing of history, thanks to both a fierce operation marketing (surpassing the already famous in that heading the project Blair Witch) and a good dose of luck.It's a romantic comedy that carries all the virtues and defects inherent in the genre. Fun as much as melosa, good gags, round, with some characters superficially outlined, very good pace and right to good performances. Nothing more, nothing less.Toula (own Nia) is a little Spanish thirties of Greek family very clung to its principles and customs. Falls in love with a high school teacher named Ian (John Corbett of Sex and the city, signs of love) no-griego - and to make matters worse - vegetarian. And the inevitable problems between lovers and the entire family, especially with his authoritarian father (a hilarious Michael Constantine) and its very comic thousand uses arise of the clean glass. Here begins the fun part with the "sacrifices" that the groom must do to be accepted by this singular troupe. Very managed the climate of traditional Greek family despite being large (all splendid roles) sometimes touching the kitsch but without exaggeration or the cartoonish. It should be noted that Nia as John bring credibility to its candid, transforming them into the column of the film and characters delivering a couple acting the former.A minor but sympathetic film achieved its purpose of being an entertainment perhaps by subtracting you points, an exaggerated expectation in advance.</body>
</review>
