<review author="Luna" title="Interview" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Acting duel of Steve Buscemi and Sienna Miller in Interview.</summary>
	<body>Interview is the fourth film of Buscemi, one of the actors fetish of such emblematic as Jim Jarmush, Tarantino directors or the Coen brothers. In this case Buscemi chooses to adapt a script of the late Theo Van Gogh, as well as surrounded by the team that usually meet Theo, included his director of photography Thomas Kist. Not just there the similarities, Buscemi opts for the same style of realization that Van Gogh: three cameras in hand and a few free actors to improvise in this acting duel between Buscemi and Miller.Tras two weeks of trial, nine days of filming and an approach in three acts which Steve Buscemi felt that he needed the history, get a result that is a real time bomb. A stage combat, a contest between two characters, where nothing is what it seems and that can only be a winner. In the words of Buscemi "is a war for power from the dialogue." The action takes place in one night, a journalist enshrined and intellectual has to do an interview for a famous actress, but choose vacuos projects and clamoring. Despite the reluctance of the journalist, we will discover that this actress has many facets.Career as actor Buscemi did that the blonde actress so superficial as it seems get him/herself and Sienna Miller a credible and successful, performances where the viewer discovers that neither Buscemi is a journalist so intellectual nor Miller.History speaks of the world of appearances and the world celebrity from a perspective that the viewer will find extremely interesting. The narrative unfolds with good pace and freshness and after many turns still holds a final surprise the Viewer.While following Theo Van Gogh style has given increased importance to the freshness of the performances and improvisations, the warm lighting of Thomas Kist underlines the history with the fair dose of glamour and becomes the perfect partner of the narration.Buscemi's upcoming projects for the 2008 and 2009 are as an actor, but no doubt with this film he discovers as a filmmaker with its own voice, and a director whose path must be followed.</body>
</review>
