<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Mr Brooks" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Failed because it aspires to much, but convincing, Mr. Brooks gives an at least worthy spectacle, which provides the unbiased viewer a return of outstanding nut to the clichés about the psycho-killer so burned by Hollywood...</summary>
	<body>The role of the psychokiller, of the serial killer taken from a manual of Criminology or America's deep and disturbed, has delivered an estimable Philo of commercial and even artistic possibilities to those who manage the crematístico matter in the all-powerful Hollywood. It was as if the murderer in question heeling his addiction to kill trails planned and exploited (the inexhaustible series of Halloween, Friday the 13th, nightmare on Elm Street and similar) or looked at the intellectual side of the bloody act of depriving the lives of others so that they arose depraved towering coefficients, illustrated in baroque painting and a conversation at the height of any circumstance the estimable Hannibal Lecter-style, absolute reference in the genre and on their own merits, inmarcesible deity of the popular terrifying imagery. The novelty of the contribution of the Harris/Demme/Hopkins támden is the appearance of the psychopath, his complete lack of physical signs that reveal the degree of disturbance that suffers from. Acts, on the other hand, betray it for what it is: a diabolical type until the naúsea. They were also brothers of guts and horror, now remember, Henry (a wonderful Michael Rooker) or himself John Doe (Kevin Spacey) in the fantastic Seven.Algunos were anointed by the breath of God and others not needed any divine breath and enough a childhood of abuse or a father ingeniously bastard for desastrar the life of the future star of evil, frivolous and coincidentally all said. Not to mention, but we will, to provoke the reader complicit smile and versed in national disasters, the presence of the black Tuno psychockiller, an infamous product of the desire that we copy outside it without commitment, style or (perhaps) knowledge. To tumultuous assassins have Pascual Duarte or Jarrapellejos, present in varying degrees in some hypothetical list of thugs in the history of cinema. Some had an alter-ego jodiente and barely presentable in society that incited them to perpetrate acts which the good soul, the civilized, either no known either it repudiated from the deeper his altered essence. In any case, I repeat not for this thread. I am not nor an expert on the subject and this is precisely not the gender that has most excited my cinephiles.Something like what happens to Mr. Brooks who plays (very decently) Kevin Costner in this failed, in part, great film. Everything is quite apparently not astonished, said Vicente Aleixandre in a poem. Costner amazed because it abandons the friendly side, buenetón, methodical parent family or respectable agent in order to deliver his craft (and it has more than) to shape a dark man necessarily tormented party by the inevitable presence of a reverse scary (William Hurt) that it precipitates you evil and we could almost say that it offers the predictable moral alibi to save his conscience and paid you to the lecherous and orgiastic sack of the outside lives. Evil in Mr. Brooks is a not very hectic cocktail suggestions and sufficiently explicit situations as the avid adrenaline Viewer out enraged and the movie buff of more restful taste and wish to see an elegant entertainment smile and understand that, without being a masterpiece, without even being a good film, round, compactrecommended without fissures, they have given for the euros of rigor is a classic film than it seems, away from the apocalyptic winds that blow and, above all, an accomplice in a way already almost forgotten to film, which is the amaze and make pleasant surprise without resorting to brutal twists of the plot or to see indications that everything has been writtenfilmed and canned to trick us. what fails then? Barely worked the script, hooked in an absolute way and it loses excessive moral disquisition and inconvenient sub-plots that never provide sensitive material to the primary. It is clouded by an excess of ambition. It malea its rich premise with a go reprise that had been able to be ignored so that the tape lasted one hour earlier. As this is not possible, they have thrown by the easiest way. Have two films in one or mount two episodes (one excellent and one very bad) in a same narrative gimmick. The devil Mr. Brooks has as malignant escort for much and dries up too soon, although the best moments (philosophies and separate lounge misticismos) give when healthy laugh about the perversion of their misdeeds and argue as two perfect partners in crime on the tricks to deploy so that the police is not silly, not caught them by too early. Mr. Brooks, the schizoid character, then surrenders to the problematic mess of guilt and there ceases to be a serial killer as some would like to mutate into a priest eaten by doubt about whether God exists or is the invention of a holding company headquartered in the Vatican. In the end.</body>
</review>
