<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Soy leyenda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Irregular, remarkable film by moments in their superiority with regard to this type of production, and that at the end and all, despite its limitations, offers something that is not anything significant on occasions in which boredom invades us, a kind of fun without excuses.</summary>
	<body>Especially gifted in his fantastic literature development in simple appearance, but at the same time difficult, whereas the confrontation and personal growth of the individual against an external element threatening, Richard Matheson acquired its well-deserved glow of writer of worship with exceptional works, novels describing this dichotomy in an impeccable way. Such is the case of the work base for the film before today us, "I am Legend", a bleak portrait of the human condition, packed with a description of the concept of solitude and nihilism, completely charming. Characteristics which, as expected, have been fulfilled in unsatisfactory manner in his transfer to the big screen in this new adaptation of one of his major works.First of all, note that the relationship of the writer Richard Matheson with film is long and fruitful, having been transferred to the cinema with greater or lesser Fortune his other novels, although to be fair, falling on the side of the approach to positive in its resolution most of them. Films like "The legend of hell house" (1973) by John Hough, "Stir of Echoes" (1999) of David Koepp, "the last man...""live" (1971) Boris Sagal, "The last man on earth" (1964) by Ubaldo Ragona, "The incredible shrinking man" (1957) by Jack Arnold, or "The devil on wheels" of Spielberg, have an obvious interest the less, being bright some of them. Precisely in the last two collaborated closely Matheson responsible pseudo-documentary for their passage into the screen, being his work in both a clear brilliance. In addition to these films, and some more, Matheson is especially loved by fans of that great series of "Twilight Zone", also being responsible for the screenplays for several episodes.The two previous versions of the novel "I am Legend" resulted in irregular results, especially popular and with an air of cult film is "the last man...""live", a really interesting film, but that seen today, it has aged satisfactorily not at all (despite being a good movie), while "The last man on earth" unfolded it closer, placing his closest to what action then all worldwide known as cinema of zombies that tape of the revealing science fiction starring Charlton Heston. In the opinion of a server, it still was to come the great adaptation of the novel so brilliant writer, but therefore will be expected back to another time.Give the responsibility of such an undertaking a Director Francis Lawrence a priori seemed a very risky work, and more seeing the results of his previous film, "Constantine", which in turn adapted the popular Hellblazer (but remember correctly, since I am not a consumer of this type of graphic novels). In that film, though Lawrence showed a certain ability to the concern, the disturbance in some scene and of interesting staging, failed to overcome the clichés of the genre in recent years, so trite just by cause apathy in the Viewer.The plot of the film, everyone will know given the popularity of the novel, us is situated in the skin of Robert Neville, the last living man convinces as if same, their routine days and his solitude with the only company of his dog, in a desolate New York, which must survive those who dwell in the shadowwhich just out of their dens when the sun sets, ready to begin their nocturnal hunting and feeding. Neville strives to find the formula that reversed the chaos caused by the virus mutated three years and 90% of the population became wild, lacking beings of every shred of humanity.The work of Lawrence as director seems very impersonal, most given to grandeur at the level that to develop in-depth the intimate story and torment internal character of Neville, vital issue that only comes to light on brief occasions, although effective, that if. Its staging, as well as in his previous film, gives small hints of what this director could offer if one day is devoted more to the plot work that to the visual, that he always has a tendency to swallow the story through overflowing special effects. One director more at the service of the show to his own growth as a filmmaker (although that is commonplace in most growers of the genre).These effects discussed, have in addition a lack of results notable, not just the film sees something burdened in the second half by the excessive appearance of beings that lurk in the darkness, they also fail to merge with the rest of the film, leaving the feeling of superficiality that, curiously, Lawrence blamed the possibility of doing a few more artisan effects, something that has obviously been a wrong calculation in the project. Not counting the scene of the port, which seems copied the previous "blockbuster" of Will Smith's name "I, Robot" (am the only beings on I am Legend seem tacked to such film robots?), and that it is so overflowing visually as unsatisfactory and free in the course of the narrative.The work of acting, taking into account the scarcity of characters from the film (removing the dreamy scenes of Neville, who are curiously well dotted in the story through memories during sleep or unconsciousness), tour the sights was Will Smith, which falls all the weight of the story, and although it is true, that the fact of being a commercial filmdevoid of double senses (beyond the absolute evidence) and deep metaphorical arguments, it did not require much more, Smith leaves also graceful work, resulting in correct and functional in their role, with a scene worthy of mention and not comment for not gutting the film who has seen him yet.Special mention deserves a script, that honestly, seems more correct, where, despite the light (and only slight) change of tone in the story from a given time when it begins the action more adrenalítica know give it a simplicity to the diary of Robert Neville already wanted passing for if same other big blockbusters (I will not talk about the stupid script of the horrendous Transformers and turns), with a narrative pace surprisingly controlled in the first part of the fim, and that is when most highlight the virtues of the film (which also them has, even if they are few). The loneliness and despair of Neville, his obsession with redemption and forgiveness of himself, to be the indirect cause of that horrible event, take over the character of Neville, giving foot in a moment of the film, the most interesting reflection of the entire film, the clash between science and faith, motivated by the null belief in God of the scientific and military NevilleIn contrast to the faith of another important character in the film, even reaching more aerated reaction to defend his atheist position. But on the other hand, the end of the film, calls into question this belief of Neville, as he had already given samples before their eternal contradiction, to go each noon to the port to see if someone had heard his radio warning message, and that it does so as an act of faith. In this subtle contradiction, not fully developed as it should be, is one of the most important elements of the story filmed by Lawrence. Although this, the film has the virtue of away from boredom to be highly entertaining.Film also contradictions at its very core, much of the film's subtle laudable intentions, faced with such hackneyed succession of special effects which sink any hope of a film that transcends the limits of the blockbuster.In short, a film failed, although by no means boring, which is slightly higher than the average of similar products by a correct script that runs without absurd twists and direct and effective manner, some bright pieces set (the first appearance of the creatures of the night is bright to all lights) and a correct interpretation of Will Smith, and even the poor dog that accompanies him. On the contrary, falls too much in the defects of the commercial cinema and that makes its own base, the very essence of the film, and it was logically the Matheson novel, see altered to create a film that does not reach to find what if he sensed in the novel, the struggle of the individual against if same.Irregular, remarkable film by moments in their superiority with regard to this type of production, and that at the end and all, despite its limitations, offers something that is not anything significant on occasions in which boredom invades us, a kind of fun without excuses.</body>
</review>
