<review author="Patri" title="Soy leyenda" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Seems a simple Christmas blockbuster, but in the background has a lot more worth seeing it although average film is not as good as the other half and remain many questions in the air, but it is worthwhile to see what it does Will Smith.</summary>
	<body>Recently most of the releases are remakes or sequels, and I am legend, a film which for the public at large is new, there are already other 2 previous versions based on the same novel, by Vincent Price and starring Charlton Heston. In this new version of the last man on earth are noticed many irregularities, the first part of the film is great but then the history gives a twist makes no worse the film which had started so well. In the first scene we see Will Smith driving a sports car while trying to hunt a deer that walks loose by the city, I read in forums and blogs how useless that is this scene, however, I think that it does have a useful, us is presenting the character, and describing certain aspects of his personality, though admittedly, given the amount of food that had been in his home had no need to hunt. During the first hour the absolute protagonist is Will Smith with the dog accompanying him, the weight of history rests on him and confirms that he is an actor of enormous, as already demonstrated with "In search of happiness", to my I loved this first part, the description of the relationship between the protagonist and the dog Sam and how the loneliness and the lack of human contact are beginning to make dent in their health mental. When the monsters appear, something not just might fit the aspect they have, too digital and the fact that there is a "head" which seems much more intelligent than the other monsters that only move by instincts. So that ultimately, I think it is a film that seems a simple Christmas blockbuster, but basically has much more, worth seeing her even if average film is not as good as the other half, and remain many questions in the air, but see what it does Will Smith worth. The second part of the film begins when the dog is infected and the protagonist is forced to kill her, in a tremendous scene, with an enormous emotional burden. After this the protagonist totally loses the head and attempts to commit suicide, here well, but when it comes to the girl child, everything is damaged, the script gives a few laps without sense incredible and it seems that at this point was when the writers began the strike leaving half a script which could have been great, as well as including the typical speech that God is very good and very bad humanYou can spoil any movie.</body>
</review>
