<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Lejos de ella" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sarah Polley performed a reading of the feelings of a couple who leads a life sharing their stocks when they are forced to take drastic action when Alzheimer's disease began to take their toll in the memories of her.</summary>
	<body>How much would be willing to sacrifice for love? And I do not speak of that youthful, passionate and torn love one experiences in the early stages of adulthood, but leisurely, secure and complete love rarely found to spend more than half a lifetime with a person. The time in which the company of the other is needed, in which the silences are comfortable and comfortable with the idea that one of the two disappear escuece strongly in much deeper from the bowels. That time in which risky Follies have moved to better life and that the best plan for an afternoon is to listen to the voice of the couple reading thousand times read, under a blanket, while you think about the present and forget the future.Probably all to check the same box of the test. If somebody manages to find this kind of relationship, I would be willing to sacrifice everything for the sake of the other half. But and if that sacrifice is risking to be forgotten? Do and if the best for one or one who love passes away of oneself? And if the happiness of your companion is the bitter unhappiness of oneself?Sarah Polley, superb actress and usual in filmographies as Isabel Coixet or Atom Egoyan, performed a reading of the feelings of a couple who leads a life sharing their stocks when they are forced to take drastic action. Alzheimer's disease began to take their toll on memories of Fiona, and although it takes a rapid awareness of the situation and tries to live with his ailing memory, there comes a time when the situation becomes complicated and dangerous. It is at that moment when she takes the determination of entering a specialized residency, trying to save his partner of a load of lifetime.Grant, her husband, is not at all in agreement and, although I would prefer be he who loved his wife, cannot be denied to their wishes. The problem arises when the rules of residence forcing the patient to stay 30 days without receiving visits for a correct adaptation to the new life. How many memories is able to erase the disease in that period of time?The story then focuses on how Grant faces this new stage of your life. Feelings of loneliness and sadness of a man with a calm character, struggling to hold on to his media naranja to memories that share. In the sacrifice which is prepared to carry out by the happiness of his wife. In the sense of guilt that lurks to errors that could commit into a relationship of more than half a lifetime.At times the plot lapses and narration slows down becoming slightly tedious, perhaps by the fact that the story is based on a short story that Polley, also responsible for the screenplay fails to expand uniformly, or perhaps due to the shortcomings that often assumed an opera prima. However, these moments of downturn are compensated with incredible force, which beat the viewer in the middle of the chest without tear gas tricks or scenes with excess sugar.These moments of great emotional intensity, they are thanks to the two main, immense actors in the construction of two extremely human characters, with strong and defined personalities that lead the story in natural and paused. Julie Christie and Gordon Pinsent are the best of a debut which shows that Sarah Polley has enough charisma and sensitivity to expect of it an interesting evolution behind the camera.</body>
</review>
