<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="3:10 to Yuma" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great film, a western upstream in the current film, who knows how to find the right point of balance between action and the characters inner development.</summary>
	<body>Many have been attempts in the past years of revival of the western, and all in vain, having still been carried out samples of proven reliability and high quality generic. Films such as the excellent (and overlooked at the time) "Open Range", or the estimable "forgiveness", put in scene a few great thoughts on the iconic sense of the genre more alien to any external influence in the form of literature or even historical, most of them shot in the genre films a compedio of an era of American society truly limited in time (a period of 10-12 years at least)being all allusion to outside this period times pure fantasy created with the aim of over-stating an anarchic and absent any moral enforcement way of life. Is for this reason that a revision of that remarkable Delmer Daves western (great movie, but nothing perfect) is a priori, wanted a more commercial decision (by way of the vast list of remakes made in American territory in recent years) than artistic, searching according to the most optimistic of the remakes, a revisitación of history for future generations in this (sic). Notable surprise meant for a server (although to be honest, if deposited hopes in this film) meet a great psychological western with a wonderful moral and deep description of characters.The plot of the film, as well as the classic version, us is situated in the skin of two antagonistic characters, on the one hand the farmer Dan Evans (Christian Bale), and on the other the outlaw Ben Wade (Russell Crowe). When the latter is captured by the forces of the law, Dan offers to accompany them to the nearest town, where will rise to Wade to a train bound for the Yuma jail, with the only goal by the humble farmer paid two hundred dollar reward and revive his indebted family farm, in the hope of a future better. During the journey, the band of outlaws who headed Wade, will follow the track to liberlo, in a race against time before the upload to their charismatic leader to jail wagon.Behind the scenes, and trying to bring to fruition so suggestive project, is the New York James Mangold, a director who presents a career full of effective work, but devoid of personality, let alone a correct craftsman in terms of the current film (remember those considered artisans makes dozens of years, they are now considered essential directors). In his journey as a filmmaker, has offered works of proven solvency, as his opera prima "heavy", interesting police thriller "CopLand" or products at the service of as "Girl, interrupted" Star Angelina Jolie or "on a tightrope" (both films with its corresponding Oscar for very limited actresses such as Reese Witherspoon and the aforementioned Angelina Jolie).The great scourge has dragged this director since its inception, manifests itself in his detractors by attacks on his little personality as a filmmaker, unable to create a staging or a personal point of view of the stories told, and this aspect has given a radical turnaround in his latest work for the film. "3: 10 To Yuma", Mangold knows to give the whole a consistent packaging and a look close to those characters so disparate that presents the story, dominating an effective and direct staging, naturalist on many occasions and a crushing sincerity in their intentions. In this case, craftsman Yes, but brilliant without doubt.You can imagine one a cast of actors more appropriate for the history after watch this great movie, while the vast majority of them to an exceptional level. Especially noteworthy performances by four of the characters in the film, the two actors main and side two of luxury. Bale and Crowe one hand embroider two roles of characters confronted in appearance, but not so disparate in the background without any effort. His two characterizations reached such level of brilliance, that when they meet face to face on screen, they follow a level of rapport and empathy acting absolutely overflowing, resulting, undoubtedly the best of the film by far. On the other hand, two secondary actors stand out above the rest, sticking out his head and screaming a higher level of prominence in future coming productions is Logan Lerman in the role of William Evans and Ben Foster in the role of the charismatic Charlie Prince, faithful companion of misdeeds of Ben Wade.Esta great acting demonstration can Excel due to a script extremely effectiveequipped with an impeccable dramatic progression, which does more than show us efectistas shootings or free scenes as in the majority of modern westerns (whose names do not want or name), being subtle and cleverly distributed throughout the footage scenes of action, in an impeccable way, at the moment. This creates a narrative that runs a balance beyond doubt, a perfect narrative duality between the physical action and inner of the characters without doing anything heavy, and through our retinas like lightning. Impeccable narrative and formal balance.In addition, the subtle metaphor involving have given greater importance to the journey undertaken by the law officers to carry his prisoner to the train to Yuma, in contrast to the version of Delmer Daves, more interested perhaps in the final showdown which in the evolutionary process that leads to that outcome have not can ignore. During this brilliant journey, we are witnessing the development of several trips, all of them parallel and indissoluble about others. On the one hand becomes special stress upon this physical distance between the two towns, but it comes accompanied by another voyage, the intern that shows Mangold with special brightness between the two main protagonists, becoming finally less than soul mates in the background, despite not to share objectives or principles, personalities counter at first, but finally equidistant. Shown above in a subtle way through brilliant dialogues, glances of complicity and acts that they honor or portray both characters.Not only shows that interesting aspect between the two main characters, but that the relationship between his son, Wade and his faithful outlaw, or Evans is developed growing form and increasingly more empathetic in a case, or distant on the other. Blurring sometimes the line that separates the good from the bad, the duty of honour or morality of pragmatism, in short, as shown by the great stories human.The negative aspects are scarce in the film, being perhaps slightly forced certain attitudes of the characters in the film, especially in the leg end of the story, resulting in empathic too much taking into account the situation in which are found in certain moments in history. And also it is obvious some tics debtor of a current film too obsessed by the blows of effect through attitudes too tied to an arrogant and overloaded modernism.In short, a great film, a western upstream in the current film, who knows how to find the point just balance between action and the characters inner development, shown with a brilliant solvency. With a few players in State of grace, some great action scenes (not yet overcome the brilliant final scene of the wonderful "Open Range"), and a message buried perhaps more debtor of the current time as in versioning film, but that by no means is less convincing. Notable film, to which only the mild Remora previously discussed prevent become a new classic (at the risk of apparently risky).</body>
</review>
