<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Promesas del Este" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An excellent film, that despite to be intimate and conventional in certain passages, does not preclude that subtle and brilliant ability to Cronenberg to show us light notes that foreshadow more show, situen the film on Olympus.</summary>
	<body>Throughout the history of cinema has constantly resorted to describe, with greater or lesser fortune, the various ramifications of criminal groups organized throughout our planet. The fact to describe the dark and part free of moral and social bonds of these groups organized by elements that even up certain principles among the members of such groups, has created in the viewer a certain attraction and empathy with these immoral characters. From the so exploited option of the Italian mafia in any of its branches (with the work Summit "The godfather" of Coppola as obvious reference), passing by the Irish mafia, including the Chinese triads (which are recurrent hotbed in the cinema of Hong Kong until exhaustion, with results in the majority of notable cases). But other groups were never motive of an accurate analysis or, failing, noteworthy beyond specific cases, as in this case the Russian mafia (perhaps due to the secrecy that the extinct U.S.S.R. always instilled in its members and misinformation given beyond its borders). So realistic and close to so unknown organization treatment seemed appropriate, but the truth is to assign the project to a filmmaker tanning in the realm of fantasy as David Cronenberg, seemed a risky decision in principle. Nothing is further from reality, that the Canadian director had already shown in his latest project, "A history of violence", which unfolds with great ease in the nearby stories, with secrets that lurk just around the corner, waiting for resurgence with vigorous force.The work of Cronenberg as director, as known for any lover of the seventh art, greatly stresses in its early days by what he called the theory of the new flesh, in which unfolded an indissoluble relationship between physical deformation and its moral consequences, resulting even applicable to a tendency to merge the human body with the technologies in a stretch of his career. Both in its inception with films such as "Rage", "chromosome 3", "Scanners" or "Videodrome" (his more disturbing perhaps in their intense early film), as once reached a status of author which was probably the best moment of his career as director, films are essential as "La Mosca", "Inseparable" or "Naked lunch", Cronenberg gradually became the champion of the transgressive fantasy film and with a point of dissection both physical and moral being human. The final stretch of his career seems, in the view of a server, highly unsatisfactory, with three films as "Crash" (with a legion of fans, but nevertheless extremely irregular), "Spider", and above all the mediocre "ExistenZ", in which Cronenberg seeks to take beyond even his obsessions, too obvious and predictable in their approach, and thereforeslowly away from the constants that made him a vital creator of recent fantasy film. But Interestingly, when one least expects it, Canadian filmmaker gives us another turn in his career, in which aspires to seek more an amorality in characters nearby common and, as demonstrated in the splendid "A history of violence", and even more pronounced and satisfactory in the film that concerns us, the no less bright "Eastern promises".History shows us as Anna, a descendant of Russian emigrants and who works in a clinic attending births, it is the night the morning taking care of a baby born to another emigrant from the countries of the East, already deceased. Through his diary, written in Russian, and that little by little it will be sorting out, Anna goes deep in a dangerous world, one of the mafia more important of all Russia, in this case, based as immigrants in a current London, the same in which Anna malvive with her parents after a breakup.The appearance of a driver who knows more about what appears, and the threats it suffers for his life to have in his possession the diary of the deceased girl and that he had suffered a terrible event in their own flesh, are the bases to create a story full of nuances and in which no one is as it seems.From a good start, with the murder which opens the film, Cronenberg makes it clear that despite being an intimate story, anytime can bloom from it the lowest instincts of the human being, through a careful staging and hyperrealist formal perfection, shows us the everyday facts of this faction of one of the most ruthless mafias that exist, with an impeccable characterization through thin details in appearance, but extremely effective as a description of an unknown world to Anna, cited as an example the localist humor used by Viggo Mortensen in his role as driver Nikolai (splendid in the role, with a full of gestures and looks sublime characterization) in the scene which exerts such with Anna, when your bike is thrown in the middle of the street. Details coming to reach each and every one of the characters in that family of criminals, described as discussed above through a subtlety uncommon, with small scraps of cotideanidad (scenes like the brothel with Nikolai and Kirill, a no less splendid Vincent Cassel, or the extremely effective and distant threat made by the head of such an organization on maternity hospital to Anna)(, they are revealing in this regard), intending to describe perfection of Cronenberg intentions in this small story in time but powerfully loaded with nuances.Narrativamente not far behind the film, with a perfect narrative parallel mode of revelation constant in the footage, which is the dual development of events through the eyes of Anna and storytelling through the words of the deceased immigrant through his diary.Tremendously powerful in its underground and rich intention to transcend, "Eastern promises" shows that not always a minimalist film with a nearby history must be flat and connotative, eternal confrontation of Nikolai of duty against his own conscience, the violence contained after a disturbing scene through family reunions of the Russian (as a brilliant and effective strain relief) mafiaall this contributes to make credible the story, working a scene in particular as a catalyst for such violence to be sensed but just not displayed in its fullness, perhaps the climax of descriptive of this history of violence as it was their previous work. This scene, which takes place in the sauna, is the highlight of the intentions of Cronenberg with the story, every human being carries within itself the duality that leads us to be unpredictable beings to let us carried away by emotions (whether part of a charming appearance as the mafia boss to become the demon that has inside)(, as on the basis of the surface caused by the frightening aspect of Nikolai, but it carries a man of pure heart), and in which the filmmaker in Ontario gives vent to the town and vengeful most violent scene in the film, with a woman struggling to survive bare of all armour (literally Nikolai found in that position, in a scene metaphorically poderosoa to be devoid of any defence) in this aseptic sauna baths.Both the work after Cronenberg cameras and the exceptional performance of part of the cast, especially those who play the members of such charismatic organization, contribute to create a film perfect quasi in which only minor details could be seen wrong, as the little deep description of a persons foot which form the family of Annadevoid of all kinds of hue and interest by the Viewer, beyond the purely anecdotal. The character of Anna is perhaps too old for the role, becoming perhaps more accurate the decision of having chosen a younger actress, which would give much more sense that rebel and nonconformist, not to say demencialmente risky attitude of facing one of the most powerful of the world mafias. The innocence of youth had more justified this attitude and it would have given even more sense the feeling of overprotection Nikolai exercised over it. Even so, Naomi Watts unfolds with ease in the role of Anna, being something limited his performance, that if.Ultimately, an excellent film, that despite to be intimate and conventional in certain passages, with a London grey by way of history hopeless as the future of those illegal immigrants who exposed guided by trafficking in human beings, does not prevent that subtle and brilliant ability to Cronenberg to show us light notes that foreshadow more to show, situen the film on the Olympus of the best films of the year. Essential, no doubt.</body>
</review>
