<review author="José A. Peig" title="Trainspotting" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In 1996 Danny Boyle offered this reflection and critique about the problems caused by the consumption of drugs, using a narrative that exposes the story with a balanced use of the comical and the bitter irony to your message to reach a broad spectrum of the public.</summary>
	<body>In 1996 Danny Boyle offered this reflection and criticism on problems of drug use and on the same society that induces the disorientation of the vulnerable minds, using a narrative that exposes the story using a balancing of the comical and the bitter irony to your message to reach a broad spectrum of the public. He gave the formula for impact to the viewers without crushing the meritorious expressive intention in a set that tends towards the simplification and the use of topics (this ultimately ends up being a lesser evil), with which we have a good exponent of cinema of social commitment akin to post-modern cultural expressions that serve reference for generations to which it is intended the product (the varied assortment of songs accompanying States of) (mood of the players plays a fundamental role as the attractive factor).Contributes little narrativamente, and altogether not goes far beyond being an aggregate of gags that structure the description of an underworld populated by beings trapped in a circle of emptiness: the image that opens the story (with the central character fleeing while the voiceover lists the material objects, which are the narcotic of the "welfare society") opposition to the closure (with the same character that ends his cycle evoking the parameters that define) ("good life"), built its essential meaning, in a message at all complacent for anyone: you're a druggie or you are a consumer of the "good life", the vacuum reaches you to the grave. Corrosive look at society, although this also entails a simplification, since that subject two lifestyles to a same proposition, which also results in a somewhat Mannerist idea. In any case, the dynamic and ribbed staging results in a merely descriptive exercise that exaggerates the profiles to be playful, employs the surrealist delirium with ease and builds his own universe without lapsing into unnecessary Bendy which invalidate the author's intention: talk to the society on drugs, not as an evil in itself, but as one piece of the fabric of things that enslave us and stripping the world of any meaning.</body>
</review>
