<review author="Moebius" title="Infierno de cobardes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hell of cowards is an essential film to understand the evolution of Clint Eastwood both as a filmmaker as author of westerns.</summary>
	<body>Lake, a village that has made his fortune through mining, is a God-fearing people, although if someone they fear more to Stacey Bridges and his two cousins, bandits about to leave prison after serving a year of conviction. They have good reason to not fall asleep at night in Lake. Some fear the wrath of Bridges. Others, knowing of his guilt, fear the wrath of Dios.Tras directing his first feature film, Play Misty For Me, Clint Eastwood returned to encased a revolver to shoot the story of a gunman with a thirst for revenge. The influence of Leone was still very evident, and the Eastwood character barely kept differences with "The man without a name" that had been popularized in the so-called dollar trilogy. The poncho had been left behind, but the enigma and the sardonic smile remained there.However, the unknown of Eastwood already shows signs of what will be the later gunmen of the actor and director. If with Leone the gunman was a hero as dirty as their enemy and that works the stranger who comes to town for its own benefit, in hell of cowards hidden their motives, although they will be be more personal. The old unknown Leone appears especially in the first half hour of the film; There you have noting coffins and facing three guardians, or "seducing" two ladies of the town: the bitch that trafficking be Madam and women's consciousness trapped in a miserable place.As the film progresses rogue Court gunman is yielding to the dark man, the avenging angel. Are you propose or not, Eastwood was taking a step beyond the harmonica of until that his time has come. But we can not only see the past of the Californian in the film. In a sketch of what we might see later in the magnificent without forgiveness, the director confronts his gunman with the past in the middle of the flames under a night sky. Hell of cowards not just bandits and revenge. As interesting as the final duel or more if cabe is the duel that keeps the stranger with the small town. Having left defenseless to the city before Stacey and his men, the gunman known powerful. And it is then when Eastwood brings us the hand to a walk through a village which is said to be God-fearing, but that after your Windows and doors are only greed and hypocrisy. In his drawers in their wallets in their business, they hide the guilt, the burden of a dead. A sound comes to them in their dreams &hellip; horizon distorted by heat appears on horseback the stranger, riding in pursuit of final retribution. A disturbing sound accompanies this ghostly vision until the rider becomes visible. It is then when the soundtrack begins to drop their notes while the gunman rides to Town Lake. Before the stunned eyes of his countrymen the stranger rides unperturbed by the main street. His apparent cold blood only breaks (as well as music) when he hears the restallido of a whip. A sound that the city holds a bitter memory.Hell of cowards is a duel with pistols and portrays a corrupt society that moves only by its economic interests, and whose prosperity is tainted blood (does refer Eastwood to any society in particular?) (That each draw their conclusions). The stranger does not forget this last, and will do that in due course.If the relationship of the gunman with the inhabitants of Lake is of pure contempt, two characters are crucial and cause some disconcerting attitudes of the man without a name. They are the two figures which could perhaps have justification to save the burning, but who at certain times the stranger will not hesitate to make it go wrong. The first is Mordecai, a dwarf that in sight well soon the importance of that alien, putting at your disposal. After your interested attitude however there is some appreciation for the quick silent shooter, that it will award naming her small friend Mayor and sheriff of Lake. When Mordecai asked who will give the order to fire before the arrival of the villains, the alien responds: "You do". A subtle joke about the gunman? The second character is Sarah, the woman in the hotel, the only person in the village who tried to help the old sheriff. But it ended up crushing the will of her husband, so the new master of the city not forgive you pass by his bed. Still, Mordecai as Sarah go well unemployed the subtle and terrible time revenge painted in red of a ghostly outsider emerged from the sands of the desert, and to which they return after having fulfilled his fatal mission. Hell of cowards is an essential film to understand the evolution of Clint Eastwood both as a filmmaker as author of westerns.</body>
</review>
