<review author="Moebius" title="La leyenda del indomable" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apart from one of those immortal characters of the film, the legend of the indomitable has given great scenes with wonderful dialogues, these iconic images that may penetrate the popular subconscious. Essential.</summary>
	<body>Cool Hand Luke. Go type. During a game of Poker is able to bet the limit without having a good hand. Not even a couple. Few would be able to fight empty-handed? That same wondered fortachón Dragline. But as said the good of Luke, Yeah, well, sometimes nothin' can be a real cool hand. And it is that after this "nothing" hides an unshakeable self confidence.Luke is not an easy to understand type, and lives in a world that is not prepared to accept someone as strange. It wrecks vending machines because there's nothing to do on a Saturday night. And why society condemns him to spend two years in a tough prison. Something smells to rotten in the judicial system. Don't follow leaders, watch your parking meters.Luke represents total, at all times and circumstances individual freedom, although the own physical integrity at risk. Does not accept any imposed rule, either society, prison, or own criminals who share sentence with him. According to the normal procedure someone like Luke would have gone through many hoops to earn the trust of thugs as Dragline. But this is unthinkable for someone like Luke. He prefers doing things his way, and will force Dragline that you fight with him. Dragline will give you a beating sovereign, but that won't do that Luke gives up. And the young blue eyes knows that reversing the advantage of the fear have veterans, they will not have no choice but to give up. The personality of Luke is so overwhelming that Dragline will be carried by it as a branch in a flood. "Why I have escaped if only I had two years?" Good question, Drag.Normas, rules, laws, repression. civilization, in short. The legend of the indomitable tells the story of the clash between the authority and freedom at all costs, the feeling primary and selfish to do at any time what one wants. The struggle between law and Luke is pitiless and prolonged. At all times the guards will try to break the spirit of the prisoner, make him one. And Luke will continue unabated, inventing thousand Wiles to avoid, to make it go wrong to defenders of the law. His teammates almost see it to a divine being, and few will be the times in Luke to show its weaknesses, their feelings. When he shed tears, real tears, by the death of his mother, it seems that the last loop linking to Luke with the rest of the world has been broken forever. Perhaps Luke learn "Plastic Jesus" of his own mother, he being a child. But the law knows no feelings, not in a prison like that. Luke will be locked in a punishment cell to avoid that is to attend funeral fuge. A free and independent spirit is the Declaration of the State war against Cool Hand Luke.Con like yours it is terrible to see him in the mud, pleading to the guard that not hitting him more. For those who admired their willingness to unabated it was as if a myth come down. But, after all, a man is only a man.The repressive authority was perfectly symbolized in this sunglasses mirror look at the world maquinalmente and cold. It is a resource that has been widely imitated, but have a special significance in the history of the legend of the indomitable. Not desviéis attention wherever they go. You remember as just? That smile of Luke. indomitable until the end.With a history and a script (Donn Pearce and Frank Pierson) so exceptional a film can have many interpretations. I believe that the legend of the indomitable values individuality, almost primary liberty, the fact that be different is not necessarily bad, and that confidence in oneself can work miracles. A scene as unforgettable as the bet of the eggs is a clear example. "Have you you ever have eaten 50 eggs?". Of course, no one has eaten 50 eggs, is impossible. But for someone like Luke, wanting to is power.Apart from one of those immortal characters of the film, the legend of the indomitable has given great scenes with wonderful dialogues, these iconic images that may penetrate the popular subconscious. In short, I am speaking of great moments to remember. Sunglasses mirror, 50 eggs, ditches, prisoners working in the hot sun. This stunning blonde is dedicated to hot all prisoners be while it soaping his car (wonderful Joy Harmon, who was discovered by Groucho Marx in his television show You Bet Your Life, and ended up working for him later). With this film the director Stuart Rosenberg left a model to follow for the subsequent prison films, especially those that take place in "prisiones-granja".And well, how does not refer to that mischievous smile Paul Newman in maximum State of grace, or that beloved great actor George Kennedy is going crazy with the chiquilla limpia-coches to not to call Genoveva. God, sometimes I think that it could talk about this film for hours! Or at least what lasting a couple of beers. The legend of el indomable, essential, speak little.Finally, a question: do you think that the picture that sends Luke is real or is a montage?</body>
</review>
