<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="El custodio" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The director proposes the viewer live the life of Ruben. Be present in their times of waiting in their silences. Witness a process that wakes up in its interior: from silence to the sound of the waves.</summary>
	<body>Today, Julio Chávez is the best Argentine actor. His last starring him elevated to that post. He received the Berlin bear for Best Actor with his last performance in the other. Earlier films such as A bear red, the stranger and the CUSTODIAN. All of them are essential for any understand the latest (new) Argentine cinema. A film full of silences, of dead, waiting times. Unbearable for some experience for others. The formula is being repeated endlessly, possibly symptom of creative crisis, but continues to operate in the European market "Festival", where receives recognition and prestige. In any case, the participation of Chávez in some of these films is the differential value. Interpretations of high caliber, which dominate the interest of these productions.THE CUSTODIAN of Rodrigo Moreno, production of 2005 and winner of the Alfred Bauer award at the Berlin Film Festival, and best screenplay at Sundance. After the break, a film with certain international repercussion that allows release in different countries.The story told is that of Rubén (Chávez), the bodyguards of a Minister. The film tells the life, work, of the custodian. In a thorough way, moved to the screen the transfer from one place to another and the silences, synonymous with Ruben (tense) pending. The pressure that accompanies your task &hellip; the always be present in the life of another, as his shadow. The silence of Ruben is filled with loneliness. Rubén has no one to accompany him. The silence that accompanies Ruben transmits the pressure of knowing that you always have to be present, to espensas of the other. Living the life of the other. Invisible to the other. The line of duty is the main objective in his life, until it reaches a day when that changes, the only thing that matters now is to know the sea &hellip; freedom.Beyond the slow camera movements, flat distant and musical deficiency, Moreno proposed the viewer live the life of Ruben. Be present in their times of waiting in their silences. The Viewer as the custodian of Rubén. Witness a process that wakes up in its interior: from silence to the sound of the waves.</body>
</review>
