<review author="Moebius" title="Harry el sucio" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Dirty Harry" was one of the best moments in the career of director Don Siegel, and definitively consecrated Clint Eastwood as a movie star and screen tough guy.</summary>
	<body>He was one of the detective films that revolutionized the genre in the early 1970s. They have a filipino Department requested a copy for use as training. It was one of the best moments in the career of director Don Siegel, and consecrated definitely Clint Eastwood as a movie star and screen tough guy. He popularized the 44 Caliber Magnum pistol. It raised protests and sensitivities, and many accused her of offering a fascist and violent vision of the world of crime and police. It is, in short, an unavoidable classic in the history of the cinema. Do you feel lucky, punk?The original story belonged to Harry Julian and Rita Fink, which together with the writer and filmmaker Dean Riesner outlined a draft of the script. There are sources to ensure that the inspiration for the story of Dirty Harry came from the crimes of the Zodiac killer was taking place at that time.Initially thought Frank Sinatra for the lead role and names is considered such as Irving Kershner to direct it. Sinatra finally fell from the project due to an injury in a doll, which the producers felt then in John Wayne, who apparently was not too interested, although paradoxically some years later would a à là film star Harry Callahan entitled McQ. Apparently it was Paul Newman who led in the right direction to those responsible for casting. Without a doubt, Clint Eastwood was the man.Eastwood agreed and soon attracted director Don Siegel to the project. Actor and director had worked together in three films, and that same year Siegel had collaborated on the debut as director of Eastwood, Play Misty For Me. The action moved to San Francisco, and the writers and directors Terrence Malick and John Milius gave the finishing touches to the script. It could not be otherwise, the most famous phrases from the film, especially that famous scene on the bullets, the Magnum pistol and other, they emerged from the Republican mind of following Milius.El step was finding the perfect candidate to interpret the murderer, Scorpio. Initially the chosen candidate was Audie Murphy, the most decorated American soldier of World War II, which had subsequently become actor. However Murphy fallacería in a plane crash. On the recommendation of Eastwood, the director called the actor Andrew Robinson. Without a doubt, Robinson was the perfect candidate, I can't imagine a guy like Murphy being able to show so psychotic on the screen. The test of the great work he did Robinson was that after premiering the film had to change your phone number to a private, because it began to receive death threats.A veteran as Don Siegel, who had already previously worked in the genre, showed their knowledge do, making one of his finest works. The film opens with a dedication to San Francisco agents killed in Act of service. Hence, we come to the image of the barrel of a rifle pointing directly to the camera. The impact of the image is a perfect Overture to a Symphony of violence and killings.When the sniper kills his victim, a beautiful young woman swimming in a pool, the next level introduces the character of Eastwood, Harry Callahan, wearing sunglasses and leaving a door to the scene of the crime. It is then when they begin to appear the credits and the fantastic music by Lalo Schifrin. Also the work of Argentinian composer marked a guideline for films and later series.Siegel plays with big and small spaces, opening and closing the camera field, using short levels and means for the scenes of fighting and clashes between Scorpio and Callahan, being almost always preceded and followed by a general level, defining in some way encounters between the two main characters.A close-up of the scale model of the city of San Francisco becomes a floorplan of the Church represented at that. Excellent step to another unforgettable scene, where Robinson and Schifrin shine with their own light. Cross the Park to the stadium of football, beginning and end of the first great encounter between Callahan and Scorpio. It is the stadium where Siegel offers in an unforgettable level: zoom away while opens the level, at the same time the violent police torture their prey, the ruthless Scorpio.Y is that Callahan and Scorpio are one side of the same coin. They are expeditious, and do not hesitate to use violence to achieve their aims. Only one is on the side of the law. They are therefore accountable less ominous, more acceptable? Everyone you see the movie and draw their own conclusions.It's funny to think that Robinson was a declared pacifist who didn't like of weapons; all an antithesis of Milius, for example. It reached the point that Siegel had to suspend filming so that an expert in weapons work with Robinson to ensure that it does not close the eyes or put faces of fear by shooting. Although this indicates how great actor who is Robinson, that being diametrically opposite could offer a performance so alive and intimidating. Well, do so are actors, not? The sadistic Scorpio became its own right one of the final villains of the film. And if Robinson had problems with weapons, Eastwood didn't put many hesitate to make himself the dangerous scenes, including the leap from the bridge to the bus. The San Francisco actor was also in charge of replacing Siegel when he fell ill. The endearing the suicide scene was directed by the own Eastwood.Harry the dirty caused (and I think that still cause) a great impact. In the early 1970s, it was not normal to have a protagonist who was violent to the usual way in which were the villains. The murderous psychopath, therefore he could not but be worse, being capable of torturing, killing, hitting children. the young girl kidnapped in this case would not be saved.Graphic violence had to add brief but stunning nude, including any full, and a scene so unusual and terrible as original and already mythical. I refer to the particular "session" of $200 which is Scorpio. Really sublime.Moreover, there was Eastwood, "Man without name", and an assassin to catch, and a poor fellow that went live in miracle. A Chief scolds, a policeman that dictates its own rules, the mayor who complains. they are mostly archetypal characters that have populated since the majority of series and films that followed the trail of Harry Callahan.La shadow of Dirty Harry was, and is still very long, and his influence persists in many current films of policemen. Some tapes even took borrowed directly some of the most emblematic scenes of the film by Siegel. For example, lethal weapon and his suicidal crazy, or the third part of the Crystal jungle, with Bruce Willis going cabin cabin at the expense of the evil and repeinado Jeremy Irons. And it is one of the major findings of the screenplay for Dirty Harry is that part that Harry, charge the money from taxpayers to Scorpio, makes the breath running from a phone booth to another, waiting for the call from the crazy sniper. Of course, could not close this entry in any other way other than with the phrase from the movie: I know what you're thinking. If thugs just five or six bullets. The truth is that with all this hustle and bustle also I've lost count. But this being a 44 Magnum, the best gun in the world, able to fly you the brains of a shot, do not you think that you should think that you're lucky?</body>
</review>
