<review author="Andrés Pons" title="Interview" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We have a fierce criticism of the world of celebrity with genuine nasty where nothing is what it seems. A work against the flow of the current film.</summary>
	<body>The late filmmaker, writer, Dutch actor THEO VAN GOG who gave much speak for his liberal ideas of great radical and anti-clerical expressed in some of his best-known films as LUGGER or BLIND DATE.A very controversial man was killed in 2004, leaving many jewels after if, in one of them one of the most special players in the industry HOLLYWODIENSE is fixed. I am referring to STEVE BUSCEMI a man I don't have a spectacular body, nor blockbusters, also starred in major scandals. Gaining respect in the independent scene where he worked with people of the stature of TARANTINO in RESERVOIR DOGS or several times with TOM DICILLO, fresh their last collaboration in DELIRIOUSSin doubt of such illustrious teachers well learned the trade in his facet in the direction giving small wonders in TREES LOUNGE, ANIMAL FACTORI.Two men so suggestive come together in this work where the American made a forceful REMAKE of the work of the European.To choose your partner opted for the brilliant actress SIENNA MILLER seen in casanova or STARDUST, which unfortunately is best known for his romance with JUDE LAW that demonstrated enormous talent.Two great actors, a good script, a single scenery is enough to tangle in a power struggle between the committed journalist and star tonta.¿Es so dumb star? Does not trap? The surprises occur in a story that leads with great agility narrative helped with a large photograph that gives solo decor elegance is required.Shot with three cameras in hand is vested that overwhelming pace as they move the surprises because the cunning of women is greater that that of the journalist sacándole all their dirty laundry.Despite everything is therefore a more appropriate for the theater film as it progresses you notice an anarchic abuse of the dialogue that leads to disorient the Viewer to save the boredom in a surprising final plot.We have a fierce criticism of the world of celebrity with genuine nasty where nothing is what it seems. A work against the flow of the current film.</body>
</review>
