<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="American Gangster" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It could have been so much and so much expected from it that at the end left only a very well resolved thriller police life, mobsters with moral led and policemen with sound moral principles to proof of corruption.</summary>
	<body>The American dream, his epic wrapped in the bars and stars, has sought to a genus, a sort of clear speech according to the material so greased of patriotic ideals, narrative of which part, as slave of the moral integrity and safeguarding of moral principles suspiciously inoculated in the cultural heritage of a people which has blood ties and sociological complicity with virtually all corners of the globe. These coated religion, moral principles sausages in the imposing nationalist propaganda triumphal March, also have their share of spectacle, of ironic Lair by a vistosidad often at odds with the real essence of the values political and spiritual that seem to guide their way of life, their semiotics of hamburger and ragtime, blues at the crossroads of roads and gospel beautiful in the floor of a church. The monstrous reality of the United States as a country, as bizarre melting pot of peoples, cultures and ways of understanding life can not escape the greedy eye of Hollywood. It has never been well since the birth of a nation of Griffith mancomunara in a same jar the essences of the mere circus show and political doctrines. This reagent stoked the national spirit, formed an ideology consensual, not written, maintained by a few emotional ties: the land as a gift, the Earth as inherent heritage man argument sold by Steinbeck in literature and become images by Ford in the grapes of wrath or the classic western; the sacred marriage of the divine designs and the policy so that the President, almost in the manner of royalty in Europe, works for God and man, as if that all-embracing God had recruited - human and not the polls - to guide the people and lead to the manna of the well-being and global primacy; and, finally, the loyalty to the flag, anthem an apotheosis, as symbols of an Empire does not die at the borders of the map that aims to colonize the world with its magnificent showcase of exportable icons, acceptable and convertible, with that fine way of doing things that have for marketing, own, when it is strange, when it is employed. The film has appreciated these ingredients so that the recipe endures basically with the same composition. Just change a Director by another or a good writer by three mediocre so often that really is worth. At the end there are the result, the message, the tone between the twilight and the spookiness, sublimated reality and colada lies as a caramel dulcìsimo enlivened the evening in the city. Popcorn, Coca Cola and the runrún obscurely of having already seen the same story hundreds of times and that feeling uncomfortable, slightly uncomfortable, but already imperceptible that we are selling the donkey and we already have a block with a dozen of similar beasts. No matter: we went through the hoop, believe that entertainment needs of your audience and already for a long time that we have affiliated with the clumsy membership and quiet, manumitida of any civic or moral, responsibility that attends the film to feed the monster of trade and receive, in return, our generous dose of deception, which is the primary way of overcoming the fears that continuously gives life and thus to parade through their frightened passages with the gallantry and packaging - forgiveness, cowboy - torero of our heroes on the big screen or the girl who contingency is the same and in these situations of accused archetypal uncertainty - what I come? To my President? At my God? To Jack Bauer? At Captain America? -know where to throw and what to do to prove manhood. Bad, sometimes, is that models exhibit narrative inconsistencies. Happens that America, the Northern erasing the bland Canada, leaves his sons were encabronen and amanceben with anger, almost denying the mother kind and lyrical. The American dream fades, taunts strict surveillance systems enabled for your enjoyment, reformulates the learned epic and translates to the murky Vertigo of the spontaneous and unstoppable, enrichment to the episode of power as the most beautiful of the lovers, with its erotic and definable territory. Then arises mafioso, the capitalist society of the seven seas pirate descendant, the capo gangster disciple offenders of the souls priest taught the wonders of faith and justice - poetry or non - coup of Psalm and obscurantism. In this peculiar context is possible creation of the archetype of the mafia and its full immersion in social texture, which emanates its force and where it operates its creativity for evil, morality cloudy and the burial of all the tenets of good citizenship, rights human and the usual paraphernalia of peccadilloes and large sins they commit to perpertrar his dream of Caesars in itsy bitsy. Already had titles in 1930s that took care of this image of the mafioso as tiny Emperor in his neighborhood, with their retainers and the Pleiad of blind mercenaries which did not cease to be soldiers of the cause have grew up from childhood. American Gangster arroba unshakeable leadership capacity and consents that his figure, apart from the larceny and extortion, poured blood and fear on the street, ranks the pastor or the Patriarch governed the destinies of a community, ensures she (with iron always hand) and manages his destiny. That neighborhood or city Regency buys politicians and law bodies, respect codes of conduct and disciplined forms of relay in power in a extreme inaúditos that the henchmen escalafonan by personal delegation or bursts of submachine gun. American gangster, unlike other models of more body film as the Godfather in all their examples, Goodfellas or Scarface, the price of power, WINS ways classical, without really achieve them in reliable and very credible environment of the seventies, reflected his political ambiguity, its inventory accurate lyrics - B-sides of singles from the time and funk devastating with thin strands of elegant soul - and its ochrespent then, film before scanning and chromatic perfection we spend today. Scott is a worker in Hollywood rather than an author as well, far and unreachable to apparently Visual incantations of Blade Runner or the forceful first Alien have been recruiting by the more orthodox machinery of the stablishment and as Bumpy Johnson in the opening scene, in which dies and opens the war of clans for powerHe has understood that personal relationships are lost and it has overcome the weight of the multinationals, which any Domesticity and embrace without hesitation to the dollar at the maximum performance with an effort and a minimum responsibility. He, as director, as Manager of a fantasy sold as a real fact, also left handle that already irrevocable premise of the labour market. The film is not a classic, from budgets that reinforce the film is not a great film, and can be: is a more than worthy spectacle of masses, a button of commercial cinema lavishly checked, but devoid of emotion. It has American gangster sufficient narrative inconsistencies (lagoons, whitespace, large holes like Central Park, say) to knock it down with more emphasis, but she is saved by the rigour with which the subject is treated, their unrestrained trade. Only this Office rescues the gangster number one offer for this newly lighted century. Who died left monuments, including a television series (oh yes, the idiot box winning pulse once more to the big screen) with legions of fans (the Sopranos, of course). Frank Lucas, the driver of the gangster that manifests itself in short brushstrokes of images as the guy ready and safe in the world, raises a formidable building of shenanigans and extortion of new laws of market and overwhelming evidence of seriousness and solvency. Yes, all that is fine and perhaps actually had to be so, but Scott and his screenwriter, Steve Zailian, have not careful enough and have thrown the mimbres of what could have been a peliculón overland. And it fails. The record, Washington and Crowe to recreate their roles with undeniable talent. They are comfortable and rise them to the rank of papelazos, but the script, plot, the Assembly of situations enabling the hilazón of an argument that can be followed without effort and which truly something stylish Meridian, strike, stays in very little, given the ganass of Scott for making an enduring product. The real mistake of American gangster is that clairvoyance in apply as a great movie. The product has been suddenly in the mirror of art and liked a lot. Vainly. The outrage that will solve many sub-plots and skillful, but discontinuous, of the enormous amount of characters handling condemns the film to an eternal want and can not that inevitably leads to the spectator, even to the hard-working, to a hint of boredom. And that, in this film, is a crime, because its material is excellent and is unforgivable to spoil so scandalously. They are the characters (Frank Lucas mainly) that defy the rules of consistency. Theirs is the main cause of the concern of this chronicler when assessing what have given you. Gangster is an update on key funky of the moralist of yore, who instructed with Psalms in one hand and atizaba with the stick of oak on the other. Because the control and tranquility are the big words in the life of a gangster in the light of the portrayed here. Not pantagruélicas earnings nor the power, so in the abstract, as cúlmen of a life dedicated to the crime. Everything very mystical too unbalanced to a cloudy sentimentality which we cannot assimilate. I, at least, is deducted from what I write, I didn't. Stating that I tried, but the paradoxes, the plot twists and the always very courageous way of telling things I vetoed one greater enthusiasm. The fact that everything comes from real-life situations not unmounted the impression that everything is caught with pins, good and expensive, that Yes, stylish and functional. The police very desastrado in his family life which, however, triumphs in his craft and is irreproachable in his morals and his honesty, stubborn as a few conjurado to overcome evil and restore the calm and peace to the streets of Harlem, on the one hand, and the mobster cruel until the naúsea, capable of unlock the brains of a type for the simple fact hinder their passage into a mild and insignificant time goal and then fall in love with Miss Puerto Rico, win the affection of his offspring and sit beside the fireplace as a selfless officer who has complied with its eight hours of tired bureaucracy and deserves a moment of evasion and tender domestic love. However, in the lead film scene of Christmas, this órdago mafia and cops, of pure American film of life, perhaps not a lost time. It is not. Get one of the film with the feeling that the film still has opportunities for rewrite and return to illustrate what already kept in memory with other unbeatable with new images. And how many. </body>
</review>
