<review author="José A. Peig" title="Golpe en la pequeña china" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In short, perfect example of work that - Pulp from its intentions and the idiosyncrasies of their own resources - achieves greater harmony and perfection than other films traditionally (the part of error which this has) located on Mount Olympus.</summary>
	<body>We often run into the dilemma between choose moviegoers criteria or cinéfagos, define cinema as art or as an object of entertainment as it is and come from where you come. This ends up revealing as an illusion and a sterile debate, because at the end, either from the cinephiles from the cinefagia, any individual possessing the sensitivity and proper training can identify that something abstract possessing all good film: call uniqueness, originality, significance of narration, packaging, coherence between the intended purpose and end result. and vice versa, comes from where it comes, also will be able to identify products that lack altogether of singularity. Big trouble in little china (1986) can be considered as a jewel for the palate cinéfago that, very often, will be despised by movie fan claim imposed by an alleged act of good taste, dispatching her under descriptions condescending when it comes to evaluate it, that this baby of the tradition of series b and z, aesthetics and the narrative Pulp. It is not only a film that, since a successful informal tone, get an honest entertainment, but that we are talking about one of the most genuine films that have been seen in the past three decades. Directed by John Carpenter, presents a story of a rayana simplicity with simple (it is always important not to confuse simplicity with simplicity, but in this case we are talking about an archetypal fairy tale in its foundations that follows a progression of mischievous demystification of clichés) which brings together with an unusual desparpajo elements of myth and the Eastern magic, the mythology of the westernPolice film and the martial arts film, all this subject to an exhibition of the story who walks among the uncanny and the comic, being both a zany adventure in an underworld of passageways, hidden cameras, wizards and creatures of the underworld as a comedy of clear parodic intentions, especially in the creation of the antihero Jak Burton, parody to the clichés and the iconography of references on which it is based. The narrative impetus that animates, is a remarkable example of action cinema as soon as he squeezed the possibilities of its theme and the means used without leaving the pot that was conceived, i.e. It provides a repertoire of magic kinematic respecting the laws of the spoof universe containing those characters whose gestures - along with the burlesque tone in dialogues - define the unique type of possible look that could be applied effectively an absurd history altogether, which is not easy. Develop a versatile and creation of great expressive qualities on the basis of an agglomerate of clichés of the comic book, film and television - and concocting various subgenres - is a feat. Jak Burton (Kurt Russell) is emerged from the mythology of the western anti-hero, a cowboy mounted on his truck, encroached in the rescue of the girl, which will star in a scene very little seen in the history of cinema (deconstruction of one of the greatest places common and repeated endlessly) when, in the penultimate sequence, refuses to give the kiss of farewell to the girl in the film.In short, perfect example of work that - Pulp from its intentions and the idiosyncrasies of their own resources - achieves greater harmony and perfection than other films traditionally (the part of error which this has) located in the Olympus of the classics of the seventh art, as for example The Party, recently evaluated in this booklet.</body>
</review>
