<review author="Kiko de España" title="Death Sentence" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With permission of Jason Bourne and Tangier, the best 2007 action sequence, a shot of adrenaline and a bit of moral lightness.</summary>
	<body>Who I was going to say however that I vomited about Dead Silence and its director would begin the year by saying what his last movie touches the genius? A couple of seasons ago our mentor Tarantino crept down his sentence in the promotion of the fast-paced Running Scared that read: you're never prepared for a film as estaAhora am I that appropriates the phrase to recommend Death Sentence: the most brute commercial movie seen in a long time. The proof of the crime was badass, Death Sentence is gross. Taking into account that the plot is not the typical story of revenge when in fact could be the mother of the films revenge of the new Millennium did not go into details of the plot (tramáticos) that if you keep away from any trailer you can even get surprised at several points seriously.The first thing is to tell you that the best sequence of 2007 (there there with Tangier) is among the 42 minutes and 51 of film, a sequence which will call persecution and parking. Well, we can only applaud the bastard that gave us Saw by planning and executing with a verve that De Palma of a couple of decades ago would have given his good hand: in a false flat sequence (false is unimportant, I insist that if it is not the best action sequence shot little last year missing) located in a parking lot the action occurs at a frantic pace in which the viewer enters head and where those who have heart problems it will happen fatal, than this is film of that which say that is it now that the cinema of truth is dead and where influences ranging from Siegel to Stranglehold, do I understand?More tidbits.The character of John Goodman appears out of a script of 90 of these QT wrote to Oliver Stone or Tony Scott (or who would like them to buy) and gives a (false) break in a plot that is a shot of adrenaline as politically incorrect as perhaps extremely melodramatic desktop: the family is said so and so hard that at times you don't know if you're watching one of Bronson or one of those that makes now Rob Lowe and ranging from families, leukemias and/or Christmas.Of course, can take you in face the general ambiguity and Pilate syndrome, but I still think that us not like us to both the film if not for the blessed lost political incorrectness for decades and is left sparingly seen today in movies such hijaputas as a Death Sentence, which still does not have Spain (Vigalounge) release date(, are not alone) does not matter, the dvd is on its way and step ended with a couple of questions: who is the genius who decides to change 75% of the album covers/posters when appear in the domestic sector? why in Sitges not scheduled Death Sentence instead of Dead Silence and thus the whistles had probably would have changed by some applause delivered?</body>
</review>
