<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Interview" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Buscemi goes a step further and shows us a concise and brief account of wounded characters, emotional scars and emotions who sleep threatening inside each of us.</summary>
	<body>Exemplary understanding of the world of the film can be described as the acting career of Steve Buscemi, an excellent interpreter whose long career has sustained in the role of strange character, or losing all that represents so well that physicist squalid and disturbing. Be able to change log from work under the orders of people as the Coen brothers or Quentin Tarantino, to do so in productions intended for rapid consumption (Michael Bay to the head), without losing too much charisma on screen, is extremely difficult, and denotes an overwhelming knowledge of the system which has welcomed him with open arms. Neither art nor show, but quite the contrary, as they would say some.After this brilliant acting career (although I repeat, with roundly heinous films that probably allowed pay their bills, and more), Buscemi gave a step beyond little more than 10 years ago, when he directed his first film, "A last drink" (Trees Lounge), a small history he was noted for being a sincere choral portrait of a series of losers and trivial concerns. After this film success in his debut, he directed a couple of films below ("Animal Factory" and "Lonesome Jim"), that incidian in this portrait of the middle-class with few pretensions of greatness, and some episodes of popular series ("Oz" and "The Sopranos"). All this in a period of little more than ten years, which has combined this work with his usual, and almost always right, work as an actor.With his new film, named "Interview" (especially revealing and enlightening about the plot of the film), Buscemi goes a step further and shows us a concise and brief account of wounded characters, emotional scars and emotions who sleep threatening inside each of us.History shows us the routine and especially unpleasant task receives Pierre Peders, a former journalist of political events, been less and with little intention of giving special attention to the character that goes to interview in a local elitist. Katya, a terrifying b-movies and actress clamoring TV, very popular and with an air of diva, with that arrogant look which gives know it is recognizable and desirable by the Legion of followers that possesses. After a nasty face to face, dinner ends abruptly and they have to follow their way each one separately, but an incident in the taxi, makes Katya look in the moral obligation to help Pierre and make sure that it has not been damaged, this leads them to the luxurious loft possessing Katya right near the place where. Once there is when both characters are discovered little by little, leaving aside the character, to discover the person hiding behind such superficial facade.In his work as director, Buscemi ran a serious risk in the face of a story like that has dared to shoot, and is to meet before a story whose narrative rhythm and dramatic progression depended not on a mise en scene hedging or a development of physical action, focusing above all that dramatic progression on the level of depth that could reach the personal relationship between the two main characters of the story. I.e. all hanging by a thread but was able to penetrate in the emotions of Katya and Pierre, and the truth is that's got especially windy so risky initiative, brilliantly a server I would say.All based on an extraordinary script, a master piece of contrasting emotions of subtle behaviors, so illogical on occasions as our own emotions dictate us. Some dialogues are converted by own merits on the basis of the story, and do so with a busy growing drama as it progresses the confidence between both characters, souls lost in works where the pressure from day to day, the effectiveness of the moment, carries with it an additional and suffocating pressure on many occasions.The acting work of both performers could not be outdone to get the true essence so laborious compedio bright and deep dialogue (or in their absence, superficially ironic sometimes). Even in that the film is victorious. And say in that, because while the work of Buscemi as an actor is extraordinary, with a point of view in their actions full of black humour, or even devilishly sarcastic at times, was less predictable than an actress Sienna Miller, usually confined to the role of girl vase function, function as well, and knew endure the interpretation a great as Buscemi duel. While it is true that the work of he leaves the feeling of greater showcasing, Miller not clashes in this emotional confrontation face to face with the character of Pierre, which already is especially remarkable, for all those that we considered this girl just a face beautiful.In addition, the film has the great virtue of not staying in the personal history of these two characters, giving rise to an underground irony with regard to the world for which both have decided to belong. Especially striking is the fact that the character of Pierre appoints Katya as little more than a mujerzuela capable of achieving what was lying with men, which, taking into account the shape as jumped this girl to fame, is a considerable ironic daring. Or even that subtle reference to the frivolous and superficial world of Fame awarded productions aimed at the general public, is Buscemi precisely someone that "sold" to it, in a display of self-criticism on the foundations underpinning the overwhelming film world.It stays in this so successful production, resulting in the most interesting point of the function (and precisely that Word would perhaps be more adjusted to the story, seeing that you it's a work close to the theatrical interpretation and the essence of the mockumentary), the confrontation between two minds without the more minimum sense of ethics. Starting the story as absolute antagonists, because one is a cynical journalist and disillusioned with a desire for, allegedly, to change the world through political means, and the other a snobbish and actress more aware of inconsequential setbacks, or continue being spoiled beyond where it will. And finishing as the reverse of the same coin, both using the medium in which they work to give rein to lies and half truths, not being so far away the positions of one and the other as originally believed.Perhaps in the negative section should be cited certain resolutions of the action in the story, or the little credible decision of Katya's help the journalist (as long as one does not understand another way to relate it to the end of the story) and take it home. And above all, that end with twist in which the tone of the rest of the film, which without being bad, could have been more bleeding and less condescending, in my opinion is a little lost.In short, a notable film, a strange case as predictable American production, a baby of independent cinema and history that speaks of how complex and cheat it is human mind and soul. A notable film, with excellent actors and a script, which is a breath of fresh air and the confirmation that some actresses, as well as attractive, have something more to offer us. Remarkable.</body>
</review>
