<review author="Heitor Pan" title="La gran aventura de Pee-Wee" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The plot was true roll Burton, a flamboyant character, surreal scenes and an adventure very out of the ordinary, but what was obviously a film commissioned for the showcasing of a comedian.</summary>
	<body>Go disaster (eye am not even speaking of the film, but it would be a good start). I open a special on one of my fetish directors and it is that takes me a month to the first review. There was no possible excuse, so yesterday, with some enthusiasm, we sat down to see the directorial debut of the great Tim Burton, a commissioned film entitled "The Pee-Wee's big adventure", the only Director that I remained to be seen. It wasn't long until we wonder if we would have not wrong film. You might have never thought that 90 minutes of Burton could do endless.It ran in 1984 and Tim Burton, with 26 years, had begun to sound in the film scene after the short films "Vincent" and "Frankenweenie". At the same time, a comedian named Paul Reubens, triumphant on television with a unique comic character named as Pee-Wee Herman and Warner Brothers wanted to launch actor and character to the big screen. "Frankenweenie" reached the hands of Reubens, which didn't offer the address of the Burton.La film plot was true roll Burton, a flamboyant character, surreal scenes and an adventure very out of the ordinary, but what was obviously a film commissioned for the showcasing of the comedian, therefore that Tim Burton could introduce was limited to very few scenes with his particular aesthetic.The plot revolves around the character of Pee-Wee Herman, a neuter type of childish voice, behaviour extravagant and egocentric, always dressed in a gray suit and Red bow tie. A sort of cross between Mr. Bean and Chiquito la Calzada. This character will be involved in an adventure full of flat and stereotyped characters in search of its most precious asset, a tacky very tuned red bicycle.From the first frame to the last, we are flooded by excessive personality of the character, so if after the first five gags, so you've already begun to hate, as I did to me, just wanting to not only that Pee-Wee can't find his bicycle, but that ends up dying with pains at some point in its search. can find something in the universe of Burton in this shed? Then some another stroke. Some surreal detail as a window overlooking a fish tank, some pumpkin of Halloween, a surrealist dream with scenarios that evoke the world of the dead in "Beetlejuice" or a scene from Ghost with a host which becomes for brief moment a character of his personal imagery. Too bad that these details are not sufficient to lift one of the worst movies I have ever seen.The only salvageable part of the movie, apart from these two or three scenes, is the soundtrack, which was the first of a long collaboration between Burton and Danny Elfman, just broken in one of his films to date. Burton was a fan of the group by Elfman, Oingo Boing Band, so he convinced the Studio to risk with music. Elfman and Burton sintonizaron from the first moment and the composer would be linked, from then on, the world of cinema, with his particular style of music.Interestingly, the director does not have my dire vision of the result. According to his words, when referring to the poor reviews that came out after the premiere: "Came out in many lists of the worst films of the year." It's funny, but I see the movie and does not seem so bad. I love it. It may have some weak moments, but it isn't so bad. "It was pretty devastating, I had never spent that." Burton is an undemanding spectator (and the truth is that neither I, nor those who know me consider me too picky) or it is difficult to do with objectivity a work, which seems very normal.It is fortunate that after this offer you the opportunity to direct a film more personal, because but, today, can not be writing in this special.</body>
</review>
