<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Ora o Mai Piu" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>While sometimes it fail in ideas or how to treat them is a tape entertaining in which if they had measured the personal and romantic part with more tino could have achieved a combination almost remove his hat.</summary>
	<body>David is a model student entering a prestigious University College in the city of Pisa. A review of finishing his Bachelor's degree in physics entertains at a meeting with one of the multiple leftist student meetings of his University. While David is not a big fan to the policy if it is Viola, one of the fundamentalists and suspended its consideration to not have submitted the rest of the summer happen it along with his new friends more concerned of the borrowed social concerns which of his own books.What looks like a film most adolescent love with some political background is actually of the few films that dare to narrate the bit of recent history which was the Summit of the G8 Summit in Genoa and the events that took place there. Now I will tell a batallita. When he was held on 19, 20, 21 and 22 July 2001 was in Rome, a German friend decided to take a train and go to the peaceful demonstration against the Summit. One of the teachers of the school tried to explain to him that it would not be safe. This week the news put scenes of how the center of the city he barricaded, metallic doors blocking access and up the army was summoned to ensure the safety of world leaders. Three days our friend returned with a gap of fifteen points in the head because nothing more reach the city received a with one blow (in the literal sense of the word) and finished in less than an hour from his descent of the train in a hospital and interviews with average Genoese police. In this film I was almost expecting found in images of file or in the own part of fiction.Perhaps that is why I think attractive Ora or Mai Piu, while the Genoese journey continues to be an anecdote in the history of David is a part important and very little treated in the recent cultural and political history in Europe. Ora or Mai Piu can be translated literally as "Now or never" and is how it describes one of the young people the need for action to change the world. It is a Leif Motif perfect for the tape but lack a little enthusiasm to carry it until the last consequences. Anyway and while sometimes it fail in ideas or how to treat them is a tape entertaining in which if they had measured the personal and romantic part with more tino could have achieved a combination almost remove his hat.</body>
</review>
