<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Mr Brooks" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An absolutely mediocre film, with a television bill impersonal and lacking nerve narrative, with a script that is lost in parallel stories that never end of of flow with fluidity, a flat realization and a horrible Assembly.</summary>
	<body>In the times, in which the thriller has now joined the list of genres seen through a vacuous aestheticism (except Honorable exceptions, that there always are), the intention of Bruce Evans, director of this "Mr.Brooks" failed, is clear from the close-up of the film, a way of making films, to create a film look looking back in time to recover. But all good intentions definitely drag a difficult burden of drop, due to the film before us resorted to worst tics of a thriller than a server type remember you those samples of suspense from the beginning of 1990s, as given to the television bill. Influences of which I will talk about below.First of all, the plot of the film, we placed on the skin of Earl Brooks, a successful businessman, owner of a terrible secret, has an addiction to the assassination, disease he believes had left behind until that one day, after two years without killing, returns to his mind, and does so in the form of demonstration material, physical in their eyes, his alter-ego, the party criminal if same, name Marshall, which in those small demons of the wrong so common that appear on the shoulder of the more crazy cartoons, although in this case materialized as a dark character, incitement le to commit more murders. When an unusual forgetfulness in it, forget one small detail in a scene of the crime, a photographer he blackmailing to to witness one of his murders in situ (which by the way, Brooks had promised if same not to perform again), so pena denounce him and end up behind bars. Starts a game dangerous for both characters, adding to the argument the persecution by an agent of the law (and rich for more INRIA), name Tracy Atwood, which Brooks begins to feel a certain admiration. To make it even more convoluted argument, the daughter of Brooks returns home with a dark and terrible secret.As discussed above, any element of the film is its fair point of balance and it does precisely the work of Bruce Evans trás cameras. Filmmaker more seasoned in the field of the script to the direction (not in vain his first and last film to date goes back to the year 1992, and it was the irrelevant "Kuffs poli by chance"), Evans knows not how to adapt to requiring the film and pinning hopes. In the field of the script, also had been extremely irregular, being responsible for pseudo-documentary the interesting "Starman" (directed by John Carpenter) and especially his great work to date, "Account with me", one of the best (if not the best) films on friendship in adolescence performed to date. On the contrary, be responsible for memeces as the story of "Cutthroat island" (if you have some slight interest, is not precisely by the horrendous script) or "of jungle jungle", subtract any shred of credibility in this filmmaker returned to the fold of the address.To a server, the film you greatly reminded those thrillers of early 1990s, popular among the general public, despite having a television bill that missed any claim to make a film lasting overland. Even so, the influence on the tone, the private tension and condescending look with the amoral characters (in a tremendously superficial way why) of that time thrillers as "Bad influences", "The hand that rocks the cradle" or "Rio Salvaje", all of them of Curtis Hanson (filmmaker who Luckily, then evolved giving rise to one very interesting director)(, albeit with a tendency to decline in his career again), or the now-forgotten films Joseph Ruben, like "Sleeping with the enemy" or "The good son", me are obvious in a supposedly aseptic and supposedly minimalist tone in the Mise en scène.It is a pity that the final product is not at all a film satisfactory, more than anything because the starting point, the interesting manifestation of the dark side of the mind of Brooks, could have been shot with more subtlety and effectiveness, instead, becomes one character of the film, and that plays against the credibility of the story. Another interesting aspect a priori was the game that gave the criminal mind of the seemingly perfect man, as a reflection on the dark side that everyone tends to, or should, hide, as opposed to its pristine presentation in society, and even family. All these transcendent aspirations of the film do not work none of them, due to an abrupt narrative pace, with parallel stories that far from enriching the film, only make to create a narrative confusion, which works more catch-up and looking for the alleged charisma on screen of Kevin Costner and Demi Moore (really mediocre in its work both), a narrative that catches the viewer with narrative pulse, thing which the film lacks completely.Bruce Evans lacks at all of a sunset in convincing scene, not even a narrative pulse or visually enthusiast, everything is cold and distant, with a convoluted and absurd script that takes the characters to the less questionable decisions, a wildly mediocre film in its final outcome. Contributes to this not too much elements which collide quite on the plot of the film, only then we can understand that condescending look, even in the final resolution of the story, a killer as Mr.Brooks, while giving rein to the reactionary concept of the family which has in places like which produces this film still unacceptable (and is not the first time that we can suffer in American productions)(, not to forget the only truly negative aspect who presided over "Embarrassing mess") the mere fact of asking a young girl abortion, in a display of fanaticism and handling than any mind open and thinking. Kill what you want if you have good heart, but you never ask you not to have a child still a young girl or teenager, really irritating.The work of actors does not help much to improve the film, rather than nothing since both Costner and Demi Moore are limited to put faces of indifference (the little credible cited pressure of Demi Moore in the parking lot, incredibly mediocre Mr.Smith character), resulting in slightly better, although not much, William Hurt as manifestation of the personality criminal Brooks or Dane Cook as discoverer of the "art" of the assassination new fan.In short, a film absolutely mediocre, with a television bill impersonal and lacking nerve narrative (despite being a genus given to this as it is the thriller), with a script that is lost in parallel stories which have never just flow with fluidity, a flat realization and a horrible Assembly (without going any further, the terrible Assembly of side events at the scene of the crime Recalling Brooks steps by the incarnate agent by) Demi Moore, is confusing and terribly mediocre), giving rise also to more characteristic of a misunderstood modernism scenes (scene of persecution by the stairs, without sound and electronic music, should be nominated for worst scene of action of the year), that of a sober and powerful film. A bland piece that although to be entertaining at times, gives rise to obvious defects in all the elements that make it up. Totally dispensable and irrelevant.</body>
</review>
