<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="30 días de oscuridad" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film very irregular and failed, but to which must recognize you that at least it isn't particularly tedious and takes place with some fluency, if we neglected its topical resolution.</summary>
	<body>After a successful career in the field of the video clip, David Slade made his debut in the long two years ago with this excellent example of psychological terror that was "Hard Candy", film recognized by various associations of critics at the time, and even winning three awards at our nearby Sitges Festival. A story in which playing the cat and mouse by two antagonistic characters, a mature photographer with dark intentions and a seemingly fragile and innocent teenager, resulting it last the great winner of the film with a prodigious by the young interpretation Ellen Page.En their next step within the industry, David Slade took one of the usual ways that driving the evolution of the new American fantasy film directors, adaptations of graphic novels, in this case that concerns us, a mini-series written by Steve Niles and illustrated by Ben Templesmith's name is "30 Days of night". A story which not is situated, as well as the film, on the skin of a number of characters who live in a small town in Barrow (Alaska), place which, as reads the film, it is the highest human settlement in the area. When it comes to the month in which the darkness seize the place, since it does not leave the Sun in that period of time, and temperatures will be frigid, most have to leave the place during that period, leaving only some people. But a series of macabre events, and the emergence of a strange character that heralds the arrival of the horror, kept in suspense to the Sheriff of the place and his assistant. Soon after discovered her arriving of horror, announced by so bizarre character, due to the invasion of the town by a group of vampires, blood thirsty and willing to not leave anyone alive. The task of Slade after the cameras is not so convincing in his directorial debut, nor much less, if at that the Mise en scene sought a formal minimalism that helped the creation of tension between the characters, the total absence of free elements which diverted the attention of the excellent performance of the actors, on "30 days of night" still more old roads of the genusstill recognizing him certain style when it comes to shoot some truly effective terror pieces set. His work is very conventional, we imagine that you owing to the already proven tendency to bend before a pattern pre-established in the genre over the past years, a form of shooting fantasy film that is doing to endanger any hint of prestige that can become so suggestive gender throughout the history of the seventh art.It is fair to recognize Slade, a certain skill, let us hope that he made in his next films, risking a little more in the Mise en scène and above all better choosing scripts that decides to bring to the screen. Some scenes of the film justify this assertion, as the attack by one of the characters on the horde of vampires that teem by city impúnemente by a snow plow, shot in a direct and effective style. Or without going any further, the great plain air during the massacre in the streets of the town by the vampires, seen from the distance air brings a macabre but beautiful contrast between the Red of blood and the pure white snow that surrounds the place. In these scenes, and some more is better not to mention for not gutting part of the argument, Slade shows that with something more commitment can become strong within this type of film worth. Even in some splendid attack from vampires, it unfolds with ample ease.The great issue to deal with in the film, the fact of the isolation, and as endure a month hiding in the village, not is Treaty as it should, proving too abrupt and quite illogical on its resolution, a pity, because as it is usual in these productions, the beginning of the film, and certain passages, was to presage a becoming much more suggestive story and with more possibilities that finally we are on screen. On the other hand, is dealt with the history of confrontation and isolation of the way conventional and repetitive, with a constant succession of topics of the last American film genre, i.e., characters who make decisions absurd as separate for illogical reasons among others, appearance of vampires at the moment less appropriate for the characters, but more predictable for the Vieweralways staying in the retina a sense of deja vu constant. A real shame because the story was for much more. The work of stakeholders is even more poor, not highlighting any cast member in that paragraph, the performance of them all quite predictable, topical and flat, in the best of cases, with some alarming cases (excluding certain main actor which I would not dare not to speak of surname Harnett), as the horrific description of the leader of the vampires, although probably motivated in advance by a description in the script absolutely ridiculous. This character is due to the honor of the worst dialogues of the film, and that they are scarce more not being able, with a succession of absurd phrases, nonsense and what is worse, with pretentiousness sought in their stupid actions. A server is still asking that demónios meant the inconsistencies released by her bloody mouth.Logically, as I said above, if the proposal stands out slightly, in a fun, above the majority of proposals of the style, is because of the suggestive location, more that could have been, that finally resulting as final product. If that add some salvageable scene in which, as commented, Slade shows small know-how in these situations (also notable decapitamiento in the swing, especially that flat overall final scene), because we are faced with a product, that despite their tremendous limitations (not to mention cheeky influences from the film, as a misunderstood aquellla "Ghosts of Mars")(, here changing the aggregate and reddish Martian soil by the nevada Alaska, but being a clear reference in the final conception of the film, or who knows if in the graphic novel even), offers a divertimento for hardcore fans of the genre. A film very irregular and failed, but to which must recognize you that at least it isn't particularly tedious and takes place with some fluency, if we neglected its topical resolution. Again, an opportunity lost.</body>
</review>
