<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="First Snow (La primera nevada)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mark Fergus chooses for his baptism of fire in the area of the film a claustrophobic history not so much space, but of emotions, with highly satisfactory results</summary>
	<body>Close to the independent spirit of can be described as the opera premium Mark Fergus, filmmaker best known for his work as a screenwriter, not only in his debut on the big screen logically, with excellent results in his best script developed to date, "Children of men", one of the best productions of science fiction in recent yearsin which he worked closely with the director of that film, Alfonso Cuarón, and several other writers. On this occasion, Mark Fergus chooses for his baptism of fire in the area of the film a claustrophobic history not so much space, but of emotions, with highly satisfactory results.The story shows how Jimmy Starks, the perfect prototype of perfect ruthless seller without scruples that would to sell their products, hangs in the middle of one of their small villages of the American Midwest road, when your car has problems, and should stay a few hours until they fix it to go home. There awaits Deirdre, his girlfriend, unfamiliar in the evolution of the events that mark a before and a later in the life of your absent partner. When Jimmy (moved more by curiosity than the belief) comes to a man that has the supposed ability to see the future, and has their place of work in an old caravan just the side of the bar where Jimmy spends the hours waiting for your car, do not imagine that a series of premonitions are fulfilled and should even raise the credibility of such claims. One of these visions greatly, marks a fact of their future which can make you tragically and against which becomes obsessed since then.Mark Fergus moves with ease in an area predominantly close to the American thriller, one in which secondary roads, talks of bars road and characters without direction or destination, mark the narrative and the development of the characters. His screenplay is consistent and develop away from clichés or turns of script in order to provoke a false surprise effect, but nevertheless move forward with strength the narration of the story. His mise en scène is conventional and with a certain formal distance, which gives the film a visual appearance suitable for the story to tell us. For its part, the work of the actors is something irregular, perhaps by the own intended emotional estrangement to develop throughout history from a point of view outside the emotions of the characters, with the exception of our main character, Jimmy Starks, starring Guy Pearce, that great actor someday will be recognized as it should (extraordinary incidentally in the magistral "Memento")If it conveys its harrowing fight against their own destiny with a superb characterization. Of the rest of the actors, mention to certain side as the visionary himself or the sick mother of his old childhood friend, that with few lines of dialogue are perfect in their role. The rest of the cast moves in a certain predictability, especially the character of Deirdre, played by the beautiful Piper Perabo, that is limited to show off Palm as the vase prototype of women who populate certain films of the genre.Film multiple readings, especially in regards to the way as we face our destiny, or failing that, the development of the present to have one. As escape from our destination, which makes bloom in our inner fears and ghosts of the past, creating therefore an unhealthy obsession that can be a burden in the present, to the point of becoming puppets of a destination that only provides fragility that is afraid. A way of penetrating the human mind and our own fears.In addition, the metaphorical vision of the typical American secondary road, seen in this film as solitary, aseptic places, lifeless, as the present and the future that seems to wait for this group of losers whose lives take place without a fixed direction, towards a road loss with echoes of any character in the films of David Lynch. Perhaps there lies the great virtue of the film, but which in turn may be the scourge that's ruined with any intention of reaching all kinds of audiences, the film runs slow and leisurely, coldly, like that first snowfall expected so afraid Jimmy. In short, a great film with great virtues and few defects, including the fact mentioned earlier of his alleged coldness, which sometimes can move away from the intentions and motivations of the characters. To a server not him was problem no waiting with tense calm development of events. Notable film that is close in its intentions and development, although a step below, with another great little film aired recently, name "The Lookout", and not just with the comparison made by way of false advertising for this film "Memento", which only has the similarity of count Guy Pearce in the performance, and its uncertain future in fiction.</body>
</review>
