<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Arma Fatal (Hot Fuzz)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Fatal weapon" undertakes to deny the fact that to find us with a parody so overused as the action film gender, should be treated with neglect or contempt for their own origins.</summary>
	<body>It is sometimes a difficult decision give him a chance to films as "Fatal weapon" ("Hot Fuzz" in its original title), and have the initiative of approaching the rooms and check-out probably even more. During the last years we have received, especially from USA, plenty of films which spoofed various genres, from comedy to horror, and also through the action genre. "Which, incidentally, has the gift, or call it as they wish, turn out to be tremendously popular, and remain in the collective imagination, not only arguably, but in the form of coletillas that everyone has in mind after seeing much of them.""Fatal weapon" undertakes to deny the fact that to find us with a parody (subtle, that Yes, but by no means less parody) gender as overused as action cinema, should be treated with neglect or contempt towards their own origins.There lies the great virtue of "Fatal weapon", part of the respect and admiration that causes its director and screenwriter (latter work with four hands with his usual actor Simon Pegg) genre action, to give a turn and through the subtlety create a perfect recreation of English humor, with a clear but at the same time subtle cynicism in his transfer to the screen.(The team creator of such notable film consists director Edgar Wright, also a writer with the aforementioned Pegg), and a regular cast in his movies, especially Simon Pegg and Nick Frost, always protagonists of their misadventures. Wright for this type of comedy talent was already evident for three years with no less great parody of the film zombies called "Shaun of the Dead" (called "Zombies Party" in its absurd Spanish title), which like the film before us showed us a few clichés of this type of film, to subvert them and bring them to the spoof ground, always from the respect, as in "Fatal weapon". Prior to that proposal, his popularity was already notable, especially in the UK, for a series that dates from the period of 1999-2001, of "Spaced" name, and which already contained the Basic constants of his film. His most recent work, after "Fatal weapon", try one of the fake trailers for Grindhouse Tarantino &amp; Rodríguez (named "Don't"), and the already announced production "Ant-Man", about a biochemist that can communicate with the ants.The plot of the film we placed on the skin of Nicholas Angel, a model police of London whose perfection and high number of arrests creates envy in her own body of police, starting with his superiors. Nothing better than send him to a small village called Stanford, which is considered the more idyllic and people with fewer cases of violence and social disturbance of the place. Once there has as companion, after a revealing first involuntary taking of contact, an inept police name Danny, to help you try to demonstrate as much social perfection is not possible, and that beneath all this hides a bad latent and causing several considered fortuitous incidents by the majority.The work of Wright after the cameras is worthy of all praise, as already demonstrated in his previous proposal, knows how to move the camera with ease, and above all, how to create tension from the comedy, which usually failed by the majority of Directors, that either they are devoted to remain static in the Mise en scène, or fall into absolute mediocrity in that regard. With a simple script in their development, but while being effective, constant allusions to certain ICT action film, or even some burlesque vision of the life of provinces, occur at a pace slow and narrativamente impeccable. Nothing is spared in this film, since a parodic vision of the typical buddy movies (or films of fellow cops) Americans, until an own vision of very bloody British society.With constant allusions to such productions come from the USA, always subtle as discussed above, the own film becomes a voluntary homage full of love and understanding, while ironic film that parodies. As an example of where the shots in this British production, an enlightening scene in which Nicholas Angel (Simon Pegg), the polícia aimed at the small town of Stanford, and his partner Danny (Nick Frost) are preparing to see a double session of action cinema, so fond of is the latter to these productions go. The double session includes "Call him Bodhi" and "Two rebel cops", after Danny moved with scenes of the first (and try to Nick analyze the film from the point of view realistic police), when it comes to the second we see a plane in which at the moment of maximum tension fall asleep as a vindication of the film action before and a certain cynicism with a view put in the Michael Bay Film hipervitáminico. All this trying to the Viewer as it deserves, without absurd explanations or obvious jokes and therefore without minor grace (more or less as a whole series of "Scary Movie" style and sucedaneos, always so mediocre).The vision of some aspects of British society is not far behind, and the british lifestyle receives attacks everywhere in this production (made by British must not forget). From the stupidity of the police of people to squabbles caused in the British capital between the own companions of Nicholas Angel as this the epitome of the perfect police, without forgetting that all prototype of social and cordial relationship in that, apparently, idyllic town, is seen with very bad grapes (obligations by Sergeant go to stupid public events)(suspicious intentions of hiding any behavior outside the ordinary for not disturbing the peace of the town, etc). A great example of containment which should learn in certain places, some of them not very distant with prototypes of fascist cops and bad taste, as look at certain aspects of a society without falling into the film shabbiness with irony.The great work of the actors is very helpful to the verisimilitude of the characters, Simon Pegg is wonderful in its work of hard poly that hides an incommunicado and crushing loneliness, while Nick Frost is not far behind in an interpretation of a pariah of the police station, an incompetent fellow that, if it will teach his new friend of the capital value of little things. The appearance of Timothy Dalton in a comic role autoparódico (remember that this man was one of absolute paradigms of the action genre for a time with his role as James Bond in the 1980s), is histrionic in his concept of ancient icon of the genre.In short, a remarkable shows spoof film, although that Yes, subtle and intelligent most of scenes, a film that a server recommend going to see without waiting unnecessary histrionics by very contradictory as it may seem, to appreciate it in its fair measure. It is acceptable to admit that the last few minutes of the film have nothing to envy to any American action film production, in which nothing is safe, or viejecitas bike (don't miss that plane please, sensational), or kind of sellers, not even the priest of the village. While the film may be little transcendent and does not become a lasting film sample, if that fulfills its purpose more than, with dignity and a remarkable claim to have fun.Highly recommended, no doubt.</body>
</review>
