<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Interview" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interview is a fierce, biting and acidic critique to the world of the star-system, frivolous and interests surrounding it and everything what generates as a result.</summary>
	<body>For those who are dedicated to the film information, a movie like Interview we are happy for several reasons. First of all, we like to see our alter ego film singing the forties a Hollywood diva. But fortunately, all stars as the character of Sienna Miller, nor all the informants are like the character portrays Steve Buscemi. No, they are much worst on each side.And it is that although it hurts us, at the end an interview not just remain but a clash between two people with completely opposite objectives. This is another reason why we like a film as Interview, that it leads to the general public a history (distorted and taken to the extreme, that Yes) of every day for many of us. Full of references and tributes to the late Theo Van Gogh (the fan in this ridiculous restaurant, that detonating truck of history), author of the tape version Steve Buscemi. Buscemi shows the side more wild and competitive of the human being in a theoretically as civilized as the film industry and journalism environment. It is the strange way in which these two characters face, two selfish cynics who are such for which, what makes it different to Interview. And the magnificent interpretative duel between a Sienna Miller who signs their best work to date, and an actorazo of the likes of Steve Buscemi, as large as ignored by the scene to criticize in Interview.Interview is a fierce, biting and acid criticism to the world of the star-system, frivolous and interests surrounding it and everything what generates as a result. And for those who we live closely, although our alter ego is not very well stopped, seeing a movie that shows all the magnificent decadence surrounding the celebrities we are happy.</body>
</review>
