<review author="Moebius" title="Días sin huella" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Days without imprint" became a film of reference when it comes to portray addictions on the big screen.</summary>
	<body>Oh demon alcohol, sang Ray Davies. Alcohol, as in life, has been indispensable in Hollywood, both inside and outside the screen. The years of prohibition gave rise to dozens of films about gangsters, while in the years 30 and 40 the Gallants and detectives always walked with a Cup in his hand while they chatting with the beautiful girl. The drunks were funny and endearing, guys like the characters of W.C. Fields or those side of nose of red of the films of John Ford. But that trend began to change when in 1945 Billy Wilder shot one of his films hard and realistic, The Lost Weekend, translated into Spain as lost weekend.It all began in Chicago, where Wilder had to carry out a transfer of trains. To regret the time bought a Novella, written by a that Charles r. Jackson, who continued the excesses of an alcoholic for five tortuous days. The novel was The Lost Weekend, and when Wilder ended read it decided he had history for his next film.The director and his collaborator, Charles Brackett, who also served as producer, worked on a screenplay which was fairly faithful to the novel. The story revolves around the failed writer Don Birnam, whose inability to write has pushed him to rely on alcohol. Despite the efforts of his brother and his girlfriend, Birnam has just always falls, and in a squalid decline of several days until "delirium tremens" writer plays Fund, in what constitutes a realistic of an alcoholic portrait as he had not seen until then.Lost weekend leaves not too much room to comedy, and it is by the time a fairly realistic portrait of the subject of alcoholism. Not demonizes too much to the addict, or he becomes a monster devouring of children; Birnam is more a victim of addiction that become victims to those around them. Within the structure of the final film, although predictable, fits well within the story, although in that part the veneer of reality disappear completely, but were those other times, and everything we saw of a more innocent way.Although perhaps not we can have among the best treadmills of Wilder, the narrative pulse is excellent, and being a film of a director so great memorable sequences could not miss. Include for example the dark scene of delirium tremens, which could have come out of some film of Batman, or as a really ingenious way, through the circumlocution of circles that the glass on the bar of a bar (vicious circles), leaves the Viewer provides of Birnam slow descent into hell.The other day I remembered this film because in him performing the recently deceased Jane Wyman, which of course for me will always be evil Angela Channing in the series Falcon Crest. It is not me it seems a great actress, but he was some presence.After aspiring, as always, work with Cary Grant, Wilder opted to José Ferrer. Paramount, appalled by a story, people wanted a more gentle star to connect with audiences. When it was clear that Ferrer would never accept, Wilder accepted the proposal of the study, so that Ray Milland was finally who would interpret to Birnam. Wilder claims that he accepted Milland because his sense of humour was rather low. The truth is that Milland, that was never an actor especially well, with a role so grateful did offer us a good performance which earned him an Oscar of the Academia.Y of lost weekend was a difficult race. Wilder stated that the alcohol industry had offered five million dollars to study so they aborting the film, and that if they had offered them to him would have accepted. While taking into account that in the shooting of this film was where he met his wife Audrey, he should not believe him too.The studies were about to not release the film, and only the insistence of Wilder got that it premiered in a circuit of rooms very small. At that time the director was called to collaborate with the army, and when she returned the film was a box office success. They arrived the nominations and lost weekend he scored four statuettes. Since then he became a film of reference when it comes to portray addictions on the big screen.</body>
</review>
