<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El espía" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spy film where an agent has to spy to a living legend of the body. Good result for a tape of international intrigue, that puts us squarely in the FBI and other law enforcement. Recommended for lovers of the genre.</summary>
	<body>Director: Billy Ray. duration: the truth is that I do not remember, although it should not be cut.Release date: 21 December liters twelfth night at my house always has a lot of special. It is not really in my house, which is in my father, but in the event it comes well. We have been all the brothers to sleep here, and we got up when the smallest House dawns. This year, obviously, the more small was my Paul, who has complied with us until eight in the morning. Among the multitude of gifts that bring us the three Magi, this year it has fallen to my sister a laptop. And what better way of inagurarlo talking about film in what little gets on his new truck?The film is about a type that pretends to be a special agent of the FBI. To do so, as well as fight against his companions to be the best, they offer a very special job. Should spy to a myth in active service, who accuse him of child pornography use. Little by little, the protagonist discovers that it does not seem to be true the accusation, and that the real reason for his work is another.Weird these films of intrigue, with international spy reports, incredible and bureaucracies characters that convey a bad roll anything recommended. I have no very clear if the movie I liked, given that it has on the one hand seemed very interesting, but as the characters feel so sorry, then leaves you badly. And it is that actors are very believable situations, without use of any special effect, you get fully into the plot. Very interesting movie, although I finished like. Too suffocating for me, I need more ligeritas stuff.In short, spy film where an agent has to spy to a living legend of the body. Good result for a tape of international intrigue, that puts us squarely in the FBI and other law enforcement. Highly recommended for fans of the genre.To start the year on the right foot.Besitos.P.D: Couples of the members of the FBI are cattle heaven, without a doubt.Pd2: at the end, comes out this review that I love so much. If, where he says that it is a true story and tells you that the protagonist lives at Wisconsins enjoying a new life with his wife, their four children, their 7 cats and their twelve dogs. This should put it always, even in the porn movies, that looks good.</body>
</review>
