<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Navajeros" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a juvenile delinquent called the Jaro. Not be based on a true story, the end is desboca and takes away too much credibility to the whole. Although it is interesting to see bits and pieces of the early 1980s Spanish society.</summary>
	<body>Director: Eloy's Church. duration: hour and half cut.Release date: October 6, 1980.Espectadores: 810.160 human beings.Not long ago the worst Spanish actor of all time was Fernando Tejero, the eternal goalkeeper said safely of "Here no hay quien viva". That was until I seen this movie, and I was reminded of "The peak", which Henry San Francisco happens to be the worst actor. You pensaréis I must be alienated, given that you have seen crying to Fernando Tejero, but about Quique San Francisco cries out to heaven. Seriously. Inexpressiveness of his face, and smooth intonation, worse than read, gives this well-deserved award. Congratulations. On the other hand, a day I will found in Madrid the boy with a tremendous jaca, which makes me think that you have other gifts beyond the interpretation.The film is about a juvenile delinquent called the Jaro. Tells the life of this minor, its relations with the rest of criminals, and as it becomes a small armed pull and theft sector leader.It can divide the movie into two parts, a quite passable first, where we will presenting the Jaro and his friends, and a second where try to put many things in the short time have left them and I think to much lower level. Players have a level low, possibly due to the youth of the same, but dan well the pego (especially when leaving Quique San Francisco, that comparisons are odious). And it is this kind of stories allow bad actors for a hard script with few concessions. It also has a special, since regustillo that many of the scenarios are lugadores where I've been I young (as the Ventilla, all my family is from there) and my attention much.In short, film about a juvenile delinquent called the Jaro. Not be based on a true story, the end is desboca and takes away too much credibility to the whole. Despite this, it is interesting to see bits and pieces of the principles of the 80.Otra of Iglesia.Besitos Eloy Spanish society.</body>
</review>
