<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Stardust" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Certainly?Stardust? does it has achieved something that I didn't think that they would be my eyes, play the worst blockbuster of the year honour to?Do Transformers?, congratulations.</summary>
	<body>After the success of certain trilogy about Middle-Earth (absolutely deserved by the way), opened the way to the adaptation of any kind of history that was part of this imaginary world of the epic fantasy. In this case the work before us is an adaptation of a graphic novel (supposedly prestigious way of life comics) of a such Neil Gaiman, which I must admit that I do not know not only the story adapted into "Stardust", but even any work carried out by the Sr.Gaiman. Because my character profane in this type of written stories, which I admit that the closest thing I've been on them has been with the work Summit Robert E.Howard on true barbaric cimmeria, my gaze has been clean of all influence in dealing with this new épico-fantasioso film viewing, being therefore not susceptible to possible comparisons or allegations of lack of rigour in the film adaptation. Because even in these circumstances, I have not been able to find anything positive enough to qualify this film or even interesting.Behind the scenes we have Matthew Vaughn, London filmmaker whose debut on the big screen for three years, resulted in a great sample of film noir, a great cover letter in society as a capable filmmaker and resourced in order to have the privilege of an interesting career in the genre. Why was a major surprise check as he was in charge of the adaptation of "Stardust" to the film, a story that had few parallels with his film debut, if any. Present in this scene with a great film as "Layer Cake", deserved a certain rigour in dealing with new projects, and unfortunately, Vaughn has not guided by any rigour. All those virtues which had shown in Layer Cake fade at the same speed as the interest might raise in the spectator as palpable shows of mediocrity is finally "Stardust". The staging of Vaughn becomes flat, without narrative pulse or claw to arouse the slightest interest in the spectator, who attends a firing squad of clichés of the genre of heroic fantasy perplexed.The alleged story that would have us believe is about the crusade by a young man named Tristan (nothing to do unfortunately with excellent Celtic legend) to bring his beloved a star that has fallen on the other side of the wall, a place guarded day and night by a security guard that prevents any human to pass to the other side, to the Kingdom of Stornhold (although as we shall see later, the reality is that what is concerned is the inverse way). The problem comes when the alleged Star turns into a beautiful young woman that arouses the interest of various pursuers, all of them with their own motives, from a witch seeking eternal youth, to the children of the King of the place, which will have the privilege of any of them being elected successor on the throne if they reach the precious stone which carries with it such a young.Thus said, history is so confusing and irregular in their development as evidenced by a script full of inconsistencies, lack of pace and a really horrific narrative, giving rise to a sort of crossed stories to which more absurd, without never being balanced in its proposal. Everything happens to an abrupt rhythm, in which the various ramifications of the script override among themselves, without never develop within the subtlety required for the story, a real and confusing headache (and not by complicated in its understanding, but by be runnig). This does not help too some actors who are tremendously conventional in the best of cases, resulting, in my opinion, demeaning the role plays Robert de Niro as a kind of zeppelin or flying boat captain (sic), in a role which, curiously, avoids certain histrionics of his latest (and mostly mediocre) films, but curiously continues to fall in the absolute ridiculous (quote the horrific scene of the attack of one of the sons of the King to the boat)(resolved in a tired absurd and anticlimática manner). The rest of the cast does not walk much better, Michelle Pfeiffer adds nothing to a role that is distant, without charisma (not by his performance but by the flat character development), or Peter O'Toole as the King of the place that only appears briefly and like it would have missed most. Of the best young actors cast not enter much analysis, given that both Charlie Cox, Sienna Miller or Claire Danes (that despicable act when he declares his love to the hero of the function, as little dramatic capacity in such absurd interpretation), are tasteless representing topical characters of telefilm almibarado desktop.Say that little can we rescue of such nonsense, perhaps the beautiful places that illustrate the story throughout the film, or some isolated detail, as the character of Claire Danes effervescent brightness when speeds up your heart, a subtle and accurate detail, marking of a magical and evocative halo. The rest of the elements are worthy of complaint, starting with a history as part of a claim too high in its visual aspect for the null story that shows us, details as a son of a King goes on a chase with just five or six escorts marked a contrast too big with elaborate special effects, the greatness of the intentions in the story just to be a scourge when media intended for the characters or even the film Extras are extremely limited. All this confabula to make "Stardust" a product forgettable and ephemeral, flat characters, resolutions of action hasty and lacking any logic, a humor that is curiously more absurd than any product of lighter intentions, and ultimately, a complete lack of narrative pulse, dan ruined with all intention of credibility in the film. One could speak of have influenced capital works of previous decades in "Stardust", but compare this film to delicacies as "The Princess Bride", "Lady Hawk", "Dark Crystal" or even divertimenti effective and unbiased as "Willow", would be a display of lack of notable real trial. "Stardust" should feel proud to do a work like "The Chronicles of Narnia" may be considered a good film, even less children being deliberately that from its first inception.In short, a bland work is an inconsequential product, and what is worse, boring and less narrative rigor, without nerve claw, predictable and overly sweetened even in certain scenes. Surprised to see how he has had its public sector which it has enjoyed, showing signs of fear by true lovers of cinema of the place toward which he is addressing certain genre cinema, and as ever we become less demanding in terms of quality film, something certainly worrying and that he should think about more than one. The requirement of a minimum of quality should not be an argumentative attitude but a movie buff duty in every rule. Since then, "Stardust" has achieved something that I didn't think that they would be my eyes, dispute the honour of worst blockbuster of the year to "Transformers", congratulations.</body>
</review>
