<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Im a cyborg, but thats ok" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie dream wake up and being drawn by this great love story between two patients who need each other. Wonderful.</summary>
	<body>There are occasions in which speak of certain directors is a film lover pleasure incomparable after view or revise his works, and the case of the South Korean film director Park Chan-Wook is just one of them. Once again a success at the diana of good cinema with this work on solitude, the need of a loved one and find the place in this world.The argument we placed in a psychiatric centre to which goes to Young-Goon due to his refusal to eat since they locked to his grandmother, and the fact that, literally, is considered to be a cyborg and fears that if you eat you can lose that capacity. There swarm inside a series of characters which more stranger, but it will be Park-Sun (played by the popular Rain) which most associate with her. This implies the fact that Young-Goon asked to use their "skills" to steal his compassion in order to kill all the doctors and residents of the Center, that this own compassion prevents him from doing so.Thus, the argument can frighten more than one, and taking into account that we are talking about an Asian film, which are always received with some suspicion by the Viewer, runs the risk of this marvelous film work go unnoticed.The work after the cameras by Park Chan-Wook returns to be commendable, with a new demonstration, as he did in his popular trilogy on vengeance, that we are faced with one of the best values of the global film scene. A director can take each and every one of the stylistic and technical resources of modern cinema and give them a personality on screen that leave open-mouthed formal perfection get. Chopped, close-ups, close-up, etc, always gives them a visual capability which refers to a realism magic remember to films like "Amelie" but high to maximum power in the particular case of the movie before us. Your use of the frame, the colors, the audiovisual magic, is a feast of references moviegoers and visual metaphors that turn this director in one of the newest of the current film, but which most.Would paragraph acting, highlight the excellent interpretation of its two main actors Lim Su-Jeong playing the "cyborg" and the aforementioned Rain creating the fun Park Sun, who know how to give him a magic special performances, without ever falling in excess or in gestures that carried the end be outlandish, an excellent acting job.The film is metaphorical richness that only after several viewings can acquire its true dimension, the use of images surreal, the contrast of colours which we have used director, always in accordance to the emotional of the characters look, all this carries itself same an air of unique, innovative and original in its results filmrather than in its own plot conception. A visual imagination full of ideas, stylistic resources and wonderful scenes. Cite the extraordinary scene of confinement in adjoining rooms of the two characters, his way of contact and his struggle as such surreal to overcome their own emotional or psychic, conflicts with that communication through the two vessels and the thread. Or go no further that plane of Kiss where she "off" literally from the soil of the emotion, just great. They are so many and so many images that are in the memory in this rich film that would be impossible to list them all them, even a comic tone which gives a smile of complicity charming in the spectator (the scene of the battery power level) or the dreamlike scene of the massacre in the hospital, or humour (the conversation with part of his grandmother stuck in a bag by way of farewell is descacharrante).Perhaps to put a but it would be fair to admit that the script occasionally is schematic, where images and the visual aspect sometimes exceeds the development of history itself, given that so much visual and stylistic imagery is not its counterpoint in any realistic aspect that gives to those moments his true emotional value to 100%, fortunately compensated ably by the director using inserts of fine irony or visual humor.In short, a film that follows in the line of great films that shows year after year this extraordinary director, although on this occasion maybe more misunderstood probably by the viewer average than previous films, precisely because of the own conception of the film and their intentions from the beginning, the plot marks much and probably not suitable for all audiences.A movie dream wake up and being drawn by this great love story between two patients who need each other. Wonderful.</body>
</review>
