<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Viaje a Darjeeling" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Hotel Chevalier short possibly the best of the tape. I make it clear that even the most assiduous followers will agree Darjeeling Limited is one of the worst films of Anderson to date.</summary>
	<body>I'm not a big fan of Wes Anderson, almost I could join the Group of opponents of the Texan filmmaker and wield against him the problems of its own idiosyncrasies and his indie-fanciful humor. But still aware of this and analyzing the film as knowing of its peculiar director and screenwriter must make it clear that until more assiduous fans they will agree that Darjeeling Limited is one of their worst films to date.Three brothers quite disturbed psychologically (and one of them even physically) embark on a unique journey for spiritual discovery. Actually the biggest of them has set them a trap so that they reencuentren with his mother who disappeared detained in a village lost in the India becoming a nun and that not even attended the burial of his father.Absurd humor of Anderson is not a mood of gags and jokes if not for situations and dialogues to the limit (sometimes even surpassing it). Thus the actors chose to give life to his brothers protagonists are also an example of this. Adrien Brody, Owen Wilson and Jason Schwartzman, to which more ramshackle and physically corrupt than the previous get at least one little bit of consistency sickening at all.Anderson does not resign because his fetish actors and in fact enjoy even allows the luxury of inviting to pass to the party to Bill Murray in a few early first and flat promising that quickly fade. In this display of gifts is also the projection of the short Hotel Chevalier, which is possibly best of the tape, a prelude on the story told in the film where the brother played by Jason Schwaetzman is reunited with his girlfriend (the same Natalie Portman naked which will happen the rest of the tape by phone spying) in a Parisian hotela highly successful short so it suggests reveals more than it really is, a kind of summary of the movie has plenty of ways to explore but wasted mercilessly finishing always in streets without exit.</body>
</review>
