<review author="José A. Peig" title="La noche de Halloween" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The structure of streets and houses, the geometry of Haddonfield is the universe of Michael Myers, and the superb staging (creates the stifling of suspense and horror without resorting to sensationalism hemoglobínico or the grotesque gesture) is the best expression of the attributes that define Myers.</summary>
	<body>On the basis of the iconography that commonly identifies the feast that gives title to the film, John Carpenter made a construct of terror rooted in a space and a cyclic time; Michael Myers, character whose ambiguous psychological universe is derived from the mythical halo that characterizes - almost supernatural, watching the conclusion of the film - and which is the look and the essential point of view used to explore the myth and folklore associated, in this case, to the town of Haddonfield.El icon par excellence - the image of the pumpkin approaching from the side of the screen - expresses the popular mythology associated with the uncanny and the morbid industryperfectly well–timed with notes, musical (work of the own Carpenter) thus constituting one of the most disturbing home credits which have been. Located in Haddonfield, in the night of the dead, the travelling and the subsequent flat sequence we are approaching the Myers House to describe the sexual game between two teenagers, game monitored by the movement of a subjective camera that comes to be the conscience of the small Michael, thereby introducing a reason essential in the story that subtly draw the tormented inner world of the protagonist: sex and, perhaps, the need of affection (which could be translated in misogynistic hatred). An introspective prologue that immerses us in the mind of the murderer, and which plays an essential role when Michael puts the mask on his face, and the sound of breathing is accentuated by the image of the plane sequence to acquire the subjective value that dominates much of the representation, prior to the murder. This is summarized (in a single movement of exploration and description of sensations and the environment) as an ambiguous psychology, some reason, a time and a space on those who return to complete the cycle.Fifteen years later, Laurie (Jamie Lee Curtis) is the austere and intelligent girl who embodies the antithesis regarding teen fashion and the first sexual flirtations expressed in his group of friends, the factor that motivates the murderer from the shadows of the interior of a car or from the hieratic coldness in the light of the day in the ends and corners of the streets of Haddonfield. The narrative explores the folklore of the rural world (space) in the specific date (time), the myth of the "sack man", underlining reason that follows a progression from the field of folklore, until the reality embodied in the presence of Michael Myers. Thus, the prospect of the murderer (omniscient, the consciousness that it plans to the crime as a consummate Act) adheres the perspective of its victims, in principle situated in the mythological context of a pagan celebration, to later face the real threat.As we enter the night of Halloween, the picture of Dean Cundey draws the contrasts and shadows in the streets and homes, the Hideout from which the murderer monitors to their victims. The structure of streets and houses, the geometry of Haddonfield is the universe of Michael Myers, and the superb staging (creates the stifling of suspense and horror without resorting to sensationalism hemoglobínico or the grotesque gesture) is the best expression of the attributes that define Myers.El Dr. Loomis (Donald Pleasence) - insubstantial character limited to articulate an unnecessary speech about the demonic evil of Myers - comes to the aid of Lauriethe only female that has been capable of disrupting the lethal attacks of the homicide, which can be interpreted as the consequent aggressive potential of the Suppression of the sexual instincts (and moralina the subtext that this entails). Myers survives the shooting of Dr. Loomis and his profile acquires supernatural range. In the final sequence, photographs of the interiors and the different spaces of Haddonfield accompany the breathing of the masked face of Michael Myers that extends to all areas of the geometry of Haddonfield. Myers is the soul of Haddonfield, a mythical and supernatural, immortal element, which cyclically returns to the origin, as we have seen in their endless sequels.</body>
</review>
