<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Sympathy for lady vengeance" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Building exceptional, once again, its director shows up to point a great creator can innovate through the start-up scene and storytelling, a major filmmaker</summary>
	<body>On a few occasions you will see a server surrender unconditionally to the qualities as filmmaker of any director in the times, thing very difficult given the difficulties that are usually find all of them when it comes to shooting on creative freedom, be slaves of fashion or the tastes of the public to reach a particular strip of spectators. But there is still film-makers which, for one reason or another, in this case a privileged position within an emerging cinematography as the Korean, they can express themselves freely. Park Chan Wook has always been my devotion santo, inevitably, film after film has marked me and made me hope about the future of cinema, at the risk of seems too risky. It could not be less in the conclusion of his particular trilogy on vengeance, a new sample of the film of Mr Chan wisdom Wook.En this time history takes us to a Korean prison, in which serving Lee Geum-Ja for thirteen years, due to the death of a child which the own Lee Geum had kidnapped. Once out of jail, we follow their first steps in freedom, as he gets a job at a bakery and plans revenge on the man responsible for his imprisonment, which is none other than Choi Min-Sik ("Oldboy") playing the Sr.Baek, a teacher of primary school, with dark secrets about several missing children, and even the daughter had Lee Geum, and was forced to divest it because of him.Park Chan-Wook takes us back to land frequented earlier in his sublime work, those in which the redemption, revenge, and the poetic justice give hand to form again, an explosive cocktail in its final result. This narrated with a dramatic progression commendable, only slow by these flashbacks they remember Lee Geum in jail of women, which, incidentally, has a theatrical tone that I do not know if it is adjusted to the reality of the Korean women's prisons, but resulting from oppression that exudes the screen and supported in the angled framing of its directorIt transmits the feeling in an impeccable way. This dramatic progression reaches its climax in the final part of the story, in which the moral ambiguity seizes the film to reach one of the most poetic end of all his work, and reminiscent, greatly to the end of Oldboy in its visual elements, especially the purity of her snows, in contrast with the long and tortuous road to redemption by our heroine (do?), as a final release.In the technical section, it must be said, that as usual, the brilliance and formal staging of this genius of the image which is Park Chan Wook, seizes each and every one of the scenes. These extraordinary close-ups that give intensity to the story, without resulting to nothing forced or free of charge, or the aforementioned frames angled of constant oppression, full of edges, as the emotions of the characters in his films, becomes, once again in his film, an element as important or more than own narration, advancing in the story precisely from this perfection. All together of course, with his particular sense of humor, always as black and Chan-Wook always know to exploit as well. Sequences as the of the execution final, that is a negrísima sunset the day of any kind of vengeful film, always from this so reburying humorous and ironic distancing, or the dream of the execution of a Baek dog-shaped (actually significant), they give us an idea for where is heading the film towards a magical realism mixed with a sense of very black humorreaching sometimes the discomfort sought by its director to cover everything with a series of religious elements as the purity of the soul, the destination or the redemption. Even allows the luxury of resorting to certain visual resources of great originality and why not leaving to be ironic, cited as an example the scene of sex on the table, and as with own sway of bodies emerges from beneath the table written banner to display on screen time of condemnation of the girl that carries such activitybright once again.Many scenes remain in the retina of the spectator over the footage, including that bright scene of the attack in the alley, with some echoes to the scene of the massive fight between Oldboy, resulting in this most violent time if it is to be dry and direct, unceremoniously, by way of operatic Greek tragedy. It is just one example of the amount of details and nuances that arise from the work of this great creator, resorting once again to the intensity of the colors as visual track of the lively or vital State of the characters, with vague images that are not in vain in the history.If to all this we add an excellent acting job, even for the most minor characters (perfect group of parents in the final scene), we will find ourselves with a film that closes brilliantly the particular and revealing trilogy of vengeance initiated by Park Chan Wook with "Sympathy for MR.""Vengeance" (containing one of final curricula more cruelly emotional that a server recalls, stirring me stomach caused concern), a somewhat lower this work "Sympathy for Lady Vengeance" because it contained half an hour in its somewhat confusing history knot, but that on the contrary, was even more painfully dramatic which is before us today. Above both lies which precisely in the Middle chronologically, is the masterpiece of Korean cinema (and world probably) "Oldboy", for which this subscribes, the best film of the last ten years.The only but will find fans unaccustomed to this type of Korean cinema, is precisely the fact that the narrative occasionally is heading towards a film elipsis that makes certain scenes to jump from one to others without going to a conventional narrative, something that in my opinion, does no more than enrich the narration, by very contradictory as it may seem. Despite this can be a small burden for certain type of public not accustomed to this common resource in the Asian cinema.Ultimately, building exceptional, once again, its director shows up to point a great creator can innovate through the start-up scene and storytelling, a major filmmaker, at the expense of repeating myself, but that has already proven his career (go no further recent and commented here "I m a Cyborg, but that's Ok") which is a privileged director and a breath of fresh air on the world scene.Absolutely essential.</body>
</review>
