<review author="Iñigo" title="Oliver Twist" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you have insomnia problems go to your doctor that prescribe you it to her</summary>
	<body>New and unnecessary the film adaptation of the famous novel by Dickens. Already it did in its day, among others, David Lean and now it is the turn to Roman Polanski. The truth is that good Roman has nothing new to offer, and the work of David is eaten in almost every aspect.The film, in general terms, is disappointing. Here there is no trace of that first Polanski amazed with works by the likes of "The Quimérico tenant" or "The dance of the vampires". "We can even glimpse some detail to remind us the drama"the pianist""."Oliver Twist" notable for being, simply, one of the minor of the filmmaker films.The adaptation is truly faithful, and the formal and technical aspect is, without doubt, flawless. Photography, in a home precocious and then gloomy, is of a high level. As well as the ambiance, sets, editing, costumes and music. There is no objection in this regard. But the problem comes in facing history and how to tell the tale. The narration is too repetitive, cold and aseptic. History gives the sensation of having an absurd and almost ridiculous, so without anything that attracts us attention and with a lack of too obvious claw. There is nothing that will make us partakers of the story of Oliver Twist, and any effort to move stays in the attempt.The truth is that, due to the memory offered to us by the book, we see that Oliver is a child (one of many) immersed in poverty and has to cope with the hypocrisy of the wealth of the London of that time. A child that force to steal against their own will, out of sheer necessity. But also a child who lives in their own flesh the betrayal, trust in friendship and forgiveness. A pardon him, nevertheless, will offer. And that is where we woke up. There is only one scene that stands out, is able to get out of the most absolute torpor, and curiously, this scene coincides with the end of the film. Very significant.In the cast. one of lime and sand other. Ben Kingsley dazzles, but Barney Clark, the child that gives life to Oliver, stays during most of the footage too cardboard. Does not help, precisely to convey and, therefore, to bring us closer to their situation.The film goes on insurance risks nothing, and therefore performs its task well. But, for being overly correct, not noted in any way. Everything is too topical, predictable, flat and bland.Ultimately, Polanski does not meet expectations and disappointed. Create irrelevant work that has nothing to do with other adaptations, such as the already mentioned of David Lean or the musical Reed, or other films of his own filmography.I don't think anyone lose sleep if it is without seeing her. Moreover, if someone has problems with insomnia, to go to your doctor to be her it prescribes.</body>
</review>
