<review author="Dragon negro" title="Mortadelo y Filemón: Misión Salvar la Tierra" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The second incursion in film and with real actors of the adventure of Mortadelo and Filemón salda with a result very similar to its predecessor, is not capable of withstanding the type for an hour and a half without coming to tire.</summary>
	<body>Our two most famous agents confront this time to a major problem of drought affecting the entire planet, that also not to suffer attacks to pollute the waters. Effect invents a machine of rain it is having the opposite effect, takes away the water. The evil Botijola is behind the attacks decides then kidnap the inventor and done with the machine for advancing the purpose of their plans, put an end to all the water on the planet so that everyone has to buy her drink called botijola.New delivery, second, of the adventures of Mortadelo y Filemón transferred to the big screen that does not differ much, aesthetic and visually, from its predecessor. The cartoon effect is present in the film with the intention of transferring the visual of Ibáñez the cinema, that universe as already happened with the film by Javier Fesser, this highly successful and even improved and much more spectacular. Unfortunately, this proves to be the only point in favour of the film suffers from the same evil from its predecessor, a script lengthened in excess and not stand level during the hour and a half of footage.Repeat the same characters as we have already seen with the only change of actor in mort, this time played by Edu Soto, that although best actor, must be acknowledged that it gave more as mort Benito Pocino pego. Anyway is Pepe Viyuela in the role of Philemon who takes all the weight of the film just mort is dedicated to gracietas all the time, and some of them of more silly, another big problem of the script, is one of the most ridiculous and sonrojantes gags I've seen in recent times.Apart from a few very accomplished special effects, in its favour it must be said that Miguel Bardem has included many details to any reader of comics of the couple will recognize, even many of the gags have traded literally, although as I have already said, not all produce the desired effect and what role does grace in the big screen causes shame others.The second incursion in film and with real actors of the adventure of Mortadelo and Filemón salda with a result very similar to its predecessor, an aprobadillo thanks to their achieved special effects and its visual aesthetic, but with a hyphen and a few gags that could have improved. The question that I am concerned about is if really Mortadelo and Filemon are able to endure the type for an hour and a half without getting tired, the answer so far is that, perhaps in a new installment, if this works at the box office, you can say otherwise.</body>
</review>
