<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Sombra del Cazador" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The shadow of the Hunter is a thriller masked as film of political denunciation, after its bombastic and pretentious appearance not found more than a vulgar history, which are not interested in or excited in the slightest</summary>
	<body>There are actors that think that its mere presence is enough to give packaging a film beyond film purely. There are interpreters that seem touched by a magic wand, and that you project involving, guarantee project. Although it is much more often the opposite case, there are many actors and actresses that assure the mediocrity of any film in which they participate.Although it seems a paranormal phenomenon, there are actors that seem to be attracted by poor quality projects irrefrenablemente, and Richard Gere is a good example. And that the last Donosti Prize (which under the Festival of San Sebastián has fallen) strives, but there is no way, a mysterious and inexplicable aura of mediocrity surrounds everything he does in recent years. In the shadow of the Hunter, Richard Gere is a seasoned war correspondent to witness the horrors of the war in the Balkans lost live nerves. After the conflict, our more partying reporter returns with the sole intention of capturing one of the most wanted war criminals. What could well have been a history of well constructed and made consistent complaint becomes a runs-runs-that-you-pill without sense. In addition the film is any less honest thing and Richard Shepard is kept key information to understand the reasons for the character of Gere and not the release until well advanced the plot. These blows of effect are characteristic of films empty and contrived, but which at the same time Sin a huge pretentiousness. There is no element that hook to the Viewer, who is also martyred in the presence of Richard Gere and Jesse Eisenberg. Terrence Howard, who hope to see away from Hollywood like this subproducctos is only saved.The shadow of the Hunter is a thriller masked as film of political denunciation, after its bombastic and pretentious appearance not found more than a vulgar history, which are not interested in or excited in the slightest.</body>
</review>
