<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Encantada: La Historia de Giselle" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A Christmas movie 100% that can be enjoyed, but leaves the taste of that could have been far more than Yes.</summary>
	<body>As I mentioned in the previous post, either by the Christmas and colorful in the dates, or acute access of fussiness, the case is that the weekend was presented with an excess of glucose important. The spirit of Disney had infected us as if we were in the camp to which they send to Wednesday Adams and was impossible to escape its influence. So, after the meeting of classical dibus, we went to the cinema to see a fairy tale as they send the canons. Or almost. "Enchanted, Giselle history" is a parody of the classic films of the Disney Princesses. It is the history of Giselle, a princess from drawing lively, cheesy and crazy for kissing the Prince of your dreams, that sing when pose you squirrels and sparrows in the shoulders (should learn from Fiona) and with an ability to out of the ordinary to weave tacky dresses. Of course, her Prince charming lives very close to it, in the magical Kingdom of Andalasia, but just when they know and are on the verge of signing the "happy forever", arises the evil stepmother of Prince to truncate all plans. Fooling innocent Giselle, sends it to a place where there are no happy endings, or what is the same, New York. The Princess of cartoon thus becomes an innocent foreign meat and bone in a world that does not understand, surrounded by people who think that it is as a watering can, looking for a way to return to his world of pens Carioca. Luckily that to help her find a skeptical lawyer and her determined daughter, which will gradually encariñando with the girl, although she to strive in destroy the decoration of the House to prepare new dresses. The film won many points in those parts where the Disney parody takes over the script, showing how different things can be when we moved in the world of animation to the current Usamérica. In those moments, are overwhelmingly the two actors that embody the characters of the tale, the beautiful Amy Adams, which we admire in a role just as optimistic character but with background much more dramatic in "Junebug", which earned him a nomination to the Oscar, and James "cíclope" Marsden, which seems that it is specializing in roles loaded with humor after the musical "Hairspray" and extravagant. Both bring us the best moments of the film, when faced with real-world with their personalities of tale without that you get to be ridiculous. But not everything was going to be autoparodia. Disney is still Disney and the film falls into too many moments in the own house kitsch. The musical number, which in the first bars serves as powerful gag, just transforming as it progresses the film in the classic musical number. It is difficult to fight against business genetics. At numerous times got to ask it would have been of the script if it comes to fall into the hands of the all-powerful Pixar. Surely, we would be talking about a completely different film. On the role of Susan Sarandon as incarnation of the evil stepmother, just has some minutes on screen, insufficient for the showcasing of the actress, who had probably come out with a character with something more than presence. Patrick Dempsey, "Gray's Anatomy" Heartthrob is limited to meet the of his co-stars in a role quite dull in comparison. A Christmas movie 100% that can be enjoyed, but leaves the taste of that could have been far more than Yes.</body>
</review>
