<review author="Luna" title="XXY" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lucia Puenzo debuted as a Director with a drama about identity. A film that won't leave anyone indifferent.</summary>
	<body>Caste comes to the Greyhound and in this case the directorial debut of Lucia Puenzo (daughter of Luis Puenzo November) comes to our screens endorsed by the string of awards it has been harvested to date (Grand Prize of the critics week and Golden Rail award of 2007 for example) and the likely to reap (it has been selected by Argentina as a candidate for the Oscars and is nominated in the Goya in the category of) (best Latin American film).If all this display of tinsel fails to mobilize the Viewer to watch this film, we are still giving him reasons to not miss this film which tells the tribulations of a hermaphrodite in 15 years, although this serves to reflect more deeply on the individual identity and the search for meaning and membership of the individual in society.First of all I would like to highlight the always splendid actor Ricardo Darín. It is always a luxury to have this great actor in the cast of any film because it manages to give life and reality few characters interpreted. In this case it makes one role rather than convincing of father of the hermaphrodite, filling the screen with its overwhelming force. But it is not the only actor that plays a great role. The Division achieved a degree of admirable naturalness, and behind them intuímos the hand of Lucia Puenzo, hitherto tanned as a television screenwriter, but with large dowries for the direction of actors, as this film shows. I would like to draw special attention to the interpretation of the hermaphrodite at the hands of Agnes Efrón, a masterful interpretation which has already earned recognition as best actress at the Clarín awards. Secondly, I would like to highlight the photography Natasha Braier, cold but nearby, which portrays with a look homesick and glacier the Uruguayan coast.It should also be noted the soundtrack composed by Andrés Goldstein and Daniel Tarrab that adapts as ring to the finger to the dramatic progression of history.In short, a film that won't leave anyone indifferent.</body>
</review>
