<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="1408" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting movie, with successful moments of terror suggested giving it a slightly above-average interest, although with a final part full of clichés and the sense of a final development of history far-fetched to confuse the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>After a more Swedish director Mikael Hafstrom interesting Hollywood debut with a film at the service of Clive Owen in the genre of police thriller (without Control") is passed in its new proposal to the genre of fantasy, in this case to terror by adapting a short story of the master of suspense, at least for some, that not for a serverStephen King.La story begins with the visit of Mike Enslin (John Cusack) to a road motel supposedly inhabited by ghosts, to be documented on his next book, moment in which we see that it is not absolutely nothing in his presence. Despite this Enslin writes books about the ghostly inhabitants of these places, with books such as "1st haunted hotels" or "10 cemeteries haunted", all of them are guides for survival against ghosts, without even, according to his own words, has ever seen none. You could be considered a disenchanted fake who writes for pure and mere desire for economic survival, as evidenced by that 3 or 4 people interested in some books, which are described later as books of cuts in the section of cheap novels only cite in their debate in a library to talk about his work. When arise you the possibility of visiting the Dolphin Hotel, in which it is assumed that room 1408 this haunted, Enslin is the perfect occasion to close his new book with this final chapter about mysterious places and create his false story about a new haunted place. There he is greeted by the Manager of the hotel, Gerald Olin, played by Samuel l. Jackson, which warns that the room should not stay her, after a strip constant tug-of-war, agrees to let him spend the night in the room with some packing 1408, but not before warning him that the "ghosts" of this room live in your own interior. From there the film becomes the attempt of survival to one long night by the character of Enslin.Se could be considered the film an attempt to move to a single room the typical haunted house story (not worth naming "The shining" Kubrick or "The legend of hell house" by John Hough)(to cite films in this style, because it would be doing a disservice), a try quite laudable and with decent results, details such as the mirror effect through the window of the room towards the building opposite, the absence of Windows on the exterior of the building except the room 1408 are more than suggestive, and help to create an atmosphere of Kafkaesque nightmareas well describes the main character on one occasion. During the footage calls into question, rather than the existence or not of ghosts, the mental health of the main character, with details such as the recorder or pc laptop, aspects which compensate for that in a moment the film take a wrong direction, the direction that usually take this type of productions, which is turning on itself, trying to play with that all real or a figment of the imagination is the fact that has already left or not of room 1408, and that is precisely the time in which the film is damaged in a high degree of effectiveness. It must be said that as the film progresses back to fall, again as usual, in a final that doesn't know how to finish the story, which is pulled by the easiest way, where there is even room for a hint of final fright that not is beside the point to nothing.The work of actors does not pass to right, giving the sense of having gained the cheque and little more, especially John Cusack, which despite being a good actor in my opinion, I just do not see it in this type of production. Samuel l. Jackson is a little more comfortable in his role of hotel manager, but neither does much more to transcend beyond be convincing in his role as mysterious. By the director, little to add, put in very simple scene without any notion of personality, typical product of custom, limited to be correct.Ultimately an interesting movie, with successful moments of terror suggested that give an interest a little higher than the average, but with a final part full of topics once again and the sense of final development of history fetched to confuse the Viewer, the most usual way break something that you do not know how to end. Simply entertaining.</body>
</review>
