<review author="Cp" title="Soy leyenda" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spectacular, well shot, fantasy film with an air of realism. Superb Will Smith carrying all the weight of the film, without get bored at any time. A pity that did not maintain most of the book, especially to show the vampires.</summary>
	<body>For Christmas, nothing better than film show. So, who played go see a popcorn movie, with one of the players with more hook of the contemporary cinema in the face of the box office, and also recognize that I like Nice and I like to see it on screen, Will Smith. After seeing the trailers, I am Legend seemed quite promising film, but would not have anything to do with the book of the same name, like I, Robot just had in common with the book, his own title. And after two hours, I left very happy film. It was just what I expected.I am Legend takes the original story to go creating a film of tension, where I admit that at times will be tense and expectant, all scenes of horror, or at least, with some shock, are perfectly designed and shot. I like the version of the script have been constructed, based above all on a Will Smith that fills the screen, completely without let us heavy nor to bore us, and which are still carefully and even worried. At times interested in their struggle, and discovering little by little as it is the New York of the future. If something was missing several flashback are showing the early stages of the infection that has arisen on the basis of medical experiments seeking the healing of cancer. All the scenes of those first moments of the plague are absolutely spectacular. But it is that if something is I am legend it is spectacular moments, some of them very well shot. This keeps the viewer tuned, with much skill, vampires are slow to appear, and also do a very calculated way, little by little, keeping expectant about his appearance, his intelligence or his way of acting.And here we reach the great problem of the film. I read in an interview the Director, Martin Lawrence, that this proved first with actors with make-up making vampires, and only then choose to replace them with digital effects. And that is the decision. Instead of vampires, humanoid, jump and move absolutely inhumane way, here have shaped aliens and spoil all the realistic effect of the film. They are not just little credible, they visually I like anything.Even so, could save the movie, but, and without anything, could say it that the ending is a bit disappointing, perhaps too toned, so after long time enjoying, just taking a small slump, just before the end of the tape.</body>
</review>
