<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El último show" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Aesthetic Epitaph, almost a masterpiece without greatest aspirations that the recreate a world gone, lost in nostalgia, the laziness that all get to cuddle by the beauty, by emotion...</summary>
	<body>Independence also has his tender side, the autobiographical time incorporated in a format añejo, prone to melancholy and soft transcendence, without sounding phrases extracted from some gigantic billet of philosophical maxims or any gathering of gurus of the mìstico which underpin apocalyptic thesis with the fragility of the world.Robert Altman has signed a tender, autobiographical, añejo, melancholic and transcendent, soft, alien to the excess, conveniently reduced work of unnecessary dramatic tension. All knowing that would be, in effect, the last show, perhaps the last of truth, without larger curls of the language.The last show is a formidable Opera on late payments, on the need to detract from the seriousness to which, indeed, does not deserve. It is also a beautiful testamentary note that the director has bequeathed to benefit of moviegoers and people of good will. Outside this gesture, there is only a movie, a strange, as a whole, too stubborn in their original point of departure: the last performance of a radio serial in an old theatre of varieties that is about to be demolished to become a parking lot. The glories of the radio that enliven the farewell do not exhibit no shame in doing what they know, ignore everything smells of demolition and that the show, the old and friendly ads and white country songs pass, has expiry date and they have just ahead.The belongings of the film, its most relevant apero, is the daily life of death, its absolute normality. Altman, the unpredictable, fickle man, which fluctuated genius (Mash, Vidas cruzadas, Gosford Park, Kansas City, the game of Hollywood) to the more frivolous crappy or the pure tedium (Pret a Porter) wanted this kind of posthumous work versase (by the way of Huston in Dubliners, although desaureolada of pathos and literature) over concerns of an artist who faces death and departe with her the reasons for the settlement, the privileges of the transit through life and misery that accompanies any human act by the mere fact of being ephemeral. So the actors of this beautiful decorated theatrical piece of country, emotions and Surrealism (the angel who wanders, erratic, in search of company) offer an intimate, cheerful wake times, colored by the reflections of life itself. Fiction uncomfortable more than reality, someone wrote. We accept the real, but it hurts the fantasy, the result of the talent and creativity, free spirit and artistic creation to offer material it disturbs us. Here it disturbs the ironic gaze of the master, which represents its own vital to driving with ingenuity dismantling and infinite love the demolition of alien which, in this case, is what always brought pleasure and to consecrated life, movies, stories, the choral world of characters who exert emotional hinge between the euphoria of living and the infamous certainty of death. Altman flirts with the tragedy, shines a couple of timidly affected scenes of any depth metafisica (the fair) and solves the cocktail with the kind assistance of the nostalgia of some appetizing romanticism which helps a memorable Gallery of characters and a script simple, minimal and practical, where raw material the anecdote, the episodic detail, loose more than the complete poem verseas if a hatillo's stories were and the director had emerged or assembled in a book of images. So the closure of the theatre, metaforizado, foreshadows the death of the creator, the omniscient Narrator, who does not hesitate to interpolate the sarcasm, the thin fabric of a crude humor, sometimes, subtle, in others and the already rare short stories (short cuts, sound it?) created the useful atmosphere so you not bored us (because that is a rather than present danger) this well-intentioned filmlower interest, but big (huge) in emotions.Rest Altman beyond where it is: perhaps the memory of who we enjoy some his work, their relatives and friends, said; give barracks hagiographies, but this is not the panegyric which probably deserves.</body>
</review>
