<review author="Plissken" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Simplistic and Manichaean, vision half way between the palomitera súperproducción and the film with message, one of the classics of science fiction of the last century.</summary>
	<body>Adapt: Modify a work of scientific, literary, musical, etc., so that it can be disseminated among public other than that which it was intended or give a different form of the original.Abiding by the meaning of the SAR, we could say that 'I am legend' of Francis Lawrence meets at least one of the requirements to be considered an adaptation of the superb novel by Richard Matheson. But a this Alfred Hitchcock, an expert in adaptations, came to say, more or less, that "the secret of the adaptation is to understand the main idea and ignore the rest". If we ignore to last it, 'I am legend' is nothing more than a bland (and neat, that Yes) remake of 'The last man alive', the most macarrada of Boris Sagal and Charlton Heston. Because falls into the same tic than the previous version: forget about why (and for what) Richard Matheson wrote the original.On this occasion, Robert Neville (a more than acceptable Will Smith) is a military virologist who happens to be the only survivor to a devastating plague that destroys 90% of the world's population and turn the rest into inhuman predators with alopecia problems and extreme sensitivity to ultraviolet rays. Their unique vital impulses are finding a cure for the virus, contact with other possible survivors and see an entire video store in alphabetical order. Until one day.Francis Lawrence has checked a harmless blockbuster to the greater glory of Will Smith, but post-apocalyptic line with the Omega Man of Sagal and introducing to shoehorn a strong element religious in the last section of the film. In addition, turn violent but rational vampires from the original of Matheson in a mixture of bloodsuckers, zombie and skinhead who come you to the hair to get another text messages on racism and xenophobia. Curious point this: while in the original book the protagonist goes to be monsters Hunter hunted monster in this 'I am legend' not only does not change their point of view, they allowed the luxury of marking a speech against racism and violence after spending three years, three, pounding the new species to "cure". Poor and pacifist military, acribillando "bugs" with his rifle's telescopic sight.And is that the script have filling Mark Protosevich and Akiva Goldsman presents several minor inconsistencies (SPOILER: If Manhattan was isolated from the rest of the country, is how come Anna and his son with his brand-new SUV?), but your greatest sin is to be more a variation to an adaptation: empties the original, grab the shell and adds what fits best at this time. Emptying is such that until the title loses its sense, resorting to a shameful final tirade in off to try to fix it.On the other hand, the technical Bill for the product is quite good, with a successful photography Andrew Lesnie and a notable production of Naomi Shohan design. The digital effects are more questionable, shabby and very linear design of creatures (even the orcs of Moria were more varied).In short, we will never know how this project would have been with Arnie Schwarzenegger to the head. We have this simplistic and Manichaean, vision half way between the palomitera súperproducción and the film with message, one of the classics of science fiction of the last century. Seen, they could have changed the title. A 4.</body>
</review>
