<review author="Bruji" title="Mimzy, más allá de la imaginación" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A bet brave by traditional toys in full era of video games.</summary>
	<body>New Line Cinema, producer of sagas multi-million dollar as 'The Lord of the Rings' or 'The Golden Compass', performs a brave defense of traditional toys to video games in this lesser title, which has one of its directors after the cameras.One of the advantages of being the director of New Line Cinema and have become a distributor in one of the most influential producers of the industry should be to get back - if you fancy - to the origins of unknown filmmaker to take the lead in a product that not succeed at the box office. Little matter that infuriating linearity which dealt with the realization, translated the invention in an irregular Court film with too many valleys and transmit any culminating peak which demonstrate the lack of that invaluable virtue which, in cinema, is the ability of knowing. Little to the four writers hired (for lack of one) to achieve, with greater or lesser success (in this case, none), shine on the adaptation of a short story of the marriage formed by Henry Cuttner and C.L. Moore. Little, because the head is up allows license look with the technical virguería that does reflect the drawings of "mandalas" of the young Wilder in glasses of his astonished Professor of science. Not with the originality with which Alfred Hitchcock shot one of the scenes peaks of strangers on a train, taking the image through similar crystals; feat later repeated by Pedro Almodóvar in women.., but, rather, the result of one of these coincidences, called "serendípitys", derived from the mere question based on basic principles of physical, easy to reach by the worst amateur video recording his girlfriend with sunglasses placed. History, interesting approach and multiple possibilities, makes the mistake of placing different and too many assumptions on the table with the clear intention not to develop any of them, causing an amalgam of concepts and specific auxiliary sub-plots than anything they bring to the central axis of the argument or it should be present in the final resolution. At times, comparable to the legendary Lewis Carroll's Alice, recurring resource where there. At times, as lost as the protagonist of Artificial Intelligence in the presence of the blue fairy. Without forgetting the worms that connect temporary gates, in clear reference to stories like Stargate or Timeline. And, ultimately, replacing beings of other spatial realities for futuristic gadgets, close to the Superman that "invoicing" only possibility of survival, or ET Spielbergriano which must return to their home after a risky huída; the director is not resisting the temptation to incorporate these two "new" techniques of contemporary cinema: the famous voices in off with telepathic excuse and imperceptible flashback that justifies the development of the action. Nor to the idea to exploit the clumsy and few special effects to adapt them to the minimum requirements of the script. However, the greater nonsense of all would be the attempt to discuss this film from a unique point of view, the film and strictly formal. Why not be lost in the wonderful world of funds that enclose well-intentioned messages?. Why not admit the possibility that all of the footage is not more than the metaphor to vindicate the importance of traditional toys, even more useless, in full era of video games?. Retomemos thread and type on a trip in the time, to reach a pure feeling coated DNA. What until that part of the past where is located our own childhood? At that time, we knew that not everything what is found abandoned on the street must be potentially hazardous, and occur to me the harmless board game called Jumanji and the curious box of Hellraiser. No. There was still the alternative of finding surprising objects, dear treasures that "inexplicable" and consistently ended in the trash. Mothers only saw wooden planks, pumpkins and paperweights in what were Pirate ships, smiling caritas and generating magical. nobody wanted to imitate the hostesses of the one, two, three and caused a power outage while he extracted a piece of the pattern of lights being on the panel of the auction? And when the present is represented by these glass dwellings that kidnap virtual pets subject to the dictates of its creators, the potential of the multipurpose plush toys of yesteryear were unlimited: protective amulets, children and students, powerful sleeping pills, monsters that aterraban the village of the barriguitas, comfortable armchairs... that Yes, with an unintelligible language that only we knew to decipher. In a mediocre Division, among which are the correct interpretations of Timothy Hutton, Joely Richardson (glow in the dark), giving life to a bland and stereotypical characters that blur without remission, we are witnessing the birth of a star name Rhiannon Leigh Wriyn; the girl's innate purity, which bears the weight of the fabric. And, paraphrasing the Broadman agent at that time that "I do not understand anything, but I'm glad," I admit I would like nothing more than have succeeded in starting a nostalgic smile in the movie buff reader with this vision of the film. If not I got, it will be because I myself lost fantasy in a steep bend of life.</body>
</review>
