<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Pulp fiction" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film made horns on two assassins and their interelaciones in a day's work. Considered by many Tarantino masterpiece. I do not think that it is for both, although it has moments that makes it worthwhile.</summary>
	<body>Director: Quentin Tarantino. duration: two hours and average, less na.Release date: 13 January 1995.Espectadores: 2.154.692 of human beings.This criticism is in response to a challenge that launched me the great Plissken. It does not much conversed with my brother-in-law on cinema and came to the conclusion that Tarantino I don't like, given that all the virtues that he told me in this respect, to me seemed defects. For example, the talks impossible that kept, in some cases seem nice, but do not seem great. Moreover, they are quite silly talks, as devised how call hamburgers in France. No, to such not term him understand.The film is about a series of sequences in the life of several people, without apparent relationship, but eventually all and each one of them have a link. This link is given by two thugs, Travolta and Samuel l. Jackson, and as is his work routine. Already imagine that if partele that legs, that if hit four shots to that, etc. On the other hand, we have a boxer that is before his last fight and this has to be a tongo. A girl who is the girlfriend of the head, a couple who wants to dock a cafeteria and some guys rather than complete the cast.Let's see, this jumbled movies will be genius, but makes me picha a mess. That suddenly leave one that was dead disturbs me. And this movie is made so. On the other hand, is full (that Nice expression) of dialogues to each stranger, on the more banal and absurd themes that you can imagine. But has good points, such as the inclusion of better secondary has given the film, as it is the great Bruce Willis (I like most in these short roles in roles of prota). Another point in favour of the film is that it has left to posterity great moments, as Travolta (which I think tad silly) dance, the phrase "Knights, not us chupemos the cocks still" Mr Wolf or the phrase not worse "Will play to the middle ages with your ass" that has given up for a song.In short, film made horns on two assassins and their interelaciones in a day's work. Tarantino in its purest form, which is considered his best film and masterpiece. I do not think that it is for both, although it has moments that makes it worthwhile.If only for the memorable moments.Besitos.P.D: thinking it bien, there are very clever phrases;-)</body>
</review>
