<review author="Taliesin" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>How is that with so many values Alatriste not working it possible? Because it is not film. It is a video clip of two hours and a half where you only see the scenes of more weight in the plot.</summary>
	<body>The feeling that invades you after seeing Alatriste is the great movie that could have been. Or better still: the films that could have done with a material of such quality. Not be if it has been an excess of ambition or naive, but the case is that we can say is that good that "who covers much, little tightens". More than a movie, Alatriste is a slide session. There is a continuing obsession for photography, for the close-ups and what is a great failure for a tape supposed adventures, for a camera that does not move. The result is a film that has a lot of historical and goes to the rhythm of coitus interruptus. And the worst thing is it shows the MIME who has devoted all the film makers and had money to spend. The work they have done with the costume is excellent and the selection of players is perfect. Viggo Mortensen is the perfect Alatriste and, thanks to his great work of interpretation, we can forgive him the strange mixture of English and Buenos Aires accents that forces him to continuously speak in whispers. I would even say that the character has lost part of its loquacity and have removed you Viggo sentences to avoid exposing this problem. Echanove Quevedo is perfect, Javier Cámara plays a very convincing Conde Duque de Olivares and Ariadna Gil gives life to the sensual mistress of captain. Even the battle scenes are recreated quite rightly, far removed from the foreign sonrojantes of Juana la Loca, and passed the harshness of a match in which he kills and dies to blow a sharp steel. How is that with so many values Alatriste not working it possible? Because it is not film. It is a video clip of two hours and a half where only you see the scenes of more weight in the plot, but with the disadvantage that we do not have the rest of the plot. Lack of development of the characters, plot and even historical reality. With this, Alatriste excites the Viewer, but not him touches. It doesn't matter who lives or who dies, because we have known five minutes ago. In fact, some characters seem to have a couple of phrases to kill them then. Some scenes that would have us leaving tacked in the armchair do not pass of anecdotal. If they had only used the first four scenes and they had added film between them would be talking about an epic Alatriste which has left us eager to continue to live their adventures. In short, producers and director have put a pistol charged into the hands of those who say that the Spanish film does not deserve huge budgets. Told with so many media, have been so ambitious, who have lost perspective of what it had a hand. I am convinced that at no time have realized what was happening. Catching loose scenes, Alatriste appears to be a lot of work, but nor the best editing of history had been able to fill some gaps that had not shot. Had just been given a couple of steps back to see the whole of the work, I am sure that you would have noticed that Alatriste lacks film from the first five minutes. Unfortunately for us, for the Spanish film and for own Captain Alatriste, has not happened. Cruiosidad: A few years ago Alatriste was about to take the film starring and directed by Antonio Banderas and with a screenplay by Enrique Urbizu. Seen, the script would have won (La Caja 507, the ninth gate), but the other I'm not so sure. Recommended audience: have read three of the five books that are published alatriste and has cost me follow the (non) storyline of the film, which is why someone who has not approached the novels will be more complicated, not filling the gaps in any way. Even so, if you are the historical film, perhaps you find interesting.</body>
</review>
