<review author="Plissken" title="Hoop Dreams" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A delight not only for lovers of basket, but for any lover of the documentary no trap or cardboard.</summary>
	<body>'Hoop Dreams' follows in the footsteps of two kids of 15 years, William Gates and Arthur Agee, who share a required: reaching the glittering early 1990s NBA. Both are among the best gamers of the dangerous playgrounds of Cabrini Green, Chicago's gangs and crack. And both are selected by the prestigious St. Joseph´s High School, birthplace of legendary players like Isiah Thomas. will they be able to Will and Art of continue shining in a very demanding environment, in full rise to the Mecca of the basket?The great merit of 'Hoop Dreams' is that it lasts almost three hours or you find out. Part of the sports documentary to use, with kids trying to emulate his idol, but very soon you realize the weight that an environment as Will and Arthur: families living on the threshold of poverty, friends putting you to the limits of the law, teenage pregnancies. If to this we add an educational system that revolves around the success and forget the second and sports requirements frankly tough for kids 16 years, we have a real Odyssey. A journey in which we see how boys become men, and how life put to the test their desire to not only succeed, but survive.Steve James, to make matters worse, turns out to be a great director. Alternately brilliant and truly epic sports episodes (from 'Hoosiers' had not lived so exciting moments) with images that portray a way of life to the limit (family living without electricity, the hustling of drugs of the father of Arthur before the eyes of his own son). And always with an enormous respect for all and each of the characters. Director clean look allows us to move with each small step given by the two protagonists in his slow Ascension (still them over four years) to fame.As only he could point out the excessive length of the film, but I recognise that in the end I couldn't believe that had swallowed me a documentary of 170 minutes, how fast that happened. Moreover, a delight not only for lovers of basket, but for any lover of the documentary no trap or cardboard. 9.</body>
</review>
