<review author="Jokin García " title="American Gangster" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A history of mafia cops, gangsters and polis, excellent Bill and recommended viewing, with Denzel Washington as the best afternoons.</summary>
	<body>American Gangster is the story of the birth, rise and fall of Frank Lucas (Denzel Washington), the man who managed to form an Empire with heroin until becoming the owner of Harlem, and Richie Roberts (Russell Crowe), honest (to the extreme) police officer that toppled the rule of Lucas, taking him to jail, and uncovering a whole network of corrupt polícías comprising 75% of the strength of the Narcotics Department of New York, in the early 1970s, in a story that happened in reality.The film, despite its duration (more than 150 minutes), presents one invoice more than notable, and although perhaps it falls a little short in its drive toward the category of películón, WINS outweigh the good movie label.Very managed the work of Denzel Washington in his role of diplomatic and friendly mafia on the one hand, but with a very dark and violent side when the situation requires, managing to create a very charismatic character. Does not become so cool as in "Training Day" but it comes close.Instead the character of Crowe is left something behind, and although his work is not bad, not reaches the height of Denzel, staying in a kind of Elliot Ness came less, although beware, that I am not saying that this clash. That is simply left something behind. And Justice said that the few times that they manage to agree on screen it is precisely the best of the Australian.The cintanos tells the story from the two points of view, mobster and police, two stories entrecruzados in which Hunter and prey just match until almost the end of the film (with the interview between both one of the most interesting scenes) with all the elements of a good gangster film. And visually is very successful also with an aesthetic very well looked after, and the unique but of a Chase at the end of the film that seem shot by Danny Boyd a day of drunkenness.In short, it is not "The godfather" but one film more than correct and worthy of being considered film.</body>
</review>
