<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="La Sombra del Cazador" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that is only based on some formal skill by the director and charismatic performance of the three protagonists, being the rest of the story extremely predictable.</summary>
	<body>American cinema we are accustomed to move extremely Manichean way truthful stories to the big screen, or perhaps it would be more fair to say partially adjusted to reality, to lecture us about alleged values that go beyond any approach morally self-critical and direct their gaze outward, or staying to mean (or sometimes not even that) not condescending look towards their own defects and errors.The new New York Richard Shepard film delves into a story based on an article by Scott K.Anderson on impunity freedom of certain war criminals in the former Yugoslavia, in this case, one of the most dangerous, nicknamed "El Zorro" and which no one seems to know his whereabouts.The plot of the film is precisely the pursuit by some journalists as dangerous character, being a unique opportunity for all of them, but especially for Simon (Richard Gere), reach the absolute glory in a world so as to consume people in the maelstrom of dependence on immediate results. Simon was fired and malvive in wars throughout the world as a mercenary of the information, while his old House, Duck (Terrence Howard), is dragged by complicity and empathy into this new adventure, despite having a job ideal and devoid of all physical risk. To them they were joined by Benjamin (Jesse Eisenberg), the son of a powerful boss of the chain for which working Duck. During his trip to "El Zorro", in which he will discover not only the immediacy of the news is at stake, will live various setbacks and deverán put their lives at risk to achieve such feat.The work of Shepard in the direction slightly dignifies a film whose screenplay, written by the same director, shows an absolute inconsistency, being a history full of topics. The staging is more than correct technically, although without fanfare, but are common throughout the film business resolutions which compensate for that mediocre script, one of those cases where the ability of the creator (although in this case nor goes far beyond the simple technical correction) out front of decent form a product with a more elaborate script, and less given to embellishment or inconsistencies in tone or the development of the action, would have been much more satisfactory. Scared thinking it would have happened if in addition, the director of the function would have been same shabbiness that history developed.It is no coincidence that Shepard previously directed at this "The shadow of the Hunter", a highly recommended film desmitificador as "Matador", where already showed signs of an interesting ability to narrate through the Mise en scène, thing lately it seems that it has disappeared in the vast majority of American directors.Is also remarkable, and a point in its favour, the effective work of the three main actors, both Howard and Eisenberg show complicity possibly worthy of recommendation for all those films that tried and failed it, with moments that demonstrate involvement by both actors, still somewhat expected a player so gifted as Terrence Howard, but being a surprise in the case of Jesse Eisenberg, whose participation anécdotica (one per irrelevant) and another for secondary in two popular films of terror as "The curse" and "The forest" (under the orders of Wes Craven and M.Night Shyamalan respectively), did not presage that ease and reliability that shows us in the role of reporter new inexperienced. The work of Richard Gere, an actor that never excite me, but surprisingly for a server, stands in this new film a character with charisma, who knows how to transmit that disillusioned tone that is assumed to someone that had everything, and no longer has anything I leave to the end. A verdader surprise. The rest of the actors better not speak, because there are cases of the police of the UN name Boris, who is representing repetitive tics of the ignorant and stupid character until exhaustion, or the reserved role actress Diane Kruger, which makes so little credible that look scruffy and lower class requiring role especially demented.In addition, as I said before, the tone Word acquires a particularly relevant meaning in this new film of the Gere Buddhist. There is a worrying contrast, by their intentions and results, gap between what it purports to tell the film and the tone of the story. While the story is dramatic dyes, as it could not be otherwise taking into account that we are talking about the history of a war criminal, furthermore there is background a grandiosely and sarcastic tone that throws negates any intention to strike a balance in the account. Resulting in bad taste many contrasts of a scene to another, or by resorting to the most well-worn scenes of this type of production (such as the meeting in the mountains between the character of Simon and a former colleague). Also, halfway through the film, the film happens to be a history of reporters in pursuit of the news, to revenge perpetrated by Simon, which it does rather than seek a blow that in advance already matched this thriller with elements of the urban western (three men hunting for another, with a reward of 5 million dollars for his head).All this, together with an extremely anticlimactic end and little in keeping with it requiring the story, and not counting the obvious and innocent vision by American cinema of its more obscure organizations, give us as a result a film that is only based on some formal skill by the director and charismatic performance of the three protagoniststhe rest of the extremely predictable and lacking history of any depth or reporting of events and characters, so they required. A film that despite having the gift of the passenger entertainment, involves a certain burden that prevents or even empathize with history. A film failed and therefore a real shame.</body>
</review>
