<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Psychopaths at this point fill: real tired of this gross gang of mindless that spare no efforts to go scoring notches on the handle of his Toledo steel. Under fill, there is not a bad film. Or not good.</summary>
	<body>I am very out of prowess in sadism and vulgar guts that the psychopaths to the Leatherface or this Michael Myers have supplied the terror of the eighties (Carpenter, Hooper, Craven) and new terror of boasting modern, but fed by these old Brats (Zombie, Aja). I consider myself a sensible spectator, in what I can, soon advancing to the enthusiasm of excessive unless circumstances recommend a good dose of euphoria and healthy nonsense, comfortably installed in the certainty that the cinema is a formidable entertainment, a sublime art and an accomplice of all sink which do not consider it neither entertainment nor, of course, art to make it. Rather let me carry for very primary emotions, which then inevitably I transformed outside the cinema and more afternoon mutual (now) in impressions, notes that perhaps only threaten dialogue to the Viewer (I) with the chronicler with the stubborn type. Needless to say that I also. So a movie like this one, joy of the batch of vicious of the orthodoxy of the body count, gore light or the aberration in the form of multiple killers, has not left me trembling, or I've been acomplejado by the glow of mythical film (the night of Halloween, John Carpenter, 1.978). This prequel without complexes, ametrallada by the vigorous Rob Zombie pulse, sparing no violence nor is hooked to what would have been easy, that is, compose an exercise in cinema for teenagers with acne and some clueless easily impressionable and retina greedy battering, saws and all the paraphernalia of masks so dear by the troops of gross that we are discussing. Rather it outlines an honest assault on a predictable story of desastrada, extraordinarily salpimentada children of all Freudian topics that the gentle reader has seen in dozens of films cut by the same commercial scissor. This part of an absolute master of his vices: Zombie loves the slasher, spoils it, granted privileges of noble gender, and I do not go on to consider whether there is or not because there is no negligible formats (understand) or minor genres and everything is left rocking by the ingenuity, the Magisterium or simply the creative value of who invoice it. Zombie, whose music is not of any of my abundant devotions, is (on the contrary) a director with punch, we would say, one which has been able to understand without excessive time in the industry what convulsive way works and how it is possible to matrimoniar film entertainment, saleable, consumable without more punches or cultural subterfuge and, moreover, a technical packagenarrative and up acting more than decent. Nothing here alarm by their mediocrity, nothing is (however) bad of solemnity and there are even moments of estimable film, well planned and with solvency. This is why what Halloween, origin leaves a bittersweet memory. Much, ultimately, thinking how little that esparaba. The film highlights the autopilot when the calibration of knives and masks leave his prison and is dragging (are perhaps many minutes) until its unruly end where Myers does not die by much that is obceque writer and one Regiment of infantry or current rambos. That end, hit up the naúsea is that uncomfortable, which lowers grata (more or less) attracting its passable starting and its intermediate entertaining. Serves me sad consolation vision geek Brad Douriz and Malcolm McDowell, formidable actors distinguished in serie B, not C or Z or which the gentle reader decide and usual always appreciable Fund of catalogue of our videoclubs, cahoots by chance to capture Myers. And there is where it is impossible not to think what good couple of wicked would be, what waste of talent for evil giving these kind roles of men who defend a cause and die or are dying loved ones, but that has been my private movie fan aberration (open here) and does not require, in any way, endorse film. Otherwise, it will have to wait to that Zombie matures more and perhaps in learning that capture other more personal essences and stop twisting the topic, the classics (for who and the nomenclature) and mythical films. For the record, however, my passion (moderated) by John Carpenter. In short, drops a revision of the tape of the 78. It is already too much (much) that I do not see.</body>
</review>
