<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Interview" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The pace of the film decays to enlarge the lies, and with him the interest of the Viewer, that before both plot twist does not cease to provide the final surprise of the film makes it.</summary>
	<body>The project which is carried out in Hollywood under the name of Triple Theo aims to make a tribute to Theo Van Gogh after his death in the hands of an Islamic fundamentalist. The fight that Van Gogh carried out in favour of freedom of expression gave way to much of his Dutch filmography, but always wanted to make the leap and see come his work translated into English to theaters around the world. Hollywood, within this lust for remakes and hiding this creative nullity under a (false?) homage to the Dutch director, decided to launch this project compiling three of the works of Van Gogh: 06, Blind date and Interview, first piece of this project which directs and stars in Steve Buscemi.Poco or nothing be said of a film conceived as a replica to an existing one that alsofor not being anything original, follows even the system of shooting of Van Gogh, who rolled his films as if it were filmed Theatre using three cameras: one for each actor and one in level master. Thus, in this Americanized version of the Interview (I refuse to call it international version) there is no place for innovation and the only thing he has left to the Viewer is enjoy the magnificent interpretative duel we provide actors.It is precisely in this area where Interview (as so many other films based on theatrical scripts - the odd couple or footprint, in its first incarnation or in the remake of this year-) plays its best asset. Steve Buscemi is reserved the role of the journalist who, after a journalistic missteps, is renegade second line to take an interview with an actress of clamoring. Sienna Miller plays Katya, this actress's second which will put things not so easy the arrogant interviewer. The psychological duel between the characters does not focus so much on fast and intelligent dialogue (so typical of the duels between character of film noir - something that alone in the approach, Interview tap and flick) as in the continued deception of a character to the other making their relationship a mousetrap in which both seek to find the exit before the other. Distrust, pride, and that hidden side we all want to portend what both characters will and will remove the table in a game of deception, lies and half truths which, if it were not for the interesting thing about the interpretative duel would be somewhat tedious and boring film.The pace of the film decays to enlarge the lies, and with him the interest of the Viewer, that before both plot twist does not cease to provide the final surprise of the film makes it. An end somewhat naïve and populist in its message, which reminds us that appearances are deceptive and that nobody is what at first glance appears. Something coming from who comes may seem us simplistic. Perhaps we will have to wait and see the entire trilogy to assess whether this first part of Triple Theo takes a turn as do their characters and end up surprising us, this time for real.</body>
</review>
