<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>They have lost a golden opportunity to make the adaptation final of one of the best fantasy novels of the 20th century. But calm, even her can pifiar more and already announced a possible sequel.</summary>
	<body>"I am Legend", the magnificent novel by Richard Matheson, had been brought to the big screen with previously twice: "The last man on Earth" and "the last man &hellip; live" (The Omega Man). The film directed by Francis Lawrence and this Christmas is the only one that preserves the original title of the novel and, however, represents a betrayal in every rule to the spirit and meaning of the same. In fact rather than an adaptation of the original novel is a remake of the version directed by Boris Sagal and starring Charlton Heston.Todo this wouldn't matter if in return they had given us a great movie or a great entertainment full of pure entertainment and hard but it has not happened. Moreover, without the good performance and charisma onscreen Will Smith movie would be nothing.Without him we are left with a good atmosphere that makes us believe that we are actually seeing a uninhabited Manhattan for three years (in only three years are already there lions, deer and grass everywhere?). In that regard the Visual effects team does a splendid job.Unfortunately as vampires, though I think that never called so in the tape and seem zombies more than anything else, I cannot say the same. They wanted to repeat the scene, compulsory in certain types of movies lately, make a lot of zombies run after the protagonists and rather than resorting to makeup have created them by computer. The conclusion is that they are, to some it ache reading this but is there is, very game and, therefore, very little credible.The film does not begin badly with some scenes to introduce you in the drama lived by the main character, their way of life and some well resolved tension point as the first appearance of vampires.But, attention here than there will be SPOILERS from the death of the protagonist dog the screenplay for Akiva Goldsman and Mark Protosevich makes water at an alarming rate and collapses completely with the arrival of the girl and the child. Here one becomes a number of questions: how have crossed an America full of vampires? If they take all day waiting for Neville (Smith) what the hell they expect to be dying to be displayed? Not would have it been better to tell that there were while he was preparing the trap? How do you know where is the colony of survivors? As they arrived in an isolated Manhattan? How they escape from there?. END OF SPOILERS.Yes, Yes, I know, all these plot absurdities nor should have importance if it were a spectacle of milk and we we pasásemos in great but &hellip; not. The final minutes of the film are very dull, completely break the pace, wrong sold at auctions and leave the audience with a very rare feeling in the body.A pity, have lost a golden opportunity to make the adaptation final of one of the best fantasy novels of the 20th century. But do not worry that her can still pifiar more: already announced a possible sequel.Final evaluation: 4 over 10.Una curiosity: the 1970s version was much more daring sexually than the 2007 version. Another example of the times of Sanctimony in which we live.</body>
</review>
