<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Deseo, Peligro" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ang Lee will revisit himself and shows us a world as contradictory as his own figure, a world of play to the masks of personalities and infiltrators who end up finding lost in a tidal wave of emotions and unanswered questions.</summary>
	<body>Say at this point I would like to, danger is a return of Ang Lee to their culture after the adventure of Brokeback Mountain or that with this new work it proves not only Jolie but that happens on tiptoe by the concept of authorship, gets nothing when it comes to talk of a director that is characterized by the (alleged) contradictions in his career. Lee is, as it was Hawks or Ford, a craftsman of film but you have more artist than many others despite being an independent soul within the directors not authors, a concept that slope understand but that it is confirmed film after film.With desire, danger Lee shows us a world as contradictory as his own figure, a world of play to the masks of personalities and infiltrators who end up finding lost in a tidal wave of emotions and unanswered questions. The film pushes us with an incredible opening sequence, to immerse ourselves in this world full of complexities armed by a myriad of intricacies that stand out (hidden) desires of his characters. In desire, danger Lee returns on the underlying theme in most of his films emphasizing the two complementary concepts of the title: the desire and danger (wish). A young student is infiltrated in a world of political bosses through a theatrical game of kids coming to stay locked in a vicious circle halfway between the theatrical plots of Lubitsch and the blackest master Hitchcock film. An explosive combination which in the hands of a director so preoccupied by putting aesthetics of the scene becomes a dangerous cocktail.And it is that, despite the more than correct end result, I would like to, danger just to leave cold the spectator than as lost as the protagonist cannot but see what happens on screen as something that is totally unrelated to him. It is perhaps this obsession with measuring and perfectionism which leads to Lee not to allow to their scenes (and here I speak especially of the sexual) contravene the danger to become desire. Everything you in In the mood for love was by implication means desire, desire, danger remains in a simple attempt to spluttering despite the incredible performances of its two actors actors Maggie Cheung and Chow Mo-wan (also protagonist of the film by Wong Kar Wai, to which Lee looks askance at this revisitación to the world of carnal desires). This coldness in the scene is precisely which makes the 157 minutes of his footage become excessive for a story that could possibly have been dealt with in less time, without despising never fantastic Assembly that throws hand Lee. All the beauty that give off their planes and the pace of some of their scenes (that exploit on the film as authentic Fireworks) are worthy to say that I would like to, danger is a great movie. Too bad we can not overlook is Ang Lee and that at this stage, desire, danger seems a second (or third) part of something that we have seen before in his filmography.</body>
</review>
