<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="This is England" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a 12 year boy who enters a youth group simply by being wrapped. Not the I recommend, because although it has English humor dose, is a film quite hard and raw. To me I liked.</summary>
	<body>Director: Shane Meadows. duration: hour and half past.Release date: January 4, 2008.Hay many ways to learn the history of countries. One that is very well is to be immortal, so can having lived all kinds of events. As this is not too common, and given that we are too vague as to study or read anything that it doesn't start by "Sea" and ends by "ca", we must see movies. In particular, I've seen several films on the contemporary history of England, such as the child who wanted to dance or of those danced in the unemployment queue, which find me very interesting. Perhaps even more interesting background than the film itself.The film is a 12-year-old boy that has a difficult life in the Great Britain of Margaret Tacher (if the read out loud you will sound better than read) given that has lost his father in the Falklands war. Total, that as he has no friends, all put to him and is extremely ugly (this fact extract it I empirically) then became a friend of the group who welcomes you. This group is nothing less than one of Skin Heads, where his life takes a major turnaround.It is interesting to see this movie without prejudice, as the Group of Skin Heads where the boy nothing has to do with the concept that we have. The film itself I liked with reservations, given that it is very interesting and entertaining, but keeps you in a tension which I don't like. The actors are all unknown, perhaps even amateurs, which gives it a unique air, as much more credible. The substance of the film shows us how, simply to find a bit of affection, anyone can be associated with any group, regardless of the end of the same. And only after very serious events, leave the same. Curious, of course.In short, film about a 12 year boy who enters a youth group simply by being wrapped. Not the I recommend, because although it has English humor dose, is a film quite hard and raw. To me I liked.Besitos.P.D: The treatment given to the humor may be even black, but I think it is more by prejudice commented at the beginning that because of the film itself.Pd2: The protagonist, with all small and ugly, acts very well and extremely credible.P.D.3: The documentary treatment of certain images with background music, is brutal.</body>
</review>
