<review author="Raccord" title="Clerks 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a film about topics so corny and trodden as the power of friendship and true love. Kevin has nothing new that bring in these aspects and the film as such becomes predictable and sweetened.</summary>
	<body>The action takes place ten years later the story told in Clerks. The grocery store where Dante and Randal working fire. They find a new job in a burger bar, but keep the same relaxed discipline of work. Dante is going to move to Florida with his girlfriend, so his friend Randal and Becky, his boss, decided to offer a last day of work will hardly forget.Kevin Smith seems to have only partly abandoned the thug and iconoclastic film of his youth and have been covered in more mature grounds, but without much imagination gala. The main plot tells of a love triangle and a few friends that are separated. What the hell? It is a film about topics so corny and trodden as the power of friendship and true love. Kevin has nothing new that bring in these aspects and the film as such becomes predictable and sweetened. Rosario Dawson sobreactúa throughout the film and Brian O?Halloran, the protagonist, plays a completely passive and tedious.The visual style of Kevin Smith has always been characterized by being very flat, and Clerks II proves again: there are more elaborate frames, many more close-ups and up some shots with a crane, but gives the feeling of being an aspect little care and your address has no personality. Instead, which has always stood out is the hilarious dialogues House brand, that in Clerks II there are some of the best examples of the career of the Director of New Jersey, combined with others that are not so.It is when they come into action side wonderful, with the essential Jay and silent Bob, where Clerks is really fun. Talks about the Lord of the rings or the Transformers, mingle with the Bible or hilarious arguments loudly on the racist insults. Although most amused me was the wonderful climax, drunkenness and sex between species included.A romantic comedy with touches of bright irreverence. Shares many traits with the films more pastry of Kevin Smith, with its beginnings, but entertaining anyway and the fans will enjoy it a lot.</body>
</review>
