<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Atonement: More Alla de la Pasión is a film, well carried, it could have been much more game thanks to the potential of its history and the quality of its players, said it in passing, are the remarkable thing of it.</summary>
	<body>Joe Wright can undoubtedly be satisfied itself, it has the honour of being the youngest filmmaker that has inaugurated one of the most important film plan in the world, the Mostra of Venice. Did it the month of August of last year with this Atonement, adaptation of the best-seller of Ian McEwan.Wright does not seem to fear the typecasting, since after pride and prejudice again with another romantic drama of time, this time in the England prior to World War II. Overflowing passion, jealousy, betrayal and all kinds of love troubles populate the screen, and will delight lovers of the genre. However, and despite the good manners that shows Wright, the film takes horror to boot. The British filmmaker takes the presentation of characters to the point of hastiar to the respectable. The fact of showing the same scene from two different perspectives of succession and not simultaneously is a decision very fortunate for the tempo of the tape. The technical aspects are very careful, although Dario Marianelli music is annoying and screeching on many occasions. Only the presence of a few brilliant James McAvoy, Keira Knightley and Saoirse Ronan keeps afloat the history and the interest of the viewer in it. As soon as there is the trigger for the plot, not arriving until the three quarters of an hour, the film back flight and acquires more force and packaging.Atonement: More Alla de la Pasión is a film, well carried, it could have been much more game thanks to the potential of its history and the quality of its players, said it in passing, are the remarkable thing of it. Hopefully Joe Wright continue learning the craft and in his third film get debugging a more classic style.</body>
</review>
