<review author="José A. Peig" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It was not necessary, but the humanization of M. Myers has given a decent result. A simple, somewhat confusing in its internal structures, product but faithful and strong with regard to its fundamental premises and explored mythology.</summary>
	<body>Carpenter created a mystique of the Slasher writing the tale of terror from the enigmatic gaze of the murderer. In the 1978 film, as we already said, central character and mise en scene are a whole that articulates the elements at stake: Psychology (ambiguous), (cyclic) time, space (geometry of terror Haddonfeld) and action. M. Myers contained what polyhedral it encloses the unknown and unfathomable.Basically, the re-reading of Rob Zombie brings humanization and/or explanation of that enigma with a sense of the risk - so - quite limited (although also honest, viewed from another angle). Implicit misogyny of Myers - the original - here is an explanation in some family roots characterized by the presence of women indifferent to the needs of Michael and the abuse of a parent borrachuzo and cruel, in a dismal socio-economic environment. Resorting to stereotypes simplifies the product. Father borrachuzo, mother of life promiscuous. how many times we have been told the same story?. The stereotype can (but not always) work when its use conforms to laws related to the mythology of the subgenre. Michael Myers is a myth and an archetype that almost reaches the category of film canon. Thus, in response to his attributes, say that characterology used to outline the social environment of Michael Myers fits well with the purpose to develop. This explains that - despite observed simplification in a product that apparently wants to offer the description of a psychological process detailed, nothing less than the genesis of a psychopath - end being a solid product when we look at it from the perspective of its creator; play with the profile and Myers attributes to find the humanity of the myth inspired by the clichés of the genre. Obviously need an intellectual work that exceeds the topics to expose the genesis of a psychopath, so that it has a narrative and artistic validity. But - and I refer to the above - let us not deceive ourselves. Rob Zombie is not intended to articulate an intellectual discourse, and his film isn't so cheat as it might seem in principle.The film kicks off unceremoniously. Photography illuminates and exemplifies the sordidness of the story. The Mise en scène - although it is light of the psychological, temporal and spatial depth that we see in the film by Carpenter - years is an adjusted instrument to express enough without falling into excesses free. Much hemoglobin, but all violent sequences are resolved with sobriety and elegance, there is no such excess of artifice that we often see in many horror and action films and do not produce anything other than a free deformation to compensate for the lack of visual imagination. Many of these sequences, it must also be said, they sound as views, situations resolved with total lack of inspiration, and the unnecessary use of enclosed levels. This, we repeat, simplifies the product, but - we again insist - from another layer of the film, it becomes an unavoidable trait, a reverential language to the common places that define the myth.The characterization of the infant is another remarkable point. The androgyny of Myers, its seráfica beauty, makes a hypersensitive profile to the universe of sexual acts that surrounds it, in accordance with the violence deployed in the second part of the film against girls that make sex a cause for mockery or sway over the opposite sex or innocence (weakness) of Laurie Strode. In this sense, not in vain the construction of the female characters (specifically, the friends of Laurie) pointing to the banality in the gestures and attitudes. Let's say that Zombie wants the Viewer to feel empathy towards humanity from Myers. The murderer defends the innocent and kills the Harassers, and all this finds a reference in the description of his childhood. However, although he alludes to Myers sensitivity towards the innocent, the profound reason which induces the prostration and the unmasking of Myers before her sister does not have a one-dimensional expression, and that is where the humanity of the character reaches a certain expression polyhedral, closest to the construct devised by Carpenter, the dimension of the real, so suggestive and enigmatic as the human phenomenon: Michael kneels before her sister, shows the picture and its true face. The silence of Myers was never so significant. Only Laurie survival instinct leads to the tragic outcome. The romanticism of the victim is that ultimately prevails in the discourse about the genesis of the myth. You have failed, says Dr. Loomis, who here defines Myers as an Antichrist originated by the confluence of internal and external factors more - and better - character integrated into the story that Dr. Loomis of Carpenter. The evil of Myers is not exclusively ontological, is a child of the circumstances. (Attentive viewers will appreciate, by the way, some parallels between the speech used by Zombie to explain to Myers and used by George Lucas in Revenge of the Sith to explain Darth Vader.)It was not necessary, but the humanization of M. Myers has given a decent result. A simple, somewhat confusing in its internal structures, product but faithful and strong with regard to its fundamental premises and explored mythology.</body>
</review>
