<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Alien vs Predator 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An invisible script prevents him from being at the height of the original sagas, but it is still a spectacular and entertaining reverential exercise.</summary>
	<body>After the immense success which saw the premiere of the "Alien versus Predator" (Paul W.S. Anderson) entertaining, it was expected that its sequel, reached the screens even taking into account the end blatantly opened the first.This time, those responsible for directing the function are brothers Colin and Greg Strause, until now designers of special effects for films like "300" or "Poseidon", which adapted a script of the fearsome Shane Salerno ("Shaft", "UC: Undercover" series).A ship Predator crashes on Earth, releasing several facehuggers (go, creatures similar to hands that adhere to the face of the dam to deposit an embryo inside), and the powerful PredAlien, a monstrous crossing between two alien races causative of the accident to kill all the crew Predator.En the planet of predatorsthe collision not overlooked and immediately sends a Hunter to Earth to eliminate any trace of the ship, the PredAlien, and the other Xenoformos that have been reproduced. Thus, while the Alien are devoted to kill any human that is put in front left and right, returns to begin the hunt, the struggle for racial supremacy.Many changes can be seen in this film in relation to the previous delivery. In fact, it almost looks managers re-confirmed from the original "AvP", which he criticized above all the lack of clashes between the beasts that give title, and the almost total absence of blood.On this occasion struggles are constants and, above all, much longer. In addition, violence has increased, by placing the action in an inhabited village, the human victims are literally countless. Just look at the first few minutes to confirm the intentions of managers: two human deaths, adding to the already mentioned fight causing the crash of the ship, including no less than a child (see suffer childhood tends to be something unheard of in American action films).Another great decision which had the tape of Anderson was a wastage of well-known sagas offer. "AvP" was a normal and ordinary, survival that well could have been starring a brand new alien species. Clearly, the Strause brothers are much more fans so well known bugs, since his film is a constant nod to the mythical works of Scott Cameron, McTiernan and company, with almost identical to the original moments. Any lover of the original sagas will enjoy of greatly with the House that moves slowly away from the terrified eyes of actors and gradually goes up to teach us the flayed by a victim of the Predator, the water attacks the Alien, or with clashes between these and the army. Even some of the phrases are taken directly from its precursor.Such is the attempt to distance itself from the original "AvP", which even chooses here to renew the physiognomy of the aliens. Thus, the Alien approaching greatly which are designed to "Aliens." "The return" (James Cameron), while the Predator leave the armor looked in the first part.But we do not release bells on-the-fly. Because if something do seem to the (so far) two deliveries, is that lack of a minimally decent script. Between homage and tribute, the story told is bland and predictable, with absolutely incoherent situations and characters flat and inconsequential. None has nothing that makes it worthwhile, to the point of be so bothersome that the viewer will want their deaths impatient. There is some decent action, a link between character and public, but to round out the slaughter Reiko Aylesworth (of the series "24") could at least be and company complete some too apathetic and amazing work. This means that, after several early and spectacular ten minutes, the film within its more tedious stretch with the presentation of each of them.Fortunately, it's just twenty minutes, because just after the action is reactivated and turns into a maelstrom of persecution, fights and death (the double beheading and impalement with a disc of tips are spectacular), who certainly do not have any sense, but in the end is what one wants to see before productions as well.Thus, "Aliens versus Predator: Requiem" meets its goal of entertaining and correct the mistakes of the previous delivery. Increases the dose of fighting and violence, while you delight any fan of the universe formed by Xenoformes and predators showing an infinite succession of tributes. An invisible script prevents him from being at the height of the original sagas, but it is still a spectacular reverential exercise.And the end, as it could not be otherwise, open to one more possible third party.</body>
</review>
