<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Juego sucio" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film sound master Hitchcock and a good film, no doubt.</summary>
	<body>"In the early 1930s England, a new rich wants to lend their land to an old marriage who promised to let them in the House." However, the wealthy has changed your mind because you want all the lands around in order to build factories. So will pollute the above-mentioned lands.The old couple attends the Patriarch of a family there installed since time immemorial and they ask for help. "Since that time, will begin to be made by almost all the people involved in the process, a game of how dirty that will stain your hands forever".Film sound master Hitchcock and a good film, no doubt.Premiered, and circuits almost almost of arthouse in 1982, reportedly in a retrospective of the genius in his English stage.Note that it is a play, even in the recitation of certain interpreters, which is genuinely endearing. But it is well done and contains various notes forms and methods used throughout his career have nowadays where can envision.The best example of this is the long and excellent scene of the auction of the land where you want the wealthy build factories that pollute the environment. There is an intensity out of the ordinary, only with looks and gestures, getting a difficult to overcome tension climax. And all this, let us not forget, in the year 1931.Por else, be well remains at all times entertaining and at times even passionate.In its should what I have already said, there are times that some performers declaman and force the voice and gestures as if they were in the theater, something to as did Fernando Fernán Gómez in the excellent "The voyage to nowhere".To highlight the superb performance (there are some point that also sobreactuúa) of the masterful and always missed protagonist of our "Calabuch", by Berlanga, Edmund good Gwenn.Una movie you can see today, seventy-three years after its completion, without disappoint the least.That Yes, I am very sorry I can not help it, think anyone that sees in screen continues live, all performers some time ago already died.</body>
</review>
