<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Blade runner" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is the film a great mix between futuristic cinema, film noir and philosophical proposal on the recurrent themes of Dick, the existence, death, fate? Although, in my simplicity, I am not able to see as much reading as they claim their fans.</summary>
	<body>It goes without saying that I am not a mega fan of the classic Ridley Scott, with viewings behind me trillion, capable of shredding each scene to get every drop of philosophy to be found behind its attractive images. He had only seen once, for a long time (in the same Galaxy) and the memories treasured when I entered the cinema to see this latest edition of the perfectionist director, were erratic and capricious. Loose scenes, any dialogue, the soundtrack &hellip; and little else. So it can be said that I've faced in a way almost Virgin (only puntita) to this facelift of Blade Runner, which is why I'm not able to establish significant differences, beyond the obvious absence of the voice that narrates the adventures of Deckard. Surely this creates envy fans of the movie, because already I'd to my that will erase me the memories of such films as "Psycho" or "The coup" to face them for the first time.I do not think that anyone needs that you refresh the argument, but just in case, here's a summary. Very dark and rainy, humans has made progress in such a way in the industry of Robotics and genetic engineering that have been made to produce beings that copy in a nearly perfect way the anatomy and the human mind, better in some respects. These beings, called Replicants, are employed in hazardous work. After being declared illegal on Earth after a mutiny, establishing a body of special forces dedicated to "withdraw". Rick Deckard is one of these Blade Runners, who will have to leave his retirement to locate and remove three particularly brutal Replicants.The film is based on a short story by Philip k. Dick psychoactive and is a great mix between futuristic cinema, film noir and philosophical proposal on the recurrent themes of Dick, the existence, death, destiny &hellip; although in my simplicity, I can not see as much reading as they claim their fans. What I do see is a stunning visual power, aided in large part by the rare and magnificent "score" of a Vangelis in absolute State of grace, with unforgettable and timeless pieces.We must not forget that "Blade runner" appeared on the screens in 1982, i.e. a year before "Return of the Jedi". If we compare them (aberration, I know, let me leave) in special effects and visual power, "Blade Runner" has aged in a much less evident way. The impressive opening sequence, with a dark, dirty, city vehicles realised furrowing the sky in an ordered chaos, enormous chimneys throwing flames to the charged atmosphere or the approach to the Palace of the creator, a huge technological ziggurat, are scenes that make back many movies made today.Another extremely successful aspect is the blend of the futuristic setting and the gangsters of the 1930s cinema, as this room of police makes that we type in one fell swoop to the time of James Cagney and Humphrey Bogart (the prota is called Rick, just as the character of "Bogie" in "Casablanca"), the persecution of a replicant among the dense city traffic or costume designit contrasts with flying cars or with sable laser handle umbrella. An attempt to offer us a tarnished view of things in a much more advanced world, as if we had already seen all that and not come to draw us attention.A film immortal, with scenes that are adhering to our minds, as the final confrontation between Deckard and the replicant Roy Batty, the final monologue, the premature death of the philosophical Android and the flight of the Dove, a series of sequences so fortunate that they are capable of raising a film to a higher level, placing the film, despite a slow pace and, in my view, in certain occasions too standing on a pedestal in the world of science fiction and a model for long film that came later.</body>
</review>
