<review author="Estesoyo" title="La brújula dorada" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The plot is so cut that it can be summarized in: some bad very bad kidnap children to remove their pets and a girl with a good very good release them. Ah! There are a few bears that fight and at the end wins the good bear.</summary>
	<body>An adaptation of the book by Philip Pullman, northern lights, for American children. Hollywood producers are still looking for another bombing type 'The Lord of the Rings', but given the results, they will have to keep trying. Here they adapt, possibly the best story of the trilogy with quite painful results. Another missed opportunity to make a good fantasy film.The movie at the end was not to both. It was prepared with food, drink and you sweets for more than two hours and they stayed in a few hour and three quarters. And despite everything made me long the this monstrosity. And I say this monstrosity, because it's combining familiar faces, with static effects (decorated) and any match of animals made by computer. Damn, if Shrek have more dynamism than this crap. If you've already seen the trailer you've seen it all.Because the dialog boxes are not wasted. They have eliminated any political or religious reference (which is not that there were many.) but try to explain the story to everyone, so we have a lot of dialog boxes without sense, that they bored children and become jerks for adults. For example, in a moment of maximum tensíon (do?) my daughter was trying to see the color of the gominola which was eating. Because if children not interested in adults less.The plot is so cut that it can be summarized in: some bad very bad kidnap children to remove their pets and a girl with a good very good release them. Ah! There are a few bears that fight and at the end wins the good bear. They promise continued. Fear gives me.The actors I can say, if that better si el que mejor trabaja it works is the bear made by computer. Special mention for Nicole Kidman, if still doing things with his body will has end get the Mummy, more and more aseptica and without personality. Now we do not know if it is her or his wax statue. Embalming also could capture its beauty and leave it unchanged forever. Damn, she was red-haired and with freckles, and now is blonde and has completely white skin. and we laughed Michael Jackson.Dirige Chris Weitz with a script that has made himself. So it is completely responsible for the crappy. So far, he had devoted to production and to address any bland comedy. This work is great, but as it seems that him, pays then okay, uncle.By the way, it has been called the Golden Compass, because apparently, the name of the northern lights was caught by another film from years ago and not got the permission to use it. So much that it gives, I suppose as well in the future may be more faithful to the novel version.This endeavour of making films for children makes me weary. If the history is not for children, what infantilize her? Don't you realize that the success of the Lord of the rings is minimally respect if not the at least the concept novel? Soon will see up to the version of the Kamasutra.La nursery is a very bad thing, and that is for children does not justify do care so little work. For this reason and destroy a great novel, deserves one of the first zeros of the year.</body>
</review>
