<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="No es país para viejos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Production, direction and screenplay is the Coens and it shows, especially in the dialogues that are able to get you a smile to their topics and situations are all less comic.</summary>
	<body>After much meditating I decided that actually I like the Coen brothers when they are serious. If you ask me that the Coen Brothers film I liked but I pestañeo not before saying that death among the flowers because it is violent and appealing equally. In the middle there has been some others that deserve to be seen and treasured in memory as O Brother! (where I discovered that I could laugh with George Clooney and all), the Big Lebowski and Fargo. But if I have to say to what tape looks like its new proposal say it seems a return to the early days, which, as you can deduce after this presentation, it is more to my favorite and certainly thank you.Production, direction and screenplay is the Coens and it shows, especially in the dialogues that are able to get you a smile to their topics and situations are all less comic. But there is also something in the tape that comes closer to the visual beauty of Fargo, a species of onirismo implicit at every level that gives a perfect finish in shades of ochre and Brown.Josh Brolin plays a poor gift anyone who meets in the middle of the desert the remains of an exchange of drugs, all participants are dead (or almost) so decides that a brilliant idea is to take the Briefcase with two million of dollars. An attack by sudden goodness done to return to the place just when the murderer more leisurely, thoughtful and quiet arrives on the scene. A quiet but bloody hunt will begin to recover the money and revenge.It could not finish a critique without making a subsection in its protagonists, although makes it a little less to Bardem, are all brilliant. Tommy Lee Jones has seemed extraordinary, after a season that had just not have greatly appreciated it has compensated outweigh, Woody Harrelson has one of those roles that, not for being short is undeserved, almost dares to steal scenes from his fellow unblinking and well, Javier in her second scene with wives already leaves several things clear to the Viewer without having to open the mouth.That Yes, maybe the murderous botella-arma tape, is so useful that I want one for the bag.</body>
</review>
