<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="This is England" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is England is the film revelation of the English film of the past year.It could be defined as a kind of England History X both spirit and conception replacing Edward Norton by Stephen Graham and Eduard Furlong by Thomas Turgoose</summary>
	<body>This is England is the film revelation of the English film of the past year. It could be defined as a kind of England History X both spirit and conception replacing Edward Norton by Stephen Graham and Eduard Furlong by Thomas Turgoose. Its director, Shane Meadows, had already made another film with similar themes once upon a time in the Midlands. This time the story focuses on a quite conflicting temporary period, the Falklands war, in the 1980s when England sent troops to conquer (I will not meter if legitimately or not) these islands belonged to Argentina. Shaun is a boy of 12 years living with his mother. It has the label failed hanging around his neck. His father died in the army and with the face of Holligan Brewer and a single tooth seems obvious to know because he is the target of all the jokes of the school. As she has no friends when school finishes his life should take sad and boring in the small town where she lives but she meets a group of young people who adopt him (before the adoption of his mother Lady I do not know that this thinking most of the film). A child with so little experience will end up facing the principles being to his around, when Combo released from prison the group is separated. Shaun has to make a decision, opting instead for the more radical group. The movie is tough. There is no way of sweetening certain things. By its language and its violence qualify for adults in England but some cities independently decided to load such protection so that most teenage boys (preferably white) could see it and be aware of what is happening in these neo-Nazi groups that it seems that they back in fashion. He remains curious England, one of the places with the highest number of immigration and foreign and multicultural population don't lead by example on its partnership with tape as well. His dialogues are profanity, vulgar repetitive. I.e. director, realistic and bright. I do not think that the tape fail in no time and the few lyrical concessions that are allowed are delicious (with the prologue and epilogue documentary basically). The film teaches and not indoctrinated, therein lies its perfection. The retaila of awards and nominations has not been waiting British Independent Film Award, Flanders International Film Festival, London Critics Circle Film Awards, London Film Festival, Newport International Film Festival, festival of Bucharest, Paris Festival, Festival of Rome, Festival of Gijón (winning Enfants terrible), and official sections in Toronto or Tribeca to give examples of what has come and what lies ahead. Their best references: American History X and breaking Stomper (excellent Australian film starring by a hitherto unknown Russell Crowe is now cult film).</body>
</review>
