<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Cuentos de Terramar" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In short, a film too long, with a history devoid of narrative claw, stereotyped characters and seeking in excess platitudes of a genre, that if had the label of genre in his time.</summary>
	<body>Debut in the field of the animated feature film by Goro Miyazaki, son of the famous Hayao Miyazaki, started in advance with some expectations maybe too high, not so much self-imposed by the director himself, but rather by simply carry with them so highly praised name. The path chosen by Mr Goro Miyazaki has been divergent in tone with regard to the film from his father, trying to find more a story simple, devoid of metaphorical power, and even visual, moving a little Japanese master of animation film. However, as we shall see below, it has not been able to bring to fruition his debut project.The somewhat confusing history certainly us situated in a world inhabited by the magic, dragons and traffickers of slaves, in a land where it seems that evil has taken over everything, and the population lives embarrassed its depressing days. In that place, a magician saves the life of Arren, actually the son of a King which he same was in charge of murder, and embark on an adventure that takes them to the big city and spend long time staying on a farm owned by a friend of the wizard. Meanwhile, a powerful witch is responsible for subjecting the entire population of the place under its terrible power. This witch seems to know our Wizard protagonist and corresponding confrontation between the two, with the final revelation by Arren and her new friend Theru, which also hides a secret magical will occur towards the end of the story.This magical story sinks its roots in the old tradition of true epic animation film that during the 1980s, and even before, great Domino is based on the Japanese market of gender, with the excellent "The heroic legend of Arislan" or the series of King Arthur at the head. The big problem in this case, is that history progresses very confusingly, with a script that sometimes lacks a sense of logical narrative or a narrative pulse to increase the interest of the Viewer, still more outstanding most of the time the almibaradas reactions of those series of yesteryear type Heidi to the Japanese anime currentas given in the times to excellent parables and metaphors about being human and what surrounds him (without therefore renounce the roots of their culture).Nevertheless, it is fair to acknowledge certain scenes very well achieved, as the description of a decadent city or the great chase sequence of the wolves at the beginning of the film. But the mixture of influences from Celtic culture, the chivalric novel and a child vision of romance and magic, just for making water everywhere. Besides the visual aspect has a mature tone, an animation anquilosada in the past, that while it is nice to see for those nostalgic for the anime in its traditional version, required that at least the force of history was greater, otherwise looks go very aimed to set in other aspects, and that visual aspect, also lame Goro Miyazaki.El film tone cold and distant does not help too to compensate for the tedious becoming of the events, especially the stretch of film that takes place on the farm, elongated until exhaustion in a film that already if it did not offer the level of sufficient density to extend to the two-hour.In addition the character conform to several stereotypes, and therefore the feeling of history already view it is no stranger to the retina of the viewer never. Being especially way certain scenes such as one in which the character of Theru, so reluctant initially to engage in relationship with Arren, gets to sing the corresponding ditty and then both characters seem nothing short of twin souls, really worrying in the eyes of any spectator such amount of decompensation in the creation of logical reactions in the narrative."With obvious influences in addition to other films epic now and always, as that scene in the magician on the back of his horse and his glowing stick, that clearly reminds the wizard Gandalf so popular trilogy, or the final decision on those threatening stairs by which the evil magician takes Theru by way of abduction, and that as cool are in the memory of the viewer more tanning in the fantasy with the estimable movie called film""Into the Labyrinth". Originality is not also, the predominant note in this film worthy of the best product direct to video of the 1980s, within the anime more presivible.Little more than add, perhaps to emphasise the fact that will be tremendously difficult that its director is removed the tag of being the son of a great, and even more if instead of searching for their place in the genre, confined to resort to the more well-trodden ground of heroic fantasy (and not only Japanese of course). With a finish so bombastic and excessive as usual in those films of animation do you a disservice to the truly interesting products, and a final message about life and death tremendously confusing, child and lacking of any rigorous analysis on the true emotions.In short, a film too long, with a history devoid of narrative claw, stereotyped characters and seeking in excess the platitudes of a genre, that already if it had the label of genre (in the sense more predictable and tedious) in his time.Surplus.</body>
</review>
