<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="American Gangster" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is told with such enthusiasm and at times it is so frenzied that one provides, not only as a story extremely accomplished, but also as something absolutely credible and incredible at the same time. A real achievement.</summary>
	<body>Francis Ford Coppola reinvented the mafia with the undisputed masterpiece the Godfather film. We could say that after this trilogy made globally famous, little they had to see the new cinematographic incursions into the mafia with such films. I.e., not repeated such quality or such success as Coppola was achieved, although some that another wonder of the genus deserving not be forgotten, as the recent infiltrators or Eastern Promises (have not seen Scarface, recorded). And as a stroke of luck, at the end of a year as mediocre as it has been the 2007 comes a marvel called American Gangster, Ridley Scott's first official foray into the world of the mafia. And what RAID! It is a truly vibrant, fascinating film one of those experiences you can't miss. It is told with such enthusiasm and at times it is so frenzied that one provides, not only as a story extremely accomplished, but also as something absolutely credible and incredible at the same time. And therefore, there is no doubt that this is a new unforgettable sample of good cinema of mafias. A real achievement.Probably has a fairly obvious weakness is that their excessive duration does not allow to end round as a masterpiece. It contains scenes that could exclude perfectly, thus creating an even more enjoyable film and not so loaded with so many details. Despite this, Scott manages a frenetic pace and scenes that are memorable and as fast as the assault on the rule of drugs or exciting as the meeting between Frank Lucas and Richie Roberts at the exit of the Church (probably one of the best movie scenes of last year). And say that everything is sustained under a screenplay by Steven Zaillian very correct, although too loaded of unnecessary moments and characters. But is that, as in all great film, situations and characters that appear are many and varied, with two protagonists of contrary ideas that dominate this cage of crickets (or drugs) named Harlem. Above all, it is a film exciting, full of life and with excellently written dialogues, these remove the hat (located, above all,) at its final stretch. And it is possibly American Gangster containing one of the endings not smarter surprise and master of recent years, including epic. Everything in this movie is rather bombastic, yet contain small personal sections as detective Roberts divorce or Lucas's relationship with his wife. The issue of drugs, however, does not show as a backdrop, and that is a big plus. Perhaps the film does not contain too many scenes related to the fateful situation of persons addicted, but we are of course which is a terrible Vice and note as in the 1970s drugs was a key point in American society. Terrible, but true.Nevertheless, the two main characters are the focus of the film. And, without a doubt, there couldn't be better choice than Denzel Washington and Russell Crowe (two actors as the top of a pine). His performances are simply impressive, seem drawn from the reality. And is that in many ways American Gangster was close to reality (unforgettable last dialogue between Lucas and his mother). They may perhaps appear topical, as if basic portraits of gangster and police were added without further and did not have not a shred of originality, but I assure you that if one is careful, it has little to see Frank Lucas with any other mobster seen in the film. Since then, Washington gives us a role exceptional, full of charisma and hard character, with a kind of transformation towards at the end that definitely excludes it gangster model. This is, without doubt, an authentic American Gangster, with personality and little recognizable hidden facets. It is a real character. And Richie Roberts, masterfully characterized by a superb Russell Crowe that has little to do with Lucas's sadistic mind. This is an honest man (perhaps too), with quite clear ideas and gross to say enough is enough. It may also seem the typical inspector of police of most film, but some of their dialogues and, above all, that keeps the end with the gangster, are so memorable and different than accustomed we are to see that it distances itself from the basic model of divorced hard to peel. The side are all very correct, but do not reach the high level of interpretation of the two protagonists.A film master, close and frenetic. Nothing pretentious social Chronicle and that can be described as grandiose, exciting and narrativamente perfect. However, its excessive length prevents to reach the masterpiece that could have been. And to round off, two performances worthy of an Oscar each one and a no less brilliant direction. I hope that over the years he will be remembered as the authentic (now modern) classic that is.</body>
</review>
