<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La Carta Esférica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about the search for a wreck full of emeralds in the waters of Cádiz. Fighting between the sinsorguez and the placidity move same ela, swinging in the complex world of novel adaptations, up sinking like a fish of lead.</summary>
	<body>Director: Emmanuel D'irube. duration: 108 minutazos.Release date: 31 August 2007.Espectadores: 275.744 of human beings.Personally, Perez Reverte is not my favorite writer. Not for nothing in particular, I did not finish like his style. But I think that the abuse that is suffering in the film adaptations deserves it no nobody. At the end I'm going to have to buy all the books from Alatriste to compensate this man, that makes me sad.The film is about a sailor of salt water that is on the ground by a little problem with the ship (something some rocks scratching himself, or something as well). Total, which is involved in the rescue of a wreck (the sunken ships are named, dear readers) along with a girl who works for a State Agency. Together with them, looking for the said wreck an Argentine and another kind that makes alien (and that it acts tad wrong, everything is said). And little else.A little roll if the film, if. It is really maintained a pace taaaaan leeeeento, of those not passing naaaaaaadaaaa, which becomes infernal. The contributions of the actors is very poor, impoverished if I apurais. The making of alien is not credible, Carmelo Gomez still does not convince me and Aitana don't know if rie or crying (although gives us completely dispensable scenes of nude, do not stick anything and are made to arouse the Viewer, although appreciable breasts the viewings, by Jove). And the story has very little strength, very linear, with a surprise ending that looks come from afar. And if you do not see coming, it is that it gives you such as the film that you not interested make soothsayer.In short, film about the search for a wreck full of emeralds in the waters of Cádiz. Do fighting between the sinsorguez and the peacefulness moves same ela, swinging in the complex world of novel adaptations, even some malicious will tell that sank like a fish of plomo.¿Lo better? Relajadito that leave you outside.Besitos.P.D: I am pleased to see that the binomial Spanish film - tits remains in force. You take something to the visual.The binomial Spanish movies - guys with horrible physical unfortunately for the sector of feminism, remains the same.</body>
</review>
