<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Deseo, Peligro" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A virtually perfect film that runs media consciousness human to provide us true and cruel portrayal of persons, whether in China, Japan, America or any other country.</summary>
	<body>A flawless sequence of scenes without apparent connection opens the charismatic Taiwanese director Ang Lee's new film. With a simply perfect title and an atmosphere more minimalist that grandstanding, I wish, danger is a mixture between the absolute cleanliness and perfectionism worthy of classic films from spies and a rude but elegantly hidden love poem murky between two opposing sides that come together, and not by fate. After several and varied films without any resemblance, Lee gives us a majestic exercise in suspense to the Hitchcock and one of the most suffocating relationships seen in recent years, with a constant (which not fast) narrative that ends up dazzle us with an anthological ending. This is a tragedy about the limits of love, as something purely pathetic violence and two people who just define themselves in unsuspected. The story, which could well be put at any other time and place, is a thorough and leisurely journey through the insecurity and the coldness of two opposite points that collide and cannot be separated with a simple goodbye. Certainly some similarities can be found with the previous and also splendid Brokeback Mountain, as that so desired and forbidden love which is however dangerous. Yes, referring only to this subject possibly dealt two virtually identical films, but I wish to, danger goes beyond the human personality and explores something as it's shockingly evil. It is a film of contained emotions, which uses not extravagantly tear musical elements to show us hard images. It is, therefore, a heartfelt film, endowed with perfectionism (his aesthetic is unbeatable) and that employs, on a couple of occasions, the master of the aforementioned suspense film. We face a masterpiece that comes closest to the classic American cinema than to the Asian. Moreover, if we changed the language and the country we would be faced with a purely American-style movie. And this is not a bad thing, on the contrary: Ang Lee has had enough courage to develop it in a place outside that is used to shoot and have as a result one of the greatest achievements of the past year. Although perhaps their excessive duration (more than two hours and a half) not allow reached pure perfection, but that, probably, is asking much. Both Tony Leung and Wei Tang (the two main characters) are splendid, giving us two of the best performances of recent years, absolutely credible and very human, despite my difficulty to understand its so contained Act, form which does not mean that it is, or much less, negligible.A film that acts as a spy in a poem of tragic love, camouflaged among the apparent simplicity and minimalism to finally be uncovered and be discovered as something terribly great. Its slow pace allows you to look in a sublime photography Rodrigo Prieto and the musical pieces of the always impeccable Alexandre Desplat, by not forgetting a script that stands out for its elegance and precision, even though it is so extremely dramatic in their last two scenes (master the flat end). Ang Lee has stripped (never better said) as never before had done, leaving a virtually perfect film that runs half human consciousness to bring us a faithful and cruel portrayal of people, are China, Japan, America or any other country. Without doubt, a film incredibly universal, deeply dramatic.</body>
</review>
