<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Lejos de ella" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Rarely there is a debut film with so much life and as an adult as far from Ella, Sarah Polley. This is without doubt, the most beautiful and sincere film that has seen in years.</summary>
	<body>Rarely there is a debut film with so much life and as an adult as far from Ella, Sarah Polley. This is, without doubt, the most beautiful and sincere film that has seen in years, and taking into account that this is a beginner in this address, one is merely being admire her already for that magnificent story that told us with truly beautiful, sad images to over not being able to. And is that it covers not only the subject of the Alzheimer in a madurísima way, also get trapped in a small place full of feelings, pains, passions and, above all, eternal love. Under a striking, polished and very convincing script, Polley portrays us the life of two couples who distance themselves from the disease. One is formed by Gordon Pinset and Julie Christie, two monsters of the interpretation that give us classes with absolute mastery. Two performances that reach pure realism, magical, incredibly transformed. The second marriage is composed of Olympia Dukakis (awesome) and Michael Murphy (who barely spoke), other two people separated by the pain that they either engage in friendship, jealousy and romance with another couple. These four human flesh and bone are the Centre far from it, which also has a direction and screenplay has little to envy of Coixet, Bergman or any other inspiration that Polley has taken into account, that not a role model. A final poignant and unforgettable shows us that we have witnessed the largest and least tear film event of the past year. And it is that it does become respond the proposal of the Canadian Director, marked by a slow pace and it turns out to be a true retrospective of the human being, of loss and the eternal love. Sarah Polley not confuses terms, know what you do; is, in this sense, a wise girl and really take into account over the next few years. This is a sensational, delicate, adult movie for anyone who knows to appreciate life as something not too simple, so you have to fight. And I cannot forget me repeat the absolutely perfect, masterful interpretation of the gorgeous Julie Christie.</body>
</review>
