<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="La Búsqueda: El Diario Secreto" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Overly predictable scenes, a too horny American President and a disastrously modeled and repetitive script as above that I hope that it will not recur.</summary>
	<body>The legendary phrase "second parts were never good" has never been true, because well we could dispense with her on many occasions. The truth is to the last consequences which have been released (all of them virtually, blockbusters), have proved to be quite lower than its predecessors. And it is that there are usually more budget in the second part, but why no more plot level? The answer is simple: the writers are lazy. This could be perfectly applied to the new adventure of treasure hunter Ben Gates, the search: the journal secret. You could well say that it is entertaining, all in all we find ourselves in a film adventures of the vacuum but with some grace. But its huge flaw is that you cannot reproduce anything new regarding the correct the search, since it stagnates in the same situations (some of them modelled) and the screenplay is virtually identical, that Yes, changing destinations and some other special effect. There is nothing new, but less smiles, more pathetic scenes (see the visit to Buckingham Palace or the oval office) and a weary protagonist. So the only thing notable is that a sequel is quite entertaining and unpretentious, which already is much in the case of a film of this calibre, but continue trying to the Viewer as someone stupid reception. There is one thing that just never understand: How do Nicolas Cage get choose so many bad movies and make rather painful actions in all of them? Please an actor can have some slump in his career and having chosen inappropriately according to what film, but Cage has spent years doing shit, and the worst is that surely it won't settlement. The cast of the film, excluyéndo latter, is simply correct, showing some fairly decent performances. But, undoubtedly, if there is someone that stands out above all is Helen Mirren, with a not too deep role but all advantage with his skilful and excellent way of doing things. Otherwise, overly predictable scenes, a too horny American President and a disastrously modeled and repetitive script as above that I hope that it will not recur.</body>
</review>
