<review author="José A. Peig" title="Viaje a Darjeeling" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He has, Yes, with an effective construction of characters that makes the viewer can connect with psychological of each one of them, States although this fails to be the appropriate vehicle for the film exceeds the lukewarm and bland in their development.</summary>
	<body>The sour look from inside a train that - looks from time to time - head to the world outside to try to see something more than chaos, exoticism as subterfuge, the only Mystic a deceit of the losers. The train is the way, the metaphor of life, and so begins and concludes the film representation, with the train that is moving towards the uncertain destiny (falls clearly in the spirit of the traditional movie road). Three blood brothers (that spirit), Peter, Francis and Jack, walk the India beginning and ending nowhere. That look of Wes Anderson, to emphasize pathos of wanting to find harmony and sense from chaos and a certain postmodern devaluation begins being absurdly expressive because it explores the empty no matter what may lie beyond the ailing personality of the protagonists. Erroneously, as the story progresses, Anderson introduces too much information about the conflict between father, mother and children (including the unnecessary sequence retrospective). To make the explicit, the story, until then very well sustained in its tonality of comical absurd but quiet and accessible (i.e., that at the end and after moves in the field everyday), drift toward a Mannerist portrait on immoral individuals in search of redemption. We believe that it would have been tougher to maintain greater suspension of the sense of the narrated, won in a singularity of affine - and more consistent - with the concept to develop: film acts and gestures supported on an idea of indefinite tragedy, the palpitation of the pain behind the comical. Anderson, starting, wants to be subtle, but ends up giving to attempt to simplify.This is a type of film that uses the extravagance of the absurd to have really nothing, and from that nothing express a nihilistic pessimism. If you look in its structure and in the Schematic of its forms we have a descriptive parable that engarza in various sequences and topics relating to alleged purifying mysticism of the far East, pose a dissection of the mood and familial of three brothers through the incompatibilidad-tensión between these and the exotic atmosphere of the India. The film, in short, is a cluster of sequences - satirical code - which reiterate the State of informalization and emptiness of the characters in respect to their peers and these in relation to the environment. And where the story ends? The future of the trip ends leaving a sediment of reconciliation of the brothers among themselves and with the life that surrounds them, and is best expressed in the sequence of the three brothers to the race, freeing the baggage which until then had accompanied them, in order to finally upload the train. And then, contemplating the baggage that lags (ambitions, affections and wounds of the past), the three faces draw a shy smile to then continue the March towards nowhere. And it seems - say Wes Anderson - despite everything, life can be deliciously absurd. The inconsistency between the subtle stroke of calligraphy (put in scene, editing, photography, landscapes and silences) and simplicity that eventually looks at global content (schematic description of a destructuring and subsequent redemption family) makes the look of Anderson finished saying very little in relation to the dramatic and evocative potential that hides its comical and its forms. He has, Yes, with an effective construction of characters that makes the viewer can connect with psychological of each one of them, States although this fails to be the appropriate vehicle for the film exceeds the lukewarm and bland in their development. In film, be subtle does not reduce the chances of the content to a schema that represents the most obvious, to then say - and forgive the repetition - the most obvious.</body>
</review>
