<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El equipo aahhgg" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Parody of the A-team film. As a film it is very bad, but as it is well set, know what you post to see her and has jokes of the bad guys that are making much laughter, so can be seen. For lovers of the genre.</summary>
	<body>Director: José Truchado Kings duration: 84 minutazos.Premiere: 1989.No is if I have spoken of the book that I have brought the Magi. Nothing less than "The guide of Spanish Cinema" a such Carlos Aguilar. It is basically an overview of all Spanish films in history, more than 6000. In the commentary for this film, throughout the book makes to give birth to Mariano Ozores, it goes on to say that if el cine de Mariano Ozores fits poorly with Mariano Ozores, imagine to José Truchado. Heh, heh, makes me laugh the commentary, which is partly right.The film is about a group of soldiers, after struggling in the war of the Viet Nam, engaged to sell as soldiers of fortune. Well, they really have different jobs, but it is my small tribute to the authentic team a. Total, which should help to one of his old company that is being harassed by a woman that sell you a horse. Script high standig, as you will see. By the way, the script is part of Antonio Ozores.El film the truth is supermalo, but to me these films make me grace. It has a very silly development, with many patochadas, but from time to time make a joke that you ries. Especially those of Antonio Ozores, which is a great gag humor. The characterization of the people of the parody is quite good, sobreactuada, but good. The scenery and costumes also resemble the original series.In short, film parody of the A-team. As a film it is very bad, but as it is well set, know what you post to see her and has jokes of the bad guys that are making much laughter, so can be seen. For lovers of the genre, of course.Besitos.P.D: Sharing comes "Bombi" than you will the younger does not have the remotest idea of who is.P.D.2: by cierto, strangely not get neither a tit;-)</body>
</review>
