<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El ojete de Lulú" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pornographic film on the hairy and talkative eyelet of a such Lulu felt underused. Since it is pornography for more than 20 years ago, is very obsolete, although it is very curious by the strange argument. It becomes unpleasant.</summary>
	<body>Director: Jesus Franco. duration: 77 minutes.Release date: 14-04-1986 Madrid: Room X (Francisco de Rojas).Spectators: 25.137 of humans (some current releases will not reach this figure) reading my book of Spanish film (I hope the author I pass a heel by free advertising) I found the word "asshole", which sparked my interest. I quickly had to do with a copy, to see this work of art and essay, the prolific hyper Jesús Franco (which not only makes movies of blood). Spinning with the theme, the male I recommend sector search for the above word in the Spanish Wikipedia. And even more so if they have seen this movie, it is a detoxification cure.The film is about a hairy asshole, specifically that of Lulu. It's raw. Reflects the loneliness that has this hole, intended to be only an only felt by a woman to know the delights that can be provided. Minuspreciado by his companion, her pussy, the history shows us the sexual evolution that receives the aforementioned hole, until finally the so desired objective. Do cachis, you've already revealed the end, je, je.¿A be counted so os pica curiosity as the eyelet to a mandrel of red ass? Because leaves you curious, that the movie has moments that gives up to disgust. It is not you have noticed that the hairy asshole of Lulu speaks. And speaking with voice of girl or woman Tulip, which is even a bad feeling. In addition, the crazy zoomes no sense of Jesus Franco, shows levels that no human being should see. Well, perhaps I spent. And it is that a film director record porn movies, and try them to give a meaning, does that they stop eyelet - pussy's most exciting films such as these, with talks.In short, pornographic film on the hairy and talkative eyelet of a such Lulu felt underused. Since it is pornography for more than 20 years ago, is very obsolete, although it is very curious by the strange argument. At times it becomes unpleasant.Besitos.P.D: to have so many years, not you espereis penetrations filmed with gynecological levels. Rather wait a monologue of an asshole who speaks with shrill voice.Pd2: The final scene rubs the gore. It is más, I prefer thousand;-) decapitated bodies</body>
</review>
