<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Sweeney Todd" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The story moves to the rhythm of the bloody navajazos of this peculiar Barber (how not, a master Johnny Depp) and the tribulations of a no less strange Baker (an excellent Helena Bonham Carter).</summary>
	<body>The film remains one of the few able to arts give surprises, and if not here's an example that illustrates this approach perfectly. How can that to a declared no admirer of Tim Burton and enthusiastic of the musicals as the who signs these lines, nothing can liking a movie that combines both elements it be?Sweeney Todd, which we will refer to the short version of his title, is without a doubt one of the films of the season, and that sound with force in the face of the most prestigious awards in United States. Sweeney Todd is a Tim Burton in its purest form, adapting a musical telling the legend of a Barber in 19th century London. From the opening credits already note the personal narrative style and the powerful aesthetics Burton gives all of his works, and feels well soon that this time, blood that will reach the River, almost literally. Sweeney Todd is the story of a betrayal, lost love and his subsequent revenge, which is flavored by a few musical numbers of great wit and formal beauty, although the latter no longer a contradiction in itself. The story moves to the rhythm of the bloody navajazos of this peculiar Barber (how not, a master Johnny Depp) and the tribulations of a no less strange Baker (an excellent Helena Bonham Carter). The film loses strength with the scenes of the soft Jamie Campbell Bower, and a greater presence of the great Rickman.Sweeney Todd Alan would have appreciated: El Diabólico Barber of Fleet Street is the last great epic visual and aesthetic of Tim Burton, which in addition to the form, succeeds fully in the background. It entusiasmará to fans of Burton and the rest us comforting that it has left of childish tales and he has returned to this kind of gruesome stories, which dominates perfectly.</body>
</review>
