<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You care more about the truculence of blood and the portrait to brushstrokes of the filthy Spain of the time than a true interest in demonstrating the depth of characters with nombradía.</summary>
	<body>Perhaps it lacks the necessary perspective to understand the reasons that make the film more expensive of our film, in the background, one of the most disappointing. I do not deny him his ambition. Neither the bombast of his iconographic offer. The film goes well, although once the image has deposited its sediment in our retina, tells the story falters, turn, hence its fundamentally fraudulent directions narrative, where care more about the truculence of blood and the portrait to brushstrokes of the Spain filthy from the time that a real interest in demonstrating the depth of characters with nombradía.There is an excess of dwarves. Velázquez's and that, in the script, did not see that this majestic effort (EUR 25 million, say) leads the Viewer to very different feelings, but all Forum in the fiasco. One has the impression that one has attended an art gallery in which the dwarves, the Swordsmen, Quevedo and the valid Spain speak. Luckily Diego Alatriste say little because it just does not understand that whisper of drunkard with asthma that drag during the little Parliament allow you.Sparing no Díaz Yanes historical knowledge and emphasizes beyond where so far the historical film only deposited places common, topics of folletín. It was missing that, on top of face and acting saddlery of posh, the film her pifiase in the fabric of history, thus capitalized. Anyway... The euros we charge pay them to taste because we are well educated and they move us the stories of brave men who defend Spain with sweat and smell of orín hands. Also Coppola painted which Velázquez, its particular Flanders in the Mekong and nobody has pulled the Apocalypse cabeza.¿junk now versus Alatriste? Both deal with the same misery: the interference of man in the Affairs of men, which is the simplified argument of the war. If the gentle reader has some friendly criticism with regard to Alatriste which take into account, have it. Go to the cinema. Hear the still small voice of Viggo Mortenssen. And when I get home, get out of your movie "Platoon" collection. Oliver Stone, before selling both to ideals so confusing.</body>
</review>
