<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Viaje a Darjeeling" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The particular universe of Anderson might be a delight for palates accustomed (and prepared) to him, but terribly irritating for which they are not (or do not want to be). To me me ha encantado.</summary>
	<body>Wes Anderson returns with "The Darjeeling Limited", a touching fable about the reunion and the second chances starring Owen Wilson, Adrien Brody, and Jason Schwartzman, and set in the fascinating landscapes of India.Tras the death of his father, three brothers embark on a peculiar journey in order to reunite after a too long estrangement. The plan, proposed by the biggest of them (Wilson), is embarking on the title track to the film and train that runs from end to end the India. As it was to be expected, as many years away and skepticism by the younger before such bizarre plan give cause for irritation, tension and secretive, causing numerous disputes even physical. Much must change things so that the spiritual journey begins to bear fruit.With "Journey to Darjeeling" Anderson once again demonstrates his skills as a director/artist, making a succession of spectacular scenes (exquisite travelings tracking the characters aboard the train) which blend with a stunning photograph of colorful design to the sound of a simply perfect soundtrack.In addition, the performance of the trio protagonist is credible and delivered, thanks mainly to the work of Wilson and Schwartzman.Por if it were little, the film opens with the short film "Hotel Chevalier" (famous for being one of the most downloaded videos of the past months due to Natlie Portman nude), beautiful prologue presents one of the protagonists brothers and contrasts in his grey hue with the warm Indian landscape which gives step.Thus it seems therefore that we are facing a real masterpiece, but like what happens with the Filmography of the director, this film does not support half measures: he loves or hates it.Again being the main engine of the proposal, the particular universe of Anderson might be a delight for palates accustomed (and prepared) to him, but terribly irritating for which they are not (or do not want to be). Conscientiously deshumanizados and seemingly distant characters, banalizadas situations, and abrupt clashes between comedy and drama are just some of the examples that characterize the world seems to nest the head of the director and that in "Journey to Darjeeling" make an appearance at all times.In fact, just accept them and get to play with them to surrender inevitably to an emotional plot and beautiful message, full of hilarious jokes that they do not seek the laugh but yes a constant smile, and also presented with an impressive formal elegance. The characters are adorable, and fail to become quickly welcomed by the Viewer.It can accuse him, that Yes, a notable downturn in pace towards the final section of the film, in which begin to entangle a conclusion after another leading the Viewer to true selflessness and detachment.But go, to me I loved.</body>
</review>
