<review author="I침aki Bilbao" title="Expiaci칩n: M치s Alla de la Pasi칩n" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good, although little emotional adaptation of the exquisite novel by Ian McEwan.</summary>
	<body>Good film, adapted for the screen by Christopher Hampton, who did the same for the successful "Les Liaisons dangereuses". Wright moved peculiarly, personally, the exquisite work of Ian McEwan, achieving an estimable tape, quite entertaining, if somewhat uneven, as well as strange at times.It could have been one movie of love and proverbs in a cruel era: World War II, that so many millions of life cost, but his narration, the way of telling the facts, make the film look with some distance, showing quite a few elements that refer unreality, causing some confusion at times in the second half, but in the end, with the appearance of the character embodied in excellent veteran Vanessa Redgrave, acquire shape and sense. Certain flash-backs are strangers when they contemplate or scenes as the marriage of the premium of the protagonists with the former friend of his brother can be understood in this way.An honest and quite literary, narrative that however could very well not be to the liking of some viewers, who prefer a more linear and clear filmic text. But does not play nor mislead the viewer simply him sets out facts which are later understood as a whole in a logical and truthful manner.The technical part is irreproachable, with a perfect atmosphere thanks to the good work of the English cinema, with notable art direction, costumes, hairdresser, as well as good interpretacines, although, in my view, not too special or noteworthy. "I think, honestly, that have overstated the work of its three protagonists, which are fine, over all the young person (13 years old) Saoirse Ronan, but as mentioned there are not superb.""Atonement" has seemed a good movie, hard and very sad, that it should have been much better since it had all the elements to have achieved, although to the retina are moments, like many of the first third or the time in which the triggering small sister of the tragedy apologises to the couple in love.In any case, very pleasant although not convincing at all. Best of all, the soundtrack, with the use of rhythm, and original music which indicates well clearly the spirit of the film, although until the end is not clearly-</body>
</review>
