<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Pickpocket" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What fascinates of Bresson, of this Pickpocket is his poetic breath, his lyrical, this fascination with stories moved by very tenuous threads, but strong in memory...</summary>
	<body>Someone warned me long ago that Bresson film was so rich as to enjoy a morning on a bench in a park reading a book about Existentialism. That or similar thing. I had the pleasure of knowing the work by the French director, I accepted the simile, smiled and kept in memory the hyperbole, the Baroque and offensive joke at the bottom. Bresson was I never throw away and the years were passed without that I could say and refute or applaud the assertion of my friend. They have had to spend 20 years (up or down) so I check the scope of the phrase occupied a little space of my memory, but that was not going. Last night I saw Pickpocket. Soon he turns fifty. I saw a film honest, thorough, raised as a research, as a choking snatched exercise of wizard who try their tricks and meets your highest level of formal appearance, a demanding in literature, in the meanings, cinema but little or no leaning to the will of theatricality that sometimes a film and it makes, by the impostada demandin a fictional event, false, alien life or, in any case, disaffected from the triviality of life, of his normal. The cinema of Bresson is pure life, physical, organic, life masculinizada, feminized seeds, animalizada, vegetalizada, urbanized, but life within. Or perhaps cinema of Bresson is not none of this and yes it is Pickpocket, this story of bland hero of autobiographical whose journey through the city in his craft of vulgar ratero, narrates a story with many elements, but in a very simple way. What can not count the words, tells the silence, the gesture, the look, the movement of the hands (our hero is a thief) and the feeling always present that literature and film are intimately twinned as a genre saved report of a fact and driving that information in a way more creative (artistic, beautiful). The format is what changes: all ends hosted in our brain, which processes the data as known or as have taught you).The intellectual obsessed with the pillería of Pickpocket is a curious type: steals to gain a few quarters and steals to enhance his ego or, in other words, to convert the looting in artwork, creative, in an act of beauty element. (Sick mother, the secondary girlfriend) life is dependent on this vandalism with pedigree. There is a purge which empties into a purity, a primary instinct that enlightens a perfection and she throws all signs of vitality, all evidence of passion. Michel is a purist, a genius in his own, a kind of magician who has elevated his misdeeds, his crime a little naïve, to a superior state, as the artist when he picks up a folio blank, a Virgin canvas or a piece of mud.The suggestion more than explicitness, leads all the footage. The apparent reduction of elements, this plot or formal simplicity, part of a film need blinded in fragment (hands, gestures, eyes).It is the idea that the end of the story is irrelevant: that the character already has written an end and that everything you note no longer an obviable extension, an objectionable Appendix will not alter what we already know from the first minutes. Pickpocket is a difficult and demanding Ribbon: you can not go to their projection with mental relaxation of cinema that now fills us with, and I know I incurro in an unforgivable exaggeration. Pickpocket is a great film, one of those that lasts much more than the precise time in which we are witnessing its representation in our memory. That, perhaps, should be a good film, which lasts, which modeled us the character and brand us behaviour patterns, forms of life.Seen one in this dizzying time of convoluted processes of Assembly and Baroque visual style, this economy of means, this need for depriving the Fund so it ballast.Long also I do not see my friend and these are other ages to taste a film of these dimensions. I don't know if everything is on a morning in a park reading a book about Existentialism. Perhaps. It will be the requirement that he did not know given, I think now. It will be a thing to see us one day and discuss without haste.</body>
</review>
