<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Across The universe" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that I entertained without problems during their two-hour long movie, but ended up leaving me conflicting sensations. That Yes, I've done with the soundtrack.</summary>
	<body>The Beatles like to almost everyone. If not all the songs, I think that the world could appoint one enjoyment of the Liverpool quartet song, because if they are not the most well-known group in the history of music, them be missing very little. For that, in the meantime disk, so good lyrics and so much melody, it isn't difficult to get together a story by pulling on his discography. If we add to this good musicians and good interpreters, we will achieve a soundtrack worthy of listening, but do we get a great movie? So in this case, say that to me so it seemed only to ratos. "Across the universe" basically tells a story of love, but contextualizing it in a point in history Usamericana that allows the Director Julie Taymor ("Frida") to make an allegation against the war, full of buenrollismo. It all starts when Jude (name evident if we look for a male protagonist based on songs Beatleleras) Decides to leave his native Liverpool, to go in search of a father who has never known, to the other side of the pond. When he gets becomes friend of a typical charming gamberrete and, with the passage of time, he will find his sister (Lucy, equally appropriate name) the love of his life. Together live great experiences and tragedies, war of Viet Nam, the sexual revolution, anti-war demonstrations, the envy and administrations in the music world &hellip; part starts in unbeatable way, putting us in the history of Jude in his new life, surrounded by his new friends, but towards the middle of the plot, the film takes dyes psychotropic substances of the experimental albums of the Quartet and becomes too unrealistic for my taste. With the entry of an enlightened Bono (of U2, not to be confused with the Spanish political) the movie enters a period of negative and distorted images paranoid and argument of madness that cuts a little the general line of the film. At that time I became too heavy and incoherent.Past experience with LSD, history returns to normal primordial, to finish with a dose of good feelings which, together with the soundtrack, leaves you with an irrepressible smile on the lips, as he gets into the drama of a heartbreaking way at any time, but that everything is treated in a smooth manner.Anyway, the strong point of the film, apart from the Beatles themselves, are the actors; a handful of young people, in their respective roles perfect and very solvent in interpretations of the songs. Evan Rachel-Wood, which had lost the track from the enormous and distressing "Thirteen", very expressive and immensely sweet, Jim Sturgess, the British cast member (why not get catch the British English?) and Joe Anderson, the macarrilla of the group, a triad of actors who will have to follow the track, as well as a handful of great singers and cameos that highten the film.In short, a film that I entertained without problems during their two-hour long movie, but ended up leaving me conflicting sensations. That Yes, I've done with the soundtrack.</body>
</review>
