<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Death Sentence" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that only highlights for the visually narrative work and implementation onstage by its director, with a bad script and an irregular narrative rhythm, not to speak extremely unbalanced</summary>
	<body>Yet recent premiere of their previous "silence from evil" (partially interesting but failed due to a bad script full of clichés of the genre) film, director James Wan returns to give us a work irregular, again failed, which shows once more their visual capabilities, but also a lack of criterion to choose their projects using a solvent and narrativamente fluid script.Prior to the aforementioned film, this Malaysian filmmaker had surprised with a great work as Saw that despite being accused by certain sectors of cheat (ignoring that the film itself same is a cheater art, the art of making us believe what does not exist), became a thriller of those who remain and maintain their effectiveness in their own right (although not reaching the masterful quality of the short film on which it was based)(one of the best ever seen by a server).In "Death Sentence", we have Nick Hume, an exemplary family guy, with a work of analyst and a perfect wife, two charming children, the oldest a young promise of hockey. His life is idyllic until the moment in which a unwelcome visit to a petrol station after collecting his eldest son, becomes the greatest tragedy that could imagine Nick, Brendan was assassinated by a group of gang members in a rite of passage by one of them. The responsible is identified, is a young man of 23 years and is brought to trial, but surprisingly Nick declares against the identification of the person responsible for the death of his son, with the intention of creating himself his own justice.The work of Wan after the cameras is the only notable aspect of this mediocre course, creating a sunset in effective scene (which not dramatic, unlike his argument) and that allows passing narration with much nerve and a visual style production, proving once again that their visual ability is beyond all shocking. This contributes to certain scenes of the film are extremely bright, especially that concerning a couple of moments Summit in its drama, the chase through the streets ending in the parking of cars, which carried the Group of gang members with the intention of ending Nick, and the final scene, in which the work after the Malaysian film camerasit reaches its absolute height with nervous and full of claw camera moves.One of the major problems of the film comes from a script (or as I say always, which has been on the transfer of the written script to the final result screen) too unbalanced, that does not help much to make believable certain attitudes, and even manages to create a narrative decompensation in the story. During the first 25 minutes we are witnessing the creation of the basis of the story through the family description, the murder and the trial, still all too abrupt and spot sick-superficial way, to then move on to the development of revenge, with a third final act where the history already falls into the empty more absolute. This decompensation makes does not believe a human drama from the murder of the son of Nick, nor to develop in-depth moral approach that may lead to the Act of revenge, becoming all too much effects and debtor of a cinema of the 1980s where revenge showed in his original political and reactionary, as Charles Bronson anyone and their "Yo soy la Justicia". Term which incidentally is used occasionally in a way quite erroneous, although not as well for the film that concerns us, the revenge something timeless and why not susceptible of being considered a reactionary attitude, unless behind this revenge justified certain political or ideological ideas alien to a fair and liberal vision of the things.In "Death sentence" the reactionary term lies in several of its passages, resulting especially revealing the idyllic vision of the family well-off compared to the life difficult for the Group of gang members, in a vision rather Manichean and distorted reality, a reactionary vision going. One can remember the initiation gang and his paroxista view of the world they belong.In addition, all the elements of the story have a whiff of moral hypocrisy in the message, striving to make a denunciation of violence as a creator of violence, but in turn using the gloating in violent and void scenes of an underground message.The work of actors can not overcome as manipulative script and only Kevin Bacon gives samples, rarely of a solvency that can't beat the hangover is a character described as manipulative manner, but that shows at least decent in their performance. Of the rest of the cast noted that meet each and every one of them to topics and archetypes already seen until exhaustion, and that does not help the credibility of the story.Unlike the excellent "The fire of vengeance" (where Tony Scott showed that you can delve into the soul of a character driven by the desire for revenge), James Wan can't overcome the platitudes of a genre so dramatic, and where even resorted to copying scenes or attitudes of infinitely superior films such as "Taxi Driver", the masterpiece on the descents into madness, in a final scene where a photocopy that final extraordinary.In short, a film that only highlights for the visually narrative work and start-up scene by its director, with a bad script and an irregular narrative rhythm, not to say extremely unbalanced, as well as a message of doubtful morality and who plays on the edge of the most reactionary attitude. Worrying the path undertaken by this promising director as he progresses his filmography.</body>
</review>
