<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Juno" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The script environment and objective. We miss the audacity to Reitman in that aspect, but the film manages to entertain and look in the eye to a public tired of bland comedies with child spirit.</summary>
	<body>Jason Reitman debuted two years ago with his opera prima Thank you for smoking of which had also written the script. It was a comedy with an incisive script that portrayed with irony the hypocrisy of American society today. Sundance recognized him for his work and took several awards at different international festivals. With his new film, Juno, Reitman seems determined to repeat career and scheme: again a comedy, again, a script that beyond being the skeleton of the film is also their means and goal, again missing hand of direct and cynical humor, and again that criticism (something lighter than in Thank you for smoking) to American society. In short, the director seems to channel his career to a style of film that does work and which not only is good but that assures the success of independent festivals both from the point of view of the jurors (Sundance) and the popular (Gijón).Juno is not the young teenage American media. Juno is mature, cynical, ironic and a conception of the world very different from the rest of his teammates: on the basis of its cultural references (musical, cinematic and literary), passing by the type of guy who likes and ending with family relationship with his stepmother and his father. Juno, the film and the protagonist, seem to reach the screens with the healthy intention of remove all established, break stereotypes and molds to demonstrate how different also exists and is also much better than usual. This differentiation the causes the intelligent work of screenwriter Diablo Cody (already contracted by Spielberg to sign his next television project) who knows to capture in his character that view outsider who has failed a prototypical life. Their dialogues, acids and intelligent, are the great starting point of the film, and are supported by the excellent interpretation of Ellen Page, who has already demonstrated with Hard Candy that his talent is proportionally inverse to their age.Although Juno part of a good script and base an interpretation which gives the time, the direction of Reitman becomes invisible in that "wanting to demonstrate" how different is of great value. All ingenious script lies in the film because the address is allowed to give the leading role and opt for a construction of the film the invisible address. Something that, although can be seen as a recognition of the director to the script (in the purest style Hawks) also can be understood as a disability directive give this script a way that was also in line with the spirit of the film. We miss the audacity to Reitman in that aspect, but the film manages to entertain and look in the eye to a public tired of bland comedies with child spirit.</body>
</review>
