<review author="Josini" title="Memorias de Antonia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Wild memories, 1995 for best foreign film oscar</summary>
	<body>With a heart overwhelmed after the last imágten and uncredited accompanying music of violins, begin to write about one of those movies that we retain and we interview, and also won an Academy Award in 1995 for best foreign film. It is also known under the title of "Antonia".Antonia is a strong and warm woman who returns to the village where he grew up on the occasion of the death of his mother, and has just settled with her daughter.In her town, nothing has changed. Its inhabitants live the horrible routine some - the more wretched - or the stupid routine others, the more ignorant. Antonia and her daughter begin being observers but end up becoming actors of change in attitudes, relationships, and behaviors that occur in the workplace. Later, her granddaughter tells in off the transit of their elders, the pain of these and their doubts at the time that, as innocent little girl, interrogates them on death.Death, is it that reminds me wild strawberries of Ingmar Bergman. Death begins and ends a tour in which the suffering of life, his main constant, and the time lag imperturbable and unavoidable, are interrogated by the most brilliant characters of the people.Next to these existential reflections comes undoubtedly lucid social commentary. Advocates criticize film to those who offer answers instead of doubts, i.e. those who do not. Christian morality, the drawer of patterns of behavior and the human relationship, leaves limping the thirty-six-minute audiovisual drama.I think that those who these days is revealed to the traditional family would have to exercise moral courage reflect with films like this. Here is reflected the harsh reality of the existence of so many well done families which, however, are a nest of moral disease, a house inhabited by horrors that hurts name.The narrated proposal ensures that the family model does not guarantee stability or health to their human products, at least necessarily. Invited to accept family next to the old proposed new sisters, because does not necessarily have to give birth to children desestabilizados, transtornados or disabled to live.Couples are forming in the town of Antonia. These are sometimes joined without love but for friendship, sometimes without love by sexual interest, and sometimes without prejudice but by love. All of them share the denominator of respect and understanding. These new family structures that arise in the narrated history are based on a unique moral, and that is important, because it is nothing bad seems out of them. The village church can not leave them to step holding the old moral order because, as it is archidemostrado, maniene a moral double.</body>
</review>
