<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Atonement is an interesting film that removes the sensitivity but above all leads to reflection on the art and a form of storytelling that is already exhausted. Expiatory Metaliteratura.</summary>
	<body>In recent years many directors have submitted a critical and/or hesitant view on the capacity of the cinema as a means of showing the reality/truth through his films. This debate, which is more characteristic of the documentary film, has reached the fiction at a historic moment in which double truths of the Governments policy is confused with the tricks and mounts the media, a situation that has achieved many filmmakers to exercise a reflection on the medium of cinema as a lawful system or no expression of reality and evidence with the theme of Iraq. But let us be clear: No, the film does not show reality, or even when he tries. Entire film, whether or not documentary, carries intrinsic manipulation that begins with the selection of the Mise en scène and continues with the delimitation of the framing. Accepted the impossibility of the concept of Objectivism in the film, it is worth being aware of the immense power of manipulations (not pejoratively understood but as selection and construction of a film) on the public. Not in vain, Eisenstein spent his career making films for political campaign purposes or Hollywood, before the growth of European presence in their ranks, decided to carry out the famous witch hunt to annihilate any subliminal messages unpatriotic (or declassified) in his scripts. On this basis and looking for reflection, appeared this year in billboard films as Zodiac, David Fincher posed by the impossibility of finding the truth in his speech, or movie before us, Atonement, posed with a goal-literary exercise something similar but of a lighter and less honest way.Speaking of Atonement could talk about clean of its staging, correctness of their performances (including Saoirse Ronan above all the adult cast), of what is striking in its work of sound (possibly the most interesting at the formal level of the entire film) or do Don? Wright to become blockbusters English novels. But the really interesting thing about Atonement is its reflection (somewhat late in the footage perhaps) about two of the functions of art (literary or film): How can capture and manipulate reality; and how through it the author can find himself.During the film, structured into three parts, it introduces us to Briony, a teenager with much imagination after finding his sister in an embarrassing position, entering a world of lies in which all suffer the consequences. This first part in which the photographic and scenic ghost of pride and prejudice flies over the work of Wright, is where sits us the lie as a strategic level to understand the rest of the film. From then on, all represent truths which deshilan one to one as a result of the child lie of the young. So we enter a more gloomy sequel in which war and the concept of the real take prominence through an incredible plane on the beach in which Wright seems to echo Bazin and his theory of the plane realistic sequence. So forget all lie to enter the world of the raw, real and pessimistic that will leave you already in the third part in which a new twist of reality makes us want to revisit all seen until then.Atonement proposes the viewer a decision-making responsibility about what what is exposed (be it literature, movies or news) and at the same time taking art as a means of atonement for the author. This second function of art which complete the meta-literary power of this work, but now it has presented to us in his images version, containing everything is that strength of the original paper.Even so, if something noteworthy about Joe Wright is his excellent literary taste and his accurate mise en scene, something that serves to continue living the film with more than decent results. Atonement is an interesting film that removes the sensitivity (at the end and the place is a story of love that is interrupted by an injustice) but above all leads to reflection on the art and a form of storytelling that is already exhausted. Because I am sorry to say, for all those who want to see a romantic story to use, that Atonement comes to an end for those who leave you ice cream by its sobriety, his sincerity and his little film magic. Already played that film put the batteries (albeit adapting novels) and started to show some skepticism about all those romantic stories with which flooded us the screens.</body>
</review>
