<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Across The universe" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Thank God and removing it, the tape has an entry, and a pretty good end and is of that kind of films that one enjoys also of actors with the excellent band sound, highly recommended for all fans of the British group, becomes so intense that it arrives to thrill.</summary>
	<body>Some time ago someone told me (or maybe I read it somewhere?) the news of this pseudomusical on the Beatles, the truth is that I thought it was funny especially when my friend Pa (now in Madrid, before in NY) told me that he had loved, also as a of criticism of Muchocine left delighted the press pass, as well as the criticism (most excellent) that I have read I have pushed more if possible interested me for the tape of Julie Taymor.Es true that its Director, saving the musical "The Lion King" (which is the author, and, which has been gold, earning the respect of to' kiski in Hollywood), because if we look at his filmography are clunkers as "Titus" a strange adaptation of ancient Rome (with cars and bikes) or the biopic Frida Kalhoportrayed by Salma Hayek, as this tape has excellent moments with each other I guess that just means the author; and is that, "Across The Universe" is an excellent musical, but. (always has to be one of these for teasing one criticises), has moments where, as if I did a musical envelope R.E.M. has parts that only appeal to the author, and is that it loses in rolls psychotropic (at that time 70's where the Liverpool given by experimenting.), as well as a couple of musical numbers (the bonus and the circus character) that I did not like tootrue, it is true that Taymor thought to lengthen the footage until the satiety and is that good Julie does not know what is the simplicity and honesty and cataloging as "the theatre Spielberg" wanted to give with this tape the chime failed with his previous films already mentioned above.Thank God and removing it, the tape has an entry, and a pretty good finish, and is that kind of films that one enjoys also of with stakeholders (must see that they sing well all without exception.), with the excellent band sound, highly recommended for all fans of the Group British, not only doesn't disappoint but that sometimes it becomes so intense that it arrives to thrill.</body>
</review>
