<review author="Moebius" title="Lenny" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Lenny" offers an unforgettable panoramic view of the life of Lenny Bruce and his career as an artist. Excellent biopic directed by Bob Fosse.</summary>
	<body>The paper called it suicide.Lenny Bruce, a name is virtually unknown outside of the Anglo-Saxon culture, but especially in the United States is revered and admired by a legion of fans who read his autobiography, buy their albums and seek any material from the comic can be found. Lenny Bruce, a martyr for the cause of freedom of expression, a comedian in a short time swept all the barriers that he found his step and transformed the comedy American forever. Lenny Bruce, a comedian who went beyond the laughter to attack the hypocrisy of an entire society and denounce the perversions of political and religious. Lenny Bruce, the enemy of the establishment, an imperfect human being, as any other which gave fighter until that finally ended with him.Probably few could have taken the life of Lenny Bruce to the big screen in a manner so masterly as did Bob Fosse. The modern renaissance man who was Fosse was that rare kind of people, as the own Lenny, who left an indelible mark after Yes uncommon talent and hard work. Looking back sometimes it feels that had barely stepped on the Earth during a few seconds. However, his work appears doomed to last for centuries.Career as filmmaker Bob Fosse is as brief as eerily brilliant. It gives the feeling of Fosse was one of those people who was unable to do something wrong. Three titles stand out in his short filmography as director: Cabaret, Lenny and All That Jazz. Is which better? It's hard to say. However, should be recalled also the delicious adaptation became the director of the famous work the little Prince.It is no wonder that Lenny begins with the first level of a mouth (an introduction similar to the godfather of Coppola, who curiously competed and lost with the Fosse Cabaret), as the word is the weapon that uses Lenny Bruce to denounce everything that you think really obscene, false or corrupt. The concept of obscenity of politicians, judges and moralists certainly wasn't the same as the comedian. See a nude was not obscene for him, but yes it was that had religious living in luxury while would have people dying of hunger or malviviendo in many parts of the world. Even so, the Bruce (the character) is not defined as a moralist or a sobering. Talking about a story in the newspaper that concerns the expulsion of two teachers of a school for being gay, the comedian has no hesitation in stating that it will not donate the collection of that night to the cause of the expelled masters. Lenny is an observer: never go to a demonstration against the war of Viet Nam, but from its particular pulpit be ahead leaders and Governors, the Pope of Rome or any other corrupt establishment. Perhaps it may seem contradictory, but the comedian, despite being more than a simple count of jokes, is not deemed the champion of a great cause, nor seems that he intends to change the world. A Life magazine interviewer confesses that only it's their livelihood. On stage he will admit it is a taker; a hedonist which of course does not reject the luxury, but will shoot with incendiary performances to those who while living to enrich himself talk about public service and love of neighbor.The more humane and private Lenny Yes looks like a cluster of contradictions. In his stormy relationship with the stripper Honey Harlow, Lenny just betraying the love of what will be his wife and the love of his life. After suffering a spectacular accident his wife lies in bed at the hospital. A pretty nurse crosses in the path of the comic, and the inevitable end up happening. In the film his wife admits that infidelities of Lenny are due to his inferiority complex and a need to always prove himself. However, the marriage of the Bruce does water only on one side. Drugs and the infidelities of both end up destroying his marriage, which still will be a mutual affection and a young daughter.Halfway between biopic and an fictional documentary Lenny offers an unforgettable panoramic view of life of Lenny Bruce and his career as an artist. The powerful address of Fosse is simply brilliant. Between continuous temporal jumps, flashbacks, fictional interviews and fragments of performances by Lenny the director offers us in almost two hours a complete portrait of the legendary comic legend. Obviously Fosse introduces some artistic license, but the essence of the real character is there. Given that the language barrier can be insurmountable to understand what meant the actions of Bruce, the Fosse film will serve to ensure that those who are unaware of its existence become familiar with an essential figure of American Comedy and one revolutionary figure as others that appeared in that chaotic Decade of the 60.Desde its beginnings as a humble comedian in a slum in strip-tease trying to fit in the standard comedy of the time telling bad jokes and doing imitations of famous, through its glory days when America media was exhausted at his feet until the end with his sad last days where authorities harassed him and in his performances are dedicated to read extracts and their multiple obscenity trial proceedings, Lenny is one of the best film biographies that we have seen on the big screen. In addition, the use of jazz in the film Fosse is interesting. That fragments of the black music and sounds of Miles Davis is not casual, that not only is that Lenny was formed at exotic clubs where the jazz bands accompanied the desvestimientos of the dancers but the comedian could get to improvise in such a way as it would have done some crazy color bopper.The figure of Lenny Bruce and the great work of Fosse after cameras there to add extraordinary interpretation that Dustin Hoffman made the American comedian. As it was usual in it, the actor was prepared to fund, and on the screen we can see one of the most impressive transformations that have been carried out an actor to embody a real character. It is difficult to believe that they had offered the same role to Neil Diamond. At that time, Dustin Hoffman was almost unbeatable, was at its best and always offered great performances, but his work on Lenny is the best that has given us this man. Therefore it is also fair to recognize the work of the sexy actress Valerie Perrine, who leaves no swallow by the talent of Hoffman and also gives us a great performance as the woman of Lenny.Suele said (and is something I agree with) the films is better to see them in original version. On this occasion I think it is absolutely essential that Lenny is referred to in English, owing not only to the work of the actors but also to the particular way which had Lenny Bruce to unleash their gags and their acidic jokes. Virtually all phrases that Hoffman drops in proceedings are taken from performances and actual recordings of the comedian. That is why I insist on viewing in the original language.Beautiful girls who drink alcohol drinks, comedians that whisper licentious words in the ear of a stripper, jazz musicians who smoke marijuana. they are images of a party after a night of trabano in a strip-tease club, splendidly shot by Fosse, and are also the environment where a good day emerged Lenny Bruce, scourge of politicians, priests and rabbis, and also those standard comedians who based their repertoires in ethnic imitations and typical jokes about homosexuals. They tried to end with him, and soon face jail Lenny Bruce decided to commit suicide by injecting a heroin overdose. However, its legacy lasted until our days. In a symbolic gesture, after a campaign promoted by the wife and the daughter of Lenny the Mayor of New York acquit five years ago to the comedian of their sentences for obscenity. As a comedian or anyone can say words like fuck or cocksucker in public, the spirit of Lenny Bruce lives on. All this and more is what you will find in Lenny.</body>
</review>
