<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los dinamiteros" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about three elderly proposed dock the mutual safe. Delicious and intimate performance of three big players in a nice history comic with dyes of protest in front of the bureaucracy. This type of film for taste.</summary>
	<body>Director: Juan g. Atienza. duration: hour and a half.Release date: November 2, 1964 in Madrid, cinema Capitol.Espectadores: 95 of human beings, which had to add was on vacation or was a commercial failure or the website of the Ministry is not reliable at 100%.Older people do not go in the current film. Indeed, even in the television series. And when they go out have roles or hiperdramáticos, or as much of secondary endearing or funny. So see a comedy where the protagonists are three elderly people and young people are nothing more than side, because it crashes quite. Even the rest of the actors are people of more than 50 years. How change the audiovisual trends. By the way, the great Pepe Isbert, always been old? I leave the question in the air.The film is about three elderly, tired of bureaucracy and the misery that gives them the mutual, decide to do a robbery as the films and novels. Shows how millimeter planned the robbery in the mutual that so many headaches has given them, until even the fruit of their deeds. Deliciosa.Este type of movies must see them sentadito on the sofa, very agustito and relajadito. Why? Because you must taste, calmly, without strain or stress. We just have to let us go by three elders, their sympathy-laden dialogues with his critical dot, to spend a very nice time. We will not change the life this movie, but if we are going to leave very tiernecitos, with a friendly sonrisilla, thinking that the world can be much better. By the way, one of the elders spoke with the voice of Alfred Hitchcock, but I think that it is not the official dubber, given that it is Italian. I guess that the so-called dubber would do likewise with this ancianito grump.In short, film about three elderly proposed dock the mutual safe. Delicious and intimate performance of three big players in a nice history comic with dyes of protest in front of the bureaucracy. This type of film for taste at home.It has very funny moments.Besitos.P.D: Anecdotally, one of the actors is called Felipe González. Nothing to do with the former President.</body>
</review>
