<review author="Plissken" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>'The Oxford crimes' serves to show us to a church less strained and spectacular, but can always get bad milk from a very conventional history.</summary>
	<body>Alex de la Iglesia, is back with an unusual proposal therein: a mathematical thriller. 'The crimes of Oxford' is returning to the international production, and demonstrates that baggy budgets and the film genre are not a secret for him. These crimes also serve to show us to a church less strained and spectacular, but can always get the bad milk from a so conventional history, in the background.Martin (an Elijah Wood too "frodiano") travels to Oxford for his thesis of end of career, with the hope that the prestigious Arthur Seldom (master John Hurt) matemáitco is your agent. The irruption of an enigmatic serial killer will be that Martin and Seldom become gentlemen detectives in a race to discover the pattern of a few crimes that seem specifically designed to challenge them.Accompanied by his usual and supported in a powerful distribution team, Alex de la Iglesia gives us a production that moves with ease by all clichés of the genre, sometimes perhaps too. Based on the novel by the Argentine Guillermo Martínez, director and Jorge Guerricaechevarría continue the lines of standard detective film, including a handful of suspects, an inept police and references to the theory of chaos, the number Pi, the golden ratio or the uncertainty principle of Heisenberg (Ah, mathematics, how much glamour added to a plot). In the end, as usual, the equation is simplified and clears something softly and tramposilla, but effective. Another good example that Spanish managers also know to make cinema in the face of the average viewer, perhaps without too much brightness but not deceive or offend the public.And even moving in conventional land, the highlights of these 'Oxford crimes' are already common tics of Bilbao, as secondary desquiciados and desquiciantes, esperpénticos corpses or the time "level stream virtuoso", which in this case manages to link in a magnificent way to all the key characters in the film in a camera movement to the purest style "intro to the Simpsons".In the chapter of interpretations, a wobbly Elijah Wood gives the weight of the film to this huge presence that is John Hurt. In a role originally intended for Michael Caine or Jeremy Irons, Hurt recreates with a cynical and pedantic, character committed to demonstrate that there is no truth through words, gestures, looks. the same Church has pointed out that the essence of the film condenses in the face of British actor, in their ability to communicate that the only truth is that there is no truth to 100%. The rest of the cast is a wonderful Julie Cox, leaving Leonor Watling, Dominique Pinon and a histrionic Burn Gorman in a flat second discrete.And on the technical side, Kiko de la Rica get a great visual invoice (with brilliant moments as the quoted level sequence). The correct artistic direction is carried out from Maria Chryssikos, and music by Roque Baños alternates brilliant moments with others in which stresses too.In short, positive for the first great Spanish production of the year. Perhaps lack something of force in its resolution and perhaps a protagonist with more grip would have left better taste but still Alex de la Iglesia of bide them to satisfy fans of the detective genre. A 6'5.</body>
</review>
