<review author="Jokin García " title="La Búsqueda: El Diario Secreto" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The search for a decent film becomes the topetazo with an insult to human intelligence than being very generous we can say that at some moments it becomes entertaining, and thanks.</summary>
	<body>Benjamin Gates is a big search engine of treasures, Member of a prestigious American family, but one day appears a Lord brings evidence that incriminate her grandfather in the murder of Lincoln.Para to prove the innocence of his ancestor, Gates surrounds of their buddies and is dedicated to wander the world in search of the legendary city of gold of the Olmecall very normal, while the bad, which is none other than the type which has sullied the name of his grandfather, and also wants the treasure, is dedicated to continue them, in the purest style villain for Willy good Fogg.Y with this argument they slip us an adventure film, but I wonder I. is it necessary to make an adventure film for all audiences, which involves an insult to human intelligence?Because, let's see. One thing is that the character of Cage is the hero, and who knows everything and everything to do well, that is able to sneak into Buckingham Palace, the White House, in a private of the President of the U.S. party. but there are things I am sorry but they grind no, me too.Thing of "I jump a semaphore that remove me a photo of this centuries old, shooting the Tablet Tablet and if that already hacking the files of the police to get the photo and translate the Tablet there" is one of the things that killed me. One thing is that realism makes their concessions for the sake of the dynamism, but what this film is excessive, since there are situations that have no feet or head.The own journal to which the title refers, is the mythological book of the Presidents of the United States, where it is assumed that a lot of secret information, comes so to read, nothing like sneak into the birthday of the President, abduct him, make colleague has of him and get the information, and no matter that they launch the FBI looking for you, a pivot is all the security measure that you will find.The argument also has some to another rather absurd thing (without having to go into the dozens of cutreclichés that uses) being the fattest which serves as a storyline. To rebut the evidence to incriminate his ancestor you don't have anything else to do than to find a treasure and prove his innocence. To who?To me the only thing that shows me is certainly there was a treasure, not that his grandfather was innocent.Then there is the issue of kicks to history, inevitable in this kind of films, being garrafal that the city of the Olmecs is located on Mount Rushmore, which is like planting a Sumerian city on the outskirts of Oslo.¿Y what about that great cultural Pearl, when someone says happy "that is pre-Columbian, must have at least 500 years"?That someone please explain pre-Columbian not means "prior to Colombo".Anyway, this movie is a blunder and leaves open many enigmas, the most important of the "do for what I paid for this?"</body>
</review>
