<review author="José Córdoba" title="Alatriste" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Alatriste is a tedium, a medley of disjointed scenes and characters without a soul. I just hope that the team is run good holidays during the filming because I assume that 24 million euros will be spent on that.</summary>
	<body>Last night saw the highly anticipated, promocionadísima, expensive, Alatriste of Agustín Díaz Yanes based on the works of Arturo Pérez Reverte. The result? You could qualify him disappointment, although having read everything that I have read these days, my dream to see the film had decreased significantly. But let's go by parts, narrates Alatriste, no, it is not the right word, shows, Yes this Yes, moments of the life of Captain Diego Alatriste, a species of soldier of Fortune during the reign of Philip IV and the condeduque of Olivares. Already from the first frame of the movie you can see that this will not be an adventure film to use, by the employment of the format 1.85 rather than the usual for this style of production 2. 35: 1. Come on, that its projection on the screen not full movie film. Díaz Yanes said several times during the promotion is not a film action but characters. This phrase justifies the use of the 1.85, which is more intimate and is used by directors like Spielberg (though not in its Indiana Jones saga) or Shyamalan. The Fox fanfare announces the beginning of the film, this is the good, my grandmother would say I wish were true. But not. Alatriste is not a film, is a trailer, a greatest hits, a medley. Narrativamente is a non-existent film, the scenes occur offline, no flow, there is no cohesion, a narrative. The film is not moving forward, jumps. And the problem does not lie in attempting to make the best of the five books (other films have done something similar and do not suffer from this), but in not having written a script able to baste everything. Thus, the film is extremely episodic, devoid of rhythm. This sensation does not help the direction of Díaz Yanes (also author of the screenplay, by the way) who seems not to shoot a film, but film actors. Its realization is flat, there are no open levels, omnipresent being the median plane of the actors, so that apart from the actors little more is seen on screen. Or a plane of crane, just a couple of drawings in movement, the plano-contraplano rest, or not even that. Really for an address as well, no need to spend 24 million euros, because, overall, not going to see anyone. An example to illustrate to the reader, of similar achievements, would be any movie of those issuing A3 on weekends and, even so, dare I say, most are narrated with more imagination. Ah, but of course, this is a film of characters, why has shot as well. Nothing wrong except for the small detail that in this film just there is a character, the rest are stereotypes when not simple sketches or simply extras with phrase. Alatriste is a character, more or less well defined, is a man whose maximum is the honour, and is for many years, because the character does not evolve throughout the film, the rest are what they seem, i.e.: the child true to his amo(Unax_Ugalde), but reckless, faithful Squire (Eduard Fernández), critical writer with the system (Juan Echanove), calculator women but kind-hearted (Elena Anaya, a character impossible to understand), etc. It is impossible to know more about them than this and to do so since neither need two and a half hours. Nothing remarkable performances, Viggo Mortessen has a great physical presence as Alatriste, but disappears at the moment that begins to speak, where takes out an accent and a stop someone who is neither Spanish nor has this language as a language materna(no_es_por_nada,_pero_¿los_americanos_cogerían,_yo_qué_sé,_a_Antonio_Banderas_para_interpretar_Hamlet?). The rest just highlight Eduard Fernández, Juan Echanove (unrecognizable as Quevedo) and Javier House (surprising as the condeduque). Ariadna Gil, does not give the pego, his interpretation of the dog in the Manger during a scene of the film is embarrassed by anachronistic resulting.Technical paragraphs are correct, highlighting the costumes, the art direction, it seemed not bad, but come on, it is not much, so I could not tell, but at least that transmits the decay, the dirt of the time. The picture has moments very buenos(en_concreto_una_escena_de_Ariadna_Gil_y_Mortessen,_muy_bella), others regular and other malos(la_lucha_en_el_barco), is also not consistent and there are a couple of scenes that appear to be made by another technical team. Roque Baños music is repetitive and lacking strength, also employs the undependable Spanish guitar. However, the Sword fight scenes are well choreographed, and at least the realization does not bother. However the battle scenes are embarrassed, which are very cortitos goodness. Special mention for the attack on the ship, which as it has been shot not conceals at all the fact of having been filmed on the Mainland. So clumsy he becomes curious Yanes.Es Díaz, the film as a whole reminds me the Kenneth Branagh Hamlet, not its full version but the trailer for two hours premiered in Spain. Although really only reminds me that movie in the jumps of the narrative, the lack of fluidity, because in the rest of aspects the Branagh film is very high and this is also a film of characters, but filmed in 70 mm.We are closing, Alatriste is a tedium, a medley of disjointed scenes and characters without a soul. I just hope that the team is run good holidays during the filming because I assume that 24 million euros will be spent on that.</body>
</review>
