<review author="José Córdoba" title="Beowulf" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Beowulf is the next step in the evolution of the Motion Capture System and despite their obvious and undeniable successes, is a little balanced film whose duration can be heavy for the viewer due to irregular of his pace.</summary>
	<body>After seeing Beowulf and start thinking about the comment for the blog I realized one thing: I've seen entire Filmography of Robert Zemeckis with the exception of her first film, Used Cars. Nor is it difficult taking into account that he has worked on films as "unknown" as return to the future, after the green heart, Forrest Gump or who framed Roger Rabbitt. His work clearly shows a progressive interest in the technique of the medium, do evolve one degree more, in providing the greatest possible freedom to directors, make the camera more flexible world element, removing all its limitations. Something very evident in three of his past works of real image: Forrest Gump, Contact and what the truth hidden. Where is the amount of flat really impossible so far huge, being the movie starring Harrison Ford, the clearest example. This particular obsession has led him to develop the technique of Motion Capture, which allows the use of real actors to create virtual from his body movement and facial expressions with the company to Sony Imageworks. This technique was used for the first time in The Polar Express, Tom Hanks being the actor which proved her in their flesh for the first time achieving portraying several characters in the same film. Forced photorealism as well as little debugging procedure did not help too much to the good progress of the film, which was an experiment right in many things like the freedom with which moved the camera over the footage, as failed in other as many as the general inexpressiveness of the characters.A year after this film, Sony Imageworks, with Zemeckis in production, returned to the load with Monster House, much more successful than the previous one, due to his particular departure from photorealism, opting for an aesthetic of pure cartoon for the characters. This decision coupled with a fun and endearing script was a good boost for Motion Capture, while at the box office it did not end be the great success that was expected.Beowulf is the return of Zemeckis film and again with Motion Capture, although much more sophisticated than in his previous attempt and benefited from the introduction of the Digital 3D system in increasingly more cinemas around the world. Another factor not mentioned is that all three films have been intended and designed to be projected in 3D, so any analysis carried out without seeing them in this format is always incomplete. Fortunately Yes her I have seen as well, although in the province of Valencia is only projected in cinemas AEC the Punt Alzira.Habiendo seen both versions, I can say that seeing her in 3D is a great help to the film. The film is technically guilty of practically the same mistakes as The Polar Express: lack of general expressiveness of the characters, much less detail as the weight of the character lapses, poor animation of elements not captured with motion capture (for example, horses to gallop). Fortunately the technique has greatly improved and the virtual actors seem more real that never though still far from the wanted photorealism, Zemeckis also get a 3D effect achieved, by using technology as one element to the story, not just to scare the viewer throwing virtual objects to the face, something that sinned The Polar Express. In the 3D projection, get introduced to the viewer in action, moving the camera between the characters, through the use of panoramic aerial very successful and a myriad of resources returning to demonstrate that the disciple of Spielberg has not lost his desire to innovative.The story of Beowulf, a classic Chanson de Geste, equivalent to the Anglo-Saxons of our Cantar de mío Cid, is about confrontation between the heroes did not name to history and the monster Grendel, which has frightened a village north of Europa.El script, works of Neil Gaiman and Roger Avary, shows us a dirty time, violent not skimping in blood and nuditytoo pudorosos that Yes. For American morale show the demembramiento of a person is not problematic, but show the penis of the protagonist Yes seems it, giving rise to a shameful scene which seems taken more than Austin Powers than a film to be more serious. The development sins of discursive, it speaks too much of things claiming to be transcendental but characters lack the expressiveness needed to empathize with them. Yet elements such as graphic violence (a film not recommended for children under 18) and the details such as the arrival of Christianity through those lands, give it a unexpected turn and nothing significant. It is in the action scenes, sparse but forceful where the film played their best weapons, making the best of the film, although it is a pity that this expiration date almost complete in a Hall for celebrations and in the cave of the monster.The interpretive plane is difficult to assess because these are more convincing due to the design of the characters as more detail presented, resulting in remarkable Ray Winstone as Beowulf, Anthony Hopkins as King Lothar or Angelina Jolie as the mother of Grendel; on the other side of the balance would be Robin Wright does Penn? as the Queen, virtually unrecognizable in its digital incarnation.The artistic design achieves transladarte perfectly to the era in which the action takes place and digital photography is very successful, despite the distraction posed to the viewer all the elements in screen are perfectly focused regardless of its distance from the virtual target. On the other hand the music by Alan Silvestri is one of the best elements of the film being very powerful, without falling into Personnages type factory Bruckheimer. A soundtrack that create love, very much in the style of Conan of the master Poledouris.En summary, Beowulf is the next step in the evolution of the Motion Capture System and despite their obvious and undeniable successes, is a little balanced film close to two hours duration can be heavy for the spectator because the ups and downs in the pace of the story. One would like to that Zemeckis will leave the system a little and back to the real image film, but we know that his next project will also be in Motion Capture: an adaptation starring Jim Carrey's story of Christmas of Charles Dickens. Hopefully, at least, that it drifts away from photorealism.</body>
</review>
