<review author="José Córdoba" title="Soy leyenda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am legend is a film very estimable during much of footage, though unable to reach that something more that you would turn it into a classic of science fiction.A pity, since its inception and the interpretation of Will Smith gave for more.</summary>
	<body>After long time without writing here, it the time to return to activity. And, instead of starting with oldest criticisms, will begin directly with the last film we've seen: I am legend, the third film adaptation of the novel by Richard Matheson.Si in previous versions the role fell to two heavyweights as Vincent Price or Charlton Heston, this time the charge is Will Smith, the only actor today able to attract mass audiences to the cinema, as it has been demonstrated once again with the release of this film.I am Legend recounts how after a biological epidemic has exterminated the entire population, the last man alive, and therefore immune to the epidemic trying to survive and find a cure for the evil he triggered, and to thus cure the beings inhabiting the night that have already lost much of their humanity.The beginning of the film is masterful. The film opens with a scene of a newsletter where a doctor, superbly played by Emma Thompson (in a surprising cameo), unveils the population who found a cure for cancer. After this news and a fade to black, the director shows New York City three years later, totally desolate and converted into a real jungle. Only the noise of the engine of a car tells us that there are at least a live human being. What follows is an unusual hunting scene, with Will Smith chasing in his car to give hunting a herd of herbivorous mammals. They have just passed 10 minutes of film and director has been fully introduced to the viewer in action and on the premise of the film. A brilliant start, certainly of the best seen this year.Lawrence during the rest of the footage shows its good to do after the cameras. It is not a director of great visual strength, but it is very effective in his choice of plans, leaving them breathe without atolondrar or stun the viewer with continuous changes in level. In fact, by his narrative, Lawrence is shown as a director of old school more in the line of John McTiernam(La_jungla_de_cristal) and Richard Donner(Arma_Letal) to Michael Bay(La_Roca). The script is also shown to be very effective in the first part of the film, perfectly conveying the loneliness of the character (aided surely by the great interpretation of Will Smith and the direction of Lawrence) and her despair. On the negative side the inclusion of two characters in the story well advanced, behind a vergonzante(por_fuera_de_lugar) speech anti-racist and a too rapid, almost abrupt ending. That coupled with a topical design of the creatures of the night (and a few lousy special effects), Miss somewhat ruined the magnificent beginning of the film. A pity.In the interpretation, Will Smith dominates the film from beginning to end, which may be his best performance to date, resulting fully convincing in his portrait of a man alone and tormented by his mistake. Without a doubt, the best of the film along with his top.In the rest of sections the film is irregular, highlighting its formidable design of production and its successful photography, being very irregular effects special, capable of the best: New York devoured by the jungle, and the worst scenes: creatures of the night. As for the music of James Newton Howards, only commenting that it is in a very discreet second level, a very similar approach to Alan Silvestri in Castaway, film that has more than one similarity with it.In short, I am legend is a film very estimable during much of footage, though unable to reach that something more that you would turn it into a classic of science fiction. A pity, since its inception and the interpretation of Will Smith gave for more. Even with everything, a recommended film whose 100 minutes spend flying.</body>
</review>
