<review author="Berto" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie begins well, progresses a bit worse, falls some moments in the tedium, and ends abruptly, and, if you press me, not very comprehensible way, all as a result of a script that he prefers entering the simplest action.</summary>
	<body>Already some time, possibly since the day of tomorrow, not we saw here an example of film of disasters that so in vogue was in the 1970s, and precisely, has been a remake, remake, adaptation or as want to call it, the last man &hellip; live, where Charlton Heston, with no one who shoot him with his rifle during the dayIt campaba by L.A. and Woodstock looked over and over again. Now is Will Smith who does Robert Neville, become a scientist of the army who, after losing his entire family and see how a supposed cure against cancer (discovered by Emma Thompson, ojito) had just been leaving desert worldwide, lives with his dog Sam as he tries desperately to find a cure for those infected.It will Smith is one of those few actors on which a film can rest without that to the respectable they do want to strangle him or ingested cyanide capsule, and I am legend is no exception to this rule. Perhaps since that Tom Hanks made the flight of the lost aircraft not watched an actor occupy as many minutes of screen solo and get keep entertaining to the public, although it is based on making dominated in bar, and always share screen with a family member; in this case, his daughter Willow (no kinship with the adorable dwarf).The movie begins well, progresses a bit worse, falls some moments in the tedium, and ends abruptly, and, if you press me, not very comprehensible way. All as a result of a script that he prefers entering the simplest action in the exploration of some concepts that they point in the movie, but just leaving once, for the greater glory of the explosion and the fight. I'm not saying that they should not be, eye, but it gives the impression that had to justify the 300 million spent, possibly on the salary of Smith, because those infected seem to have emerged from Blade II, and look on the screen pretty bad, to be honest.The head of the tape is Francis Lawrence, whose only reference in cinema is Constantine, and comes of &hellip; well, sure that not it it takes much guess, isn't it? Yes, naturally, the world of the music video. It isn't to do especially evil, and there are even some interesting point (the disturbing presentation for the first time of the infected, for example, with its back to Neville), but in the fights not we learned much, although you are a black type of feet against the ugly brother of Gollum. still, as the thing is does not extend much more than 100 minutes, and Smith it goes without charisma, can be seen with pleasure while one doesn't start to ask too many questions about how the alpha male has made to learn crafts, or why it is worse cold Vermont than in the raw New York winter. Fortunately, by what we see in the film, none will have to swallow in theaters Batman vs. Superman. It is something.</body>
</review>
