<review author="Berto" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Quite entertaining film, that has the addition of further a little childhood of so hold psychopath, and that efficiently solves the memory of the original film.</summary>
	<body>Halloween has to his credit with the label of being one of the most profitable films of the history of the cinema. The budget that Carpenter had managed in his day is derisory in comparison with the global collection which went around the world, apart from the achieved fame and lay the foundations for a genre that would be fashion and that from time to time continues making a comeback, of the slashers. This handicap he had to fight the producer to get get a remake more than worthy of the first film in the series, and is that after that several directors and writers to leave the project at the end they managed to bring forward thanks above all to the interests of the director of this new version, the singer converted to filmmaker Rob Zombie. Already in his two previous films had demonstrated very good manners, being their debut, with the House of 1000 corpses, and then its subsequent sequel, the forsaken the devil, two already considered to be cult films.On this occasion, the Remake tries to go a little beyond, and while in the original version of Carpenter murder that would usher in the mythology of Myers was told very in passing focus on the killing of the day of Halloween 15 years later, in this new version takes a full hour to try to show us the Tinder which is I think one of the older murderous psychopaths in film history.During the second hour, focuses more on the classic, reaching copy murders and situations, but I think more sincere tribute a blatant, copy because after very different home that has this well show new generations that was what really gave the success this film.Actors are quite well, Tyler Mane meets perfectly when it comes to embody a giant Myers that scary just seeing him standing up on screen, and manages to create an aura of supernatural about the character, although part of this success is due to the outstanding leadership of Rob Zombie, that my already liked a lot in their previous two films and that in this film he continues to demonstrate that it is one of the values in any future upside project to this cinematic style, although it on good authority that the rest of Clockwork partners will be happy to refute me any recognition to the director.Child, played by Daeg Faerch, Myers is another interesting role and makes a very convincing recreation of the childhood of the character, something key to the evolution of the character throughout the footage.In short, a fairly entertaining film, that has the addition of further a little childhood of so hold psychopath, and that efficiently solve the memory of the original film, something that according to recently seen in the film is very take into account, that are not generally find worthy remakes.</body>
</review>
