<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>His greatest achievement is the binomial consisting of John Hurt and Elijah Wood, two actors able to capture our attention although the plot no longer interest us.</summary>
	<body>After having offered as unclassifiable and at the same time as personal titles such as mutant action, the day of the beast, Perdita Durango, community, 800 balas, dead of laughter or crime ferpecto, Álex de la Iglesia returns after four years of silence (except for the child's room) with the crimes of Oxford, starring Elijah Wood, John HurtLeonor Watling, Julie Cox, Burn Gorman, Anna Massey and Jim Carter among others.Based on the novel by Guillermo Martínez crimes imperceptible, the film tells the story of an exchange student who discovers the lifeless body of his landlady, who was married to one of the mathematicians who deciphered the Enigma code in World War II. At the same time, a Professor of logic at Oxford receives a note warning that this is the first of a series of murders. Thus, the student and the teacher join in the search for the person behind the deaths, using mathematical codes to find the pattern that follows this Assassin in series...Beyond the quality of the movie itself, it must be said that the Oxford murders is a radical turn in the film career of Álex de la Iglesia. But, for better or worse? Without any doubt, is not his most brilliant work, but not a product that renege. And, at the same time, it is still most unclassifiable as the rest of his filmography, ironically, he is his more orthodox film.The Oxford murders is a thriller that revolves around a series of murders, and as all film of this genre, there will be ready on duty claiming that the final outcome is already sensed from the first minute. This sometimes is a good and a server has served such a claim on more than one occasion, but I do not think that the Oxford murders is as deductible as more than one pretend.The film of Álex de la Iglesia is totally recommended, endowed with a brioso pace and always something interesting to tell, although one must recognize its mescolanza of philosophy and mathematics can get tired in some fragments. Their characters, in greater or lesser degree, we still Recalling somehow to those used usually by the director bilbaino, while the alleged international character of the film seems to have them jeunetizado considerably, and not I refer simply to the presence of Dominique Pinon, but rather to the characters played by Burn Gorman and Jim Carter.Por other side, can be said that the plot of the Oxford murders is interesting although not overly complex, and his greatest achievement, beyond the fact that its resolution is completely arbitrary - or what is the same as any other would have been as feasible as the chosen, is the binomial consisting of John Hurt and Elijah Wood, two actors able to capture our attention although the plot no longer interest us. That, and the portentous mammary glands of Leonor Watling, sincerely, impeding me analyze its performance.</body>
</review>
