<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Mortadelo y Filemón: Misión Salvar la Tierra" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Instead of mission: save the Earth, this surplus sequel should have been entitled mission: sink further national cinema or mission: kill the film.</summary>
	<body>This 25 January, and in commemoration of the 50th anniversary of the comic strip created by Francisco Ibáñez, premieres Mortadelo y Filemón. Mission: save the Earth, directed by Miguel Bardem Javier Fesser replacing and with Edu Soto, Pepe Viyuela, Berta Ojea, Mariano Venancio, Janfri Coronado, Carlos Santos, Emilio Gavira and Carmen Ruiz as protagonists.Coinciding with a major drought, a group of thugs proposes to eliminate the water reserves left in the Earth. The best secret agents in the world urgently meet, but do not have no clue. To make things worse, the evil Botijola plan to undermine that meeting, thus ending all actors. Its intention is to convert the drink that bears his name in the replacement of the water. To this end, it will try to also kidnap Professor effect. However, there are two things that Botijola did not. On the one hand, effect, before being kidnapped, hid the pieces of his invention in different historical moments, using the time machine. On the other hand, there are two international players who have not attended the saboteada meeting, they will become the only hope for the world. Mortadelo y Filemón will have to put aside their disputes to return to the action, with the invaluable help of Ophelia and following the designs of the Super. rather than mission: save the Earth, this surplus sequel should have been entitled mission: sink further national cinema or mission: kill the film. As it happened with the first installment, the adventures of these mythical characters of the printed paper have been altered to become a sort of absolutely despicable homeland freak their gags. And is that enough doubt that someone who has been raised with the comic strips of Ibáñez found the slightest grace to this peñazo of film, in which have place to imitations of the cuñaooo!.!.!Far is the memory of graphic humor of stories as the Chapeau the Esmirriau or similar, in a boring to kill movie and that is sometimes closer to aberrations in the f.b.i. (Frikis Buscan annoy) that line in the early work of the previous director, Javier Fesser, as the short film the tlompeta secdleto or the curious El milagro de P. Tinto. I speak of the previous director because the hand of Miguel Bardem is not appreciated anywhere, while maintaining the same aesthetic and style than its predecessor, the only thing salvageable from a film that broadly is certainly better to forget.Just a couple of gags can save its something more than a hundred minutes of footage, as the cameo of Toni Albà imitating the King - as does every week in the great Polònia- and some more. The rest, despicable, included the digitized dog Bush, completely expendable and lacking in grace, and that pulls on the floor general computation of special effects more than worthy broadly. Even Edu Soto ago let us miss the previous mort, Benito Pocino.Un insulting the intelligence and what is worse, to strips of Ibáñez.</body>
</review>
