<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="La criatura perfecta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Little you can highlight the perfect creature, with the exception of its Gothic setting. The rest, to forget.</summary>
	<body>The perfect creature is a co-production between New Zealand and United Kingdom directed by Glenn Standring and starring Dougray Scott, Saffron Burrows, Leo Gregory, Scott Willis, Stuart Wilson, Craig Hall, Robbie characters, Lauren Jackson, Peter McCauley and Glen Drake.La film puts us in an alternative and retro-futurista 1960, where vampires and humans coexist peacefully for over 300 years. But this delicate balance will be broken when a vampire begins to feed on humans, spreading a strange disease similar to rage, threatening peace between the so-called brothers and the rest of society.Little you can highlight the perfect creature's film next Friday to reach our billboards. With a Gothic atmosphere fusion of Underworld and the compass Golden – although its closest analogy would be that of Van Helsing futuristic - the perfect creature is one failed attempt more attracting to the public from the vampire myth.The film is based on the assumption that a 15th century alchemist created vampires while trying to find a vaccine for pests around the world at that time, such as the plague. Vampires, regarded as an aberration in spite of not serotra thing that one more step in the evolution of man, found the cure to these pests and vowed to protect human, forming the so-called Church and becoming themselves Hermanos.Como idea, certainly, is not bad at all, but both the Fund and the form of the perfect creature makes water everywhere, resulting in its Gothic aesthetics only thing salvageable from this tape whose influences range from the aforementioned Underworld and Van Helsing, to titles such as Equilibrium or Ultraviolet: the plot loses all its appeal once it has been raised, presenting us with a succession of archetypal characters played by actors that seem to compete for the award for worst actor of the year, among which one might highlight to a bland Dougray Scottprobably the most bland vampire of recent times.Although, let's be honest, we could say vampire as we could say ukelele sociopath, a contained thirst for blood and a greater physical power are the only signs that point to confirm the nature of undead vampires of the perfect creature. On the other hand, the leitmotiv of Edgar, nemesis of the tape, nor do we have excessive clear in no time, justifying their actions from an illness that he himself has created.That Yes, sequel rather than open, of course.Direct output to DVD product, and little else.</body>
</review>
