<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Alien vs Predator 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Terríblemente fun for fans and quite superior to its predecessor. That Yes, or soñéis to find something similar to the original movies.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Colin and Greg Strause special effects technicians, and starring John Ortiz, Steven Pasquale, Johnny Lewis, Reiko Aylesworth, David Paetkau and Chelah Horsdal among others, Aliens vs. Predator 2: requiem, is the second movie facing the two mythical alien creatures of the Fox.Cuando a ship Explorer Predator crashes, appears in a Colorado town. The Aliens on board escape and kill all the Predators except one. The last surviving Predator must now end with all the Aliens, as well as the terrifying Predalien who was begotten in the previous installment. Meanwhile, the inhabitants of the village are being needlessly trapped in the middle of the last confrontation between these two mythical creatures.As a faithful follower of the series and sickly collector of McFarlane Toys of the initiated sagas by Ridley Scott and John McTiernan, I have followed the development of this sequel with considerable interest from its origins, despite the weak outcome of previous delivery. One of the things that most called the attention of such production was the claim by managers that the film was going to be a tribute to the entire saga, from four at Depredador.Y 2 Alien movies go if it is.Objectively speaking, as film Aliens vs. Predator: requiem leaves much to be desired, especially if we compare it with great versions of Scott, Cameron and McTiernan (and Fincher, although reniege it himself), but as a staunch follower of both creatures, have to say that this second installment is terribly funny, bloody and, above all, full of winks. Finally, say winks is little, since it could ensure that its plot is built based on Parallels and tributes to the previous installments and will still say more, when Aliens vs Predator 2: requiem ceases to do so, quite lost.With blatantly archetypal characters, the Strause brothers leave us well clear from the outset who are true stars: the film starts immediately after the events in Aliens vs. Predator, when the alien inoculated in one of the predators completed its gestation process forcing the rest of the crew to return to Earth.A from there, and after giving us for the first time the planet Predator, starts the succession of tributes: a death (plane by plane) identical to the of Harry Dean Stanton in Alien, an ambush similar to the one suffered by the colonial marines in Aliens: the return (tank included) or a sort of Ripley trying to get safely to their particular Newta flat first also identical to the one of Ripley and the Alien of Fincher, the aquatic Alien by Jeunet, the discovery of a corpse scraped with a movement of also identical to the predator camera or another camera movement also identical to the opening credits of Predator 2, which gets the jungle to the citynot to mention the room trophies displayed at the end of that same second installment, are just a few examples of an infinite list.On the other hand, one must recognize that the special effects are very worked, while accused a too dark, and the prealien laugh quite less than the mutation also report that Jeunet released the manga in Alien Resurrection, in the film with more deaths per minute of the saga.Terríblemente fun for fans and quite superior to its predecessor. That Yes, or soñéis to find something similar to the original movies.</body>
</review>
