<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Technically perfect, but totally devoid of soul.</summary>
	<body>Atonement is the new film by Joe Wright, director of pride and prejudice, and his second collaboration with Keira Knightley. In addition to British actress, the film features cast James McAvoy, Saoirse Ronan, Romola Garai, Vanessa Redgrave, Brenda Blethyn, Juno Temple, Patrick Kennedy and Benedict Cumberbatch.Basada in Ian McEwan's novel, the film begins in England a day of 1935, the hottest of the year. Despite the growing threat of World War II, Briony Tallis and her family live as authentic privileged in his enormous Victorian Gothic mansion. The entire family gathers for the weekend, but the oppressive heat and the emerging repressed emotions create a underground sense of danger. Briony, a writer in the making, is a girl with lots of imagination. A series of catastrophic misunderstandings makes that you accused Robbie Turner, the son of the housekeeper and lover of her sister Cecilia, of a crime he did not commit. The accusation destroys the nascent love between Robbie and Cecilia, in addition to dramatically change the course of their lives.Divided into three segments of irregular length, Atonement has received great praise from international critics, fact that has granted nothing more and nothing less than seven Golden Globe nominations. Unfortunately, at least to me seem, I must say that the new collaboration between director Joe Wright and actress Keira Knightley is not precisely to throw rockets.As I said, the film is divided into three clearly differentiated parts, the first of which is undoubtedly the most precocious and extensive, with an atmosphere truly worthy of mention and a very well-conducted dilated plateamiento, as well as being the only time in which the love affair between the two protagonists, trigger for the coming events, has something of true passion through their veins.After that, Keira Knightley disappears during almost all the rest of the footage, focusing the plot on the wander of James McAvoy Europe besieged by the Third Reich: is in this second part, despite its great setting of a London destroyed by the Blitzkrieg, where the film makes water, diluted in a nonsense which aims to delve into the tyrannical fate suffered by the (the) protagonist (s) due to a child's tantrum. Already in the final leg, the third excerpt puts us at present, where a now elderly Briony Tallis confesses his sins of youth and argues why in his novel, in a somewhat watered-down twist but that manages to wake up the spectator of the tedium of the central section of the film.So, Atonement, which the distributor of turn has added to the bombastic tagline from beyond the passion, it is a great film adaptation, with an atmosphere, clothing and photography worthy of mention, as well as the excellent soundtrack to Dario Marianelli, but whose story is completely alleged passion that should erect as a leitmotif of the film.</body>
</review>
