<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Viaje a Darjeeling" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do you know what 'I went on trip to the India and it changed my life'? Then that. Nevertheless, eresulta entertenida, with Jason Schwartzman in State of grace.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Wes Anderson's controversial and starring Owen Wilson, Adrien Brody, Jason Schwartzman, Anjelica Huston, Bill Murray, Amara Karan, Camilla Rutherford, Irfan Khan and Natalie Portman, Darjeeling Limited is one of the first releases on our billboards of this Australasia it, Francis, Peter and Jack are three brothers who are have been distancing with the passage of time and longer even speak. The death of his father brings together them again and this reunion arises the need to strengthen their family ties. It is then when Francis, the eldest of the brothers proposes a journey by train by the India as a spiritual pilgrimage. The tour will do so in the Darjeeling Limited, the railway line that runs through the country from one end to the other. Already on the train, they begin fighting, until physical and verbal disputes and his behavior comes to such an extent that they are forced to get off the train. From here on, left to its own resources, begins a new journey which was not in his plans.Like all movies of this Texas filmmaker, Darjeeling Limited not leave anyone indifferent, not because it is a controversial film, nor much less, but because of the style of its director; films such as the Tenenbaums and The life aquatic have received ovations and despellejamientos alike, and no doubt same thing will happen with this trip to Darjeeling.Enfocada as a spiritual journey in which three brothers in high class return to (re) join through a journey along the India, Darjeeling Limited is starring three actors as private such as Owen WilsonAdrien Brody and Jason Schwartzman, in some peculiar curiously hierarchical roles serving as breeding ground for all kinds of accusations, grudges and unspeakable fears.But go by parts: the film begins with the short film by way of preface entitled Hotel Cheválier, played by Jason Schwartzman and Natalie Portman, and that helps us clear scale to be able to guess the Darjeeling Limited paths. In this way, the bucolic Paris grey gives way to the vivid colours of the India served through curious levels of the Chamber of Wes Anderson, who shows us a sort of totally nonsensical initiatory journey and supposedly irreverent, although in general terms, and apart from certain conatuses of brilliance, we please something decaffeinated and inconsequential in various bars.Despite this, Darjeeling Limited is not a bad film or much less, and contains certain passages that you simply life thanks to a perennial melancholy patina, before returning to a film which, unfortunately, is diluting hopeless slowly despite the more than decent interpretations of the trio protagonist, among which stands out above all, and by far a Jason Schwartzman who never ceases to amaze me, while Owen Wilson is who leads the main weight of the movie with pretty solvency.It is true that Darjeeling Limited seems to one server as the personal experience of an accidental tourist who discovers his own happiness in unhappiness from the rest, a true existential journey for a few days. Wes Anderson's film sins perhaps bombastic and some emotional walk at home, despite all its efforts to shun those labels, so its ninety minutes seem quite longer than they actually are.</body>
</review>
