<review author="José Córdoba" title="Monster house" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not only the technical level is exemplary, script the film works, you are their characters, their feelings, in addition the director knows give rhythm to the action and even get some other startle in the armchair.</summary>
	<body>Monster House represents a return, rather, a regression to children, these 1980s meaning for many our innocence. Then the film premiered products aimed at children, but that they could be seen and enjoyed by adults. Amblin, hosted by Steven Spielberg stood out among all the producers that emerged at that time. It emerged classic child film like the Goonies, E.T., the secret of the pyramid, the back to the future trilogy and who framed Roger Rabbitt, among others. I grew up with these films and I keep fond memories of all of them, have also stood the test of time in an excellent way. Why the premiere of Monster House is a joy, as it recovers the spirit of that film. Set in the early 1980s (although without saying so in no time) tells the terror that has a child into the front of his house. A house inhabited by a hateful man named Nebencracker and he seems to have their own life.The film, produced by Spielberg and Zemeckis, portrays as usual in these productions about events taking place in the suburbs of a city, a neighborhood of homes where children can head-on at your leisure. In addition it introduces us to two children that do not stand out for being the most popular of the College and with emotional problems (the father refuses to tell you I love to his son, while the mother is requested with insistence when they go on vacation; or the parents always absent from the other child nicknamed Croquette), a common factor in the film and Steven Spielberg productions. These two children joined the know-it-all girl and insect repellent, it ends up being the only one who believes in its history and also marks the sexual awakening of children are already close to enter in full puberty. We also have the nanny "zamanfou" with a boyfriend sobón "fumeta", who, of course, nor believes in warnings of children on the House and a couple of policemen that disrupting the attempts of the protagonists in discovering the secret of the House. And then there is the House. A House with life, terrifying, with clear references in Poltergeist or night of fear. At the level of history, characters, the film is, as I have said, nothing a contracorriente, returning us the characteristics of the missed children films of the 1980s.The film could frame as in animation film, although it has a radical difference to the productions of Pixar or Dreamworks: have been carried out with the technique "Motion Capture". This technique allows to record the actors doing the movements of their animated characters, so that movements, bodily expressions, dialogues are directly taken from the work of the actors who play the characters. This technique was first used in the movie Polar Express, though fortunately it has evolved a lot since then. In this the faces of the characters, the eyes convey emotions and despite its cartoonish design can reach parececernos real beings, something that never happened with the movie starring Tom Hanks. Another radical difference in this technique is that it allows to managers with little or no experience in the field of animation, filming a movie in this style and it shows. Digital technology makes the camera not a difficult move cumbersome but simply a point of view, that can move anywhere without hindrance and in this film applied it. A camera always on the move gives personality to the film. Clearly influenced by Spielberg and Zemeckis, the rookie Gil Kenan, presents a few levels in which the camera moves, turns, has freedom of movement around actions and characters, obtaining extraordinary moments such as the scene in which the House back to life. In this way, get away the film of traditional animation which tends to mimic the difficulty of movement of a camera in a real shoot, with multitude of fixed planes or crane, without benefit to the fact of being in a non-physical environment. But not only the technical level is exemplary, script the film works, you are their characters, their feelings, in addition the director knows give rhythm to the action and even get some other startle in the armchair. In addition, perhaps to close the cycle, the legend that surrounds the House just proving very burtoniana and beautifully sad. In the field of music the film is also very achieved with a score escritar Douglas Pipes, a composer for me unknown, that performs an amusingly approach to the music of terror of the B.En series summary, a film very advisable, nothing pretentious or ambitious, far removed from the technical virtuosity of Cars, although, on the whole, quite better resolved. A wonderful surprise which stands for on top of all the animated films I've seen this year, and that, in addition, get have eager to see the new project by Zemeckis filmed with the same system and inspired by the legend of Beowulf.</body>
</review>
