<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="El último tren a Auschwitz" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is complex enough that a film about the Holocaust not spank in one way or another our chord. as well, 'The last train to Auschwitz' fails.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Joseph Vilsmaier and Dana Vávorvá and starring Gedeon Brukhard, Lale Yavaş, Lena Beyerling, Juraj Kukura, Sibel Kekilli, Roman Roth, Brigitte Grothum and Hans Jürgen Ludwig Blochberger among others, the last train to Auschwitz (Der letze Zug) was triumphant in the past Film Festival, Bavaria.La film puts us in the middle of World War II, in 1943. The nazis want to clean of Jews Berlin definitely. More than 70,000 have already been deported from the city. In April 1943 the Grunewald station leaves a train with 688 Jews to Auschwitz. The trip takes six days. The train begins a fight against the heat, hunger and thirst. In desperation, some attempt to flee; among them, Henry Lea and Ruth. But time is short and Auschwitz hovering ever closer.From time immemorial (cinematically speaking) the Holocaust has been one of the cornerstones to stir consciences in the world of the celluloid, being focused from a multitude of perspectives and offering large jewels as Schindler's list or the great dictator, to cite two examples sufficiently distanced both chronological and conceptually. In fact, historical revisionism, generally speaking, has given rise to much of the blockbusters of the Majors in the golden age of Hollywood.Por against, the ab (use) a theme you may well exercise the opposite to the desired effect, and an excess of productions focusing on a same fact may well dishearten the Viewer, something that, in a completely different context, is ocuriendo in these same moments with fantastic adaptations of superheroes or video games. In fact, in recent years there have been many films about the Holocaust, from the aforementioned Schindler's list, passing by the pianist, life is beautiful, or much more humble productions as the ninth day, Amen, the sinking or the grey zone.Unfortunately, the last train to Auschwitz is not, nowhere near, at the height of none of the above, resulando a somewhat bland product not by its own staging - more than two hours inside a train-, but by the little substance of his performances. As well, and despite the extreme agony and panic suffered by Jews crowded on the last train to Auschwitz, and despite also the repetitive flashbacks intended to, on the one hand, to liven up the story and, on the other hand, further humanizing its protagonists, his story fails to apprehend us despite the predisposition of the own Viewer: nor Henry, or read, Ruth, Albert or Gabrielle have own face, none of them comes to move us despite its terible historical context.Thus, the last train to Auschwitz is composed of two hours something tedious, repetitive and lacking nerve, except for specific moments in which inevitably the viewer must feel the aflición of its protagonists; but the truth is that the film is not cruelty, tension or Poetics.</body>
</review>
