<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Interview" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The idea, despite being a remake, never ceases to be equally bold and the effort that both actors play is truly commendable, giving the viewer truly brilliant moments and categorical dialogues.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Steve Buscemi and starring Sienna Miller and own actor, Interview is the first installment of the review of a series of three films carried out by the late Dutch filmmaker Theo Van Gogh.En she Pierre Peders, a reporter of war with international reputation but now low hours, is it has hardened seeing greater unimaginable horrors committed by men. One day your editor forced to interview Katya, the most famous American soap operas star in the world. Offended, humiliated, lowered, Pierre gets in contact with Katya to do the job, convinced that it will be an absurd interview more unimportant, but it is confused at all, since his encounter with the woman bring you more than one surprise. Pierre discovers that under glamour, whim and luxury that it surrounds, there is a woman intelligent, sharp wit, and like him, with hundreds of scars and recesses. Between the two they begin spinning a relationship full of traps, sharp criticism, sexual tension and lucid reflections above all and above all.Conceived and embodied as an interpretative duel led under theatrical guidance, Interview is a funny and entertaining exercise in appearances in which dialogue between its two protagonists puts with difference the way: with the loft of the actress, and (almost) exclusive scenario with the only help of three digital cameras the film directed by Steve Buscemi is served solely on the acuity of their sentences to keep the viewer's attention during their just 86 minutes of duration.The idea, despite being a remake, never ceases to be equally bold, especially if we take into account that the CGI claim seems increasingly more impresincindible to be someone at the box office, and the effort that both actors play is truly commendable, giving the viewer truly brilliant moments and categorical dialogues.Unfortunately, sometimes Interview is guilty of being too innocent: certain sequences will seem a too artificial and forced and some of their twists - included the final outcome - are somewhat predictable. Despite this, the film directed and starring Steve Buscemi gives us a pleasant viewing, always entertaining and interesting, a way of doing diametralemnte opposed to which you often find us in Billboard, and this only fact worth our respect.As you would expect, Steve Buscemi interpretativamente eats a dutiful Sienna Miller, but whose career seems to approach it both to his role in Interview, ending its likelihood resulting rather odious. Personally, I would highlight the opening sequence in the restaurant, where the guidelines to be followed by the film and where both actors are superb translating their respective characters are marked.</body>
</review>
