<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="This is England" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A first half of truly attractive footage, a sort of manners portrait of workers England in the 1980s.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Shane Meadows and starring Thomas Turgoose, Stephen Graham, Jo Hartley, Andrew Shim, Vicky McClure and Joseph Gilgun, This is England has been one of the most acclaimed British critically films, as well as obtain the award for the best film in the last edition of the British Independent Film Awards.La film puts us in the Thatcherite England 1983, and schools are on holiday. Shaun, from 12 years of age, is a lonely child that grows in a very grey coastal village, whose father has died in combat in the Falklands war. During these holidays, find new male models when adopt you the local skinhead. With his new friends, Shaun discovers a world of festivals, meets his first love and discovers the charms of boots Dr Martens. It is then when she meets Combo, one racist skin quite older than him, that just came out of prison. While Combo band harassed local ethnic minorities, everything seems prepared for the start-up of a maturation process that will lead to Shaun's innocence to experience.Putting us in particular, we could say that This is England is a mixture of the aesthetics of Trainspotting (despite being located a decade later) and the fabric of American History X. In fact, the fourth film of Shane Meadows has quite a few (and inevitable) points in common with this small wonder Tony Kaye directed in 1998, both in the own correlation of events many symbolism.Odious comparisons aside, This is England is really a great movie, although neither the wonder that some British critics have wanted to see: history does nothing new in itself, while the atmosphere is very successful with these industrial areas as a backdrop background, reggae music, the Falklands war and the iron lady in TVs. But let us be realistic, any degeneration of the patriotic glorification for racism contains the same elements as he is call national socialism, fascism, Nazism, Francoism or nacionalcatolicismo, so This speech is England loses some of its charm to the already ubiquitous. Instead, what it offers us the Shane Meadows film is the counterpoint to the original skinhead, embodied in the characters of Woody and Milky. so therefore, This is England is very well carried and, above all, it is very pleasant, with a first half of footage really appealing and interesting, a sort of manners portrait of England working in 1980s to, unfortunately, lost (something of) force with the arrival of Combo, not because her character lacks interest, but by the mere fact that does not add anything new.Anyway, it's a fairly round film.</body>
</review>
