<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Olvídate de mí" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Finally, a beautiful film with a staff of excellent actors Kirsten Dunst, Mark Ruffalo, Elijah Wood, Tom wilkinson... and with a soundtrack of dreamy...</summary>
	<body>The producer FOCUS has presented some time this part some of the best films I've had occasion to see, theirs are titles as "Lost in translation" "21 grams" and now this "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind" directed by Michael Gondry known for my as the director of one or another music video including Bjork and also by his opera prima "Human Nature" a comedy quite fun. If to this we add you the talents of Charlie Kaufman screenwriter and director of many of the best films I've seen in a long time we have a guaranteed success.And to loop the loop my favorite actor, Jim Carrey, is true that Carrey will not leave anyone indifferent, or hate you or you love, has no medium term, can not be 50% with him, and there are two "Jim Carrey's" comic actor of films as "The mask" "Two very stupid fools" and the more recent "like God" or quasi-dramatic actor of tapes as "Man on" "the moon" "The Truman show" "The Majestic" and this that brings us.For me one of the best movies of 2004, tape, undoubtedly is a masterpiece, with an opening of impressive credits, after 10 min. Movie Flipalo! With a theme of Beck "Everybody's Gotta Learn Sometimes" course appears on the soundtrack, and the touch that Carrey gives its interpretation is a sad man, abandoned, broken, torn apart. All have suffered to a greater or lesser extent a sentimental break and we can put on the skin of Joel (Jim Carrey) when he sees that you can not forget Clementine (an excellent Kate Winslet) and even though in principle struggle to remove the mind realizes that the love he feels for her is much stronger than any rancor. Truth is of those movies that you finish see and you have left the heart in a fist, with tears in his eyes, also actors speak in a tone of voice low, almost whispering and everything you say you burn fire in the mind, if I had to stay with some of the phrases I heard I would be with this: "How innocent virgins are happy!"The world forgetting by the forgotten world: eternal shine of a perfect mind."Each prayer accepted and each with resignation". Tremenda! Had I been goose bumps to hear her.Finally, a beautiful film with a staff of excellent actors Kirsten Dunst, Mark Ruffalo, Elijah Wood, Tom wilkinson. and with a soundtrack of your dreams. In addition to what I have already said.</body>
</review>
