<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="XXY" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film deals with a subject unknown to most of the public. Therein lies their courage. But it goes no further. Not deepens, it stays on the surface of relations.</summary>
	<body>The identity has become the main theme of the Argentine cinema. And it is that identity has a very important socio-historical weight. Get in the skin of hundreds, thousands, of children stolen during the dictatorship military adopting them as a prize for his patriotism. These children of the disappeared in recent years, with the essential work of the Grandmothers of Mayo, have been rediscovered with its past, with their identity &hellip; synonymous with freedom. Quite an achievement for an Argentine society which, in this case, has become model to follow. So films ranging from the later official history the Kamchatka stop there, as well as countless documentaries as representative as the BLONDES.The identity is definitely installed in contemporary Argentine cinema. And it makes covering a wide range of stories. Note: EL ABRAZO PARTIDO (where is my father), born and raised (lost, without identity), LUNA DE AVELLANEDA (I was born in this neighborhood), EL OTRO (the search of identity), the dead (recover my identity) &hellip; the list is endless. A last case speaks of sexual identity: XXY.The hermaphrodite, which has the two sexes. The first film of the hitherto writer Lucía Puenzo, tells the story of Alex, a teenager of 15 years who was born with what doctors call genital ambiguity. The parents of Alex escape from Buenos Aires, and his daughter becomes a phenomenon in the people. Now, adolescence, Alex must decide which sex to have, who.The film deals with a subject unknown to most of the public. Therein lies their courage. But it goes no further. Not deepens, it stays on the surface of the relationship between Alex and Álvaro, son of a friend of the parents of Alex. The epicentre not power, but blurs the internal conflict of Alex (played by the young Inés Efron), his relationship with his father (played by Ricardo Darín), with the comunidad.todo is small, ridiculous, as if it were a movie. In line with the development of history, the end fades, betting on the interest of the public, with a moralizing tone than attentive to the intelligence of the Viewer.The identity once again in Argentine cinema. The film travels to the Oscars and the Goya. Now question is (it is an open discussion) by the identity of the latest (new) Argentine cinema. XXY responds to the formula of the presentable film to any festival and award. Today that is the sole purpose of the film is done in Argentina. An identity problem.</body>
</review>
