<review author="Sandavito" title="30 días de oscuridad" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A vampire movie coming out somewhat from the norm, with characters and items closest to the films of George a. Romero, and with abundant blood and scares for all lovers of the horror genre.</summary>
	<body>The next February to reach our screens the umpteenth adaptation of comic that Hollywood has done lately, "30 days of night", whose provisional title in Spain is "30 days of night". With this so suggestive title appeared not so long ago a comic book in three installments (with its subsequent sequels) presenting us with an unusual history of vampires. More in the style of the genre of zombies, the history of "30 days of night" introduces us to the town of Barrow, Alaska, with one month a year of constant Sun and another month to the year of total darkness. Is taking advantage of this month of darkness that a group of vampires arrive on the scene to give a real feast.David Slade is correct, with a couple of fairly suggestive planes (I love an aerial overview of the city, all snowed in full attack of vampires), but in general feels an abuse of the slow, to the current fashion, in the action sequences, which becomes tiresome. Photography Jo Willems clearly distinguishes us two spaces, interiors and exteriors, with the differentiation of the shades of bluish and cold for snow, and more yellowish, but not so hot for interiors, somewhat in the style that already followed in Hard Candy in 2005. The script, as I say, is more typical of the genre of zombies, and perhaps in this aspect is its originality: a small village is infested with vampires, and the few survivors must resist a month until the Sun again to leave or die in the attempt. It should be noted that they there are, as it is logical and is normally the case in adaptations from comic book to film, differences of characters, relationships, the sub-plots and others, to make them, in the eyes of producers, more attractive to the Viewer (the happy marriage protagonist, for example, happens to be in procedures for separation in the film). However, the greater fault on script is which is usual in all films, calling them, "monsters", in the history of hollywood. The monsters become flat beings, with nothing more than hunger as motivation, without intelligence (as it has happened almost always to Frankenstein's monster). Thus, calcuradores and eloquent in the comic book, vampires have become a Pleiad of pale men suits to the Armani Exchange barely thirty sentences on the tape and the rest of the time is spend it screaming and growling while they teach teeth. Had been "invented" a guttural language for them, as it already did in previous films of vampires (see Blade, for example), to communicate, to make it more extravagant, and fill as well the gap that the sandwiches and the typography of the comic filled perfectly.On the sound side, the incidental music of Brian Reitzell is pretty well done. Reitzell has experience as a musical supervisor for, for example, Sofia Coppola, but this is his first time as a composer of the music for a film. It is not loud or pretentious, as it seems that it is the it style lately in too many productions, and fits perfectly with the dramatic use of sound effects, quite successful, by the way, over all the footage.Interpretive weight rests with the couple Josh Hartnett and Melissa George, with a constant game of attraction contained (remember that they are separating) arriving to be credible at times, and at other times, especially at the beginning of the film, is of zero credibility.In summary, a vampire film coming out a bit of the usual norm, with characters and items closest to the films of George a. Romero, and with abundant blood and scares for all lovers of the horror genre.</body>
</review>
