<review author="Matías Cobo" title="American Gangster" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film of high quality, denoting the wise firm behind she and Scott reconciles with your most demanding audience</summary>
	<body>The career of Ridley Scott wandering in recent years irregular terrain that seemed to predict the decline of his master. Except Gladiator, abultadamente award-winning in the 2001 Oscars but enmarcable in the tradition of the best epic film, tapes as A good year, the impostors or the Kingdom of heaven left barely glimpse the shadow of the filmmaker who coined myths of the eighties as Alien or Blade Ranner film. And for his resurgence has been employed in his latest work subgenera, such as mobsters or the police thriller, as addressed by other great conductors with magnificent results. Without going any further, Martin Scorsese ended its debt with the Oscar thanks to a film located between two themes with its excellent but master The Departed.American Gangster assumes no with respect the long tradition of tapes set in the mafia and baby also in typical universes of James Ellroy as the político-policial corruption. The protagonist of his last great film is also for Scott professional reunion with Russel Crowe. And his first collaboration with Denzel Washington, actor which continues to demonstrate its capabilities to interpret almost any role.The script of the film, that part of a true story, is structured as a parallel narrative of the lives of the two protagonists, the mobster Frank Lucas and Richie Roberts police. The lives of both run along similar paths but in opposite directions. While Richie must suffer in the beginning of his career the contempt of his teammates by not acclimate to the environment of entrenched police corruption, Lucas will build on the knowledge gained from his boss, an important leader of the mafia, to collect their witness to his death and prosper to become the biggest dealer of New York of the 70.Otro key to the rapid ascent of Lucas in the heroin trafficking business was the war. In Viet Nam, many soldiers became junkies that imported his addiction to his country. The heroin was the drug of fashion, which everyone wanted and should try to be cool. Lucas, aware of this growing demand, went straight to the coveted opiate-producing source. Put in the streets a heroin of high quality at a reasonable price with excellent conditions of import obtained by rinsing with senior political and military officials who facilitated her transport to EE.UU. directly from the own Vietnam.Muy different and probably more difficult was the road until the success of Richie. His incorruptable status earned him few friends and bad reputation in a police force corrupt to the core, but on the other hand, it enabled him lead a special anti-drug unit that would remove the large tentacles of a business in full swing.Needless to say, with Crowe and Washington in the starring roles, the artistic section is covered with excess solvency, even joins them the great work of the side that surround them. On the other hand, most New York City atmosphere, in the words of Ridley Scott, les was not easy given the distant which is now the current city, clean and orderly aesthetics up in neighborhoods taken by suburbs years ago, of the look worn and dirty that the film manages to recreate splendidly.Factors such as these, as well as the agile and entertaining narrative, make American Gangster a film of high quality, denoting the wise firm behind she and Scott reconciles with his more demanding public.</body>
</review>
