<review author="José Córdoba" title="La noche de los girasoles" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The script is very weak and falls into the trap of its structure that wants to be enigmatic and surprising and becomes obvious and boring.</summary>
	<body>Me too lazy Spanish cinema. I lose faith in him because of both as soon as a film that worth seeing and is a big surprise, but in general I don't like, so I have chosen Spanish films to see in movies with dropper. I was curious to see this film, I had read good things about it and I thought, well let's give him a chance. Unfortunately I made a bad choice.The night of the sunflowers is a rural thriller, perhaps that would be the more correct definition, although the word thriller is very large. The film, narrated in a non-linear manner, presents a same story told from the points of view of the various characters involved in it. A priori, an approach if well not original, at least different, but that ends up being the most serious problem of the film. Tape tells the visit to a people of a group of speleologists (led by Carmelo Gómez) to investigate a newly discovered cave and try to find in her paintings which can be achieved that the economy of the town increased considerably. At its exit of the cave occurs an event to mark their lives. The film begins well, although with a horrible picture, the narrative has some tension until that happens the traumatic fact, towards the half of the footage, and from there the movie dies, dying, slowly. The characters that players had been hitherto disappear to make way for two others, both civil guard, who end up being the protagonists of the story in the last stretch. A clear error, because it is really more important that does not have the history of the first protagonists. In addition to having all the tension and practically solve the story half of the footage, the rest does not matter, rather bored and makes you look at the clock.In its look at the rural Spain, to the disappearance of villages, the movie succeeds and is stimulating, but as a thriller fails. The script is very weak and falls into the trap of its structure that wants to be enigmatic and surprising and becomes obvious and boring. Actors, with the exception of Carmelo Gómez and Celso Bugallo, not give much Yes, really, aren't credible, even though they aren't the worst of the film. The address shows an alarming lack of pace, very conspicuous in its final stretch. The picture is frightening, full of noise, without contrast. The music repetitive and without force as director only uses it when nobody is talking about, not know what to do with it.In short, a mistake. Although rather a disappointment because the film in its initial section pointing to something better than just being at the end. A new failure of Spanish cinema, to see whether Alatriste improves the picture.</body>
</review>
