<review author="Moebius" title="Excalibur" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The story of Arthur is immortal, and this movie is a good example. J.R.R. Tolkien was, and after all, a simple apprentice. And "Excalibur" is without doubt the best film John Boorman addressed to it.</summary>
	<body>"Excalibur" is without a doubt the best movie has directed John Boorman (other worthy to see the director's films include Deliverance and El General, latter an entertaining biopic about a famous Irish thief.) (The emerald jungle not I keep a great memory, but I saw many, many years ago). Her particular vision of the Arthurian myth (the film is based on a review of "The death of Arthur", an epic of the 15th century) is excellent. Boorman decided to leave aside any historical point (notably the absence of any Christian reference) to focus on mythical history, but tell the evil, the cycle of life, the man as a being halfway between hope and despair.The cast of the film is excellent, which include a sober Nigel Terry as Arturo, lHelen Mirren as Morgana, and the excellent stage actor (and one of the notable assassins in series Colombo) Nicol Willliamson as Merlin, certainly the central character of the film, rather than the own Arturo. The story progresses with and through the old and twisted Wizard.It's funny, but apparently the United Artists told Boorman who could choose any actor for the role of Merlin, except to Williamson. I do not know until that point is true this story, but apparently finally Boorman came out with yours. God thank you.Perhaps at a first glance it may go unnoticed, but is Merlín who machine the events that are happening behind the curtain. As the good son of the devil that is, Merlín handles men at will to achieve its purpose. The story is simple: Uther Pendragon, with the help of Merlin, manages a difficult peace after years of war. In the celebration of celebration at the castle of his erstwhile enemy, the Duke of Cornwall, Uther Pendragon infatuated women's Duke, Igrayne. As usual, the Duke is not very happy with this idea, and the truce is broken. While the Duke died attacking the camp of Uther, it lies with Igrayne thanks to Merlín, who has granted the appearance of the Duke. Nine months later, Uther and Igrayne have a child that night fruit. But the treatment was that a descendant would be put in charge of Merlin. This leads to the child, and Uther, repentant, runs after him. However, he falls into an ambush. Badly wounded, he sinks his magic sword, Excalibur, in a stone. No one except he could have her.The beginning of the movie gives us an idea of how Merlín uses low human passions and weaknesses to capitalize and bring forward their plans. Although in principle his intentions are good, note that they are not human owners of their own destiny. Is lawful control over lower beings, even if it is for their own good? Should man give up their free will in pursuit of a world better? Merlin this belief, although welfare seeking is actually your own.The story that continues is well known: the son of Uther, Arthur, manages to get the sword of the stone and becomes King. After several years of wars against opponents it manages to unify England under his command with the help of the famous Knights of the round table, and a period of well-being and peace extends over the years. While Morgana begins to conspire, comes the crisis: Arturo discovers the infidelity of his wife Geneva with his best Knight, Lanzarote (this scene was shot by Boorman with an image of great strength, where lovers wake up and see the sword of the King stuck between them). The Earth has been riven by the sword; Meanwhile, Merlín loses its force and he is cheated by Morgana: the order has been lost permanently. Shortly afterwards, Morgana seduces Arthur and becomes pregnant from it.They come years of crisis, famine, uncertainty. A weak Arturo languishes in his Castle, while Morgana and her son Mordred conspire to take over the lands and the throne of Arthur. The last hope is the Holy Grail, the sacred Cup that will return the forces and faith to the King and the Earth will rise again.Ultimately, the Grail will be found, Mordred and Morgana defeated, and a new world will emerge from the ashes of Camelot. Arthur succumb from their wounds and will be held at his funeral boat adrift. The magic sword, Excalibur, will return at the hands of the Lady of the Lake. When they occurring dark times, and all seems lost, Arturo again wielding Excalibur, and will save Inglaterra.El Arthurian myth has many interpretations. In its Genesis is a story about hope, about a happy future, a confidence in a Savior in moments of weakness. With the death of Arturo finish time of Merlin and other mages. The Freemen are left adrift, but free to shape their future.That freedom had its price: on many occasions those men of the British Isles would be dark times: the Roman withdrawal and the barbarian invasions (which fits the historical Arthur), civil wars, Viking raids, the Norman invasion, the world wars. But in any evil is not despair: men suffer, fear, but finally confident in its future, because they know that Arthur will be: is this Arthur a man? Obviously not. A man perhaps convey your message, but the Arturo salvador perhaps the strength of the character, knowing that fighting and not down the arms will be the salvation.Returning to the film "Excalibur" is a film of great visual power, with a large photograph, an excellent script, and one of its most outstanding aspects, an excellent use of the music. The soundtrack lacks original compositions; great masters of classical music such as Richard Wagner and Carl Off sign the melodies of the film. It is probably the film (along with 2001: the Space Odyssey) which makes better use of already existing scores, to such an extent that seem to compound that someday appear in the film.The story of Arthur is immortal, and this movie is a good example. J.R.R. Tolkien was, and after all, a simple apprentice. Very applied and with great talent, but apprentice to the end and Cape.</body>
</review>
