<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="The Lookout" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>UA great film making by own merits in one of the best films of the year, a sample of film noir with dramatic overtones and internal improvement, with a lot of work in all the elements that make it up.</summary>
	<body>There are occasions in which a modest film becomes by own merits one of the surprises of the year, and that is precisely what is the vision of this little film on media but big in terms of results. Undoubtedly one of the best American films of the year.Chris Pratt is a former student outdone the rest, its popularity as a hockey star, his wonderful girlfriend and friends show him as the prototype of young winner, but all this is truncated the same night which has a car accident and causes serious consequences, in addition to the death of two of his friends. These consequences affect its central lobe, which causes distortion in the senses, confusion, sudden aggressiveness and loss of short-term memory. He lives with a roommate of middle aged and blind, which does not prevent that despite his blindness he see much further than the majority of the people. The mysterious appearance of a former student of their school and their dark intentions in securing the collaboration of Chris in the robbery at the bank where he works, will lead to a series of unexpected turns in his life. Scott Frank made his debut in the direction of feature films with this film before us, after having devoted his career to the development of screenplays serving directors of renown as Steven Soderbergh in "A very dangerous romance", or Steven Spielberg in "Minory Report". And could not have better debut showing by this excellent drama hidden in a history of traditional film noir. Classicism in its domain in the narrative, both in the most dynamic scenes such as those that require verbal confrontation between the protagonists and the Mise en scène is commendable and worthy of compliment. Everything shown without Visual fanfare but if classy a lot when it comes to telling the story.Special mention deserve the excellent players, all of them in a State of constant grace, notably Joseph Gordon Lewitt as the protagonist of the story, an actor who already demonstrated in another excellent example of recent black film as it is the essential "Brick" that we are faced with some of the finest actors of his generation. Its ability to show sadness, melancholy, their anger contained by a fact that marked him of life, makes its interpretation a masterful display of acting ability. Not far behind Jeff Daniels in the role of Lewis, his friend and confidant, that borda also his role as blind man with good heart, smart and marked by the tragedy. With respect to the rest of the campus actoral, its mission, all of them comply with far from Matthew Goode portraying the villain of the story until the emerging Isla Fisher (attention to their small but effective nuances throughout history). To all this it helps an effective script that despite the lack of convoluted plot twists and some inconsistent decision in the characters, is very effective and melancholia, with a dramatic rather than correct progression, showing a history that begins as a brilliant drama in which doom seizes each and every one of the characters in the filmwith scenes brilliant and forceful as the encounter of Chris with the character played by Carla Gugino or the dramatic family dinner, displayed with a simplicity that does not prevent to be tremendously powerful and revealing. Even when all this brilliant drama gives rise to the scenes more blurred film, those pertaining to the preparation and development of the bank robbery, the film maintains a balance of surprising taking into account the error of much of the recent film.Brilliant history in its approach and in its outcome, this dress inevitable sad and hopeless, no less a story on how to accept our mistakes, those which we mark of by life and not let us move forward. Our decisions or errors can become a slab in our life, and this brilliant film witness.Looking for the negative points of the film, perhaps the very fact that halfway through the film history takes a radical turn and this causes a sense of rupture in the history, that is why suffer as I said anteriorme the film but without allowing him to reach a level of excellence.In short, a great film that turns on their own merits in one of the best films of the year, a sample of film noir with dramatic overtones and internal improvement, with a lot of work in all the elements that make it up and with an exceptional protagonist that outboard his role as it did in the previously mentioned, and excellent, "Brick". History with many layers of background that shows, once again despite plaintiff voices, that American cinema is not dead. Notable film.</body>
</review>
