<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Jindabyne" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A new display of privileged domain of the description of characters through a narrative slow in appearance, but stormy emotional decline.</summary>
	<body>After surprise friends and strangers with that excellent thriller of name "Lantana", filmed in the year 2001, five long years had to elapse until that Australian Ray Lawrence has had the opportunity to prove their worth in film-making, in this case recovering the dense and complex tone of his previous work to take it furtherIf it fits, in a new show of privileged domain of the description of characters through a narrative slow in appearance, but stormy emotional decline.The story of Stewart, Carl and Billy, Rocco, situated to these four friends in one of their routine meetings of fishing weekend, in which, by random chance, discovered the lifeless body of a young topless woman in the isolated rio of the desolate place that serves as their escape to their routine and sad lives, a place in which to escape from their daily chores. The decision agreed to leave the body there awaiting his return from weekend, unleashes an aerated reaction not only from relatives and friends, but the Australian Aboriginal community. No one understands the reasons which led to these four friends to ignore the fact and continue with its weekend of entertainment outside the moral dilemmas posed by its decision.In his work as director in the film before us, Lawrence shows possess a difficult virtue which few current directors have, give it to your staging calmly and outstanding close-ups with the reactions of the characters, a fantastic look, full of puns and hidden feelings under a tangle of contrasting emotions. Occasionally a mise en scene and a classic narrative pulse are not hotly contested with personality that can exercise a filmmaker in the final product, and the work in this great film by Lawrence, is worthy of recognition.The film takes place in slow, almost desperate way probably for the new film buffs eager for extreme sensations, as alien to all prevailing fashion in the times, but not so is sterile in reaching the most tanning spectator in this type of storytelling with your message. This extraordinary capacity possessing the film to convey the sense of apprehension always reminds that maxim of David Lynch (always so revered in showing the most hidden part of the human soul), in which every person has its history, its past in the form of constant threat that sleeps dormant to resurface someday, but in the form of real and tangible threat, emotional and destructive level if internally. During the footage, Lawrence shows us the daily evolution of a small Australian community through silences in epochal talks, looks lost in search of a release emotional and spiritual that it compensate internal bitterness that breathe each and every one of the characters in the film. This fantastic look manifests itself on-screen in the form of threat invisible, giving the sensation that something is going to rob us with extreme virulence, with an air of bitterness at all times. From the first to the last character of the film, giving the sense of hide things from his past, implying, that behind every door of each of our houses, a sad story is hidden.Mention apart for the great acting cast that knows to give all and each of the characters of his own personality, without be swallowed up by this transcendental tone of the film look of its director, while Gabriel Byrne and Laura Linney, a step above the already if large cast, with action sublime in its subtlety, a wonderful recreation of a marriage in crisiswith those emotional that sooner or later criticisms come to light at the least opportune moment.It is also clear that such successful work of actors, would be impossible without a solvent script, and in this case is not less true that the libretto by Beatrix Christian (based on a short history of Raymond Carver, title "So Much Water So Close to Home"), a gradual and surprising description of day to day of these failed characters, is careful to detailresulting in a story that begins brilliantly and just sad way and desesperanzadora (despite spiritual and metaphorical flat end), a gem we.By so wise direction, screenplay and acting level, obvious references to this great Australian film can pass unnoticed at first glance, but it is clear that this blend of intimist drama and Aboriginal mysticism, baby clearly the film one of the most prestigious filmmakers emerged from the Antipodes, the essential Peter Weir for his early work in his native Australia, "Picnic at Hanging Rock" and above all, "The last wave", with item Fund in both cases Aboriginal.If there is an element that prevents this film to achieve even higher levels of quality as film piece, it is precisely the change of registration in certain passages of the film, despite the fact that they aren't unsatisfactory, perhaps smaller some variation of pace narrative, in order to be more effective the alleged blows of effect, which here fade to create a tone uniform throughout the story. It is shown as pending the film for the soul of the characters, that isolated occasionally forgets what it means to the narrative pulse. A lesser evil in any case, does not prevent the enjoyment of such an interesting film.Ultimately, absolutely recommended film, mixes intimist and mild complaint social, disguised in the form of racial thriller that will be a real treat for those who still love the narrative and classic cinema, one that opts for tell small stories of paused and way more emotional in the characters that effect not effective blows of effect pending, or free script drafts. The film is likely to be misunderstood by a sector of the audience raised faster Assembly and current narrative, at the risk of being considered "slow", which nothing further from the truth, because the film stands out certainly above the average of recent films, regardless of their nationality. A fully recommended, multi work (although without reaching the level of impact of his earlier, and essential, "Lantana") fairly in various competitions. A small great film notable and essential.</body>
</review>
