<review author="José Córdoba" title="La Huella" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The footprint is a remake of stimulating, very different to the original work, and yet, complementary, with a bold direction, a few performances to remember and a surprising reinterpretation of the original text.</summary>
	<body>The current rush of remakes has no end, usually focus on action and/or science fiction films, but also make you disgusted for comedies or dramas. I can understand the remakes when game material isn't much less a classic film, as for example the case of Thomas Crown, whose new version the Thomas Crown secret is even higher than the original. Not quite understand what redo authentic classics or masterpieces such as psychosis or the window indiscreet. Such operations always have seemed to me insured suicides because comparisons are always odious. And however they continue because they certainly tend to be very profitable. All this comes in the wake of the release of the remake of the footprint, the 1972 film, posthumous work of Joseph l. Mankiewicz from the work of Anthony Schaffer (Amadeus) adapted by the author himself and starring Michael Caine and Laurence Olivier. The new version has a sheet of enviable: the address is borne by Kenneth Branagh and adaptation has been written by the prize Nobel Harold Pinter while performers are Jude Law and Michael Caine.La plot begins when a young actor is invited to the House of a prestigious writer of mystery novels. Once meet begins a long dialogue in which replicas and contrarréplicas occur which more acute.The best that can be said of the Branagh film is that it is a reinterpretation of the original material, both aesthetic of content. In the Mankiewicz film everything revolves around the idea of game, the appearances of the great pantomime in a lighter tone, with very successful comic details. However, this new version has a much more serious tone and dark present both in its staging in the characters. The game still present, but the reinterpretation that makes text Pinter, perhaps gives more importance to other factors like for example a homosexual rapprochement between the characters.The direction of Branagh is also opposed to proposed by Mankiewicz. The second got something really difficult, namely, that a work with only two characters would be fully film and hold tension and interest for nearly two hours and twenty minutes. Kenneth Branagh has always stood by know adapt the theatrical environment in an excellent way to film, so surprise your choice. The English director, in a very risky decision, plays to do theatre within cinema, i.e. to make a film film but with elements of the theatrical language. The scene, one character is undoubtedly a minimalist house, with the minimum of elements to focus attention on the characters. In addition it has a continuous game of flat "strangers" and even allows the characters to play with the lighting environment, so every scene has its own light, chosen in "live" by the protagonists. It is a difficult decision, which does not work in all the scenes, but in general it is surprising and refreshing as well as being a very creative way to combine both codes (of the theatre and cinema) from the point of view of the address. As director of actors, Branagh is excellent as always.In the commentary for the orphanage commented that Belén Rueda was the movie, in this case is the same Michael Caine. Jude Law is also fine, but what has been achieved Caine is really extraordinary. A character complex, full of nuances, with impressive a poise and serenity and whose you silencias and eyes say more than many dialogues. Also get closer to its character radically different to the one done by Olivier in the original, and yet at the height of that prodigious interpretation. Photography and art direction are appropriate and discrete, surprising the design of the House in which the action and that ends up being one character. On the other hand, Patrick Doyle achieved his best score in many years, away from excesses as Eragon, achieves an extraordinary result based solely on a topic that receives different variations as the film progresses. A lot of work at the height of the best of the author.In summary, the footprint is a remake of stimulating, very different to the original work, and yet, complementary, with a bold direction, a few performances to remember and a surprising reinterpretation of the original text, which takes about an hour of duration, unless the result will suffer so notorious. But above all the footprint is the finding that Michael Caine, when stop Phooey as Miss special agent, is one of the greatest geniuses of the interpretation which we have at present. Only he should see the film, fortunately the rest of the elements are also worthwhile.PS: Must see the footprint of Mankiewicz, a masterpiece of the truth.PD2: Don't miss the funny cameo by Pinter and Branagh in the film (a track, attentive to the television screen)</body>
</review>
