<review author="José Córdoba" title="El Orfanato" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The orphanage is a film of a level notable, capable of achieving the complicity with the audience and duration never weighs on the Viewer. Its main fault, no doubt, is their total and absolute lack of originality.</summary>
	<body>The orphanage is the Spanish most anticipated premiere of the year. An ambitious horror film and that is expected to become the boat of salvation of the patriotic cinema box office this year. Following the footsteps of the others, The Haunting or Suspense! It tells the story of a family who moves to live the old orphanage where he grew up the woman (Belén Rueda). Not long until that the son of the couple disappears from the House.J. a. Bayona, director who made his debut with this film, get a film of impeccable invoice with an elegant but with some not entirely justifiable excess narration. Avoiding unpleasant scenes and sound effect shots get a classical narrative film closest in spirit to the films horror classic that the current, too dependent on the viscera. It is therefore a film with a clear reference close in time: the others of Alejandro Amenábar. the screenplay, written by Sergi Sánchez, is very appropriate in the description of characters in the sequence of events, and the successful ellipsis. On the other hand, its main fault is the excessive proliferation of clichés. The plot altogether reminds the Poltergeist(con_escena_con_médium_calcada_deel_film_dirigido,_no_oficialmente,_por_Steven_Spielberg) but the atmosphere and storytelling we refer to the others or Suspense, which in turn drink the other back nut of Henry James's story. We even find details of films as diverse as The Haunting or final destination. Of course, the end refers to the film from the others and therefore of the sixth sense, although it is less cheater in the film of Bayonne (though on the other hand, the film does have its trappings that soiled somewhat the memory of the film when he thinks it).In the interpretation, the film is at a high altitude. Highlighting a formidable Belén Rueda. She is the movie, the other characters are necessary floats on its side. It is certainly his best performance with a wide range of emotions and a weight of impressive character. For a server, it is one of the best performances of the year.In its technical sections the film is also at a high level, from photography to the design of production through the locker room. All are adecuadísimos and tight. On the music of a composer also Rookie, little to say, very close to the images but little remarkable and clear references to previous works.In summary, the orphanage is a film of a level notable, capable of achieving the complicity with the audience and duration never weighs on the Viewer. Its main fault, no doubt, is their total and absolute lack of originality that frustrating taking into the account the level of the rest of the production.</body>
</review>
