<review author="José Córdoba" title="Caótica Ana" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a very personal film as failed, that wants to be magical but it is too explicit and obvious.If it did not have that end it would be one film more failed but interesting aspects, but the way in which just does damage it in an irreparable way.</summary>
	<body>After several years away from the cinema of fiction Julio Medem returns with a film that must have been very special for him.Caótica Ana tells how a young painter hippie discovers that he is the reincarnation of many other women who died tragically at age 22. Through hypnosis sessions will be getting more and more in the history and the life of its predecessors. will be she sentenced to the same end?Ana Medem 22 died in a traffic accident, and July, his brother erected him a tribute with this film, which reflects many aspects of the personality of his sister, in fact the tables appearing in it were painted by Ana Medem or are adaptations in this style. Therefore, the director of the Basque feels personally very involved in the film.The penalty is that the very commendable and understandable effort not just reach the Viewer. The film is narrated by way of home behind, ten to zero, showing various moments of the life of Ana (Manuela Vallés), from the moment in which a mysterious French woman decides to become his patron and bring it to Madrid, away from her father who lives in a cave in Ibiza. Because of the chosen structure, the narrative has holes, ten ellipsis which affect the fluidity of the whole, to make it go faster. Once arrived in Madrid the film begins to show their problems, offering a vision of the kind of hippie commune in which he lives surrounded by artists, superficial, stereotypical and politically correct. Furthermore as already happens in sex and Lucia (with which holds many similarities and that repeated images: floating naked in the water or contemplating the Moon next to the sea, together with the own character that reminds a little to the interpreted by Paz Vega), presents a love story that's as "poetic" is incredible, as it already happened therein the two characters Anna and Sayid look in the eyes, exchanged a couple of phrases, make love, and she is already in love with forever ever with a pure, clean, crystalline and indestructible love. The film continues with an atmosphere that wants to be magical and appealing but which never becomes it completely, despite trying hard, everything seems forced or already seen. There are scattered details that function as the idea of the boat of the father of his best friend, Linda (baby), called as she is who the Save die drowned, although the scene itself is very forced; the idea of the cave with the doors that lead to their past lives, not very original, but effective visually.Even with its problems, the film is welcomed and is not heavy actually, but Medem loses the roles in the last five minutes of film that completely destroy what has been achieved so far. I do not usually have the end, but this time I am going to do, so if you don't want to know what skip the paragraph. After reaching the last of their lives by hypnosis, Ana has taken a radical change, has found its sense in life, even inadvertently as she says and decides to make an act of poetic revenge cagando literally in the face of a high office of the George Bush administration for the war of Iraq. If we were against a clearly political and demanding film because it would make sense, but in this film this theme is dealt with very briefly, is named the Saharan conflict, war of Iraq or the sad state of the Indians in the American reservations, they are named, they appear, but always in a superficial manner and the protagonist appears never really interested. Therefore, the end as it is raised is very unsuccessful and destroys the film by incoherent. One could speak of the shift in Ana which leads her to that, but is not seen on screen, so it seems to me a very comfortable choice by the director put in the hands of the viewer all the necessary transformation.As regards the direction of Medem little objection, his style is very peculiar and staff you like or you dislike but does not leave indifferent and that is appreciated.The interpretive level the actors are irregular starting with Manuela Vallés (Ana) in practically the same registration throughout the film, except for the hair, not the character changes are reflected in its interpretation. A pity because it has a very expressive look and is very comfortable in front of the camera. Baby (Linda) makes herself, a racial with great force, perfect but little courageous character. The rest of the cast is uneven with a correct Charlotte Rampling as the patron and a dreadful interpretation by the actor that makes hypnotist.Saturate in blue and Red depending on the scene, digital photography is very effective and demonstrates a clear evolution from his previous film, Lucia and sex, where the technique was not mature enough. Finally the soundtrack of Jocelyn Pook (Eyes Wide Shut) is also very suitable to the images with moments truly successful and beautiful, very much in the style of the work carried out by Alberto Iglesias for earlier films of the director.Finally, Caótica Ana is a very personal film as failed, that wants to be magical but it is too explicit and obvious. If it did not have that end it would be one film more failed but interesting aspects, but the way in which just does damage it in an irremediable way.Summary alternative, Caótico anus is a film about a girl with a serious problem of constipation that finally arrives at the healing hands of a senior of the Bush administration.</body>
</review>
