<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="En el valle de Elah" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film exquisite way of disturbing background, with a cast of actors in State of grace.</summary>
	<body>Starring Tommy Lee Jones, Charlize Theron, Susan Sarandon, James Franco, Jason Patric, Josh Brolin, Jonathan Tucker, Rick Gonzalez, Barry Corbin and Frances Fisher, in the Valley of Elah suponde the second feature film after Crash of Paul Haggis, who has collaborated with Clint Eastwood in the scripts for Million dollar baby and the diptych consisting of flags of our fathers and letters from Iwo Jima.La film tells the story of Hankveteran of the war of the Viet Nam, who must investigate the disappearance of his son Mike, soldier serving in Iraq which is mysteriously absent without permission from its base. With the help of the detective Sanders and his wife, will be reliving the experiences of the boy in the middle. What you discover will make you even question his own military career.In recent months, lots of films have deepened sectional in the Middle East conflict in general, and the American military interventionism in particular; Some examples of titles like Redacted, Lions for Lambs, the shadow of the Kingdom or the battle of Haditha, and in the Valley of Elah must join this growing list, albeit with some points.And is that, unlike most of the above titles, the new film of Paul Haggis has the gift of timelessness, because his criticism not focuses in a specific military conflict but the consequences of that conflict, porm what well might move its moral to any time and place. Although, let's face it, any minimally successful war film should possess intrinsic way that quality, but in the Valley of Elah would be perhaps closer to movies as born the fourth of July that Apocalypse now, Platoon or metallic jacket, and that is perhaps what makes it different.With Tommy Lee Jones in the role of the typical patriotic father Made In Usa as the main protagonist in the Valley of Elah inoculates his criticism against any armed conflict and less visible consequences through the investigation of the disappearance of a soldier after his return from Iraq, in a plot of calm pace which, luckily, not abused the increasingly more recurrent turns 180 degrees, for the benefit of a greater deepening of his characters. And it is that if something noteworthy in the Valley of Elah, the remarkable interpretation of its cast, especially Tommy Lee Jones, Charlize Theron and a Susan Sarandon almost anecdotal but that, as usual, robbing who were put ahead any plane as soon as they leave two Palm OS field.In the Valley of Elah is shown both as an open criticism of all conflict armed, as a severe warning to the consequences less visible of these conflicts, such as a touch of attention to excess of patriotism and pride, national and personal, so therefore inoculated in us from birth society and that, increasingly, drifting in a malaise and a disappointment to, unfortunately, often discover when it is too late. Highly recommended.</body>
</review>
