<review author="Sandavito" title="La boda de Tuya" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A sublime masterpiece based on real facts, half way between fiction and documentary.</summary>
	<body>Almost three months ago came to us a small great masterpiece in the form of Chinese drama: the wedding of yours. Brand new winner of the Golden bear in the 57 Edition of the Berlin Festival, reels the penalties of an average family in the huge and arid steppe North of China.Precedida Mongolian for its international success, this film which, otherwise, would be minority, seems to have garnered great success in theatres, with full after three months in poster. It is no wonder, since yours, embodied by the actress Nan Yu, whose latest work we'll see will be Speed Racer, the Wachowski brothers, and that has been winning awards since 2001, really moves. A sincere woman who is overwhelmed by the circumstances, have to take care of his family, especially her husband that was disabled in an accident, receives the news if still pastoring his flock and loading weight it can end as invalid as he. It is at the time when you should take the most difficult of his life decision: divorcing husband and find another man willing to load with her family and keep them all.That point of rotation so alien to our society, the investment of the values of the pyramid of Maslow accepted so easily (are the own husband and sister-in-law who encourages her search to another) one of the many elements that make the film so suggestive and attractive. It's have a life and a situation without artifice, without dramatismos, with this resignation and acceptance of who knows that if does not find another husband, or still not digging the pit until you find water, he will inevitably die. And still go ahead without shedding a tear. A plot and film reminiscent of the films of Zhang Yimou before that he fell into the megalomania of his latest productions, more in line with, for example, one less, or the long road home.The wedding of yours has a classic scheme of five acts and a simple and effective realization with a camera who exercises more than witness the omniscient observer which we have so used the current film scene. Wang Quan'an manages to convey the desolation of the enormous landscapes and subjects at the same time as delicate as polyandry or a kind of marriage prostitution for survival, and that far from the Happy Ending and more European, American reminds us that reality always surpasses fiction, and that after the ate partridges life goes on, and does not always have to be for good (as masterfully tells William Goldman in his novel the Princess Bride).An elegant atmosphere and truly nearby characters, many of which interpret real surviving steppe Mongol, which adds realism, flavored with a soundtrack precocious, those both yearn lately in the film, which not only does not hinder, that enrich the whole, confirmed the synergy to create a film that nobody should miss, a sublime masterpiece based on real facts, half way between fiction and documentary.</body>
</review>
