<review author="Torbe" title="Los Increibles" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Why are the animated movies much better than normal?</summary>
	<body>It is not the shit anywhere, all the movies that are increasingly better. Even not fall into stereotypes that it is so easy to fall, which is repeated and repeated, as the shit of American Pie 3, which is to do the same jokes, bad few and predictable to the mile again. What is it hidden behind these movies? How is that you they not bored a single moment it? What they entertain alike to children than to adults? I have no fucking idea, launched the questions into the air, if someone knows, that answer right now in alto at his home. This time I happened something that not I had never happened before with a movie (well Yes, with Pocahontas a bit). And it is that the mother and the girl I been brutito. The mother at the beginning of the movie this quesito, her entire mona, and then at the end of the movie when he gets in plan wrestler also, on the other hand when this mother is the downturn of total penis. The daughter at the beginning cool plan so sinister pseudo freak. But not pa fuck yet, only to give him handshakes and muerdos. It is then, when thrown to the pa hair the laos when this to do evil deeds. Why I possible females ready for mating see up in cartoons? Why I put the woman for being a woman, both natural, movie or cartoon? I guess it's a default physical characteristic of my hobby for reading comics erotic. They are pictures, Yes, but you put as aquatic motorcycles, throwing water foam on all sides. Damn, I want to see the second part of the incredible, and the third. That pussy make not more than this kind of movies and are so much pain in the ass shots, serial killers, polis bad and good, natural disasters where all are saved, boring dramones, comedietas do not laugh, superheroes who do not have anything, and a thousand movies for teens is to kill them all? Make more movies like! And if possible with more good aunts! In this movie there is a phrase that I love, which is when the father tells the mother what mania have the Yankees in enlarge and continuously celebrate mediocrity. In reference to go to the Party of end of course or that make the Yankees when they run studies, my cole called party of course. There were diplomas I think. Therefore, id to see this great movie that is funny, witty, with great action and entreteniemiento. It for once you get a movie this good, must be said!</body>
</review>
