<review author="Uruloki" title="En la cuerda floja" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting at all times and very but very well crafted</summary>
	<body>This past weekend we went to see a couple of movies of those that are worth being seen, that Yes, each in their own way. On Friday we went to the heinous rooms Valle Inclán in Santiago de Compostela to see a new biopic of those that make the Filmography of the actor graceful with the starring role to go down in history in some way.Tightrope (Walk the line, 2005) is a good / great movie. Interesting at all times, very but very well crafted and very but very typical. Although this is not his fault. Somehow all the famous rockers of the musical universe world artists have reached agreement so that their lives are all virtually identical. They usually start with problems in his youth (a trauma, a difficult childhood, a complex social circle), end up succeeding thanks to its quality, retozando with fanatical females and stuck in drugs to finish out the strength of will that treasure (a few) or by passing a better life (mostly). That is the life of Johnny Cash, Elvis Presley, Jim Morrison, and a long etc.You can personally detach completely from that is a chapter in the long biography of Johnny Cash, the film can be seen as a film based on the life of anyone and it is still a lot of work. Joaquin Phoenix plays its role of pearls, Reese Whiterspoon is also very good and the setting of the film is great. The work done by James Mangold is good, well worth a look. I do not think that you be awards at the Oscars because he has tremendous competitors, but the movie is worth.What I did not like at all is that we hear bits of songs, never completing them and that I don't like. In addition, as I've been saying time immemorial, Valle Inclán theaters are a garbage. This time 2 minutes from the end was cut the movie! 15 minutes after seeing as the lights lit up and they apagaban continuously enjoyed the last sentence and House. missing a bloody phrase! So they spoil any movie. (Grotesque Valle Inclán suffered in the return of the King, grotesque Valle Inclán suffered in Spider-man 2, large grotesque Valle Inclán suffered seeing El Bosque).</body>
</review>
