<review author="Sandavito" title="Alien vs Predator 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A waste of time and money, it will only please more fans of the most unconditional and may be only if deceive themselves.</summary>
	<body>A marvel of horror film whose main virtue was that not taught the monster far advanced the film came out back in 1979. Almost ten years later, an intergalactic hunting enthusiast made sweat the blind to the very Governor of California while it waving their dreadlocks to the tribal music of Silvestri. In 2004, Paul w. S. Anderson, in his role as champion of the adaptation of the video game to celluloid, brought the first installment of this crossover between alien bugs, version I did either not seeing the film and waiting for the DVD; something that has not happened with its continuation.Admittedly, Cameron added a more attractive and spectacular to the history of Alien environment (development of the Weyland-Yutani Corporation, all the paraphernalia of the marine space.), David Fincher provided the subjective vision of the Alien so many joys we produced to those who play the Alien vs. Predator video game and its sequel. Jeunet also did something productive for the saga. Although right now I can't think what, the truth (well, Dominique Pinon in a convertible wheelchair in a cropped, may be interesting - my inner voice tells me, and I reject it with a drab the hand gesture). Predator 1, with the same McTiernan's the Crystal jungle to the head, had his grace. And in the second part of 1990, it was curious, to say the least. I even dare to say that AVP:Aliens vs. Predator, the first installment of this mini series of two films (and hope that no more), was entertaining. But the crappy with a capital of the Brothers Strause, us is more than a cluster of absurdities, topical and estulticias one after another, in Indian row, that are humming as the film progresses and increase yawning.Nevertheless, this film has its audience. Without going any further, leaving the projection I could hear two people elucubrando about new features provided to the universe of the aliens and predators. And they spoke excited, Hey. But let us not deceive ourselves. There is truth, cinema popcorn cinema (as what I, which serves only to have a good time call), and monsters that should never see the light of a projector; even of the hose used the writer to write it.I played video games. I got in the skin of an Alien and a predator. And I enjoyed it. But gentlemen Strause, this is not a video game. And not a film of truth.To start the script can not be more obvious, topical, typical or meaningless. Acartonados characters taken from popular imagery (the prota newly out of jail, the sheriff scared, pretty silly.), sub-plots that begin and end in one or two sequences, horrendous dialogues. Shane Salerno, that comes from the television and whose greatest achievement seems to have been collaborating on the screenplay for Armagedón (1998, Michael Bay), delights us with a string of disjointed nonsense from the very beginning of the film.Music, to not vary in this type of production is more scandalous. Instead of supporting the film, it seems trying to compete with the image in terms of pretentiousness and bombast. It clogging more than provides, and one has to make real efforts of self-control to see ensuciada part of the music of Goldsmith and Silvestri of the original movies, registered between fanfares and trumpeting blows. And that composer Brian Tyler has a couple of interesting work, as Constantine y. y. y. well, okay. Only Constantine. And almost by the hairs.Let's talk about the picture. Daniel Pearl chooses to lighting notam of day and dark armpits which of cricket at night. And 70% of the movie occurs at night. The moments of struggle between the predator and the hundreds of thousands of aliens that seems to leave suddenly from nowhere become a succession of reflections between black spots and sound effects, a Fresnel enoooooorme of zillions Kw backlit so you can see rainwater, which is very nice. It is by the screams that differences who or what appears on the screen. It will be to throw imagination, and thus fill yourself the gaps - huge gaps - the movie. Out of the world of the video, Pearl seems to find lost in celluloid.The direction of actors or I am talking about. It is wasting time talking about nothing, and there as says Natalia Mateo in Traumalogy, Daniel Sánchez-Arévalo, "nothing is nothing, asshole".Realizing. Uy, the realization! Strause, appeared from the universe of the special effects seem to have not seen more than the extra contents of the DVD of the great films. Its realization is hackneyed and devoid of sense. They want to see it, but do not want to have anything with her.Finally, and in short, a waste of time and money. Loosely exit the market research that only appeal to most fans of the most unconditional and may be only if you cheat a little themselves.</body>
</review>
