<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="XXY" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lucia Puenzo a decision that the honors, avoids completely the way the easy curiosity, limited to narrate the story of a teenager who feels different, marginalized by a cruel and intolerant society.</summary>
	<body>A few years ago the Argentine cinema lived a period of great splendour, in which all movies arriving we were interesting, intelligent and innovative proposals. However, this wave was losing strength, and now almost all arriving us are or comedies rather simplistic and vulgar or stories are not but mere cheap psychoanalysis.At this point in the decline of Argentine cinema, arrives XXY, the directorial debut of Lucia Puenzo, a proposal very risky, different and somewhat provocative. The story of parents who must flee to protect his hermaphrodite daughter could be an excellent bait for a filmmaker that focus the history from the sensational point. But a decision to honor Lucia Puenzo, avoids completely the easy morbid way, limited to telling the story of a teenager who feels different, marginalized by a cruel and intolerant society towards everything that is different and does not understand. Puenzo also falls in the melodrama or in the easy tear, but it is also true that the film does not acquire the dramatic and emotional strength that might assume you, the final result being something weak and disappointing. Best of the tape, and what sustains it, they are actors, and between them is impossible not highlight an extraordinary Ricardo Darín, is able to convey more with a look that all the dialogue of the script.XXY is a different proposal and risky that we hope will help revitalize an Argentine film found in low hours. It is also the opportunity to see the promising debut of Lucia Puenzo, and the privilege of attending another master class of interpretation of Ricardo Darín, that if he had been born a few thousand kilometers to the North, would be considered one of the best actors in the world without any discussion.</body>
</review>
