<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Alien vs Predator 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>AVP2 should not be more than a project for television. The Strause brothers desauciaron any possibility of creating a third party.</summary>
	<body>There is not much to say with regard to this tape is one more than the unfortunate copies infiminidad made the first version and that nothing beats the one made by Ridley Scott in 1979; "Alien the eighth passenger", which has become perhaps his most promising work and who has stayed in addition, in the minds of his followers, apart of course from Gladiator of the year 2000 and American Gangster nominated for best film at the Golden Globes this year among other nominations, speaking in more recent terms. It is sad to see how it has been 29 years, with much more technology and the capacity to achieve more realism in special effects, how it destroys the good image that these two aliénigenas have.Alien Vs Predator 1 premiered in the summer of 2004 to assume since then, that its future was not going to much because the history and struggles between these two beings did not imagine otherwise. Apart from this the low collection of that time; 171 million dollars confirmed. However, thanks to the successful results of the comic books, novels and video games environment, made this second version that has managed to pick up little more than 76 million dollars.Inevitable is the fact to compare these two versions and before such discouragement and despair with what the film is constructed, becomes much more preferable to its first part. The problem in both is the story and his script but in the version number 2, these defects are accentuated. The plot is really stupid, stubborn, alternating a story of teenagers a little awkward and very little credible. Many are the gaps that have and many are the cliches that are handled throughout its short duration of 1: 26 Min, not only in characters and history, but also in sound clichés. The desire for making this franchise a success with low-cost movies, has done is to acquire low budget actors also, that experience they do not contribute to the story and that on the contrary they tarnished the few results that may have. At this point what manages to save himself no more passing the "raya" are: music on the one hand that resembles to a large extent their predecessors and the respect by being faithful to the previous characters, which is something that if it is due to their great knowledge of AVP the Strause brothers.The setting but did not help the characters in the judgment, as I said earlier, is appropriate, unlike its rhythm which is a back and forth that goes and returns in the passing of the minutes. After his home is given much return to action, what is a clear reflection of the lack of hyphen and when the climax makes its appearance, the action is obvious and too bland. Dramatic space is just the tight, focusing on a small Colorado town, deepening in this way in their disadvantage and thus justifying its final outcome.Aliens Vs Predator 2 in my opinion should not be more than a project for television and much less should have been created the possibility of generating one third of this story. The Strause brothers desauciaron any possibility; at least in the majority of your audience, that happen.</body>
</review>
