<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Planet Terror" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Visual revelry, absolute binge, but need a nod complicit, some need to communicate with this blatant, shameless, offer pure dynamite for the more hooligan eyes.</summary>
	<body>I have no hope of that thug cinema report me greater pleasure than the more vulgar escapism. The truculence, the chabacanería and irreverence have the charm of the transcultural, this kind of aura of decadence that is granted all benefit of the extravagance, hubris and film vandalism as patterns of some form of filmmaking that hence (to post, happy) of the Canon of orthodoxy. Me is perhaps becoming a spectator gentrified, little flexible in accepting the discomfort of being being cheated or less specifically, of not to be enjoying the gender. I can fascinate music and deny me in round to listen to an album of hip hop or folk music from the Balkans. I can enjoy with the poetry of José Angel Valente and feel guest of beauty and intelligence and feel boredom if you give me a collection of poems by Rafael Alberti, that it is not of any of my abundant lyrical devotions. In film, there is no excessive change in speech. Films made Ford and movies does Michael Bay, to which you have taken an inargumentable tirri since a few months ago. Then Planet Terror, under the previously poured verbal cement layer, should be considered a waste, a simple slip of the film, a roll, and isn't it. At all. Planet Terror, part however separated from the combo with the splendid Death Proof Grindhouse by strictly mercantilist reasons and indissoluble, is cinema thug, autoparódico, unquestionably attractive case that one accepts the rules of the game. Once we have taken the flanges of the divertimento, must be left to carry ninety minutes for the pranced of the plot, its air to the mad doctor movie, its wildness and self-assurance. What the second part open until dawn, another work by Rodriguez, felt me disconnected from the first, facilonamente resolved with the wink gore or giallo, here Planet Terror seems a necessary demonstration of which gender lives and pays its intentional faults, their volunteerism when enfangar a perfect Bill taking into account the budget handles. So Rodriguez, a movie buff of video store to the way in which it is Tarantino, but less tight by success media corsets, recreates his particular vision of the Apocalypse zombie version with Audacity, with artisanal blurs with the fake trailers and with the stench of capricious orgy of someone who has received carte blanche to desmadrar badass plan fond of collecting geeks in their films: collecting emasculados testicles, go-gos with submachine guns to thirsty of blood draining leg or zombie mode. Not we can under the mantle of this visual terrorism conceived rigorous criticism. There are times in which one enjoys without powering the lever of sanity. Case of trigger her, wasn't yesterday the case when alguilé in the DVD video store, Planet Terror is perhaps one of the biggest mistakes that movie buff one can lie between eye and memory, the most fabulous waste of time, but he sticks with scrupulous devotion to the mythical inventory of a format and a way of making films in crisis or already out of print (programs doubles)(, barbarian session of violence, sex and much blood, amateurism in State of grace).Viewing at home, pass by the domestic system, by sophisticated and chulito, should not be for the show. For this or almost none, but Rodriguez requests shouts his film (and Tarantino) are seen in cinema, in a pantallón as manda Cecil B. de Mille and the cohort of emperors of the film as mass entertainment, bombastic and extraordinary. The cinema screen provides the extra winks a TV screen does not provide: those cuts, these mutilated levels, dust, spent color. Up the trailer that principia function, the immeasurable Machete, the Introit, which advises on nature rogue what us remains to be seen, only requires tricks and the complicity that reports a cinema of truth with their chairs and their darkness twinned with our infinite (always) capacity of astonishment. Because astonishment there in Planet Terror until bursting the púpila and ask for enough with tears as oranges of Gandía. Cumbersome to nausea, lit by the twisted genius of a teenager with ways to director of prestige, this joke made film can be considered the outburst of the season, a dangerous precedent in the commercial circuit made in USA. If it has succeeded the sequel, the absolute remake and unworthy (on occasions) inventions of prequels and several parallel montages only lack that the luminaries of the film business to discover that the staff refused this game of descartes and frivolities to uncovered breast, leg high, killing zombies as that takes coffee on a terrace in Paris. in the absence of more delicious food and most demanding palatesPlanet Terror is freshness, hilarious freshness. Without more.</body>
</review>
