<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Escuela de pringaos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It seems that Billy Bob Thortom has definitely lost its way and needs to find its niche in the film. And is decanting dangerously by Disney comedy teen misfit made in USA.</summary>
	<body>It seems that Billy Bob Thortom has definitely lost its way and needs to find its niche in the film. And is decanting dangerously by Disney comedy teen misfit made in USA. Which is not that it is all bad, but those who believe that it has been a great actor feel deeply their loss.Pringados school is an anecdote in the unsuccessful film. Jon Heder (seen in blunder to glory) is Roger, a common type, works as an agent of mobility (these gentlemen that you get fines and do not reach the category of guards or police) and is not only a failure at work, can say the same about his personal life. It is not able to talk to a girl without faint is and even you want to in a program of older brothers as a volunteer. Why give the phone number of Doctor p. Acaba in this way in a class where will try to restore the self-esteem and teach him to be a man of truth. This is what at least teaches us the trailer. The reality is that half of the film takes place with the confrontation between Roger with Doctor P for the love of neighboring newly conquered by the apprentice. Does it lose grace? If the reality is that although that part I'm not fan of this type of one hundred is much more entertaining than the second and managed to boot I any laughter. I can not miss the tape the presence of unmistakable Ben Stiller, think that if they try to do something that smacks of comedieta you have to put the head albeit as a cameo. Another Lost in Translation on the tape is Michael Clarke Duncan (not ask why have deceived you because surely he had green ticket form) Although it seems that you as secondary in this type of comedy may earn the bread very well.Otherwise correct the direction of Todd Philips is already shooting with films such as Starsky &amp; Hutch or Road Trip. It seems, that has really brought a little and dare not do once suggesting that it could unseat the Farrelly as new Disney comedy genius.</body>
</review>
