<review author="Bruji" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Playing to be Stanley Kubrick, Joe Wright discusses a tragedy in three acts with the pulse of the big.</summary>
	<body>The technical showcasing breaks the formalism in the narrative structure of a tape devoid of soul which, however, has good elements to enrapture. Joe Wright discusses a tragedy in three acts with the pulse of the big. This way to traverse the corridors. the frantic persecution of the protagonists with fair depth of field and the minimal camera movement, the elevation of the target to the category of character, that unmistakable "lateral travelling", levels sequence taken at ground level. Who remind me? Joe Wright, film director born in the 1970s, has been unfairly compared to James Ivory, perhaps by the successful completion of his directorial debut, pride and prejudice. But even in a story by Jane Austen, Wright knew away from the slowness and the solemnity (which were never synonymous with depth) inherent to the Filmography of Ivory, print a new, accurate, pace in line with the belief that feelings are universal and, therefore, atemporales, with the purpose of getting this kind of stories to a greater number of viewers; as Ang Lee propose for sense and sensibility. On this occasion, which is his second film, a project that takes over after being rejected by director Richard Eyre, is can continue appreciating his huge talent after the cameras, to discover a series of technical aspects of particular relevance, which did not appear in his first job, and come you to one of the big. It would not be unreasonable thinking that this challenge, undoubtedly important for his career, wanted to be addressed taking as a reference to the greatest novels of all time adapter, to Stanley Kubrick. Moreover, I would ensure that the incomparable style of the master floats in the environment since the conception of the script. Although it does not appear in the opening credits, the director works with screenwriter until exhaustion, getting disestablishment the story into images of the written word (Lolita). The presentation of the characters and the treatment given to these, glimpse of the most absolute of the drifts, while history is shown with the greater asepsis as possible, without symptoms of sympathy with none of the protagonists to make the viewer which draw their own conclusions (determinant in the universe Kubrick, who never wanted to give an explanation of his Odyssey in space). The three flashbacks in the first narrative Act, virtually imperceptible and close in time, manage to analyze the same fact from different points of view (perfect heist), to be wisely introduced through objects on which becomes repair. A technique that brings the good movie fan memory make immemorial times, which would have achieved its maximum expression in the timetable for written on the wind of Douglas Sirk. If we add to these inclinations technical virus identified in the beginning of this article, came to the conclusion that it is difficult and dangerous play to be Stanley Kubrick. The master, considered a mechanism of watchmaking, never lacked or left over a single element in the final exhibition of his works. A success that Wright, in this film, can not boast. Atonement is, basically, an amalgam of images and sounds, in which raw material on the narrative technique. The excessive obsession with the MIME of every detail gets exalt parties at the expense at all, leaving the feeling of a fund perfectly colored in a unfinished silhouette which never comes to perceive. A blow that works during the first few minutes, and that soon seems insufficient to come to fruition. Thus, in the third narrative space, when it gets to be profiled, hackneyed plot based on the passage to the India of David Lane weighs too to pay attention. Against the abuse of scenes that contribute nothing to the plot or contribute to the progress of the action (remember the maze of flashbacks of the second time that only allow the showcasing of the filmmaker), will yearn those others that would have given perspective of their interpersonal relationships, objective fundamental development of the literary original and the thoughts of the characters. Without embargo, the coldness with which presents the facts, no involvement of the filmmaker in the story, originating a lack of empathy in the course of the events, which make it a precocious story to feed the senses, without reaching the heart. With this approach, is paid the ground makes prosper various aspects technical, deserving of the highest accolades. The impressive artistic direction recreates the atmosphere of luxury and apparent serenity that is breathed in the mansion of the Tallis with the same accuracy that collects the desolation of London in World War II, or the devastation that offers impressive level sequence in circular from the French of Dunkirk in 1940 Beach (actually filmed in British territory)until the present time. A few major changes which are also collected by the excellent soundtrack, in many moments mixed with the insistent typing of a typewriter, or the acceptable picture of the director of the hours, which gives their C's with a piece of vase deposited at the bottom of a source. A deplorable image of that mythical that Nestor Almendros got an oscar in days of heaven. Within the cast, we have what is, without doubt, Keira Knightley the best performance so far, the miracle that makes think to those who don't believe in it that something must have water, apart from hydrogen, when they bless. Also, stresses the excellent performance of Saoirse Ronan, teenage actress, and is worthy of regrettable inexpressiveness male bet, James McAvoy, responsible, in many moments of overwhelming lack of chemistry in the purported romance. All of which leads us to believe that many will be nominations appeals on Atonement, and badly should be things by Hollywood so that, finally, it is considered the film of the year.</body>
</review>
