<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Deseo, Peligro" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film round a stylistic exercise as years earlier we not witnessed.</summary>
	<body>With desire, danger Ang Lee won the Golden Lion at the Venice Film Festival past for a second time, and opts for the Golden Globe in the best film of non-English speaking section, which is why the Taiwanese filmmaker could well return to repeat the success of previous titles such as Brokeback Mountain or Tiger and Dragon. Interpretada by Tony LeungJoan Chen, Wei Tang, Lee-Hom Wang, Johnson Yuen, Chih-ying Chu and Anupam Kher among others, be jie we moved to Shanghai in 1942, when the city is occupied by the Japanese. Mrs. Mak, a sophisticated and wealthy, woman enters a coffee, makes a call and sits down to wait. Remember. how it all started a few years ago, in China in 1938. In fact Mrs. Mak, but Wong Chia Chi is not called. Shortly after World War II his father fled to England, leaving her in China. I was a university student and met Kuang Yu Min, who had just found a theatrical society for promoting patriotism. Wong Chia Chi became the first actress of the company and discovered that it was able to move to the public and Kuang. The latter persuaded a group of students to carry out an ambitious plan to assassinate an important contributor to the Japanese, Mr. Yee. Assigned a role to each student: Wong Chia Chi was Mrs. Mak, who should win the confidence of Yee becoming friends with his wife to end up seducing. The young man turned internally and externally for his role. Everything was going as planned until an unexpected event happened.The truth is that my relationship with Ang Lee is so strange. Despite the popular outcry, or Tiger and Dragon and Brokeback Mountain convinced me too much, I think that sense and sensibility gives many turns to the previous two, and Hulk may be the best treatment that anyone has ever done a superhero despite drag various scourges starting with the unfortunate role of Nick Nolte.Con footage that may be excessive for someI would like to, danger oozes smell classic by each of its pores, from his careful setting, its texture, its exquisite soundtrack or the treatment of his characters, his own plot and context, reminding us, directly or indirectly, to titles such as Mata Hari, chained, to have and have not or Casablanca; Although, much closer in time, we find ourselves with these inevitable echoes from wanting to love and, above all, of that (almost) great film by Paul Verhoeven is the black book, whose similarities to the new work from Ang Lee are you seem to one server rather than merely anecdotal.As said, desire, danger could have lasted well half an hour less, and would have been even more round than it already is, but the truth is that jealous detail that Ang Lee describes the initiation ritual of his femme fatale is not weary, catching the Viewer, but with history, with the own setting of the film nowhere. That Yes, when plot and passion overflow, I wish, danger reaches its most álgidas heights, with a final time of truly impeccable footage, while the continuous and explicit scenes of sex, far from shocked me, found me a somewhat repeated mixture of Turkish passion and a guide of the Kamasutra.Como was to be expected, the espionage plot loses force for the torrid romance of its protagonists, with a fairly round performances by both the novel Wei Tang and my dear Tony Leung, capable of Marvel titles as diverse as Hardboiled, Chungking express, foul play or 2046.En summary, desire, danger is a movie quite round, a stylistic exercise as years earlier we not witnessed, and although its duration can be somewhat large for somethe new work from Ang Lee does not reach tire at any time to the Viewer, trapping it in its atmosphere of irretrievable way.</body>
</review>
