<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Mimzy, más allá de la imaginación" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It brings together fantasy, science fiction and even mysticism equally in a solvent formula but forgettable once a server has left the film, but at least not makes us feel that we have wasted our money.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Robert Shaye and starring Timothy Hutton, Joely Richardson, Michael Clarcke Duncan, Rainn Wilson, Chris O'Neil, Rhiannon Leigh Wryn, Kathryn Hahn and Kirsten Williamson, The last Mimzy, translated here as Mimzy, beyond of the imagination, is a markedly child film although aimed at all types of public.While they are on vacation, Noah and Emma Wilder discover a box black floating on the sea. The box is very mysterious. Its bright surface of Onyx seems impenetrable and shines and vibrates as if it had its own personality. When the box is finally opened, the children are captivated by its content: a precious object of glass with a strange and supernatural, bright stones that irradian colors to turn and, in the background, what looks like a stuffed rabbit. Emma becomes fascinated with the rabbit, which seems to talk in whispers. She puts the name of Mimzy.Grata surprise was for a server Mimzy-beyond the imagination, not because it is a good movie, but by the mere fact that a markedly child film did me pull me hair.The film of Robert Shaye is pretty law-abiding in general terms, with a story that sounds like a mescolanza of other titles, children or not, and an extremely complex plot in appearance but ends quite understandable (and foreseeable) resulting. In addition, Mimzy, beyond of the imagination, brings together fantasy, science fiction and even mysticism equally in a solvent formula but forgettable once a server has left the film, but at least not makes us feel that we have wasted our money.With a halo of eighties air that pervades all his footage, Mimzy, beyond the imagination has not been able to leave remind me the fun explorers, Joe Dante (do you remember the legendary phrase I was weeks wondering why the hairy child did not speak?) it will certainly evoke the adults to their children/adolescents, which will keep more young people aware of the screenThanks to some good special effects, which are conspicuous by their successful lack of excess, and certain passages that may even be somewhat disturbing. And is that, somehow, the film can even remind us a sort of encounters in the third stage in child key.On the other hand, I must admit that the film of Robert Shaye is quite tedious in its first section to trace then surprisingly the flight, despite the somewhat odious interpretation of its young protagonists, and is that not all children are Jodelle Ferland. So, in short, we could say that Mimzy, beyond imagination is a good title if you you see the obligation to the Cherubim to the cinema, but it is perfectly surplus as a movie fan, that does not cinéfaga.</body>
</review>
