<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Irina Palm" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The strength of Irina Palm lies both in the self-development of its protagonist in the delicious romance that it maintains, always present but never dominant.</summary>
	<body>Nominated the bear gold at the last Berlinale, Irina Palm is the second film directed by Sam Garbarski German starring Marianne Faithfull, Miki Manojlovic, Kevin Bishop, Siobhan Hewlett, Dorka Gryllus, Jenny Agutter, Corey Burke, Meg Wynn Owen, Susan Hitch and Flip Webster. co-production between, great Brtenaña, Luxembourg, Belgium, Germany and France, Irina Palm tells the story of Maggie, a widow of fifty years to find money for the treatment of his grandsonas well as encourage her son Tom and his wife Sarah. To see an ad that reads "Se necesita stewardess", Maggie enters. When he discovers what kind of companion is, she is shocked, but he accepts the job. Maggie is shy and it would frankly wrong in the Empire of sex if it were not for Luisa, a companion who teaches him the tricks of the trade to make very requested Irina Palm. But the double life of Maggie does not pass unnoticed to its neighbours and must face the double provincial standards and ask serious questions.Irina Palm is one of those films that you would know how catalog, if it is it necessary to do so: it could be defined as a light drama, either as a tragicomedy, or in any event as a black comedy, but the truth is that if we are to judge it in one of these encasillados, the Sam Garbarski film loses many integers. It is Irina Palm works and is therefore a pleasant experience, if not we try to cover it in any category. Some have not hesitated to find the similarities with Full Monty, but latter is much more focused towards the comedy film genre that here we try, it combines the drama of manners, so to speak, with comedy and romance.With a burst of tear desktop telefilm drama, Irina Palm takes not too to show us their true strengths with a couple of subtle comedy gags and quite black, who barely effortlessly manage to make us forget our most dismal omens. Since then, slowly but surely, Irina Palm develops its sordid plot with a predominant tone of black comedy or, rather, self-assurance, desdramatizando in the same way that makes his protagonist, finding the comic side of situations as weird as the elbow of pajillera, home decoration of the room, or the sincere admiration of clients of the local, health benefit, which glorified the figure of Maggie icon of prostitution, as if of a footballer or a pop singer were.On the other hand, and to alleviate the shortage of unexpected twists or complex plots, Irina Palm focuses its development on a subtle portrait of the characters, both in the reactions of her female protagonist as, above all, to its environment, in addition to the great shift that takes the professional relationship between Maggie and Miki, a character who just only need serve his impassive physiognomy to embroider his role. Finally, and as you would expect, the situation takes the classic and expected 'twist' of turn, predictable though why not disappointing, taking us to the expected outcome of the film.In this way, we could say that Irina Palm part of an original although sordid premise, and from that point of origin its director develops an absolutely obvious plot but no less meritorious. And is that the strength of Irina Palm lies both in the personal development of its protagonist and, for a server, delicious romance that it maintains, always present but never dominant.Come on, that I liked.</body>
</review>
