<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="Skizo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Probably to any viewer will create much rejection in advance. However, the tape is not as bad as it may seem a priori.</summary>
	<body>The second job of Jesus Ponce?Do Skizo?, is one of those Spanish films that probably to any viewer to create a much rejection in advance. However, the tape is not as bad as it may seem a priori. It is solvent and even has some good moments. He has a well-structured screenplay and not only correctly portrayed characters, but rather to present psychological evolution. Photography, by Javier Aguirre, is not bad, and the atmosphere is well achieved. For being a film very few characters and only two scenarios, does not produce the typical feeling of shortages often occur in these cases. Is true that the poster and photos seem to be short and that the problem which often have these films is that they are a short lengthened in any way. However, the script from?Do Skizo?, signed by David Sarasketa and Javier Etxaniz Petralanda has enough arc to fill a long. Not very long, that Yes, but a feature film at the end and after.What much of the audience may have problems with is the interpretation of the actors, in particular Oscar Jaenada (?)Shrimp??(XXL?), which has a more complicated role. To accept his way of speaking it should make a kind of "Act of faith" and believe that the macarrillas speak like that. The truth is that I do not know many and don't know if his tone is realistic, so I prefer to think that it is to watch the movie without rechinen me ears constantly. Anyway, very different roles, such as the of?The game of truth?, me has seemed even more forced and performed worse. So pretty is that here is tolerable.Secure BEA and Eloy Azorín (?)All about my mother? , ?Kisses for everyone?,?Warriors?) they are good in their roles, although it happens what Leonardo DiCaprio in?Do Titanic?: not you think that the posh is not him. Secure (?)Do do with me whatever you want?,?Do Lola sells Signet?,?(La dama de Porto Pim?) It has the responsibility to carry the role with more psychological evolution. That seemed an innocent victim is a manipulative Princess which also hides a goal. Does particularly well, but it is at least credible. Patxi Santamaría is more correct the tape and Asier Oruesagasti is well characterized.There are a couple of moments in the movie Yes that may be close to the lack of quality expected of it in advance. The first consists of a few dreams have Ivan and Susan while they are locked in the House. And the second is the end, as sudden as absurd. It seemed to me to hear that other end had shot, or at least, that there were other alternatives presented in script. It would be well to know if so.Since its title, the film deals with schizophrenia, about which I spoke in another entry length. While is made that criticized the author of the book?Images of Madness?: submit to patients as people dangerous and ultraviolent, seems that the script has been carried out after a documentation about the disorder.Jesus Ponce, 1971 from Seville, account with a long experience professional as a TV Director, editor, director of commercials and short film maker. In a completely different line, his previous film,? 15 days with you?, was a magnificent portrait of the lumpen with much emotion and a realism rarely achieved in cinema. Was the picture of Daniel Sosa, as part of the team of this film, and was the Director of photography in the short film?Silent world?.</body>
</review>
