<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Cuento de Navidad" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In short, a feast for lovers and nostalgic the eighties film, with plenty of references.</summary>
	<body>Brilliant initiative which supposed from the once popular Narciso Ibañez Serrador, recover that spirit that imbuía their essential series "stories to not sleep", through a series of medium-length films of little more than one hour, intended to be distributed by television, with the fantastic theme and collaboration in tasks of direction of various promising growers of the genre in our country. Pity that the display of ignorance, contempt, and little attachment to the genre by Telecinco (possession of their rights to emit), us is private to enjoy on a majority basis, having to resort to the rent in the form of series B despised or in lieu thereof, to the compilation that has emerged recently in the shelves of retailers in sale of dvds.It is true that six projects, not all have been entirely satisfactory, resulting in the productions of the own Ibañez Serrador ("La Culpa"), and above all, Mateo Gil ("return to Moira") and Enrique Urbizu ("guess who I am"), mere samples of television limited, both in its final content and in the form of poor quality in general and why, products that should have survived solely on these television passes which never (or at least didn't put them in any normal hours). But it is also true that another trio of creators, perhaps the most gifted surely in this storytelling despite its flaws, they offered us three stories of the most suggestive, that transcended beyond the foodstuff or the television movie fan initiative, to know avail themselves if same as products unique and non-transferable. Balagueró offered a clever turn of the screw to the very problematic case of housing in our country with his "to enter to live", which gave vent to his usual brilliant capacity for the creation of coatings with a striking visual aspect and a story very well told, although the small defect that usually have their worksa script and a narrative too debtor on occasions of clichés, contrary to his brilliant visual capacity, even so, a more than interesting proposal for its part. On the other hand, Alex de la Iglesia offered us a story even better if it fits in the "Room of the child", full of moments of pure horror, suggestive and narrativamente impeccable, with a visual resource (from the visualization of the alternate reality through monitors) that gives rise to a scene in the ghostly child, really overwhelming, room in an excellent work. The latest work of "Movies to not sleep", had been signed by Paco Plaza, a great director formally and technically, but on the other hand, lacks in times of a narrative pulse and a personality marked the appearance visual, in contrast to his partner and friend, Balagueró (as I already mentioned in the review of REC).In this last story, Plaza us situated in the skin of a number of friends in the mid-1980s, the eve of the day of Christmas, in a Catalan coastal town (well known for a server by the way). When they discover the body of a woman dressed in Santa Claus into a deep pit in the middle of the forest, they are intended to provide aid to such unfortunate women, until they discover that you it's a dangerous criminal who has fled with a bounty of two billion pesetas. He then begins a dangerous game by the Group of friends, who takes them to treat it as its mascot, with the intention of knowing where hide the two million before releasing it to the police. Uppercase surprise can be considered this production of Paco Plaza, not so much by the quality treasures (which also), but by the fact of being a rare avis within an industry so stiffens as the Spanish. Plaza knows to give you all a tremendous personality, of a sunset in brilliant scene, which is his best movie solo without a doubt, with camera movements and visual resources even, that resemble the charismatic eighties film, one that an entire generation, among which myself, enjoyed despite their ambiguous ideology.All this contributes a script full of references to productions of that decade, from the most obvious and named by the protagonists of the story, as "Karate kid", "The A-team", "The fantastic car", "Dynasty", etc.hasta the most subtle introduced in the form of homage and reference to charismatic films such as "The bicivoladores", "The Goonies" (that gang bike by those greenish places), "Account with me" (the discovery of the corpse in the Woods) or the more stark slasher, which square clearly shows fan.Perhaps the great virtue of the history becomes your default for some thing to some extent understandable. It has always been said that there are two ways of making films, the first is closer to reality for once established the base, create a history fictitious with the objective of showing the obsessions or views of a creator. The other form of film-making, as they say, it's create cinema from the film, the cinephilia carried to the extreme as the basis for the story, as for example do the great John Carpenter, and above all, Quentin Tarantino (reaching the latter perform true pastiches of films little known for the vast majority, but recognizable by the most unbiased cinéfago)(, brilliantly).This last option is which has taken as a square base to create his reference film, a delicious movie and a wonderful tribute to an innocent Decade for many us, but full of magic and empathy with the stories that we had. Can play with the nostalgic aspect (not only movie buff but even making reference to the "Pink Panther" cakes, that popular the Simon game, or the series "V", etc) brilliantly, and there is where lies the great strength of the film, from nostalgia creates a history, on the other hand, possessing an impeccable narrative rhythm, a brilliant script references and ironic vision of that child passion (significant the fact that does not remove in the) (compose the faces of adults) distant enough to be effective.Outstanding work by the Group of young actors, a true delight listen dialogues so close and in turn so believable, being all of them at an exceptional level, perhaps maybe even, and a no less brilliant history Maru Valdivieso in the role of bad function. Little thing can lend you in face of this successful film, perhaps a fund structure and narrative elements and progression analysis would result a certain approach on its credibility in the history, but let us not forget, this is the toll to pay for to revere the time, in which thousands of stories transcurrian more on the path of accumulation and little likelihood that a coherent approach. So ultimately being so reference may not be liked by everyone, but even in that scene, Plaza shows a good taste in the Mise en scène, to not show true fact supposed that it has happened.In short, a feast for lovers and nostalgic the eighties film, with plenty of references that would walk in a long debate on the occasion of identifying them all (even posters of "Not desecrate the dead dream" and "The night of the blind terror" that decorate the room of one of the children), with truly bright scenes and a story that works perfectly so cinéfilo-festiva reference above. A great film, and probably, in its very essence as a reference to a series and a way of seeing the gender, the best of all the series of "films to not sleep".</body>
</review>
