<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="Soy leyenda" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The tape of Lawrence seems a very sweetened version, optimist, glib and comercialoide ultimately from the excellent book by American author, which makes it something fully forgettable after leaving the room.</summary>
	<body>It is seen that we walk too far from the courage and the suggestion in the genre of science fiction / horror of the 1950s. The current guidelines that preside over the productions of the majors are exclusively of a commercial nature, without risk, more concerned to show and give an explanation to all that suggest and respect the intelligence of the Viewer. Films such as "The incredible shrinking man" by Jack Arnold proposed a serious look at human loneliness, isolation, the struggle for survival in a hostile environment and the value of lost everyday. The same Matheson - author of the novel, wrote the screenplay, won the freedom that they don't nowadays seem to give the producers and the result confirms, that possibly the best film adaptation of a book by Matheson, as well as an excellent example of great cinema made with few resources (such as much of the B series of yesteryear).Obviously, Francis Lawrence, has not had the same fortune that Arnold, since it has as writers - I think we can say it - two of the largest Hollywood churros, able to write huge jumbles in the form of libretto as "Poseidon", in the case of Mark Protosevich or "code Da Vinci", in the case of Akiva Goldsman, possibly the worst writer of USA for a server and regular collaborator of the execrable Ron Howard. Work with such useless has have been a mental torment for the good of Francis Lawrence, a filmmaker not as mediocre as a priori may think, since his work on the film, from my point of view, is decent (not very notable). That if, please run a thick veil on this thing called "Constantine" with bland-man Reeves.Si entered comparative between book and film, the film is as something really unattractive. Not only has lost all that anguish and terror of the novel, but also much of its meaning, in addition I do not see anywhere the fight psychological it stuns Neville. As in "The incredible shrinking man" in the novel the protagonist was the stranger, be "marginalized" and a killer for "new humanity". This is the step on the other side of the spectrum.The tape of Lawrence seems a very sweetened version, optimist, glib and the comercialoide dessert of the excellent book by the American author. Pessimistic novel nothing air is reflected in the tape. The Existentialist draught also seems to have disappeared from the map. Everything seems in the service of the FX (very good in terms of locations, very bad and totally failed in regard to infected), as well as containing any other scene out of place that clearly break the rhythm of the tape for example: those of hunting initial with the car at all milk (almost gives me something xD), moments "Shrek" and "Bob Marley", both certainly regrettable and pure gobs comic made in the principe de Bel-Air.En as in the end, what?, then falsely hopeful and nothing as chachi and "worship" of the novel. SPOILER that suicide Will Smith seemed almost to patriotic and penosete and a statement somewhat dangerous anti-11S, martyred to give life not to remove it, Yes, but beware, never occur at Neville as what it is: the last link of a strange and murderous race, but almost as a new Messiah salvador. END SPOILERTanto "The omega man" like this, assume two failures to adapt one of the best sci-fi horror written novels. Charlton Heston or Will Smith convinced as Neville (though I must admit that, although he hates the actor, Will Smith is more content than usual and is welcome).A churro patatero entertaining and enjoyable. There is already talk of sequel, I propose to leave Tomatito Bloom as cousin Neville brother, leaves just so something even worse.</body>
</review>
