<review author="Plissken" title="Kiss kiss bang bang" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Shane Black Fox kept for himself his best screenplay: one that, once exposed and assimilated by all the clichés of the genre, the dynamite after Yes, to make impossible any revision or Variant.</summary>
	<body>As many people had put by the clouds the premiere in the direction of Shane Black, the kind that led to the action to the top film in the 1990s ('Lethal weapon', 'The last Boy Scout', 'The last action hero') and then it disappeared almost without trace (at least in the IMDB), I decided to see the work in question. And despite expectations, came to surprise me. And how. 'Kiss Kiss Bang Bang' (2005) boasts the classic elements of the film Shane Black helped make the past decade: an unlikely pair of researchers, a complicated plot with kidnapping and bulk dead, an anti-hero seeking her redemption, caustic dialogues, a high end of about $ 15 million, minimum.But Shane Black Fox kept for himself his best screenplay: one that, once exposed and assimilated by all the clichés of the genre, the dynamite after Yes, to make impossible any revision or Variant. He created the monster, he destroys it.Shane Black strives to be contrary to itself, with surprising results: the protagonist, Harry Lockhart (great Robert Downey, Jr.) is a species of apprentice of Martin Riggs or Joe Hallenbeck, with the proviso that no paste or stamps, and kill or talk. Gay Perry (finally another great role for Val Kilmer) is its companion of adventures, nothing less than a white detective, gay, pedantic and disgruntled (the Antipodes of the characters played by Danny Glover and Damon Wayans in 'Lethal weapon' and 'The last Boy Scout'). Harmony (impressive and fun Michelle Monaghan) is the sexy girl, young and which always kidnap on the successful previous screenplays of Black, but here is less sexy, young and less good, say that more difficult to hunt. The criminal plot is a matter of small fry compared to the drug trafficking in the U.S. Army or the corruption of the football idem. Instead of flying buildings into the air, flying a paltry coffin.And what is surprising, as I say, is that it works. Probably because Black known as nobody to the public who is directed this film: same fans of his films of the 90s, but ten years later, saturated, impressionable but hardly nostalgic of the genre, to the end and Cape. The key elements are there (impeccable chemistry between the actors, a clearly autoparódica torture escenita, evil pasts of thread, a car sinking in water.). And on this occasion reinforces the product with warping direct nod to the Viewer, which has only two options: leave the shocked film with this scam, shouting "this is not going with me"; or well forget about depth of argument of consistency of frames, etc., and enjoy each autohomenaje, of each gag, each broken unwritten rule, muttering to himself: "it's about time that back, Shane".9, While the plot it police is not sustained. That's great.</body>
</review>
