<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Late rose, filled with hope as extreme situations are an absurdity that reveal only the mere commercial interest to bring sequels.</summary>
	<body>Once again and for the third time, leads to the giant screen the science fiction novel by Richard Matheson, with same name, which was established in 1954. At that time Matheson built a highly interesting, futuristic novel in which imagine the terrible situation that would be the last man on Earth in the late 1970s and in los Angeles, California due to the extermination of its inhabitants by a deadly virus. Viruses that make it a species of vampires or zombies.The first film who wanted to bring this story to the big screen in 1964 was "The last man on Earth" Italy. A film which featured an adaptation of the screenplay of the own Matheson, which is that most resembles the novel and which truly explore and closely reflects the aspect psicólogico of the central character. Not too distant to this first production, in 1971, carried out the second movie called "The last man alive", also known as "Omega Man". This has been the version away almost entirely from the original novel that bothered much to fans of the book. Many qualified her unfortunate and little bright in terms of history and technique. Indeed, that revising broadly, because the reality is that I not resist finish it, this version is a reference point for not to mention.This latest version that managed to disappoint such point to write about her late because I saw her the day of its premiere, I can not measure it under the eye of what was the first adaptation. In I am Legend there is a noticeable evolution of its main character and vampires. The mode of Defense are no longer mirrors, cuttings and the chains of garlic, they see all the time in the last man on Earth, but weapons, what is undoubtedly a success. Although the version vampirezca created by computer for this version in some scenes is irritating and I'd rather stay with the last prototype of this beings, created in the film "30 days of night".I am Legend focuses on how the last man on Earth after 3 years of living in solitude, has adapted to its environment and spends his hours hunting animals, sending press releases have if someone hears it, exercising in half or better "over" military aircraft (heh, heh, heh) and defending in the nights of the monsters that the rest of the humans have become. A coexistence that will envelop the audience in the psychological aspect of the character through looks limp, the sadness of a notoriously exhausted face and the use of moderate but little explanatory flashbacks in comparison to the real story, unless it comes to comply with such objective actually. Unlike the first based on the novel, there are no dilemmas for sure, there is no real crisis situations, there is no deep fears, nor crying nor explosive laughter of the last man on Earth involving one in feelings of deep emotion, thought and morality caracterísiticos of psychological tapes.Unlike the novel, there is a longstanding relationship with a dog German Shepherd named Abbey in real life, which aims to generate a false emotion in the viewer more than anything else, but that without refute it did, because the performance of this little animal is exceptional and get compungir the heart, thanks to its final destination. However are these innovations in history, with its final part which does not convinced me and by which evidence a somewhat tiresome tabloid and commercial interest.The problem here is not the performance of Will Smith, nor the desire because made his debut her young daughter of 7 years, Willow Smith, because there is no dispute the enormous effort made to build his character, discipline had to do so, which included down around 10 kilos and intense physical training to be more slender. Indeed, thanks to their interpretation and the enormous and undeniable charisma that has the tape is not worse. Nor it falls on the diseñora of production which took an enormous amount of work to build in the middle of a real scenario of the size of a city like New York, absolutely and incredibly desolate streets where weeds and wild animals are the Kings. This is the point that can be enjoyed the tape, its more actractivo and was a great achievement using real scenarios, which include places where had never before allowed filming that they reflected good shape, thanks to photography, should also be mentioned, in the final product. Nor is the rhythm, which incidentally is very good, nor the narrative structure.It's definitely the adaptation of the script that was provided, that at times tug of war and leaves show "silly" details in history, gaps that are not looked after. At this point I return his end we talked about in the beginning. A hopeful ending that reflects more a desire to generate or leave the expectations a sequel, to the desire to be consistent with the critical situation in a man to stay almost alone without many possibilities for subsistence. See more a desire to create this history to a "hero" disguised as a legend who saved us, resulting in Jesus, life for us.</body>
</review>
