<review author="Heitor Pan" title="This is England" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie with a pace and an evolution perfect, of those who are able to emerge a huge range of conflicting feelings and that leaves a bitter sediment which takes to disappear.</summary>
	<body>New ration of stirrer and political film of consciences. After the Italian "my brother is only son", where we were still a teenager through his changes of ideology, paste a leap to the British Isles of the Government of the iron lady in the early 1980s, where a boy of 12 years attend first-hand to the birth of the movement skin head and his right-wing nationalism.Shaun is a lonely kid with a tendency to get into trouble and marked by the death of his father, combatant in the war of Las Malvinas. At that stage of life in which something is needed in what they believe and be accepted by a group, meets a group of skin heads of moderate mood that they treat it as an adult and accept to an equal, despite the obvious age difference.The Group disgregará with the arrival of Combo, a violent and unstable skin which takes the ideas of a right-wing party, forcing Shaun to choose between part of his friends, who prefer to turn back on this change of direction and an ideology which, according to Combo, honors the memory of his father, killed by safeguarding the purity of England so as "my brother is only son" was characterized by the attempt of the director to remain neutral to the narrative, without position itself clearly in any area of the ideological spectrum, the director and screenwriter of "This is England", Shane Meadows, it takes a clear match. Even so, does not load to the skin as a whole head movement, they clearly differentiates those who adopt a violent attitude and extremist, which were simply guided by a distinctive aesthetic and that, later, Usamérica, desmarcarían of the "skin heads National Socialist" giving rise to the Sharp movement (Skin heads against racial prejudice).The director makes use of a series of characters with different characteristics to show camaraderie, rivalries, the joys and stresses of a group of friends, in this case framed in a social movement. Firstly, the protagonist, the more innocent and with the purest look about what happens to your around, without ideas preconceived. A character has the need to process the information as it is occurring because it has no points of comparison and that is that marks the development of history.On the other hand, the people around him. Woody, the most charismatic and leader of the group until that Combo appears in scene and the first to accept and sponsor to Shaun within the group. Milky, the Member of color of the gang, which quickly becomes fondly Shaun and will serve as one of the points of rupture between moderates and extremists. Gadget, an obese kid that time when suffering the mockery of the companions and the first claim to feel accepted by the new Combo extremist group. Smell, first love of Shaun and a neutral and look almost equally innocent of what happens to your around or the own Combo, destabilizing element and an excuse to show the two sides of the coin.The film progresses in a crescendo soft but steady, adding tension and action to a story that tries to undermine the drama in its first part with situations that lead to laughter, but as it progresses becomes harder and descarnado, wrap in a powerful and dramatic, final climax that leaves the viewer played, without the clear sense of a happy ending but printed a sense of hope to the future of the boy protagonist.A movie with a pace and an evolution perfect, of those who are able to emerge a huge range of conflicting feelings and that leaves a bitter sediment which takes to disappear.</body>
</review>
