<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="Saw 3" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Horrifyingly shot (a very mediocre director, no doubt), a script from the more simple with a plot that little people you can reach interested the slightest and above all an aroma of series Z (not even sympathetic) really alarming.</summary>
	<body>If a server the successful first part seemed a huge joke, at the same time, it served him to save that (presumably) vomit sequel, but now, thanks to the dvd provided generously by Buenavista, one has viewing the third part of this unnecessary and filthy trilogy (sextalogía road) and although it started from a level very low, the results in this installment manage to make us believe that still can be a more mediocre than the mediocre filmDespite the redundancy. While the first film directed by James Wan - sobrevaloradísima for large part of the public-was miserably dodgier, raving to try to play / mislead the Viewer without any justification, with tricks of cheap (and looking for the constant surprise, what made it more commonplace and fake), a montage disgustingly videoclipero and a bad taste more than evident, this third installment continues in this turbulent path.Aside from a script of the more implausible, ridiculous, inconsistent and up cochambroso, Lynn Bousman tape lives on the rehash of past deliveries (which has even more crime), copying the Manias of the other previous directors (mounting of video clip, start-up regrettable scene, mediocre photography, awful music and amateur performances) rather than innovate and renew (boldly)(, as for example did Nolan with Batman) a series that walks more burnt than the "Rocky" (which already is).Part of the macabre sr Jigsaw jueguecitos (sick terminal, but Duracell plan), we have some of the worst resolved "terror" scenes of last year and I don't think exaggerate with such an assertion. From camera moves sharp and accelerated which fail to stun the Viewer, flashbacks unnecessary reminders that emphasize too much and do not respect the intelligence of which is seeing the film, an invoice really poor with a mise en scene almost non-existent, a lack of aberrant suggestion (coupled with the lack of ideas, imagine the result &hellip;), some sequences which produce true grima to say the disgusting (there have the unnecessary and my scene of as) (Dr. bore the head of the murderer during the operation), because there are still who believes that bad taste can scare (ahem).Finally, a silly movie, there is no where to take her and I think an idiocy devote more lines. Horrifyingly shot (a very mediocre director, no doubt), a script from the more simple with a plot that little people you can reach interested the slightest and above all an aroma of series Z (not even sympathetic) really alarming.</body>
</review>
