<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Despedida de soltero" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a couple of boyfriends, where she is to marry as soon as possible and he go to seek his fortune in the Americas. Given that it is very outdated, and that actors are not for nothing, see it now predicts boring.</summary>
	<body>Director: Eugenio Martín. duration: hour and a quarter.Release date: November 27, 1961.Espectadores: 69 of human beings, it seems that lockers control was more than necessary. That I said that if the Ministry does not have the data, to not put it, right? I if that is a number guarrindongo.In the world of the Spanish cinema classics, we have films that after the passage of the years become endearing, which they remain in existence and some to tráfago the years have devoured. This, unfortunately, is closer to the latter. To begin with, the theme go to the Americas to seek his fortune we have lejanísimo (now come them). Women no longer want to marry sole purpose in life. The only thing that remains is complex that is to buy a flat. A penalty.The film is about a couple of boyfriends in the 1960s. She animated in excess by his aunt, is wants to marry when previously. On the other hand, he encouraged by her uncle wants to go to the Americas to seek his fortune, to then go and marry. All this ends it tangle the arrival of a President of a South American country.Because I have much more to add. Almost remains is film as an anecdote of the funny dramatic film Spanish, given that now see is rare. Curiosities is to see the Spain of the early 1960s, their customs and others, but little else. The performances are even outdated, with a girlfriend which I think you do quite loose. As a curiosity, it has two moments that clearly which put people to make the scenes her shit. The two on the beach, with horses, which actors returning back from a jump, and another with the car. NA, to say the least.In short, film about a couple of boyfriends, where she is to marry as soon as possible and he go to seek his fortune in the Americas. Given that it is very outdated, and that actors are not for nothing, see it now predicts boring.Besitos.P.D: Has a couple of funny comic moments, but little else.Pd2: The only reason why I saw is that get Pepe Isbert</body>
</review>
