<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Interview" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite being an entertaining and correct exercise in all fields Interview makes water at times and the dialog is forced and even turns you can see come without much effort but you can enjoy fairly.</summary>
	<body>Pierre Peders does not have a good day. You need to interview an actress in B-movies and cheap television programs and the truth is not very aware. So from start attempts to boycott the interview to go to more interesting things. What does not expect is that the stubbornness and tenacity of the actress you will become entangled in an interesting night full of discoveries where he'll realize what kind of person she is and even what person is himself.Sienna Miller has never been my devotion Holy because, like his character in this film I have heard about it by with who has been lying for his interpretive work. Not in vano the American (or English for convenience because he grew up in the UK) enjoys great fame in the tabloid newspapers in his country by jumping from bed in bed with almost all actors of the tape where the head has gotten, without doubt one of the most high-profile is the "with you and without you" which has been for years with Jude Law, with whom he appeared in Alfie. For this reason that costs much believe you on this occasion which is appreciated because to share almost the entire load acting with Steve Buscemi, it would not be easy to endure the hour and twenty minutes without this effort on your part.Steve Buscemi is brilliant, as almost always who if not I could have left quite lightly things with Air with reputation intact?. And this time also gets behind the camera to correct or theatrical form direct tape consistent with the pace and turns that proposes.Despite being an entertaining and correct exercise in all fields Interview makes water at times and the dialog is forced and even turns you can see come without much effort but you can enjoy fairly.</body>
</review>
