<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Oxford crimes, not ceasing to be one film more than correct, is quite aseptic as it has neither force nor the hook that could presuppose a work of Álex de la Iglesia.</summary>
	<body>Spanish cinema has begun 2008 with enough force, at least in theory, and is that the premiere of the new film by a filmmaker of the stature of Mario Camus joins now of the crimes of Oxford, the new work of another great director of our filmography (literally and metaphorically).Álex de la Iglesia gave vital impetus to the cinema of terror and mystery, or what today covers with the simple name of cinema "of gender" in our country. They were better or worse their films, they always are couldn't recognize the style of the Bilbao filmmaker, who always gave his works a hilarious touch of black comedy. For these reasons, and for the bad film harvest of 2007, the Oxford crimes expected as water may, but the truth is that after seeing her, the most appropriate word to describe it is disappointing. History is more grandstanding and empty at the same time, and while it is true that keeps the interest, isn't that leave you stuck to the seat containing the breath. The script embarulla with so many logical series and philosophical digressions, and without wishing it, diverts attention from the real heart of the matter, whose conclusion, stuck with a shoehorn, not convinced at all. The characters are quite flat, and some of them come to be ridiculous, or are mere vases, Lorna a lost Leonor Watling is neither nor the expected. Álex de la Iglesia-style is not recognized except at specific moments, as one of the discussions between Anna Massey and Julie Cox.Los crimes of Oxford, not ceasing to be one film more than correct, is quite aseptic since it has neither force nor the hook that could presuppose a work of Álex de la Iglesia. And it is that it is impossible to create the ideal climate calling loudly for a good mystery story with so many philosophical and mathematical theories.</body>
</review>
