<review author="Sandavito" title="Pozos de ambición" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>No fanfare. Nothing free.We are seeing real men, fighting themselves and the world.</summary>
	<body>We have to wait to see the latest film by Paul Thomas Anderson, who already bring us the wonder called Magnolia, as well as interesting Punch Drunk Love and Boogie Nights in Spanish theaters until February 15. On this occasion has been with Daniel Day-Lewis as unquestionable protagonist to speak to us, once again, the human miseries, a role which has earned the award from the Broadcast Film Critics Association Awards.There will be blood tells how Daniel Plainview is possessed by the idea of the competition, being the best, the richest, but to support others to do you shade. Search gold and silver converted in oil magnate, Plainview will be falling increasingly lower to achieve your goals no matter what or who has to trample.Following a more or less linear plot development, without large excesses or extremely portentous turns, the story takes place, as in the rest of tapes by Paul Thomas Anderson, using the characters as foundations, such as the main base and engine of the entire film. Weight falls on them and you know take it very well. Daniel Day-Lewis is a true American of the 19th and early 20th Centuries, hardened by dint of peak and Palau. It exudes rude and cold blood. Her accent and their movements are perfectly worked. In short, you see on screen is not Day-Lewis, but Plainview. Very in keeping with its name (plainview, in English, would direct view), progresses without artifice by history, making it clear what he wants and that nothing will stop him to achieve this. But there is always some obstacle, and in this case the obstacle is none other than a young man got his own sect, the third revelation, Prophet epitomized by Paul Dano. Dano, whose role better known to date was elder brother in little Miss Sunshine, he is surprisingly mature performance, knowing stand up to Day-Lewis without any problem, balancing the interpretative balance perfectly. Maybe that Paul Thomas Anderson has discovered a new Norton Edward with this film.The realization of the tape is, without packaging, calling history. Levels of long duration, for the most part, none of syncopated mounting, violence, when it appears, told with coldness exquisite, close and distant at a time, without recreating it but ignore her, as a necessary element more. Very studied frames and games with the internal contracampo in the moments of more privacy or in the light of a campfire. No fanfare. Nothing free. Here we are not seeing giant, with the wonderful James Dean suffering before our eyes by misunderstood. We are seeing real men, that could well be his grandparents, fighting themselves and the world.The rest of the elements support the development of the film perfectly and her highten. Photography Robert Elswit, his collaborator from Sydney (1996), even without being too spectacular, has grandiose moments, especially when playing with high contrast and low-light conditions. On the music of Johnny Greenwood he succeeds in creating an almost hypnotic atmosphere of tension, playing with minimalist movements occasionally, with very present cords which almost suffocate the percussion have base. Only there was a moment of the footage that seemed just right; the rest of the time, a real find.There will be blood is an essential event for those who enjoy watching movies with more than just shooting and explosions, film that has something to tell, a film in which each element, each character, works with the accuracy of a machine of watchmaking.</body>
</review>
