<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Freaks, la parada de los monstruos" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A masterpiece of the genre, which despite that Court in the footage, endures as a film full of double readings, some of them harsh, and that it might force even in our days with so much worship extreme to the cult of the body.</summary>
	<body>Born as Charles Albert Browning a July 12, 1880 in Louisville, Kentucky (USA), Tod Browning was an exceptional case during the prolific period of fantasy films from the 1930s, because, unlike other peers, their almost unhealthy obsession for a bizarre cinema and out of any prevailing fashion at the time, earned him be always considered an extravagance in the horror film. The Chronicles describe him as an introvert, manic and unpredictable, man that avoided any hint of popularity to confine much of the press. At the early age of 16 years, Browning joined a traveling circus, guided by the growing love for a dancer, which gives good example of well-founded knowledge of the filmmaker in this world so little rooted to the stable, traditional life. Between 1912 and 1914 he moved to Hollywood, where he met D. w. Griffith, and that means you the privilege to intervene as an actor in "Intolerance", the director himself. After intervening in several works commissioned, especially screenwriter, Browning directed his first film in 1917, from that moment, starts a prolific and rich career with one element in common throughout all his work, the manifestation of abnormal in the area of the real. While it is true that the groso of his work was developed during the time of the film mute (with room even for the legend, as that film's name "London After Midnight", which today is missing, but rumour that possessing a private copy could become millionaire when the rights in the work by the proprietary producers expire)It is also true that it has been particularly recognized and valued over the years, and so absolutely fair, by their few incursions in early talkies during the 30s. Films such as "Dracula" (1931), "The mark of the Vampire" (1935) or "Dolls Hellions" (1936) are today in day bright manifestations of talent for creating large pieces of gender by its director. But it would be "Freaks, stop the monsters" (1932), the masterpiece of his career, the film that would pass to the annals of the history of fantasy film in particular, and the seventh art in general, where Browning showed his mastery of the dark elements (remember that he studied psychology and was a renowned collector of books on occultism magiay)to offer us a ruthless vision of humanity human. The plot of the film us is situated in the everyday lives of a group of members of a traveling circus, where we have on the one hand the characters that play deformed employees, in this case, dwarfs in most cases, either cripples missing them elements of your body, without the typical bearded woman, the two Siamese or one person half man, half woman. And on the other hand, people, say normal, they are responsible for the rest of works that make up the elements of the circus, in this case, the strongman Hercules, the clown, the tamers or manipulative Trapeze, protagonist of the hub of the story, attempting to take advantage with Hercules, the Fortune inherited by the Hans dwarf, with subsequent intention to end his life to be free of any tie. A halo of disturbance crosses the few, but forceful, 65 minutes of the film. Browning introduces us to a world which, as discussed above, knew perfectly given his experience in life real surrounded by peculiar beings. Having for the main roles with real members of circus, they are all deformed, considered fair, and not only in the film monsters (the label that warns us about the treatment received by these beings in the reality of the time is devastating), gives the finish an extraordinary ability to analyze semi-documentary although from the base of a fictional story. As well described by Umberto Eco in his latest book, the contrasts of life is when it takes on real meaning each of these contrasts, without the macabre, there would be no basis for considering any element of our society as beautiful in that eternal comparison is when we realize that the Poles opposed van together hand in hand, which tend to be the reverse of the same coin. Throughout the film, deformed beings, or freaks as I will call from this moment, give sample of an enviable sense of honor, friendship and education extreme even (cite the two dwarves, Hans and Frieda, and impeccable chivalry), driven by an inner beauty that instead manifests itself in the opposite way in the more "human". The other characters are shown as strong, beautiful and looks pristine in their physical appearance, but on the other hand, hide some of them more stark evil inside. Browning play again with this fact, the duality between spiritual and physical beauty, implying that what hides something beautiful, sometimes it is more monstrous than any physical malformation. Significant in this sense is a point made in the film, as annotated dinner of compromise between Hans dwarf and the villain of the story, the ambitious trapeze artist and little scrupulous who intends to marry to seize the money and then end the lives of so polite be (with the help of her lover herculeo as discussed above). It is that humiliating demonstration of malice and contempt towards the Group of freaks, the trigger for the behavior of these beings become twisted and macabre, United by a desire of survival before any external element. But not in vain, subtly insinuated by Browning as a virus full of evil that seizes slowly beings seemingly good heart, without being so casual the engagement, i.e., the clash between the two worlds, blurs the line which separated the duality of physical or moral beauty, already nothing is safe from the evil, or even those of greater spiritual purity (citing as one example the innocent clown transformed into avenging lover). The film is full of scenes really unpleasant and discouraging about the human condition, marked by an appreciation that certainly felt Browning by less gracefully beings of our society, scenes like the beginning of the film, with the humiliating attitude as ruthless woman when drop his attire that Hans, being a dwarf, putknowing that his small stature makes the situation in a little humiliation Juniper and vile, or the own the dinner scene, causing a disturbance in the viewer that freezes the heart, give sample less clear that we are facing one of the most cruel films in the history of cinema. Everything is a constant moral unease just create a feeling of discomfort seldom achieved by any filmmaker throughout the history of cinema. Discussed even in a multitude of analysis the fact of considering the film as an advanced product to its era, full of a dominant modernity on the look neat, spotless and even superficially beautiful productions of the era, without having either a happy ending which implied a contrast to such evil, as a collective catharsis of much of the cinema of the time regarding the troubled time that was happening in American society. Accordingly, while it is true that I believe that it is unquestionable and gave him an air of film damn, misunderstood and massacred at the time, am not convinced that it implied a look modern conventions of the genre, more than anything because no film has returned to this area who knew so well how to show Browning, or even films 50 or 60 years later have managed to develop these as dangerous terrain. In his absence, has meant a great filmmaker contribution to the history of art, and not only of the film, being an exceptionally rare case of timeless film, not on the sustainability of its proposal (which also), but by not belong or conform to any film movement or social gaze. It's an enduring, extraordinary film and a capital piece of genre fantasy, not so much in its subject matter, but in what always has been called as the fantastic look, the way with which certain unique filmmakers knew how to provide it with a mise en scene to his films to intuian a fantastic tone, even in films, or even scenes, away from the genre. Multiple legends are about the film, starting with the fact that the film was cut in almost 30 minutes, in which, they say, Browning went even further if it fits in their capacity to disturb the Viewer. With a final in which it is said that the character of Hercules was deprived of his masculinity, finishing as one eunuch, and nothing but a dwarf in the body of a man. Also the mere fact of having forced Browning to add a final more optimistic with the character of Hans (although there is still one more elongated and optimistic that adds nothing remarkable to the film), perhaps to compensate for the horrific scene where you see the final destination of the Trapeze manipulative as that which had always detested and despised, a monster of fair. He commented further, only Browning could relate in every day with such deformed beings that populate her film, being the only "normal" that allow him to sit at the table with them, in a clear of the mysterious of this sensational film tone sample, which, despite stay clear sense of cut film, where the narrative pace is set in some sequence of the film with some inequalityIt has the ability to be tremendously enlightening on such unique beings. Or go no further, scenes such as courtship by two men to the Siamese, full of black humor taken to extremes. In short, a masterpiece of the genre, which despite that Court in the footage, endures as a film full of double readings, some of them harsh, and that it might force even in our days with so much worship extreme to the cult of the body above the intellect or the heart. Powerful and direct, cruel and magical, the pure essence of good cinema in the end. </body>
</review>
