<review author="Caruco" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Joe Wright is not confined to create images as nice as surface (for-that-are-good), or a mix cheap poetry and romanticism of announcement of perfume, they are full of meaning and content in this prodigious film.</summary>
	<body>I have not read the novel by Ian McEwan British, although it has been rated as one of the best works of the last years, and (almost) impossible to adapt into a film. Instead, what I've seen Joe Wright movie. And can sense that the starting material was not easily translatable to the big screen; but at the same time, he does wonder why it was so difficult to adapt it, because the talents of Joe Wright achieved that result, relying more on the images in dialogs, be extremely cinematic.Filmmaking qualité, with the british label, and at the same time commercial can bring you quite a few enemies, and more with the impudence and shamelessness that attempts to combine the two elements Wright. But one cannot more than surrender to the results achieved. A single vision of the film is not sufficient to unravel even half of the virtues and secrets of the Mise en scene full of Visual ideas, and also dominates Assembly and the flashbacks a charm inserts.Of the lightness of his first Act, to the grey tone of the second and the darkness (with light at the end) of the third, Atonement is humming various topics: desire and guilt, pain, ethics, capacity of fiction and even lust represented in a bar of chocolate!, in a thread of situations threaded for a girl of twelve years, Briony (Saoirse Ronan), rowdy scenesletters and words that you don't know how to read and that will cause the conflict to mark its protagonists.Also his sister mayor, Cecilia (Keira Knightley), to be delivered to their chores and illusions, wrapped in bouquets of flowers, either drowning in his travails and thoughts in silence, as he exhaled the smoke from a cigarette, becomes another example of excellent character portrait.Exhibiting an overwhelming amount of resources, Joe Wright up allows a curious choreography during the presentation of Briony 18 (Romola Garai), between the rest of body of nurses in a hospital of war in London. Briony who, then, will check that it is hardly able to speak, but barely whispering phrases. Or the Fireworks end, with a memorable monologue performed by veteran and reputadísima Vanessa Redgrave.Incluso in its middle stretch, the less grateful, placing Robbie Turner (James McAvoy) in full battle of World War II, on the French front, and dotted with a superb level sequence on the beach (mark Wright), where the defeated English army waiting to return to their island; the force of the narrative, leaving it basically the image, and not the words, who transmit, seems the best despite the fact that might lead to the (false) idea that the main story, between the three protagonists, has been stagnant. No less great is that blatant level detail of a cinema screen projected a scene between two lovers, and in which the silhouette of Robbie is torn between desperation and the need to return to his life, in a period of unusual film vampirism.A few examples to demonstrate that Joe Wright is not confined to create images as nice as surface (for-that-are-good), or a mix cheap poetry and romanticism of announcement of perfume, they are full of meaning and content in this prodigious film faults and redemptions, and capacities of fabulation, in his double-edged: for better or for worse.</body>
</review>
