<review author="Andrés Pons" title="La Serpiente y el Arcoiris" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Why the snake and the arco iris is a rare bird in the trajectory of the author decanting a much more mature script, a more developed staging, notable means that help in the Visual scalping to offer a beautiful dish on their picture with elegance in all technical aspects where beautiful landscapes are one trump card in all the elegance that is breathed from the foreground.</summary>
	<body>A strange title especially if takes into account of who signed and at the time that took place. Again I repeat strange being of WES CRAVEN that despite being one of the key names in the genre, his filmography adorns not serious titles with a terror developed particularly in the more youthful area where its greatest merits is restricted.Nightmare on ELM STREET was its greater recognition as well as provide a key character in the scene of horror with the figure of FREDDY KRUEGER, played by ROBERT ENGLUND. The SCREAM saga gave again boost his career especially in the face of the box office not quite critically.Low-quality titles bloating his work as for example the basement of fear, deadly friend, 100,000 volts of horror &hellip; &hellip; &hellip; &hellip; &hellip; etc.In its early days it surprises with works of extreme violence in the last House on the left or the hills have ojos.¿Pero all these titles have in common? I think that its brutal beginnings it took party for the exploitation of the time with films troop a good degree of torture, revenge, violations and of course GORE along with sex, in the other group comes to the edible merchantability for adolescents. Everything always focused on easy grossing exploitation.Why the snake and the arco iris is a rare bird in the trajectory of the author decanting a much more mature script, a more developed staging, notable means that help in the Visual scalping to offer a beautiful dish on their picture with elegance in all technical aspects where beautiful landscapes are one trump card in all the elegance that is breathed from the foreground.If it were little CRAVEN risks in the 1980s where the ZOMBIE Cannibal raged in all productions of series b changing the optics to delve into the VOODO being of form is the subgenre to its beginnings of for example I walked with a ZOMBIE. The always excellent BILL PULLMAN leads the cast with his usual charisma in one of her first roles, time then jump to stardom in participations of success as INDEPENDENCE DAY or as dormías.A horror film brilliant well above the average of its author that maybe flojee a little credible final act.</body>
</review>
