<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="El Cebo" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film with many notable influences, with a multitude of layers to analyze that would give for a great movie buff debate and that is, by its own merit, one of the best films in the history of our cinema.</summary>
	<body>Throughout the history of the Spanish film, there have been cases of works that go unnoticed in completely unfair way, and the case we are discussing today is one of those cases, a film that despite being claimed with the passing of the years, remains a big unknown for much of the Spanish public. It's the special criminal thriller "The bait", a portrait on the evil and the shabbiness that can reach the human being, seen from the perspective of several characters, the adult gaze opposition to an idyllic vision of the child world, and as the encroachment of the first in the second creates absolute aberrations.The plot of the film we placed on the skin of a Swiss police of provinces called Matthai, who is advised by a peddler, which by the way has previous convictions for petty offences, of the appearance of the corpse of a girl in a forest near a small village. What follows below is the testimony of the seller, and as certain evidence seem to implicate him in the murder of the girl, despite being he who denounced him to the police. After some event, throughout the body of Police believed to have closed the case, except Matthai, who still believes that the murderer of children, had already acted a few years earlier, is still free.In the direction of the film we have to Ladislaus Vajda, a Hungarian filmmaker settled in the Spanish film and even ended his life in our country. Author of several popular films in the late 1940s and early 1950s, directing to one child prodigy of Spanish film as it was Pablito Calvo films like "My uncle Jacinto" or "an angel passed over Brooklyn", or with the seminal "Marcelino pan y vino". But his creative Summit reached her with this excellent work of suspense which saw "The bait", in co-production with Germany and Suiza.Mucho will be spoken of this work, but is never more remember the master points of this piece of jewelry with a multitude of subtle layers in their development. That most stands out in it, as well as the excellent and thorough research to find the real killer, is probably the main two constants that run throughout the film from beginning to end, in the form of intrusion in an idyllic world and that assumes as spotless and devoid of evil threatening elements for these worlds, mainly the issue of the murderer in a place as the small Swiss villages, which one you already imagine if as ideal for a placid and simple life, and the cruel, corrupt and manipulative world of adults in the clean look and without evil from childhood.Constantly resorts to this confrontation, being in the case of adult vs child world, the more marked. Bright scenes such as the cops in school, where they they lecture children about bad people and which in turn becomes a struggle to find out more about the murderer in the eyes of children, become frustrating to the police to see how the best friend of the murdered girl recounts the story told her best friend in the form of fairy talewhereas the murderer as a "giant" which gave him some small sea urchins, which we will then check as it is discovered that these were chocolate truffles, and as the "giant" was more than a burly man. Not just in that scene, nor much less, the vision of a story so macabre as a perverse fairy tale (which Harry Powell in the absolute masterpiece "The night of the Hunter"), giving rise significantly to the crusade of Matthai to find the real murderer with a drawing created by the murdered girl and her visit to a psychiatrist to get into the psyche of the killer by this simple drawing full of imaginationa sketch of kid humor which becomes the key to continue to give with the resolution of the case. From that moment every insignificant detail that drawing, become a runway to come up with, of course, real killer in a titanic struggle in which even Matthai leave aside their obligations of police to act incognito owned a petrol station on the road, through which the killer chose his small victims.The adult world unfolds in a corrupt manner and with little morality, beginning by the adversarial interrogation to the Peddler, which ends tragically, giving rise to a vision of life very provincial, devoid of any logical sense and guided more by that ignorance by the true meaning of Justice, without being safe from this locals (the scene of the tavern or the commentary about the single mother are especially significant). Even without get rid of that vision the main character, risking the life of the girl that welcomes in the petrol station along with his mother, as a bait for the possible killer that runs along this road often somehow. Another boot of macabre and very black humor involving for example the scene of the construction of the cottage to play girls, a few meters from the road.This narrated with effective and commendable pulse by Vajda, with a narrative pace in its simply fantastic development, in which it introduced these details phased giving rise to a final climax excellent and revealing, when finally Matthai understood, in a scene of precious lyricism, which the child world must remain incorrupt and clean dark glancespreserving the innocence, without to say if he himself or the conversation as a mild rebuke from the previous day with the girl's mother when he discovers the affair. In any case a final again that Board the macabre with the beautiful in an extraordinary scene.The acting part is shown in State of grace, one success of the film, starting with Heinz Rühman in his role as Matthai, showing a few extraordinary nuances, from tenderness to the dryness of prodigious, a scene of tender child conversation way, to really dark in his eyes moments (cited that revealing scene when discovers possible clues to discover the alleged murderer in the drawing)(, with a look at the empty denoting satisfaction without resulting in no time sobreactuado). The rest of the cast is shown no less excellent, both the dysfunctional family consisting of mother and her young daughter who share these days with Matthai (excellent scene, again, which implies the attempt to find out the girl who is the "Wizard" that gives chocolate in the forest), as the salesman in his eternal despair, which is heartbreaking, or, ultimately, true protagonist of the story, the true mcguffin of this excellent work, the murderer, played by Gert Frobe, which saw pigeonholed in that role during much of his career.All this contributes a great staging in each and every one of the scenes, citing for example, one in which the girl plays with his boat on the River in the forest, and then appears the mysterious serial killer posing as a magician in a scene replete with readings in the form of influences, from Frankenstein to the pied, luring the girl into the Woods not with the music of his flute, but if with the magic that, in the eyes of the girl, is capable of doing our ruthless murderer. Also add everything is debtor on occasions of the Fritz Lang film, or at least one server has seen the shadow elongated master lang in this from the close-up of the characters, reminiscent in form and content that falsely accusatory film also that he was "Fury", up to "M", with that extraordinary rendition of Peter Lorre as a disturbed even greater than this film of final Vadja.En, film with many notable influences, with a multitude of layers to analyze that would give for a great movie buff debate and that supposed by own méritor, one of the best films in the history of our cinema. Essential.</body>
</review>
