<review author="José A. Peig" title="La vida de los otros" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film that combines with enormous ease various manifestations of human life into a coherent whole: feelings, ideology, power and influence, the intimate to the institutional, love and hate, trust and betrayal, beauty and art front of manipulation and oppression.</summary>
	<body>The coldness of a Machiavellian profile gives the sensitivity of the man which is what I wanted in a way forbidden by the laws of a secular theocracy step. The transformation is one of the reasons that better serve the explanation of the human fact, and here, the character known as Gerd Wiesler is a remarkable example of metamorphosis that operates from the intimacy and in reaction to an oppressive atmosphere. The construction of the character is a matter of creating environments and psychosocial contexts, not so much of outline its idiosyncrasies. Please take this as a good example. Little we know, really, about Gerd Wiesler, and this unknown area we find the best description of its multidimensional nature. The subtle narration implies omit the relevant meaning in the text base to let the implicit drama stay expressed in a set of interconnected phenomena. We don't need the text to explain the interior of the central character State, which would be his "objectification", simplifying the complexity of the drama. HGW and Gerd Wiesler are two signs that allude to a same story in different facets and dramatic meanings. Real humanity behind the institutional identity. In the early sequences, and through the expressiveness in the eyes of Ulrich Mühe, the expression of slavery was established in a hieratic profile. The flat end shows the released man. The expressiveness of the eyes of the actor is one of the dramatic centres throughout the footage. The eyes of Ulrich are interpretation and the feeling before the description of the Communist Germany, to whose sordidness and coldness is the austerity of the photography and the Mise en scène. Art (music, poetry) plays a crucial role in this metamorphosis evening between spying and loneliness. The speech renquea in Mannerist land: above the homeland and the ideology of this beauty. But at the end, rises in the last portrait of Gerd by buying the book which confirms - and you can see it expressed in its pages - their humanity, the end of an era and the beginning of another. Film that combines with enormous ease various manifestations of human life into a coherent whole: feelings, ideology, power and influence, the intimate to the institutional, love and hate, trust and betrayal, beauty and art front of manipulation and oppression. It is possible that you finf a certain Manichaeism, but this single trial indicates an attribute unavoidable if we look at the features of the story. We speak of Manichaeism when reality is simplified in two poles that do not transcend the topical idea. Florian Henckel Donnersmarck film, on the other hand, exposes all psychological and sociopolitical keys that justify and argue the characterization and development of characters placed in their corresponding fields.</body>
</review>
