<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="Deseo, Peligro" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excellent romantic thriller of Ang Lee, with a wonderful classical, a remarkable narrative structure, a photograph of r. Prieto impeccable and some major interpretations of aupa. The flat end is simply memorable!.</summary>
	<body>Ang Lee is, without a doubt, one of the few Directors of today which has a more sensible and regular work environment to the genre of melodrama. A filmmaker tremendously comprehensive and capable of amazing reflect "The ice storm" average American family life, presenting a nearly utopian western and offender (in terms of plot) full of bravery in "Brokeback mountain", adapt to the screen of a memorable, dynamic and sensitive the vignettes of "Hulk" or present an atypical Wuxia Pian, with moments full of lyricism in "Tiger and Dragon". Lee always proposes films with multiple readings, full of depth and emotional charge (although some seem cold, there lot of internal tension between bodies) and a formal finish flawless. And that is "Desire, danger," a film with an impressive classical invoice, with a script joining seamlessly with a very remarkable narrative structure (much based on elaborate flashbacks) and stands as one of the tapes more reflective, moral and subtle energies from the year. With a reconstruction of the Chinese of the 40 memorable, Ang Lee proposed a story that moves between (1) espionage thriller and melodrama, with moments of sex filmed in a truly exemplary manner and sometimes metaphorical intent. As well the title indicates, the tape speaks of desire, anger, hatred, love and despair. Also speaks of the Monster (Tony Leung), a perfectly fabricated character, in as love can also dent therein and the absence yet can be more painful for persist in his "moral" ideology. There is a game clear between morality and desire, that all this is linked to the danger that lurks to both (her by being discovered and he be carried away by an alleged spy).Mention that party are the main actions, both Tony Leung Chiu Wai and Wei Tang are immense. Tony Leung plays the evil Mr Yee, a traitor to the country which resistance followed by long time. Its interpretation is restrained and fierce at the same time, building a perfect monster that unites elegance with brutality (in bed, where really unmasks the sadistic and bloodthirsty monster). One of the best actors of the time, always excellent it.As to Wei Tang, a surprise to be his debut. Impressive role of femme fatale, which leads to his back all the weight of the film in an incredible way, a character that mutates and using seduction always takes control. A performance that unites (sexual) hard moments with others more emotive. Sensational creation, one of the best mataharis that a server has seen on screen.As the biggest moments I would stress above all four. First bed scenes, shot extraordinarily, worthy of the Cronenberg more hardcore (which learn Mr Winterbottom). The way they have become "entangled" bodies, almost as if they were a single body, the forms that they draw and so acrobatic positions are nothing more than an example of a relationship forged by desire and danger, carrying to the limits of the precipice sexual intercourse as their own lives. She will learn to live with her "dress" of femme fatale/spy, delivered to his new role, using as a main weapon the sex appeal that produces in the sr Yee.Segundo, the sequence of the killing by the Group of friends, in a scene of extremely distressing. Thirdly, the sequence where she accompanies him to the jewelry, moment in which resistance will act, starting with a beautiful idling and ending with that look sincere it is supposed and that escape him. One of the most beautiful scenes of the film, in where through their eyes cross concepts such as love, repentance, forgiveness, surprise and danger. Fourth, the final sequence, one of the most beautiful and subtle year-round. That Tony Leung in a room full of obscurity until then avoided, noting the traces of the absence and consumed by hatred towards his person.However, both arguably technically part of the excellent formal finish and interesting proposal (great work of Rodrigo Prieto in the picture or Tim Squyres in editing - to highlight the initial departure of Mah jong-), the tape is at times somewhat devoid of soul and sensibility, providing moments excessively cold, as well as having an excess of footage as a whole (remember the first part of the tape unnecessary passages). However, despite lacking something to be considered as an excellent film, Lee delivery another notable film about struggle between morality and desire drawing an emotional game on the edge of the precipice.Ang Lee comes to say in the film, as it already did in "Brokeback mountain", that love makes us vulnerable, makes us change and while Ennis (Heath Ledger) embraced the shirt of Jack (Jake Gyllenhaal), here we have Tony Leung asking if same because renunciation of love and not its corrupted ideals. Here she is who is sacrificed, but do it for love, and that's what stuns sr Yee (Leung).(1) With (more or less) similarities to other tapes of the genre as "Suspicion" and "Encandenados" of Hitchcock, "Matahari" by George Fitzmaurice, "The Paul Verhoeven black book" or some of the teacher Fritz Lang.</body>
</review>
