<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="El milagro de P. Tinto" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tale. Once upon a time a director named Javier Fesser proposed to make his first film. I now had to decide which story told. Until that one day an extraordinary fact happened in his life. He was a father for the first time.</summary>
	<body>A tale. Once upon a time &hellip; a director named Javier Fesser proposed to make his first film, after the recognition received for his short film entitled the SECDLETO of TLOMPETA (1995). I now had to decide which story told. Until that one day an extraordinary fact happened in his life. He was a father for the first time. After a period of strain and pressure for what was going to happen, by how they educate, what do, ask if it was prepared &hellip; suddenly, seeing his daughter, everything changed. Really realized that he was who would learn from his daughter, grow and mature with the most important experience of his life. A discovery. A liberation. He had something to shoot. Then, it began to shoot creating a very particular universe. Cartoony characters as a Spain of post-war, with real resources (Science) fiction. Gazpacho. Nothing to do with the construction of a family type home and car, paterno-filiales relations with some other conflict, etc. Fesser, in his opera prima, I wanted to tell all what he had seen, lived &hellip; A surreal gazpacho. A narration in a tone of comedy, comic, with dramatic overtones. From small p. Tinto (great, played by the charismatic Luis Ciges) has a dream: having children. Know what will be the woman of his life, Olivia, blind and stingy. Isolated in that had been a bully of a railway lost, create their home and spend all his life, hoping to have offspring &hellip; this fails and they will take a couple of Martians before the arrival of "his" big black with canister. Fesser gives color to a negrísima period in the history of Spain. Raises the education received by the boys, directed by the Church, in which the family institution is the epicenter of all social organization. Everything for the family. A greater number of children, better parents. Clear that any type of pedagogy in the sexual field is to espensad of Divine Providence. And, of course, that is a terrible problem. A drama. Even up to reach the fact in the stepson to teach to his stepmother, in the twilight of his life, the pleasures of the flesh. Incest? Not, nor much less. One more thing to learn from "our" children &hellip; Finally, life as continuous learning &hellip; and a constant struggle to get what one intends, beyond the obstacles, in the form of black robes, exemplary ignorance, waiting for miracles &hellip; without losing hope. THE miracle of P.TINTO is, without doubt, one of the best exponents of the latest Spanish fantastic cinema, along with the day of the beast by Álex de la Iglesia and opens the eyes of Amenábar. The film of Fesser a prodigy, full of imagination and rhythm. His best son film to date.</body>
</review>
