<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="United 93" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Greengrass has managed to create a gem of a film on the basis of a human tragedy and has given us wonderful and distressing ninety minutes while they are culminados by a final quarter in which it is impossible to contain the emotion.</summary>
	<body>Lot of courage was necessary to deal with events so recent and traumatic for a country such as the attacks of September 11 to the United States.UU. For that reason alone Paul Greengrass deserved applause for carrying out "United 93". But that also has given us a peliculón which are few.If you do not know what happened on 11 September 2001 in the USA do not stop reading this criticism because it contains some very revealing details. If you know, probably not need remind you that United 93 was the aircraft that day, while New York was suffering from the attacks on the twin towers, crashed in Pennsylvania after being hijacked by a few terrorristas.It is not necessary to say so, but respect for the victims and their families was obviously a prerequisite to let anyone you direct this film. In that sense the script and the direction of Greengrass are exemplary. But it is that also not incurred in the stereotypes that I thought would it incur with respect to the figure of the terrorists, who are here portrayed quite objectively. What they did was a brutal and no possible excuse crime and the fact that seemingly normal people can commit such an atrocity is much more terrible than if portray them with bad face, scar on the face and antipáticos.In order to make us much more real and credible the story, the style of the film deliberately reminds the documentary film. It also helps to get into the movie the use of almost unknown actors, coming in fact to use authentic flight controllers for some scenes. However we must not forget that it's a tape of fiction and their fidelity to the facts should not be what to decide our opinion about it. And even more so bearing in mind that possibly never know exactly what happened that day.The film is divided into two distinct parts. Do the first attended the gestation of the tragedy: terrorists beginning the journey to the airport, the preparations for the crew of the aircraft, the control tower, the aerial surveillance centres? In short all those that played an active or passive role in the fateful day. Does the second part focuses already definitively what happened inside of Flight 93: the hijacking of the plane and the progressive conviction of passengers that the only possible solution was to fight against documentary terroristas.¿Estilo? Almost unknown actors? Two different parts? Scenes with authentic air traffic controllers? Do counted so perhaps to many not you sound very attractive but? the pace is so frantic, so alive, that there is no place for boredom. From the beginning the spectator attends hooked events. Even more. Despite knowing in advance the outcome of the story, has even the hope that something happening to avoid in (feeling that they transmit only the major films).But if a word defines perfectly my experience watching the movie, that Word is angst. For a long time that I got so into a film and passed so distressing moments in its interior. Paul Greengrass has managed to create a gem of a film on the basis of a human tragedy and has given us wonderful and distressing ninety minutes while they are culminados by a final quarter in which it is impossible to contain the emotion.My only doubt about the score of the film is to see how the passage of time and generations trafficking that narrated tragedy find distant. It will be in a few years when can decide with greater objectivity if "United 93 &#8243; or not is a masterpiece." What no doubt is that we are one of the best films of the year.</body>
</review>
