<review author="Bruji" title="La vida secreta de las palabras" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not only by &#8220; how account &#8221;, also by &#8220; what is decided to have &#8221; and, above all, by &#8220; what calla &#8221;, &#8220; the secret life of words &#8221; is, without a doubt, one of the best films of the film Spanish.</summary>
	<body>"The stories are passed through me" is the phrase that Isabel Coixet summarizing "The secret life of words" in the 2005 Goya Awards ceremony. As beautiful as transcendental phrase which, alone, defines the work of a great writer who one day felt the need to put pictures to their stories. The phrase with which should remember this film and its creator; someone that never lived in my film feast. The students of Middle Europe danced "La Dolce Vita" by Ryan Parish with the sole concern of choosing the color of eye shadow that compatibilizara with a new bag. When we convencíamos that the red and the grey could form a perfect combination, we would open our textbooks to memorize that UN, successor to the S.D.N. of 1918, created after World War II, was signed by many countries, and its fundamental objective was to solve the various and possible future disagreements in a peaceful manner. Ultimately, it should intervene militarily to prevent new wars in the world.While we were still humming the "I like the dolce vita", the territories of the Balkan area, historically conflicting, were at war; something unthinkable for a Europe in which we had played live. During the following years, the fifteen players in the narration of Cora, - girls of our age, with our same aspirations and concerns-simply because of the chance of being born in a particular geographic area, would outline a smile to remember that bland Italian pop song, and would understand if that good intentions of international organizations were sufficient or, or that everything that you learn in the history books is strictly true. On the basis of this argument, any filmmaker - fairly acceptable - would find relatively easy to develop the rest of the plot, rolling in cities devastated by a war, like all, meaningless. However, how terribly difficult must be wanting to convey the same story by selecting as only allies a small stage, two characters and some support in which to write. -A small stage, which moves to an oil platform located in the middle of nowhere. The small footprint which is the lowercase extension reached the thoughts when you don't know look in another direction, when you fail to see beyond an insurmountable Ocean offered few alternatives to who "don't know swim", as admits one of the protagonists. Isolated and confusing place in the messy sea of their own minds, day and night plagued by waves likely to be listed, as they are the experiences and two beings tormented remorse. -Two characters. Hermeticism to the Extraversion. "The patient indiscreet" extraversion (Tim Robbins); that which rises in those who have the imperative need for everything that happens - or not - in their lives. It faced those who tend to the impossibility of silence their feelings, their feelings, and decide to express his perception of the facts to others, without foresee the consequences. The same relict of those who, in reality, the only thing that have always tried it is diverting attention to the true story who ever wanted to tell, which neither dare to mention. An episode of which the male protagonist only preserves a picture, a message that will not hear, the evocation of a book that should never give and a eternal question in the eyes: how you get to live with the past?.The secrecy of the "redhead" nurse (Sarah Polley), that will take care you for a few days. The position opposed to the excessive extraversion. The hermetic introversion that persists in those who nothing have, not because nothing have to say, but because they believe more enriching than words silence and listen, the best way to look to the future. The decision of those who can lower the volume of the world and know to ask to be left in peace. Same Hermeticism that he does not hesitate to speak clearly and openly come the time, and that, courageously, faced every pleasant or pernicious aspect of its past. She does not care to admit his incompetence to live reconciling present and preterite, when their own circunstancian advise that one way of doing so is "kill the time, before the time you kill you". Two characters. Hermeticism to the Extraversion. Two mechanisms of psychological defence of identical intensity, with the same goal, equally valid to survive. What you have, what you prefer silence, what we want that you rolled, which do not allow that you decode, what we want to pronounce, which deliberately omit, to relegate the Presidency over to oblivion, which sentenciamos to death in the thought; the essence that hinted at in the secret life that all hidden word. -A support in which to write. When the Director decides to tell this story with such limited resources, the only way that this "pass through it" and get reach the viewer in its purest form, is the soul of the characters to be used as single write support. It is not a matter of immaculate simplicity, it is a clear symptom of film masters, which is based on one of the external signs that characterize the unusual form of transmit of the Catalan filmmaker, and to confer on this work the adjective of "must have". It is this excellent "American touch" eavesdropping in this creation and that, of course, has nothing to do with the obvious fact of placing the story beyond our borders, request an international cast, and apellidar the characters with Anglo-Saxon names; but it arises from (especially present in women), innate ability, to delve into human hearts. Not only by how "it has", also by "what is decided have" and, above all, by "what is calla", "La life secret de las Palabras" is, without a doubt, one of the best films of the film Spanish.</body>
</review>
