<review author="Bruji" title="La Strada" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>No one had ever tempted to comment on two movies at the same time? That is the essence of souls in the street.</summary>
	<body>No one had ever tempted to comment on two movies at the same time? That is the essence of souls in the street.Gelsomina has soul of girl and why is only comfortable in the circus. It was sold to Zampanó, a strongman with little brains, to make lover, Assistant, clown and escrow. And, little by little, with the innocence of children, is going realizing that his mission in life is to care for the strongman because if he does not she. who will do so?Augustus has a soul without conscience. For this reason it is only comfortable among thugs. It is sold to life, a forzuda of little brains to make scammer, Trickster, dishonest and collector. And, little by little, with the self-consciousness of the weary is going realizing that his mission in life is to take care of another life, because if it does him. who will do so?, Gelsomina candor in la mirada, expressiveness in the face, wanting to be useful in the middle of a permanent wandering on roads of second and third peoples. Peace has her only when he leaves to his look of illusion, and knows that his suffering is the only apparent happiness of a man who not the ama, that no repairs it more to their advantage. A man that, one day, looking at the stars, will realize that lacks that more shines; which, with only his soul, guided you as man for the only time in his life. And will it collapse. He alone, collapse exhausted and surrendered, the pain of raising its unavoidable share of failure and remorse.Augustus takes the hard look, expressiveness in the face, wanting to cheat with scams of little mounts on discrete farms of helpless people. Can't find peace except the spotted, a little there in the distance, his beautiful and forgotten daughter need money for their transition to the University, and knows that his suffering is shame for her, which is the slab that he has to wear when police he treads the heels of accusing him of thief, fraudster, useless, of vividor, nothing.And one day, looking to the top of a path, you will notice that the happiness of a song from a family who returns from work is a reflection of what should have done you man and abandoned by the easy life, without conscience money. And will it collapse. "Will it collapse alone, exhausted and surrendered with the pain ripping without awareness that money is lost time.""" Souls without conscience".""La strada".Souls in the street.</body>
</review>
