<review author="Red Stovall" title="Clerks 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Smith has made his second best film and removing to Rosario Dawson, has written the best and more affectionate updating possible for its mythical characters.</summary>
	<body>After a film too "geek" even more radical fans?Do do Jay and Silent Bob Bob?, and a soft and conservative comedy family?Does Jersey Girl?, which fell on the topic of "Dad never came to the role of the cole," Kevin Smith was at a crossroads. ?Clerks II?, is undoubtedly the best way to regain the attention and lost followers. There are many expectations raised with this film. Meet them Kevin Smith? Almost?Do first, can say that?Clerks II? It has more than one memorable dialogue and more than one thug joke that, surely, will be remembered. For example, the discussion about what trilogy is better, if the of?The Lord of the rings? or?Star Wars?. Or the politically incorrect debate about whether calling someone a "slave of shit" is racist or not. Lapidary phrases and irreverent humor that manage to sustain a film of irregular rhythm. Of course, each entered in pounds O Brian?Halloran and Jeff Anderson still have that same chemistry in the first part.The problem comes by the side of the construction of the story and the character of Rosario Dawson. ?Clerks? It was a respond very cleverly linked anecdotes succession to conclude with a concise and powerful reflection on two characters unable to take charge of his life. In this second part, the characters remain dependent eleven years later, and the central plot are the efforts of the protagonist, Dante, to try to change his life. This change in life is to go to Florida with his girlfriend while parents of this paid a flat and portraying Dante to work in a car washing business. Does the problem lies not only in what little appeal of this perspective? and his girlfriend, Jennifer Schwalbach, wife of the director in real life? but, moreover, we see that his boss, Rosario Dawson, and Dante have a strange sentimental story behind. Does chemistry between O Brian?Halloran and Rosario Dawson is null. This could be to forgivable, despite its lack of verisimilitude, since we know that the name and the extremely good aspect of the actress were an asset that could not dispense with Smith if he wanted to attract viewers to the box office with more than the fame of the original film. The problem is that Kevin Smith, as well as at the worst moments of?Chasing Amy?, gets involved in lengthy and deep dialogue terribly sobreexplicativos. The pace stops, the tone of comedy lost and Kevin Smith, as any clumsy writer, dedicated to making explicit dramatic conflicts. All triple of what should be hard and one wondered where is that Kevin Smith who, disguised as "Silent Bob" in the first part, was able to solve everything with a lapidary phrase. Do anyway, it seems that this is what Kevin Smith meant by "maturity", and that the disastrous legacy of?Chasing Amy? and?Jersey Girl? leave note in the film we are discussing now. But we must not be so hard. ?Clerks 2? It tells the story of two characters who, eleven years later, have failed to do anything with their lives, and this, by force, should be noted. The lightness of?Clerks? It is no longer repeatable. If you want something, better view?Do marching?, a debtor film of?Clerks? of which I spoke, located in a burger bar (do scenario, where, interestingly enough, takes place?)Clerks 2? (do homage to the homenajeador?). Having said that, "deep" dialogs are not so many nor sink both the film. Even, occasionally, Kevin Smith manages to remove melodramatismo to many times placing them in hilarious scenes or rounding them with really good jokes. Even more: If had lasted half, the final discussion between Dante and Randal scene is full of successes, interesting reflections, and gives the key to enjoy?Clerks 2?: a romantic comedy gay (or Brian?)Halloran and Jeff Anderson want more than either of the two and any girl) where the character of Rosario Dawson is an absolute and impostado pad. The problem is that it seems that, for the director of?Does Jersey Girl?, maturity can only come by the way of the marriage and parenthood. E equal to that I said this about Eduardo Noriega when writing about?Do do Alatriste?, have to say about this awesome woman: often sacrifice marry Rosario Dawson.Y Yes, I know this is getting into ideological issues of each, and that Kevin Smith has every right to think very conservative? it is, although it garnish his proclamations of nerd jokes?. The problem comes when this conservatism leads you to make clumsy, fake, script decisions impeding the pace and that make you want to wait for the next moment in which Randal, Jay and Silent Bob make a new cafrada.The final balance, in short, is positive. Kevin Smith has made his second best film and removing to Rosario Dawson, has written the best and more affectionate updating possible for its mythical characters. The final sequence, surely, even to those who, at the time we enjoy with?Clerks?. I would even say more: I am surprised is not produce a big applause, as also deserves it the fun opening scene. ?Clerks? was a single film that will not return, although it was true that he deserved to be among the films more overvalued in the history of the cinema, but?Clerks II? It is what is called aging with dignity.</body>
</review>
