<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="El verano de kikujiro" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Kitano builds a beautiful minimalist fable. A film delicious and extremely fun, not without moments of great cinema. The very best of recent Japanese cinema.</summary>
	<body>Masao (Yusuke Sekiguchi) lives with her grandmother. One day finds a photo of his mother and decides to look for her. But Masao may not travel alone, so a friend of her grandmother, Kikujiro, offers to help you in your search. It seems the ideal company is an accustomed to easy money type and is not equipped to deal with children and less with a child as sensitive as the small Masao. But he will soon reveal that both have in common more than it seems; Masao will discover that the world is meaningless without a bit of magic and Kikujiro learn that sometimes, a simple game of children teaches us what does not work in our own lives. Reminiscent of Jacques Tati "my uncle" or "The boy" by Charles Chaplin, in 1999, Takeshi Kitano, finished his eighth film: "The summer of Kikujiro". After his previous films police forces and full of violence that did not exempt his personal humor, such as "Sonatine" or the award-winning "Hana-Bi (fire flower)", in "The summer of Kikujiro" departs from this kind of film, to deliver us a delicious comedy full of vitality and message. It is a road movie that joins comedy with drama in an exemplary manner. The film opens with an image of Masao crossing a long bridge in the city of Tokyo (where we can see that it has already been the Angel Wings, which gave him a few puppeteers, hung his backpack) and from there occurs a huge flashback we are dealing with the rest of the film until the end. Kitano separates the film in various episodes as if it were summer Masao book. These episodes are the following: the friends of the grandmother, the man that is scary, the Lord is very rare, it went wrong, the Bell's Angels, the Lord play with me, the Lord falls down the stairs, the Octopus man, goodbye. Masao crossing the summer puenteLlega and Masao, a child of 8 years, only stays in the city. He lives with his grandmother who works and his mother lives outside working to earn money for him so his grandmother tells him that he must study hard and strive, to part him her has ever. To make matters worse, his friends as Yuji leave vacation to the beach with their respective families. The poor Masao suspected that this summer will be a boredom, a summer full of loneliness and boredom (see the bleak scene of the field of football and the mockery that makes the man going by bicycle (one of the almost ubiquitous things in the Filmography of Kitano) to Masao, who has gone there with his clothing and the ball). One day, while the grandmother was at work, comes the postman and gives a letter. To see her Masao, he sees that it is his mother. Point the direction, collect their savings and decides to look for her and finally meet her. The friends of his grandmother (Kikujiro and his wife), decide that he, Kikujiro, accompany Masao on his trip. Here us occurs to Kikujiro (Beat Takeshi) as a carefree man, without apparent task or work. We are told that he is a man without studies due to his laziness and already gives hints of his later proven arrogance, poor education and pimping rudeness. Kikujiro giving a lesson of irresponsibility, the first site where leads to Masao is bicycle racing. Bet all the money that has more saved by the child, and for more INRIA the only time they earn they spend it on sleep a night in a luxury hotel. There occurs the first dreams of Masao. Note that flat from within surrealist of the glass where the champagne is poured. Below you can see other somewhat risky planes such as the vision of the Dragonfly or the Masao and Kikujiro reflex on the wheel of a car. From there embark on a journey in search of the mother of Masao, Kikujiro will try by all means have fun and replace the misfortunes or disappointments for children's elements and actions that move between the chaplinesco and absurdity. Due to the spending of money given by his wife to Kikujiro more saved by Masao, both are aimed at pulular on the roads in search of someone to carry them or simply walk. Kitano in the film baby much silent film, large silent films such as Charles Chaplin or Buster Keaton. However, not leaves behind his more circus side and gives us a series of numbers to the purest style humor amarilloque plays with absurdity more radical and sometimes surreal. Kikujiro and Masao by the caminosEn initially, Masao does not trust the Lord, which is how he calls Kikujiro. Kikujiro has shown his lack of maturity despite their midlife, looks almost like a cartoon character, like something strange to know, thanks in part to immature actions committed as bets, the robbery of a taxi, stepping on the grass ignoring the poster which small is not, fishing in a pond of a hotelconfronted with a trucker, impersonate blind, leave the hotel without paying and a long etcetera of circumstances and situations unbecoming of a man of that age and more so if it is in charge of a small. As you will see later, this trip will be a lesson not only for Masao, but also for Kikujiro, which reencontrará about yourself. See that phrase that says Kikujiro when are at the bus stop: "Is very similar to me". The second dream of Masao in this case starring the man that is scary (a pederast who attempted to harass the poor Masao), as if wanting him to do harm, to his side a woman (perhaps representing much sought after mother) which cries and finally the man resembles the back of Kikujiro tattoo, this is evident that crossfade between the tattoo image and the onset of sleep. It comes to say as if also Kikujiro has 2 personalities or faces in life. Kikujiro may have solution and can change and be responsible for something. In subsequent dreams can be seen as the Lord (Kikujiro) adopts a position privileged in them, already trying to an important person and trust in the life of Masao. Second dream of MasaoLa Kikujiro attitude with the characters of this film, so grotesque and way is at least unlikely. Perhaps the fantastic touch of the story and above all the fact of being at the bottom of a fable (remember explained or remembered by Masao, child), explain this. Or perhaps explain it to his last yakuza. In "The summer of Kikujiro" we can see easily 2 clear tributes, one of them very clear. After sticking with a trucker and leave with Masao with a few puppeteers in his car, there is a transition from the stick to the Orange, that reminds us inevitably to the mythical scene of "2001: A Space Odyssey", the scene of what is the tool, its importance and its usefulness. In a transition or ellipsis, of course, shorter, simpler and less elaborate than in the Kubrick film. Another homage is to "Kagemusha". Masao dreams remind us of the dreams of the ersatz in the Kurosawa film. Kitano is a self-confessed fan of Akira Kurosawa. Going through a bridge, after having left the poet. Fishing in the pond of the hotel. Waiting, call for Kikujiro: "the oldest bus stop in the world" when they finally come to the place where supposedly have to find the mother of Masao, produces one of the most beautiful scenes of the film. In fact, there already does not live his mother, and the pessimism and the sadness seizes Masao fleeing towards the Sea (another key element in the Filmography of Kitano and pillar of films like e.g. "Hana-Bi" or "A Scene at the be"). Kikujiro will then make you a gift and will earn part of the affection of Masao. In this case, the deception will be pious not as in none of the previous occasions, it tells that it is a gift that has left him his mother, when it is not. Face of disappointments of Masao and Kikujiro after the frustrated encounter with his mother. The moment when they leave the beach and decide to return home. In the final section of the film, both are in circumstantial camping accompanied by calls Mr. Nice (a poet who rediscovered it after having them removed from the bus stop) and Mr. Gordo and Mr. Bald (naive motorists). And here begins the festival of humor yellow made in Kitano full of absurdidades and children's playground only to remove head to Masao anguish that causes him not knowing again where is his mother and above all not be able seeing. And Kikujiro "abused them" using them as "soccer ball" so that the child have fun as for example: motorists making fish, Octopus (for fish that the river no longer fish), games with strings, the Indians, game if I see you pay garment, dress extraterrestrial, &hellip;. and many more kitanianas squalor. And it is to these characters, Kitano, it presents them as clumsy, naive, deluded, but with great background and a heart which do not mind losing their dignity as that Masao laugh and you have big. Masao playing a game with these unique cartoon in the world kitaniano. In this section there is a paragraph where Kikujiro takes a moment to visit his mother which is entered in a residence or hospital relatively close to the place of the campsite. When he sees, Kikujiro enters a state similar to which had been Masao after the disappointment caused by the expectation frustrated to see his mother. And begins to give account that have to change their attitude to life and others. At the end of the film in a scene to remember, Masao asks to the until now called Mr which is his real name, and this tells Kikujiro. And he promises that they will return back to find his mother. Nice, the poet. Kitano became interested in painting after the serious accident suffered by a few years ago. "Hana-Bi", even in "Battle Royale" appear in some of his paintings. It has been a journey of learning for both very fruitful. They have proven although it seemed that initially they had nothing in common, at the end seems to be that it was not true. It is the beginning of a friendship and mutual affection. The film itself, represents a lesson important Masao: that there are to keep fighting for want you without leaving it be. To Kikujiro journey has taught him that it is able to deal with someone, take responsibility for something if you want to. Initially, seemed the least suitable person to accompany the small but despite the difficulties and the irresponsible committed by him it has complied with the deal agreed with his wife. And it is that sometimes a simple child's play teaches one what does not work in his own life. Both left and 2 unknown with so many things in common unknown to the 2, as for example that both adore their mothers feel unable to be with them. In the circumstantial camping. The fact that the voyage in question has been more important for Kikujiro to Masao, who I think it is obvious, it is also reflected in the title of the film, when the protagonist is apparently Masao and is for him to be both travel. In "The summer of Kikujiro", the music is borne by one of the illustrious contributors to Kitano: Joe Hisaishi (which has also incidentally, composed for the Studio Ghibli films directed by the great Hayao Miyazaki). A melody that unites simplicity with quality which inevitably produces nostalgia. Along with Kenji Kawai ("Avalon", "Princess Blade", "Ghost in the shell", "Innocence"), one of the best composers of current Japanese soundtracks. The main theme is one of the best scores of Hisaishi so far. As an anecdote to say that partly this film is a tribute to the father of Takeshi Kitano, curiously named Kikujiro. The relationship that occur in the film between Masao and Kikujiro is similar, only it is partly clear. His father, seems to be that it was a distant person, with little relation to his son (Takeshi), we saw as a hard character but with a good heart as the film Kikujiro (ex-yakuza problematic and insultón but with a great heart and ultimately an exceptional person). In conclusion, "The summer of Kikujiro" is a beautiful, minimalist fable and that it will please all audiences for the first time in a movie of Kitano, since they are usual Eastern film or not, because what it conveys is a universal message and uses a language (except in the dreams of Masao) linial and without too many narrative uses as abstract as in the majority of his remaining filmography. And another thing to keep in mind, the violence is practically non-existent in this film. Kitano always surprises us in every one of his movies. It is capable of making films with large doses of violence, comical or chambara and succeed in the attempt, and I think that we we have one of the best filmmakers of today and possibly history. A film delicious and extremely fun, not without moments of great cinema. </body>
</review>
