<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El espía" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Icy, it requires little risky, is left wanting for a cleanly filmmaking, which like and repels at the time.</summary>
	<body>Breach, crack in English, is a formidable title. The spy has been awarded, to the detriment, some topics. Simple and flat, earn interest in the extraordinary performance of Chris Cooper, a traitor that swings between the Catholic fundamentalist, porn, Catherine Zeta-Jones and the curiosity of being the mole and desenmascarle encargardo. The rookie officer that nearby (Ryan Philippe) involves too much and just zarandeado by side effects of a life consecrated to the service of the fatherland. Nothing new: federal agent lacks family, cannot maintain stable relationships, just staying in generous limbo and reliable alcohol and arises to abandon their work. The argument is overused, and will not only by one ahead of the plot but it inevitably closes before the splendid and already Tacitus The End us back to reality. And despite this litany of Puya, the Spy is not a bad film. It has enough charms as to merit some attention and give the honors its stylistic, mathematical, objectively, sparsely rich in nuances, he claims. What is new, what her extracted from the tedium, something that plays to their benefit, is the religious side and the weight of the characters. The mole, the unsurpassed spy dies inside: what fulminates daily his Catholic advocation, his consecration to a faith that does not stop the slow dismantling of national security, the dispatch scheduled and clean of secrets for 22 years to Soviet intelligence. This is remarkable: that a spy film obvious topics and will take the possibility dramaturgical that the viewer at a particular time creates watching a religious film or at least one of spiritual contradictions, a of those that explore the agony and the ecstasy (Carol Reed in memory) of whom scales between the obedience of a creed and the ancestral betrayal palpitationdouble life and all that predictable underworld poachers delights. A neat political cleaning (an officer removed a portrait of Clinton and puts Bush's, there is no excessive verbal attacks to the domes of power) the Spy is not ambiguous, or stays in the hint - signs of other spies film more burdened by the showmanship and the mix of action and moral implications to the Bourne or Ethan Hunt mode -confined to the operation that trapped the Betrayer. This moral cleanliness is managed with impeccable photography of Tak Fujimoto (signals, the sixth sense), which sows the sadness with his cold, perfect colouring to build the credibility of the offices, where most of the film takes place. The construction of the plot, which grows with delinquencies reaching an icy, necessarily expected outcome is also clean.Cold and aseptic, spy assumes the rules of the game film without visible effort, without the contest of twists in the plot or in his speech: the direction of Billy Ray (screenwriter of Flight Plan: Desaparecida or know what hicísteis last summer) is thorough, too much hampered by a desire to be artisan and ensure sobriety to what, in appearance, perhaps would have required a more flexible hand, a director of higher risk. Although well seen, other times call for just the opposite: restraint, restraint. Here Ray displays it with Office and proposes a show worthy, entertaining, which is missing a point of warmth, despite the remarkable interpretation of Cooper (what more sad man, by God), which makes of tormented as nobody in recent American cinema (American Beauty) and spare you time, intellect. Perhaps that its charm, which makes that not can one regret his viewing. At all. Is, in any case, find the reasons for the informing, the inventory of excuses to justify the felony of a professional mature, Catholic comprehensive, accepting the charges and public defenestration without revealing what moved him, if the money, the temptation to lead a double life or a conducive exacerbated patriotism to demonstrate laxity of the State when it comes to care for their childrenthe crack under the original English.</body>
</review>
