<review author="José A. Peig" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Alex de la Iglesia handles the staging and the film has a couple of planes quite memorable sequence. Shame that everything is in a capricious and self-indulgent, set in an indefinite dramatic tone, and an unfinished when not incoherent philosophical discourse.</summary>
	<body>Films defined its quality by the strength that we see in used tones and forms. It is not enough to have an interesting story if filmmaker does not apply an efficient look between hands. The new film by Alex de la Iglesia is a good example of mutual distortion between the conceptual basis of the story (fairly dense, complex) and the playful objective pursued, akin to the classic thriller and the features that better define the genre of suspense, placing the viewer in a puzzle of characters and data coming to be codes, the material to follow the proposed game. Combine these two facets was meritorious and of course the film implies a risk welcome in the times. We do not know the text in which it was inspired, but have a feeling that the writers - in an attempt to synthesize the history so that it can be more accessible to all audiences - have failed to come up with appropriate scheme and development, so we have a very loose and runnig script. Being a product that plays with the keys and the mythology of the genre in order to create a particular effect (surprise), it is more predictable. The same characterization of the characters and - above all - the presentation already pointing to some obvious resolutions for any attentive spectator and connoisseur of the keys of the genus. The different nut laps that appear in the final stretch not transcend that range of possibilities. Therefore, where this surprise?.On the other hand, intended as a fun work, you cannot find the necessary fluidity in a dispersed development due to excessive exposure of philosophical and mathematical concepts. It is not lawful to devote so much footage to this type of elements (which are otherwise unavoidable in the construction of the meaning of this story) without that the viewer can be part of this. Obviously, it is not explained or require the viewer knowledge about mathematics and Pythagorean philosophy. It is a problem about implementing an effective look, rhythm, tempo, synthesize this data set so that it is articulated in a certain dramatic exhibition. In sum, narrative agility. And what we have here is a narrative too thick.In its abstract content and philosophical discourse it sinks in a mere statement of concepts which ends in inconsistencies. This film talks about senses or absence of them, indeterminacy, causality or chaos. Solve the riddle of a crime depends on know your patterns that guide the conduct of the murderer. If there is an implicit order that governs the universe, we can predict and modify the flow of events. The speech - represented chiefly in Professor Arthur Seldom (John Hurt) - points to the unknowable nature of a universe ruled by chance.Curiously, the final scene is intended to emphasize the truth of thought of Seldom, with Elijah Wood doing propiciatoria victim, the butterfly that flaps the wings and determines the development of the story. Indeed, in the universe, there is an implicit order (and we know, and therefore, there is no chance), which produces an inconsistency delves into the story, and is at this point where most notices that the writers play capriciously with items without specified a meaning and a dramatic tone. Worst of all is the last level, the expression of surprise in the face of Elijah, which aims to reflect the (unprompted to effects inherent in the film material) surprise the Viewer. The expressiveness of his eyes was never so badly used.Certainly Alex de la Iglesia handles the staging and the film has a couple of levels quite memorable sequence. Shame that everything is in a capricious and self-indulgent, set in an indefinite dramatic tone, and an unfinished when not incoherent philosophical discourse.</body>
</review>
