<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="En el valle de Elah" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the Valley of Elah, the new masterpiece of Paul Haggis, dissects with great poise, restraint and without a drop of cynicism the devastating effects of the Iraq war in American society.</summary>
	<body>Less than four years ago, Paul Haggis caused an earthquake in the world of cinema with Crash, his first film as director. From one of the scripts more humane, exciting and full of truth of recent years, Haggis built one of those memorable films, which are themselves in film history, and remain in the collective memory.After a few years in which has developed over his facet as writer, leaving its mark in films such as flags of our fathers, letters from Iwo Jima or Casino Royale, Paul Haggis presents his second film as director. Entry you have to praise the courage of Paul Haggis to deal with something so hard and thorny as the war in Iraq, roundly view from the perspective of young soldiers coming home. The research that a father carries out to unravel the mysterious disappearance of his son is used by Haggis to portray an American living content of war horror and the terrible consequences on those who participated in it. And does so without looking distorted the facts count, rejecting the bombast and focusing on a small community, a microcosm that refelja the reality of society as a whole. It is a harsh and harrowing, film that has moments of an extraordinary emotion, capable of putting out of breath up to the coldest Viewer. And when the story seems to have concluded, Paul Haggis gives that wonderful flat end, which sums up the feeling of the film. Of course, interpretative level of the tape is very high, with some extraordinary Tommy Lee Jones, Charlize Theron and Susan Sarandon.En the Valley of Elah, Paul Haggis's new masterpiece, dissects with great poise, restraint and without a drop of cynicism the devastating effects of the Iraq war in American society. It's a great film, bashed in his country and unjustly forgotten face award.</body>
</review>
