<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="88 Minutos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Correct thriller to overal that keeps the viewer's attention mainly due to the relative difficulty of finding out who is really behind the whole shebang against the protagonist. It premièred in cinemas not be Pacino?</summary>
	<body>Dr. Jack Gramm (to Al Pacino) is a University professor who also works as a forensic psychiatrist for the FBI. Few hours before that carried out the execution of a prisoner imprisoned because of their work, Gramm receives a call threatening him are only eighty-eight minutes of life. So, in little more than an hour and twenty should find out who wants him dead, and try and save his life.They are not few those who argue that in recent years, to find good American cinema in stores must go to the section "television series", where products of highest level such as "Lost", "Alias", or "24" are. Precisely the starring Kiefer Sutherland is the more footprint has left on screen (large or small), because its innovative montage and his revolutionary scripts begin to be emulated with increasingly more often.And "88 minutes" is a clear example of this.In fact, many are similar (almost plagiarism) between the film, incidentally directed by Jon Avnet, and the legendary series. Obviously, the first of them is the choice of telling the story in real time (or almost) with some element which constantly reminds us of the intervening minutes. That television screenshots were black with a thunderous digital counting clock seconds, on this occasion are calls Recalling life which fits with the protagonist. This resource serves to influence certain feeling of strain during the footage, and indeed it does, but much less so in the same way that happened in "24" (and is perhaps one thing keep that frenetic pace during the forty minutes of length of a chapter, and another do it into a feature film).More blatant is still the character of Pacino, Jack Bauer into something else in years, but with the same characteristics, since their interrelation with the rest of characters (Dr. Gramm is passed almost the entire film glued to the phone, just one), the way of solving their problems, the mistrust which sometimes generates his character, and even your tone of voice.In fact, this is not negative, that without elements such the film would be lost without remission, becoming a forgettable as bland as a little stimulant thriller. Because there is nothing to highlight it.The script is quite conservative and is dedicated to moving by the most hackneyed clichés of the genre. It is a correct history to find out who is the bad guy, but nothing more. Appreciated the large amount of dialogue containing the film (that even though they cause more than one slump of pace, her apart from the rest of products nowadays), especially the last which Pacino maintains with one of his students, in which leaves an open very difficult to answer question, but apart from this there is absolutely nothing more remarkable.Nor can praise is too actions, because all seem apathetic and desganados, carrying out monotonous work except for some time Pacino (phone talk--as non-with the sentenced to death). Negatively highlights the presence of Leelee Sobieski, whose character does not change its facial expression, either in class or being attacked.But in reality, the real problem with "88 minutes" lies in the direction. A director with something more than mordant (Michael Mann, for example) it would have perhaps been able to build a far more stimulating work, but Jon Avnet signs a film completely impersonal, without a single plane that can remember five minutes of finishing the viewing, a dangerous scent of this tv-movie from the first minute. A real waste.In short, "88 minutes" is a correct thriller to overal that keeps the viewer's attention mainly due to the relative difficulty of finding out who is really behind the whole shebang against the protagonist. However, the approach of certain questions cannot be avoided. There would be this film does not exist "24"? This genus of small to big screen translation needed? And the most important is premièred in cinemas not have the presence of Al Pacino?</body>
</review>
