<review author="Luna" title="La boda de Tuya" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A twisted story without artificial realization, Wang Quan'an creates a masterpiece that speaks directly to our hearts.</summary>
	<body>Dir: Wang Quan'anInt: Yu Nan, battery, Senge, Peng Hongxiang, Zhaya arrived at the Berlin Festival with his sincere nature and naturalism achieved and took, as well as the hearts of the jury, the Golden bear of the 57 Edition of this festival.It does not have a complicated script of convoluted story, but quite the opposite. This Chinese film tells the vicissitudes of yours, a young woman that cares for her children from her invalid husband of livestock in a region of Mongolia. She is strong and is tanned in the hard physical work, but their body deteriorates. If don't want to die (and his family) must divorce her husband (who loves) and find a new husband that can be responsible for the family.Wang Quan'an ' an not used artificial realization for telling the story, they resorted to the less complex motto better. Abound the flat long, camera in hand to feel the greatest spectator verismo, and balanced compositions.It has a minimalist aesthetic, but strong colors and striking elements of culture where elapses the story, which are visually stunning to the Western Viewer.All this is the wrapper that presents this little masterpiece. Really admirable of this story are the great verismo of interpretations and the fact that it is one of those movies that you come direct to the heart and are a breath of fresh air on the Bulletin Board, saturated with topical and boring films. They could already learn certain screenwriters and directors of this film and the motto less is more. Hollywood should be noted that the important thing are not the great Artifice, nor the most luminous Fireworks. Important thing is to have a story to tell and tell the tale with the heart. And that is what succeeds admirably well Wang Quan'an. A touching story that allows us to sneak in the experiences of other coetaneas realities from ours and gives us a small pill of wisdom: it seems that you will make happy is not always what will make you happy.Not let escape this film of Billboard, which although it has been since October in poster, in January still filling the room in which it is projected.</body>
</review>
