<review author="Dragon negro" title="La criatura perfecta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An interesting proposal that despite to have offered more, stays in a film is especially recommended for lovers of the genre as a curiosity.</summary>
	<body>Glenn Standring brings us his second film, from the first, one unknown the Irrefutable truth about the demon, six years have passed, clear that we must also take into account that which we are discussing dates back to 2006 and are already entered in 2008. This is a co-production between United Kingdom and New Zealand and counts with the presence of the known Saffron Burrows giving something more than output to this moderate budget film.We are in an alternate world where vampires live in harmony with humans. 300 Years ago, an alchemist who was studying genetics believe this superior race, as well as a myriad of pests and diseases, after which the use of genetics was banned worldwide. This new race was aposentando and creating to your around a sort of religion and acting as if they were priests. They are feared and idolized equally among human beings in the current era is situated where the history, that would be a beginning of XX century with retro-futuristas touches. These 300 years never before a vampire had taken a human life, even if their livelihood is the blood, this is donated by the faithful followers of the religion. But now one of them is killing people, and will be the appointed his own brother to catch him, it will also have the help of the police. Dark secrets that keeps the brotherhood of vampires inside Iran uncovering during the investigation.We must assume that we are dealing with a product away from the Hollywood machinery and that it has a moderate budget with which his mise en scène although effective, is really poor. Anyway, is this one of its best assets as well as an initial approach that promises quite and proposes a new situation in the relationship between man and vampires of which we are accustomed to seeing. But against we have a development of rather poor history and severely limited that accuses excessive lack of pretensions and personality, also next joined the little claw that put the actors in their respective roles. The good idea will deflate slowly without knowing seize it or take full advantage of it.Anyway nor what it would consider a crappy or anything, but an interesting proposal despite to have offered more, stays in a film is especially recommended for lovers of the genre as a curiosity and in general as a counterpoint to the films fantastic American and that no mistake, are neither nor by far much more recommended that is before us.</body>
</review>
