<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great movie, a story that choose to play in the field of intellectual, finally same if laughing in a macabre way, with some solvents actors (which is not little) and above all a strong and effective staging.</summary>
	<body>Sensed in the promising career, and already consecrated bilbaino director Alex de la Iglesia, a capacity to tackle greater challenges which they had enjoyed so far. His previous films, from that first-time "mutant action", through work at the service of the popular Santiago Segura or El Gran Wyoming as "The day of the beast" and "Dead of laughter", were productions where already showed an innate talent to create his own world full of lovable losers, without the slightest interest in being drawn by prevailing fashions and so able to arouse in the viewer a sympathetic emotional affiliation. Then changed maybe a little third, resulting in their most elaborate film with more class in the implementation stage and films as "Community", "800 bullets" (endearing tribute to the spaghetti western, defined by himself as marmitako western) or "crime ferpecto"(este_último_quizás_uno_de_sus_peores_films_en_mi_opinión) represented a step forward with regard to earlier work (ignoring the failed RAID by the back door of American cinema which meant "Perdita Durango"), while retaining that special touch that shows his film. Perhaps the biggest problem of all those tapes was precisely the own demarcation imposed by the filmmaker, almost always resulting in too parochial, with a humorous little given to cross borders and deliberately geek (in the loving sense of the term). For a server, always entrusted in the capacity of this filmmaker to be eligible to larger companies, to his latest work, "The crimes of Oxford", is the definitive consecration, and let us hope that a road to travel regularly in their future projects (whose capacity already showed in his excellent episode for "movies to not sleep").Church leaves its limited common areas on one side and he embarked full in international cinema, showing signs of being a skilled craftsman (remember that this term has been forgotten by the terrible work of filmmakers without talent), a creator can be passionate in their work and create intelligent entertainment products.The plot of the film shows how Martin (Elijah Wood) is preparing to create his final mathematics thesis with the help of Professor Arthur Seldom (John Hurt), being too optimistic hope, given that the Professor, is a taciturn, apathetic and lacking the minimal sense of emotional empathy with fellow human beings. Martin, whose only visit to Oxford from his native United States, is due to this purpose, looks like the death of the elderly that inhabits the House which houses himself, makes the intellectual Union with the Professor Seldom a fact, with the intention of resolving a series of crimes that occurred after the death together.Remarkable work in the direction of Alex de la Iglesia, always framing the view at the time and the exact location, some visual, clearly identifiable with the large capacity of the Basque filmmaker to create scenes close to the Viewer, and to help advance the story. Even allows some luxuries where da sample of the technical mastery to which we are accustomed, as that plane sequence in the streets of the small town, where is presenting the daily routines of the series of main characters that populate so dismal town.Helped, if, by an intelligent screenplay (in collaboration with its usual writer Jorge Guerricaechevarría, based on the novel by Guillermo Martinez), a meticulous and progressive penetration into the mathematical foundations, theorems, and above all, on how all this affects the relationship of the possibly and its alienation from the world outside them two. It is precisely in the elaboration of such a relationship where the libretto becomes his best trasladación to the screen, that helped if, for effective work of actors, especially the incombustible John Hurt, no doubt, and despite the intended coldness of interpretation, the best of the cast, leaving perhaps only in correct the work of Elijah Wood as Martin, something that on the other hand, expected before such unfair confrontation of talents. The female roles pass to a second level, being mere comparsas of the investigations carried out by the master and his apt and inteligentísimo student, as both Leoner Watling (more pending offer carnality than anything else) and Julie Cox, should lift underdeveloped roles (although still Cox quite better than Watling as to credibility of the role).There is precisely one word that describes perfectly the tone of the history, the coldness which referred above. Will surely be the sensation causing many viewers this story, most outstanding of the mathematical technical aspect that do pass the story of fluently through the advancement of tangible action and not so much of the own discovery of the intellect. Of the Church, it seems to care little gloat was in duels on knowledge, if same and insurance of the mental depth with its fascinating history. There lies the real conflict of the film, to enter or not as a spectator to the interest which could lead to the supposedly intellectual aspect (some call it pretentious, I do not), which, truth be told, caused me an unusual interest, taking into account the banality and look flat and predictable most recent film productions. The choice between passion or brain of the Church has opted for the second, with highly satisfactory results.There is no doubt that in addition, this great movie very much reminds others developed in similar areas, with influences which reach to remember works of discovery criminal as the films at the service of the charismatic Hercules Poirot, the adorable Miss Marple or even the giallo more cold and brain, in contrast of the other so dramatic. With certain notes of the renowned British producer film Ealing (as bright in that kid humor presiding works such as "The ladykillers" or "Eight statements of death"), from which it takes borrowed certain bright touches of ironic humor, as the resolution itself in the history it without gutting the end, offers the largest joke macabre history. After such a demonstration of privileged intelligence by both characters, where reason and mathematics were imposed in all their decisions, just as uncontrollable passion paths that give with the key in the history, in a brilliant final sketch of this great director.And while it is true that the end of the story closes with some light theatrical, a twist of script that leaves some loose ends that probably would have no place in a completely logical analysis, let us not forget that this is precisely the final moral of the story, the loose, as decisions motivas by heart, they are always randomly.In short, a great movie, a story that choose to play in the field of intellectual, finally same if laughing in a macabre way, with some solvents actors (which is not little) and above all a strong and effective, staging a remarkable thriller which proves that a talent Manager, custom products become intelligent entertainment.</body>
</review>
