<review author="Yul B." title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Miami Vice is not the best work of Michael Mann. Sometimes slow, but never boring for those who enjoy stories of policemen with easy trigger.</summary>
	<body>I would have preferred that Michael Mann, architect of the magnificent Heat and Collateral, had not gotten into this trouble. Start this project with the slab series tv screen is too much. Many prejudices when comparing a product of the 1980s had his grace with a pure style Mann action film, understanding this style as radically different from the spirit of the series.To understand what I say unto you, a note: the city of Miami appears in the first twenty minutes and the last twenty. Something unusual if we talk about what is the essence of the original Miami Vice. There are no patinadoras blondes of day or latinos in the beaches toast is. Action occurs at night in most of the film, and also serves to show the night life of the city. Put him corruption in L.A. and is equal.Therefore, and after a few minutes scanning a relative comparison to the series, ends one convince you forget better and the Portas names are thus as a matter of marketing. We are going to see a movie of Michael Mann, and point action.A from there, everything looks better: the atmosphere of the film is tremendous, Mann handles the camera as if it were a documentary that accompanies those policemen who appear in television. Repeat this formula for Collateral do so fast-paced action.The plot is the basic narcos-polis: Crockett and Rico will infiltrate as carriers in a network of Colombian drug traffickers to get to the man, which does not allow many jueguecitos. All telling you more would only serve to destroy you with the rhythm of the film.Okay that the script is nothing out of this world, but the skill of Mann with the light and the camera give a different dimension to what had been with another director. Perhaps lacks that kind of action and pace that is inherent in the summer blockbusters, but let us not be mistaken, this is not a blockbuster. That is the slab that I mean when you add a well-known name.Colin Farrel as deadpan as always. It has the same face as in Swat. Without a doubt the best quotes them has been Jamie Foxx, and is that more force radiates from this duo. Farrell is not my favorite actor, and this film has not done enough to change my opinion. Foxx is not you leave either, but at least he looks much more involved and human. Farrel seems doing trabajitos of fontaneríaY to say about Luis Tosar. What a face of ca **, because I have no other adjective. Mejorcito of the cast, and no it is by sweep for House. This guy has taken the opportunity of working with Mann and do so splendid way, not like others. Girls I am not, because there is not much. With the warm Miami expect see more meat, but Mann has not thought the same thing. Gong Li seems too cold for the role, and when he joins Farrel already is the peak of the ice age.Only one thing bothers me: like milk are so lined the Miami Cops. Not only in this film. Two policemen rebels: lined. C.S.I. Miami: lined. Crockett and Tubbs driving through the streets of Miami a mmorg that since it would like the cops in my neighborhood. Nor is there time to disheveled or stain. The two protagonists wear suits whatever you do just fresh. If it is final Vice.En Miami, and with a longer last summer only has given us trouble, Miami Vice is not the best work of Michael Mann. Sometimes slow, but never boring for those who enjoy stories of policemen with easy trigger. A renewal to the memory that was the series, where the only thing that remains is the name.</body>
</review>
