<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="Habitación sin salida" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The tape, although entertaining, committing some unforgivable errors: abuse of the close-up, play with the spectator, trying to create tension so vulgar and dramatic, the improbability and predictability.</summary>
	<body>There is no doubt that the horror genre is one of the hardest in the times. Every year we have the misfortune of having to endure products of the more chusquero drink in excess of superior works, without owning any interest for the avid Viewer. And that would be the case of the tape in question, because not only it brings nothing new to the genre but that above at any time the viewer can empathize with the protagonists, by importing a real green pepper happens them or stop moving, and that has crime.Putting on record of the few lights in a script filled with well-worn situations, the relationship between the protagonists: Luke Wilson and Kate Beckinsale, is already taken with pins and ultimately very badly built. Since those initial minutes that seem to be there to present his personal and loving situation - topic among topics within the (bad) current thriller - and during the rest of the footage, both the character of Luke Wilson as the Beckinsale are pure stereotypes of by-products to which we are accustomed the tireless and dubious quality Screen Gems, subsidiary of Sony Pictures.A part of the bad construction of the characters, tension and enemies (rather than unsettle, arriving in hastiar the viewer thirsty something decent), the direction of the Hungarian Antal, certainly leaves to be desired. That not only there is not one thing original or worth mentioning in his speech, but above the Ribbon has one of the endings precipitated more implausible and the crappy dessert a humble servant has been suffering in a movie theater.Following Antal, giving cane here believe "Room no exit (Vacancy)" could have been an estimable tape if I had one iota of risk and more dusty gore (see to see if the director Rob Zombie!) and part of the blame we are in the realization of the brother of Puskás. We agree that this project was a Commission aimed at box office with little to negotiate, but that does not mean that you can not get a poquillo of oil to the matter. And is that tape committing some of the things that I hate and not forgive more: abuse of the close-up, play with the spectator, trying to create tension so vulgar and easy, the improbability and predictability.However, the tape is entertaining and enjoyable, but too predictable and glib. The enemy (s) is discovered immediately, is unattractive for lovers of the genre and we still wonder why it takes so much to Act (well, of course, but the film would last 30 minutes). Everything is very unrealistic and poor but above and to make matters worse it isn't a nice Ribbon. What could have been an interesting tape around the snuff phenomenon and the possibilities that gives a room of an isolated motel, the solution of escape via the dialogue between them or through the display continued the tape looking for tests or methods and a hostile enemy lurking nearby, finally gets a very conventional tapemore close to the style of films such as "Never play with strangers" (John Dahl, 2001) that of other more interesting (than not good) as a "Thesis" of our Alejandrito.La photography of the film carried out by Polish Sekula shows grim environments certainly improved lighting, nothing to do with the work of other early operators such as Darius Khondji, or Harris Savides, which appear to move with better ease and precision in sordid and dark environments. With regard to the score of Paul Haslinger, very typical and little talented.The film should have opted for the psychological thriller rather than by the game of cat and mouse. This is his great failure, its stereotyped approach, knot and outcome, looking for a surprise and a shock never arriving because the mechanisms for achieving them are pure theatrical cheap.Another piece of the genre to rule out of our collection of jewels of suspense-terror. But good friends, do not worry, because we were always wonderful classical tapes, those of the Hammer or contemporary works of filmmakers of the caliber of Fincher, Shyamalan or by some underrated Rob Zombie. Hopefully the proportion of current genre cinema quality was the reverse: every ten films, notable eight. But we all know that, sadly, nowadays is a utopia.</body>
</review>
