<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is one example of talent after cameras by Álex de la Iglesia. Perhaps lack a pinch of canallismo to the tape, and perhaps also a booklet with a best finish, but no one takes away that is both targeted and told.</summary>
	<body>While it is true, it went with some fear to the movies to see the latest work by Alex friend still had in mind that awful trailer (with its horrendous installation), but also with some degree of hope given the approval of some movie fan confidence people that already her had been able to watch. And though it has some details that do not convince me, we have a film with a rhythm, a narrative and a direction certainly remarkable. Once again, of the Church (1) demonstrates the good artisan it is and I think that it is not unreasonable to say that it is one of the directors with more sense of rhythm and more agile on the national scene, in addition to being a very good Narrator on images and above all, a guy with personality before the camera.Among the many qualities of "The Oxford murders", emphasizes the fact of being an extremely humble tape, nothing pretentious and proposed (apart from an irregular plot) a professors certainly worked and interesting relationship. Of the Church, in this film, opts for a classic speech, something to be welcomed, and gives images of true elegance, but without neglecting his own style, being able to stop certain (inches) touches very him. Alex has always been faithful to his side more Geek.The Basque filmmaker, in his film, pays a clear tribute to the great master of the genre (Hitchcock), themed as related to his figure as the false guilty, the blonde and the brunette (femme fatale), sensuality, disaffection and as no, Mc Guffin. But it also marks a flat sequence in the first murder, simply memorable, from those of guaranteed orgasm, Orson Welles Spanish going xDD.Y is fat and the actors work is well above what the script offers, especially in its final stretch, where fades everything a little. Obviously the interest has the plot of the film about the search for the truth through sound methods but it is somewhat unlikely that an experienced teacher and a pending his thesis student kept, at a first term of the tape, (dedicated to a wide audience) clarifying discussions which would have to have more than known given his condition. Of course, all this remains enough credibility to that part of the film and its characters. Even so, the tape perfectly maintains the attention of the viewer through a remarkable narrative structure. Let's be clear, the novel (and its adapted screenplay) is much improved, but much worse was submitted Goldsman to Sony entitled something bosses as well as "code Da Vinci" xD.Tanto John Hurt as Elijah Wood are great, but especially the first, with a remarkable presence on screen. They are average film. Michael Caine (first choice of the Church for the role of Professor Seldom) could also have done fabulous, but since then, John Hurt is to rise to the occasion.Also great are the side as Leonor Watling and Julie Cox. On it, say that of the Church becomes his character hard to beat sexual icon. Despite having a character purely "girl vase", the Watling transmits perfectly what his character means: sexuality, carnality, warmth. Scenes of squash or apron, do not have too much weight in the overall plot, but, without a doubt, assume an enjoyment for the viewer male or lesbian. What wonder woman! However, there is no chemistry between Watling and Wood, and sadly it shows. In French Dominique Pinon, it has a role although almost testimonial for the set.Other things to note are the elaborate score of Roque Baños debtor master Herrman, replete with string instruments. One of the Spanish composers I like, along with Alberto Iglesias. Photograph of Rica Kiko - which I loved his excellent work in "Sex and Lucia" - very consistent and effective.The film is one example of talent after Álex de la Iglesia cameras but also is of imperfection - globally - that surround some of his films, because they have not just been round. Perhaps lack a pinch of canallismo to the tape, and perhaps also a booklet with a best finish, but no one takes away that is both targeted and told.(1) Always found me a capable of the best and worst director. Creator of tapes as interesting as "Crime Ferpecto" (with a fast-paced and masterful initial part), "The community" (excellently shot and full of freak) "Perdita Durango" (his first and good jump international) or their more horny short "Killer Mirindas" (great Álex Angulo xD), but also works as the infumable minor "800 bullets" or other less interesting to predict what you out there: "The day of the beast" (which does not hold subsequent viewings, the humble point of view of a server).</body>
</review>
