<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lot of money well invested but little performance and originality. That is, very complacent and therefore somewhat disappointing. It had been a star more if it had not the burden of having an excellent Director somewhat untapped.</summary>
	<body>Arthur Seldom is a brilliant and surly British professor specializing in mathematics, Martin is a young American student who travels to Oxford in an attempt to convince him to lead his thesis. When it gives everything for lost a mysterious crime involves them in what looks like a murder in series in the quiet university town. It seems that almost all are suspects so work together to solve the mystery is your only solution.I am a little disappointed. I recognize that while many films of Alex de la Iglesia I don't like too much their own way of making films seems laudable. Why when I saw the crimes of Oxford I found a certain tension to not to see any moment of brilliance in his way of filming, no twist his no guided them to their previous tapes, no recognizable iconography &hellip; many directors recognize that make stories that aren't theirs makes them behave otherwise directing thing that can clearly apply to this film. I do not mean that the film is not good, it is. The problem, although he hates to tell is that it actually looks more to the DaVinci code than to a good thriller. A couple of attempts to unusual film looming just at the beginning of the footage as the plane sequence that leads to all the characters that ended up being the usual suspects of the tape just before the discovery of the first body, that was something intended to be bright but it is actually more a technical display than a narrative necessity. Something that will define the final result: money well spent but little performance and originality. That is, very complacent and therefore somewhat disappointing.He has good pace, a dash decent (although not to throw rockets) and a few players that work best for separate that altogether. Brilliant John Hurt (very funny point V of Vendetta), a little bland Elijah Wood and a rather unusual partner in Leonor Watling that despite to be correct and sensual fails to create an iota of chemistry with his film partner.It had been a star more if it had not the burden of having an excellent Director somewhat untapped.</body>
</review>
