<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Bitelchús" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Burton manages to have a desire to mad by giving us a tour of the another world or find us a couple of ghosts as close friends.</summary>
	<body>The directorial debut of Tim Burton big scare, we'll be with the work made to start to fall in love of the unique universe of this film Platypus.Back in 1986, after the premiere of "The Pee-Wee's big adventure" and su - for me entirely inexplicable - blockbuster in Usamérica, Burton had begun to work on a screenplay for the Warner on a possible adaptation of Batman for the big screen, but the project had not just receive total support from the company.At the same time, the director was looking for some script to adapt to their tastes, in order to build his second feature film, with very little fortune. Until, after a few years, it has reached your hands one written by Michael McDowell with the strange title "Beatlejuice" (later translated in our country as "Bitelchús"). As if by magic, the story concentrated imaginative way you discover with the passage of time as the great obsessions of the director: the death, the duality between the friendly world of ghosts and frightening and scary real world, eccentric and/or marginalized protagonists and the ability to innovate with special effects that knew to move their unique ideas from his bustling mind until the Viewer. Later, once the film, would also Visual elements that are repitirían over his filmography as a black and white striped costumes, models, cemeteries or if you look at the scene in which Betelgeuse appears with a hat shaped carousel, can see until Jack Skellington head atop.The creation of the final screenplay was a long and complicated process. The writer himself, Michael McDowell, along with a second writer, began trying to give shape to the kooky comedy full of unlikely characters and without defined structure, in addition to the own Burton trying to give their own vision and continued with the hiring of a third writer. But the true personality of Betelgeuse arose when Michael Keaton entered the draft and connected in full with the personality of the director. The charisma, sense of humour, improvisation, the taste for parody and Keaton energy were the true architects of the great character of the film and one of their greatest successes.The story of starting the tape is simple. A couple living in a huge House has an accident returning from the village and dies. From then on, converted into ghosts will be forced to adapt to his new situation, unable to leave his home and attempting to take to a family of yuppies coming from the city that can make his long eternal wait even more endless.In their excursions into the world of the dead know the bureaucracy of the other world, the catastrophic consequences of suicide to the bio-Exorcist hooligan, most irreverent, I marrano and ironic another sphere, or already in the living, eventually making friends with the daughter of the new inhabitants of the House, an adolescent depressive and trends suicide performed by Winona Ryder.En film Burton gives rein to his fertile imaginationghostly transformations are as grimosas as hilarious, the world of Hades is full of flat strangers and impossible perspectives and possessions become - as you said one of the characters - the experience in an amusement park. Burton manages to have a desire to mad by giving us a tour of the another world or find us a couple of ghosts as close friends.But above all, it is the powerful interpretation of a Michael Keaton full and tireless. A whirlwind that gives life to a unique, intimate and detestable character in equal parts, capable of being cruel in a fun way. A character who, despite not appearing in long sections of the film, steals the prominence to the rest of the actors in a disproportionate manner.Again, Burton chose Danny Elfman to compose the soundtrack, and as is the case with the director, Elfman shows its true potential composing a "score" as appropriate and resounding that turns into a character more than the movie.Ultimately, Burton second intrusion in the feature film was the confirmation of the director and, for some spectators, including myself, the beginning of an unwavering devotion to his filmography.</body>
</review>
