<review author="Lady Winter" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Impeccable in the aesthetic, but with too many gaps in development. It is long and lacks sufficient action to hook.</summary>
	<body>The expected and desired the film adaptation of the legendary Miami Vice television series is already among us with a final result that I doubt to meet fans of the original. Michael Mann signed a flawless film in the aesthetic, but with too many gaps in development. A history of action should not that the Viewer is bored and make your imagination too far from the room. This is the biggest mistake of Miami Vice: action scenes with other vapid that serve to unite one and another. But even the action is most common within this film of policemen. Except in the final scene, the shots are scarce as if there is a tremendous crisis in arms of blanks.Formulates it failure and feels terrible chapter too stretched. The best is, without doubt, Jamie Fox as Ricardo Tubbs, in his role as faithful follower of disposing of all of Sonny Crockett, played by Colin Farrell zarrapastroso that are chasing a china (rather than bad) during most of the footage. In the end, Miami Vice has become the loving pursuit of Sonny, which is limited to follow the dictates of their hormones showing that it is a rebel. A nonsense. As our Luis Tosar? What could we say? Let's say that it is correct. He plays the villain, a capo of the drug in Cuba who hires two policemen (incognito) to make a little. Tosar has a couple or three appearances shows him sober and content (didn't have to do much more). On the contrary, their Academy English seems good, perhaps too forced. But, what does it matter that if already folded you here with Cuban accent.It there is little to say about the film, which tells the typical police story style two rebel policemen. Tubbs and Crocketts must infiltrate a network of drug trafficking to finish with the greatest Chief of the market, but someone crosses on its way (a girl, clear) and everything is complicated. The story is that expected of a film as well, but it is long and lacks sufficient action to hook. The good aesthetic result is all positive, but little value taking into account the high budgets that handles Hollywood. No doubt, we repeat that Jamie Foxx is the best, it demonstrates once again that goes the same for a serious movie that for another not so much. Tosar may have more luck in his next foray Hollywood, although his safe pocket that does not complain.</body>
</review>
