<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La insólita y gloriosa hazaña del cipote de Archidona" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a glorious cock and eyaculadora strength of the people of Archidona. Kids in porretas, sympathetic expressions and some funny situations for a final cameo in Cela. Decent film uncover, for which the genre we like.</summary>
	<body>Director: Ramón Fernández. duration: 86 minutes.Release date: March 2, 1979.Espectadores: 933.973 of human beings.Many years ago, when a server was a preteen, I found in the House of my grandfather Manolo (in peace rest) a graphic novelilla with this strange title. Since that was the only thing graphic for a prepuber, because I ended up throwing him a visual. The book only remember the cartoons, in particular that of the final scene, that made me laugh. Not be if you have something to do with future onanistas passions.The film is about a village called Archidona, which are visited by a magazine music, full of women in leather like every year. This coming, as it is assumed, removes the low bellies of all inhabitants, with more or less fuss attending the annual meeting. But this year, four members get to flirt with four young girls good looking, what comes in direct conflict with their girlfriends of all life. These, rather than riding them a number, choose dry las médulas so that they can not meet her new lovers.I have to say that when appeared the first tit, before the "Sueno" look of my little, I said "Oh, didn't this work outside the destape". Curious hallazo, by Jove. The film, like so many, has little chicha. There are nice scenes, based on curious expressions, that made me laugh pretty. Then leave women in porretas, with more justification than usually. And finally Cela leaves reading part of his work (or whole, not is), providing a touch intellectual and cultured what was nothing more than an excuse to draw naked women. It can be seen.In short, film about a glorious cock and eyaculadora strength of the people of Archidona. Kids in porretas, sympathetic expressions and some funny situations for a final cameo in Cela. Decent film uncover, for which the genre we like.Besitos.P.D: My baby is amazing. I put a movie of these and stays with eyes as dishes. I put Pocoyo, and runs. Caste comes to the Greyhound, which says the conventional wisdom.</body>
</review>
