<review author="Jose Contreras" title="En el valle de Elah" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film launches against a few political depth charges that his country had abducted during two legislatures.</summary>
	<body>In a good script, the nail makes the character in the first act serves to hang in the third. The writers have a name for that. The nail, i.e., the element that is going to use later, is called "planting", and the horca, i.e., the second time the element that is used is called "pay off". In each one of the Wilder films would be an endless list of pay offs. Wilder reuses nearly every sentence. In his masterpiece, "The apartment", spare one. Needless to pay off in the end. "That will do Mr Sheldrake?", she asked Baxter. "Send you a cake for Christmas," said Miss Kubelik, recalling the ex-girlfriend of Baxter sent to Baxter a cake for Christmas (planting). Have also left me the "pay off" in this film of Haggis final because, with all its beauty, is too beautiful, too artistic. I think that I'm getting a naturalistic spectator, increasingly want less art and more life. Life does not end with pay offs.Also have too me the story of David and Goliath, which gives rise to the title. It makes me too smart. The father of the dead soldier must tell a story to the child, and as not known storytelling draws on the Bible. But the story that brings by the hairs is that it is the same story, read between the lines, gives us the keys to his own drama.Where Haggis shines with their own light is in the art of storytelling we known to launch us transgressors messages. The father of a young military man of the Iraq Guerra investigates the death of his son adelantándo every step of the research to the inept police. The self-sacrificing father becomes involved in inquiries and details as a sniffer infallible. Work heroic, effective from the father, goes step by step uncovering the murky antiheróica of the child life.The resource to tell two stories is a useless mobile that a street programmer is recovering the media files. The phone is the best Haggis, Haggis "Crash". The screenwriter that offers few facilities and forcing the Viewer to create history since the evidence.Haggis overhangs the Narrator means when it comes to spun separate genera. Cinema black, disappointed, accusing serves to speak of policy U.S. against a country that has not made them any harm. Police movies of good guys with good intentions in the end always discover the bad by far that they hide, serves to speak of emotion of the father, of truncated lives that are falling by the wayside. The film launches against a few political depth charges that his country had abducted during two legislatures. Which, incidentally, they have shown so little moral worth and crucible in their decisions to, certainly you will see Cape to tail the film without being remotely offended.</body>
</review>
