<review author="Monica Jordán" title="La vida sin Grace" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Where the hypocrisy wins the battle of morally.</summary>
	<body>"Grace is gone" starts with a scene of pseudo-desnudo emotional hand a group of women whose husbands are soldiers in the Iraq war. The lightness of his speech (remember laughing sexual farewell given to his men) and the appearance on screen of a serious John Cusack with gaunt appearance, point to a rather ironic film treatment: are we going to talk about something hard, but using the flag of humor., or so it may seem. The breakdown of this alleged ironic speech comes not so much by the impending news of the death of the wife of Stanley (Cusack) and his hurt reaction but with chords of the music of Clint Eastwood (Yes, the director, actor, producer, the already ubiquitous Eastwood) composed especially for Grace is Gone. Say chords, giving two-round twist over to melodrama to convert it (thanks also to address decisions) in one tear history.And is that "Grace is gone" is consumed in his bisexual as it progresses and carries with it to his characters. Stanley is presented to us already from the beginning from the point of view of who drew the unsuccessful: works at a store without ambition, suffers from a major limp (metaphor for lack of stability caused by the absence of his wife), does not know how to talk and hides all his faults (including the not be part of the army) under a false sense of security that raya despotism. It is a soul lost in the chaos while preaching the straight life that taught him the marines. No doubt, thus sees the director (James C. Strouse) and thus wants to see the viewers through their angular anaphoric and bursts of planes in empty rooms: Stanley is alone and plunged into the chaos of who does not know how to deal with a situation.The dilemma of Stanley (an expressionist less but more expressive Cusack) is to stop being one to become the leader of a clan that does not know how to apply, i.e., their daughters. Fleeing from the time of the confrontation that has to tell the girls that her mother is dead, decides to start a trip that will be used to gain time, take confidence and as a means of personal growth (what are but the travel film?). During this journey, the melodramatic moments will appear (especially among the eldest daughter - Heidi - and his father) and will be lightened by Dawn (small) who will be responsible for subtracting drama to the set of the film. A tandem perfect to prepare the Viewer for let go the tear at the peak: the conversation between father and daughters.It is right there where Strouse is overcome by hypocrisy and you can not hide that he is a rookie director. Full conversation between Stanley and her daughters, the director takes the decision to show their faces in the foreground to remove the sound to average conversation, certainly with the intention to give their characters a moment of intimacy. But it is not hypocritical to show average conversation and leave the viewer with the faces of girls crying bereaved? Do not been less pornographic emotionally withdraw right at the start and let the three a place of real intimacy? Strouse dubitación as the duality of his decision was more than clear: staying with his camera in the center of the action but covering the ears of the Viewer; I see but I do not listen. It is at that moment when one wondered where was the wise Council of Eastwood at the time of filming that scene. Perhaps Strouse saw no "Million Dollar baby" and did not learn of the composer of his film that ethics and morality in the film starts at the point of view that takes the camera. And Eastwood, knows that a while.</body>
</review>
