<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Tiempos Modernos" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Through the introduction of the voice spoken in modern times Chaplin manages to carry his criticism beyond Taylorism and relate the manufacturing process with the sound with films.</summary>
	<body>The battle of Charles Chaplin against talkies (or for the silent film) is one of those constant struggles can be seen in each of the films made by the director since the appearance of the singer of jazz (1927). Already in the beginning of lights of the city (1931) single RAID sound dialogue is used as mocking the political power of the city but is in modern times (1936) and the great dictator (1940) where Chaplin puts all her cinematographic tools for silent film.The use of sound in modern times is mostly a comedic intent that helps the gags that make up the film. In that regard, Chaplin has does not hesitate to take advantage of advances in cinema to reinforce its expressive jokes through sound effects or to rely on them, as it is the case of the scene in which Charlie, sitting next to the wife of the Mayor, is suffering from gastroenteritis. It is at times like this when we realize that, despite the refusal by Chaplin to talkies, is aware that he can also take advantage of something that is why be so harmful for the film.Despite these discrete uses of sound in modern times are also spoken dialogue after which hide the views of Chaplin on the new film of the word. Mostly off voices that appear throughout the film come from machines (radio, the apparatus of food, etc.), these entities through which we are dehumanized man and that reduce the human being to pure capable devices only make a gesture towards the production badly called evolution. Through the introduction of the voice spoken in modern times Chaplin manages to carry his criticism beyond Taylorism and relate the manufacturing process with the sound with films. His point of view concerning both clear: neither of them benefits the man and leads to the continuous desensitization of the person and the film.Chaplin talkies sees the death of expressive capacity that both has cost him get on screen and believes will be the talkies which become simple talking busts actors limited to recite a few lines and coerced in his expression. This is reducing the expressiveness in the actor and limit the interpretation as up then known in the film. Similarly, the industrial revolution seeks to reduce the movements the worker makes in his post to take more advantage of the time factory. Both processes are similar as they set limits to human capabilities and is why criticism of the sound in the Filmography of Chaplin takes special relevance in modern times.Despite this refusal in talkies, and accepting that the music and sound effects are a worth contribution to the expressiveness of the film, Chaplin includes two unique characters that use the dialogue: the tyrannical head and the own Charlie. The first of the characters supports the duality of the criticism the industry and talkies to incarnate the tyrannical head that does not hesitate to exploit their employees and use their voice to express themselves. The second of these characters can be paradoxical if it were not because of Charlie (only) foray into the world of voice makes it singing and unintelligible language. Thus Chaplin used his humor to reinforce his idea about the "talkies" and send a message to all those who you want to see in the world of sound: if Charlie could speak, would be understood.</body>
</review>
