<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Vértigo" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The spiral of Vertigo</summary>
	<body>Vertigo (1958) is the name that he decided to give his Alfred Hitchcock work perhaps think that the original of the novel ("D' between les morts", Pierre Boileau and Thomas Narcejac) usurpaba much of the mystery and intrigue that both baby him in his film the Viewer. Such is the strength of this second baptismo that while in some countries (including Spain) he chose to retain the title in its literary version ("from the dead"), the time and the shadow of the director has managed that his title is finally which give name popularly this story. In this way, and knowing perfectionist was, is not one that understand the change in title for Vertigo is given not an uncertain Hitchcock by mental illness (Pshycho) fetish, but a strategy intended to underline the hypnotic idea that generates Vertigo (and the film).The Hitchcock film has in its clarity one of the fundamental bases for your enjoyment, and is that while the English director handled the information as few have, the viewer never feels cheated or lost in his films. Allowing some plot twist to another (in Vertigo the surprise comes with the Madeleine/Judy impersonation) unexpected in Hitchcock is not limited to the impact on the plot but that leads it to the visual and structural impact. While others had taken advantage of the duality of characters of Kim Novak to finish the film with a surprise (deciphered at the same time for the main character - James Stewart - and for the Viewer) Hitchcock decided to give that information only the public who notes how the male protagonist is launching into an unhealthy abyss in the last half hour of the film. Which until then was an interesting story due to the mystery of Charlotte Valdés, forks into two paths that the viewer has the privilege to go to add the plot of film noir pursued by a unreal ghost detective. This punto y aparte in the film, mark and the interest of the director by the rupture structural bearing its most vivid example in psychosis, in which Hitchcock did not hesitate to kill the lead actress a half-hour of footage in one of the most remembered sequences of the film (the shower scene).This structure of suspense in which elements are showing one by one, in a consequent manner, without repeated and creating a storyline ever more distant from its starting point, responds to the shape of a spiral, hence that the presence of this type of curves in the titles of the home and also at other times of the film (the hairstyle of Madeleine)(, for example) can serve as example that Hitchcock did not leave nothing at random and that this change in title which might seem pure whim, responds to the most intrinsic need for the film. In this same way, and knowing that the Vertigo is characterized not only by the sensation of circular motion suffered by a person but also by "an embarrassment of the trial" (RAE dixit), Hitchcock shows on more than one occasion a filmed reality in large angular (mostly foreign) giving the image that feeling of FishEye that distorts reality. The decorated with steep slopes, the lighting that gradually changes of intensity in the same scene, the constant use of the strips and contrapicados and circular camera movements (the final kiss of the couple, for example) offer a staging that frames the viewer in the own sense of instability that has the protagonist. Thus Hitchcock manages all the elements that make up this movie (also through the Viewer) arrive to lose in this spiral of reality with dreams aspect which is the Vertigo (and film).</body>
</review>
