<review author="Natalia Eseverri" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When someone wants to be out of what normally makes, you must first make sure that it is a good project.</summary>
	<body>The basis of a good film is in the script. That is an obvious axiom to every director and cinema connoisseur. Everything else, actors, pictures, mounting. they are additions that make the film to be perfect and that the message you want to convey through the script, is clear and spectacular.That is the failure of the Oxford murders, by very good direction employing by Álex de la Iglesia, imitating his admired Hitchcock in a blatant manner but which makes it a nice tribute, and for many good performances that have, part of the basis of a novel very loose, in which topical characters drift what could be a good story and it is an overwhelming disappointment.Many writers believe that the public can only be you won presentandole a few initial theories of some formulas to solve, that they are happening until you reach the final climax, where everything is resolved and after mislead the viewer with twenty thousand suspects, at the end the culprit was in front of your nose. And it may be true, but even so, this story must have a hook and an attractive pursuit, and above all a spectacular ending that leaves you no indifferent.Explanations of because these crimes were seemed loose, topical characters as the girl in love with the protagonist that is frustrate not get it or the vengeful student went unheeded by Professor star and drowns his sorrows in alcohol, are mere insignificant forgetfulness that add nothing and damage history in general, because you misleads but not to have a logical consequenceto resolve the film raised. That if, technically it is a lujazo of film, and interpretations of each of them are book, but without a good material behind, this is left empty and vain.I hope the Lord of the Church, going by his comic and ironic vein of the community or crime ferpecto, that there really wears their true stories and know very good advantage.</body>
</review>
