<review author="Moebius" title="El gabinete del doctor Caligari" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari was listed as one of the inescapable reference in classic world cinema.</summary>
	<body>A good Berlin day dawned with posters on the walls that praying one sentence: Du mußt Caligari werden! (You must become Caligari!). Berliners amazed due of scratching your head trying to decipher the meaning of that phrase. On 26 February 1920 the mystery was dissolved. Premiered in the German capital the Cabinet of Dr. Caligari.Como all great artistic work the Cabinet of Dr. Caligari has given rise to studies, criticism and theories offering various interpretations on the background of its history and its importance within the European and world cinema. Usually consensus to consider this classic silent as the beginning of the German expressionist movement in the film and the first horror film (or at least the horror film) as we know it today in history.Producer Erich Pommer would have wanted that Fritz Lang will shoot the strange story written by Hans Janowitz and Carl Mayer, but unable to the creator of Metropolis to be implemented after the cameras the project went to the hands of Robert Wiene. The historian Siegfried Kracauer generalized theory that Janowitz and Mayer had been based on the horrors experienced in the great war to stop a script by dyes anti-establishment director Wiene would end up corrupting. Most modern currents have discredited these facts. It was true or not, the truth is that the revolution of the Cabinet of Dr. Caligari was not political but film cutting.Robert Wiene, whose work had apparently been quite discreet within the UFA, surprised friends and strangers with a film that although not lost sight of the commercialism (do some film lost ever?) it introduced all kinds of artistic elements of modernist currents and built a narrative with two parallel stories really intricate. Never ceases to amaze me that a very old film can be reached remain valid today, but so is. It is curious to see that plot twists as the sixth sense are as old as cinema.The plot of the film, briefly, is thus: a type by calling Francis is sitting on the bench in a park chatting with another man. When a beautiful young woman that seems to walk in a cathartic State, the young man preparing to narrate a story about him and that girl that occurred long ago. Francis and his friend Alan are enamored of the beautiful Jane. As they leave their choice who will be the lucky and swear eternal friendship, a strange man calling himself Caligari requests a license to have a seat at the next fair in the city where all kinds of inventions, gadgets and phenomena will be displayed.Francis and Alan attend the fair, while Caligari speaks to the masses on his show: the case of a sonámbulo called Cesare who had been sleeping and years. To the general astonishment, Dr. Caligari announces that the sleeping will wake up before your eyes and then may ask any question. Cesare has all the answers. When the sonámbulo abre los ojos, Alan interrogates him about the date of his death. Cesare tells him that that same morning will die.When the terrible fact finally happens, a sorry Francis is going to give the terrible news. Other strange crimes happening in the city, Francis, with help from the father of Jane, seek to find out the connection between Cesare, Caligari and assassinations. Later, Jane, concerned by the absence of his father, goes to Dr. Caligari. He tricks her into its particular barrack of fair, and there it will be attacked by Cesare. Thereafter Francis will try to unravel the secret behind Caligari and Cesare.La most of the narrative of the Cabinet of Dr. Caligari is, therefore, a huge flashback which in turn contains another lap back in the timeline in the scenes in which Francis reads the diary of Caligari. That particular narrative structure should add all that dream and at the same time depressive atmosphere in which moves the film. The sets of clear modernist influence are hurtful, loaded of hostility. Impossible angles, sharp corners, strange shadows and twisted lines. It seems as if citywide express the anxiety of Francis, while by contrast Caligari and Cesare can sometimes appear weird objects in motion, trees and faces that once were part of the city and had now claimed lives. Cesare, accompanied by the shadows, with that strange makeup that makes him look like a twisted some crazy Alice Cooper show dancer, is the epitome of the villains of the horror genre. From Frankenstein's monster to the silent Michael Myers, all saved some parallelism with the disturbing sonámbulo.And the Cabinet of Dr. Caligari was the first step all that expressionist movement that influenced both the classic old Universal horror, and hence in virtually all films of horror have been filmed since then. Janowitz and Mayer were the first to collect the seed of science and horror planted by Mary Shelley and her moved to cinema. So to speak, the Cabinet of Dr. Caligari's the myth of Frankenstein what Nosferatu was the of the Bram Stoker's Dracula, only that Wiene tape Yes constitutes a modernization of the classical figure while that in the work of F.W. Murnau film conforms more to the original story. And it is that the Cabinet of Dr. Caligari goes beyond the monster and mad scientist to play with the psychological factor, a key element of the film. Everything that happens in the narrative by Francis, from the manic decorated to the same labels (the restoration of 1996 sought respect original garish banners), passing by the characters, especially those of Caligari and Cesare, depends on psychology. Enter the world of this film is to travel to the bottom of the psyche, unconscious, to the interior of the human mind. For this reason, and for many other reasons that you must discover, the Cabinet of Dr. Caligari was listed as one of the inescapable reference in classic world cinema.</body>
</review>
