<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Beowulf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Animated film about a hero named Beowulf fighting monsters in pelotas. He had too much advertising as to be entirely neutral with her, so we tell you that it can be seen, although this did not lack both deployment.</summary>
	<body>Director: Robert Zemeckis. duration: according to the Ministry 115 minutes, but the hour and three-quarters ignited the cinema lights and everyone stands. That each draw their own conclusions.Release date: 23 November 2007.En times. BeO wulfs. With this remnant of fine humor on a server I want to say that I have reached the not inconsiderable figure of 400 reviews. If I get to know I do not see this film, but we will not walk with squeamishness. How time passes, when I started I was a poor boy from people arriving with his bunch of carrots and cabbage under the arm to the city, and now I have become what I am. I have eaten carrots and cabbage, and little else. Muahahahaha, Tito Chinchan you left for a while. Take you so as you want.The film is about a King who has a little problem that is he is eating the Warriors once mounted one mijica noise (Note mental - recruit the monster to end my neighbors - end of mental note). One day he is enough and requested, via Bard, a hero who aniquile the monster in exchange for half of their wealth. There is Beowulf, which has more eggs than Mr Pascual (mental note - the owner of the largest company of eggs - end of mental note). And there they lían espadazos and brabuconadas, which I do not more not counting everything.What stands out in the film is dubbing, in my humble understanding. I.e. you spend throughout the film thinking that Beowulf will shout "this is Sparta!", or that the partner will say "damn orejaspuntiagudas, that worth for one". By the way, why communicates with cries this Beowulf? What little education and moderation. I have not told you that you it's an animated film, with some made characters and other less (in particular the Princess). The story is not great thing, and the worst thing that has that you finish do not understand what you want to count. Especially that you expect a more linear story and the end I tad leave open-mouthed (for the worse). It can be seen, but has very weak moments, and certainly not what you expect from a film of this type.In short, film animation about a hero named Beowulf fighting in balls against monsters and similarly against the young girls. He had too much advertising as to be entirely neutral with her, so we tell you that it can be seen, although this did not lack both deployment.Besitos.P.D: There is another film, name similar, recorded rather format telefilm that I was not able to see full (sofa + loose movie + the siesta hour = baba on sofa + face textured sofa + jump area temporary for 3 hours).Pd2: The digital Jolines Angelina is to make you an analog wreck. Lol, think that nothing could be worse than the first joke.</body>
</review>
