<review author="Javier" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>As can you write a script so boring taking as a backup four books and almost unconditional support from the author of the novels?</summary>
	<body>I remember how, when I began to part in this film, he devoured everything that had something to do with a movie that I had enjoyed. I did it with many of Almodóvar, with the twilight of the gods of Wilder, but above all I did with Pulp Fiction. He was seeing her in the film (twice) and start my mass consumption of elements of the film: the script, soundtrack, posters, interviews to Quentin Tarantino and Roger Avary, the avalanche of criticism that led to the film. and of course the tape in VHS, CD with the movie in DivX and DVD for when it went out. I say all this because there was a time, not so distant, in which there were movies that it was worthwhile to do all this. From a few years to this part, can not find anything that I fill as before filled me a simple hour and a half of entertainment. I have to rely on the classic film (I mean not only the film made until the 1960s, but classics in the sense that I understand by classic: lands as you can is a very good example of classic) to see something that not sounds me, something that surprised me, something that does not make me feel a little more asshole. Yesterday, seeing Alatriste, I did again many questions, somewhat justifying all this introductory tirade: how is it possible that can be disappoint in this way to the Viewer? do as a promotion as well done (for his arrival at the spectator level) can be done then not meet even half of expectations? as can you write a boring taaaaan script taking as a backup four books and almost unconditional support from the author of the novels? where is the hand of the director in this mess? Because I know, Agustín Díaz Yanes was a good director, or at least made a very good first film. Stroke of luck will call one, competent team will call others, but there is no doubt that there is nothing of what there was.Everything is great in this movie. The light, the costumes, the make-up, the atmosphere, the music, the locations. All, less what has to be large (and which is not achieved with money, as above): the script. Not is if someone from the team has ever heard talk of the three acts. Or the dramatic progression. Or stoppages in the narrative play. Apparently not. And that makes that during more than two hours that lasts the film, you you ask constantly when going to get the pivot point, where is the premise of the characters and why the secondary plots are not interested at all. Really did not need put the four books in the film. It had not been bad to choose a main story for the personjae of Alatriste and one compendium of others for the secondary plots, and having taken all at once and they confluyeran at some point, and thus to solve them in a logical manner. Instead, the script condenses (more well apretuja) four books in parts of the film, half an hour approximately, with a parallel plot (from the love of Alatriste) that lasts throughout the film. This makes the emotion shine by their absence in all and each one of the moments: fencing struggles, battles, nor love scenes or dialogue are the more minimal emotion. Everything just in, as stated earlier, the ambiance, the music, costumes, makeup, lighting and Javier camera. A nonsense that hurts, by expectations that had been, and makes no more than confirm the Spanish film will remain dependent on Almodovar and Amenábar during most time of the desired.</body>
</review>
