<review author="Renegado" title="Alien vs Predator 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film which happens to be a poor excuse to again confront two legendary characters from the science fiction film. Little and nothing of what is intended and expected in a job that does not do justice to the tradition of the respective sagas.</summary>
	<body>I must confess that you as a fan of comic books and stuff, crossovers (for those who don't know that it is, is when you agarrás two main characters Gros and do them interact in a same story) I love, I always enthusiastic and any of them is brought to the big screen will insurance with my presence.Unfortunately, as often happens, most of the time projects fail to be commensurate with the expectations they generate, and you end up going half disappointed and somewhat hot cinema.With this installment of the series happens something more or less like this. Both Alien and predator are two icons of science fiction film; two real "monsters" in the literal sense as in the metaphorical sense of the word, so it a confrontation between the two is supposed, obviously, be something spectacular.Their first meeting, in the first "AvP", did not seem all bad, but I remember that I felt the feeling that history could have been much more.The idea of an underground Temple in Antarctica, in which predators bred Aliens for use as training, found me something quite well thought of as a way to deal with both creatures, and a terrestrial scientific expedition to stay trapped there, in the middle of the war between similar species, gave the human involvement the justification needed to be part of everything without clash too.However almost as everything there was just good ideas.More than the feeling of confinement of certain scenes and a another fight between the bicharracos decision, the film offered not much more.As well, however, that first delivery was far better than the latter. This time the story begins just where the previous one ends, i.e. at the time when the lifeless body of the predator which, together with the human survivor, had fought the alien Queen (not, to Cristina not &hellip; the Alien...)(is that it has less botox and is least bad) arises the parasitic aliencito that had been infected during one of the first fighting in the temple.Obviously, as it was seen this time, the bug this is a cross between two species that, as all know, the Aliens are parasites who adopt certain anatomical features of the host organism in which hatch.In this way, the new species is introduced in history: the Depredalien or Aliedador, or &hellip; presiosa.Bueno &hellip; as it is called &hellip; to make more easy we put "Tito" and ready.The issue is that this new longer of chiquito is more bad than the plague and to sneak in the nave of predators, is loaded a few (apparently coming increasingly less trained) and weapon les a quilombo so great that causes that they hit the back and crash again in the Tierra.Mas precisely, fall into a wooded area close to a typical and quiet town mountain on the outskirts of Coloradoinhabited by those typical settlers of pueblito Highland with its typical life stories of Yankee film.Worst case, is that the predators had the ship full of bottles with living alien chicks (seen they collected them) so to crash escape them all through the forest to the cry of "that is left is a fucking!". "!!"As expected happens long up that a human half gilastro and quite rabble is close to the place with their mouths open to see what happens, just that one of these bugs violates it orally and implant you a sympathetic parasite in the middle of the chest.A from there and very shortly afterwards, thanks to these bugs reproduce as dirt and apparently become adults almost immediately, you're all full of Aliens everywhere.To all this, as the nave of the predators had a LoJack or something as well, to crashing automatically sends a signal of emergency to their planet of origin, which is received by a veteran predator calling to see everything that happened like crazy "cannot be!!!" - says the chabón - "I lent the car one night and these idiots collide me!." It is possible to che! That outrage!!! Now go to see &hellip; "there just fits the hull, slightly arranged the braids and leaves to the farts to Earth hot re."Meanwhile here, rather, back in the village, they are happening inconsequential stories of its inhabitants for the film not troop otherwise than putting human characters (above quite poorly presented and interpreted) in the middle of the quilombo to give food to the Aliens.Para give an idea of where comes the hand are more or less: is the single guy who is in love with the pretty and popular girl who is girlfriend with the fachero and evil Flaccus who mistreats and mocks the simple boy whose former convict brother is now good and which, moreover, is friend of the people's Commissar was formerly Jet with him. There is separate one milica returns from Iraq and has to regain the love of his daughter anticipada that much does not register her because she grew up alone with dad.Or whether, appeared an Alien and is them he dined all together in the same scene, around the film lifted a little, but well, it wasn't.The issue is that not long after the accident, the predator owner of the star-shaped ship (his planet must stay here nomas because it didn't take anything), and it lies with the ship was all made ball, with the other deceased predators and above, realizes that escaped all the Aliens that had gathered.Is passed a hand through the face with gesture of annoyance while he mutters "that crazy shit!!!""and knowing that you have no other, it undertakes the mission to destroy all the Aliens and erase any trace of their passage through the planet (which uses a frasquito with a blue liquid that apparently is infinite)".Hence nomas, whoring means quietly and thinking that I could be at home watching television and taking a beer, weapon to the teeth with what he is and goes hunting, but not before breaking up the remains of the ship for no trace (and of course to collect the insurance).From there occur events that all hope and imagine a film of these. Aliens killing people, predator killing Aliens, fleeing, dying extras, actors much blood, screams, roars, shots, music of suspense, more extras dying, and other delights of the film pochoclero.In short, the film isn't nothing more than an excuse to return to deal with the characters.The script is loose, without too many surprises, full of clichés and with supposedly shocking scenes that fail to comply with this task.The special effects are well made but still we did not find anything new. Most of the fighting between the creatures occur in the dark (which is sometimes too much) it is quite difficult to distinguish who is who or who is winning.The role of the new species, the Depredalien (Tito) was needlessly wasted, that except for some features of its appearance is not very different from any other alien that one can find on the street.With regard to proceedings, was convened on this occasion young "stars" of successful series (which here is called a "string") pretending to reiterate what was done in the first installment was convened where not well-known actors to make the real protagonists monsters. However this time was not as actors not contributed anything to please, but rather some dots against, with characters that do not end or convince to generate the necessary sympathy as to make one want to eat that not they them.They are Steven Pasqualle as Dallas, Reiko Aylesworth (known for her role of Michelle Dressler in the series "24") as Nelly O'Brien, John Ortiz as sheriff Morales, Johnny Lewis as Ricky, and several more if they want to know who they are, you can see them in the end titles.The film was directed by brothers Colin and Greg Strause, who wore as directors of special effects in movies such as "300" and "X-Men 3", but that in this case demonstrated that to direct a film complete lack long way to go and much soup to take.Rating: 2 forsaken (Regular.) Most that are beyond the convening of both characters, the film does not do justice to the tradition of the respective sagas, or brings an improvement on the first delivery. Disordered rhythm, forced Vertigo, deaths and blood because if, and a too poor script, make this proposal something unfortunately historiographic and mediocre).Recommendations: If you is a fan of any of the two creatures and want to see them on the big screen again, go, but I warn you can leave disappointed.If you enjoyed watching people die because Yes, &amp; care three cucumbers the script or the direction, this film is theirs.If you are of those who enjoy classic suspense scenes of the old movies of Alien which suggests much more than what is shown and that kept him interested and tense, not go. In this film the alien they show all the time and you lose the grace.If you are that is outraged easy when he sees that two great characters are wasted on a bad story almost adolescent video "Friday the 13th" last type, not go. It can give a kick to the liver.</body>
</review>
