<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="Buenas noches y buena suerte" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film which invites reflection and that manages to give a lesson in ethics, commitment and cinematography fully rewarding, erected as a necessary document and required viewing. An ode to freedom of expression.</summary>
	<body>After a few initial minutes of the film where several semimudas scenes (with only sound and background music), serving as a choral presentation of the characters confront us and reminds us of the beginning of Cimino films as "The Hunter" or more loosely to "Schindler's list" of Spielberg, we can predict that the film will formally be impeccable, and this is confirmed during the rest of the footage.Many will qualify the work of Clooney as tedious or a simple pain in the ass, with a theme last historic surroundings and current importance, and it has deficiencies of rather outstanding pace, but nothing further from the truth. The film has a brutal narrative force and ethical not only exemplary but necessary and entirely valid message even today because the visual manipulation and cheap partisanship still exist, the politics of fear is still alive in many parts of the world (especially United States) and promotes and recalls the journalism, courageous and committed to society and its problems.Leaving aside the plot and narrative, issues that are largely valuable, visual and technical treatment of the tape is masterful but difficult to assess by many people, that it's a film of a formality based on minimalism and the correction. Enviadable is as Clooney tells this story, its resources to give dynamism or tension to a scene, the because of the narrative use of according to which levels or the beautiful setting worthy of a true master.Remarkable are the use of lenses in this film with a tremendously clever focal game, the flat sequence to provide realism and breadth to the scenes, so measured frames, scenes with depth of field and exceptional use of show a large amount of information in a scene and same framing, or movements so subtle and almost immeasurable camera sometimes which are not free or much less.The silent or semimudas scenes are a display of address, see for example the scene that we lose the image of the replica of Senator McCarthy to the show which aired 3 weeks before inculpando it, in which the character played by Frank Langella moves between shadows by the firm while not let hear the conversation of McCarthy, a representation of the fear of the possible reprisals Government or the fall of a television or medium by a committed risk. Clooney used silence or with only background music scenes to extol a moment or a person. Sometimes silence says more than words and here is an example. Also, the use of characters in off is something very right and splendid in the film by filmmaker.The superb photography Robert Elswit manages to transport us visually to the 1950s, helped by a minimalist music that complements perfectly beautiful and well-kept images. A fascinating lighting work and received a nomination to the oscar merecidísima in its respective section."The performances are very convincing, but highlighted one above the other is excellent and hit actor David Strathairn, which makes a marvelous reproduction of his character, the man who planted face McCarthy himself together with his team of the CBS, Edward R. Murrow.""Good night, and good luck", is a film whose tremendous quality is possible that it is difficult to detect by a vast majority of spectators because the subtlety of its details lies the greatness of the work of Clooney, as presents to the characters, as it uses the contrapicados to enlarge the figure major news and popular Murrow, as it presents the important moments with silencesas usa actors or as light eyes opens field to the image among other things. A director who already excelled in his brilliant but somewhat irregular Opera prima "Confessions of a dangerous mind" and here reaffirms her undeniable talent both visual and cultural. A film that portrays fantastically well an era of political repression, lack of freedom of expression scandalous and the struggle for a better future.The film is an ode to freedom of expression, we are told that the fight against injustices will always be present and although not achieved the desired objectives or perhaps miss the illusion, should not be left that commitment in the struggle, in this case speaks to us of the fight using the power of the word and its importance in our society.A film which invites reflection and that manages to give an educational lesson in ethics, commitment and totally rewarding cinematography, but above all, a necessary film and compulsory viewing.</body>
</review>
