<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The perfect definition of the film would be telefílmica tragicomedy. Typical film that both like at Sundance and so little to the cultivated spectator. An example of bad independent cinema.</summary>
	<body>and this is the film of the year? Juas! In part, and although not reaching those limits, I pointed to the case of the film-nonsense "Monster", a telefilm that was intended to impersonate an indie film, when in reality, was full of mediocrity on all sides, including realization and performances, I am among those who think that the overacting of Theron is so monstrous as her character.Do not be fooled, "little Miss Sunshine', is not or the jewel which intend to sell, not even a good independent film;" It is nice, but little else. Also that a server still does not understand how this telefilm (Yes, because complies with many of the parameters that characterize them) has been able to achieve important awards in festivals of a supposed prestigious as Sundance or San Sebastian and what one takes you to rethink as they are configured the jury of festivals, because lately they seem to be not isolated cases (see a few years ago as "directors" as Michael Moore earned the Palme d'Or) (in Cannes snatching her injustísimamente to Park Chan-Wook or go no further, about this last year in Sitges, a list of winners or Christ understood in some sections).Going back to our "Dear" pinicula, the same if it isn't more than a road-movie, with an exaggerated style semi-indie, with camera in hand and all that stuff, they are fine if they are used to give a touch documentalist or realistic to the plot, see the exemplary use of the camera in hand in some sections of the excellent "being John Malkovich" or "Children of men", but Miss Sunshine are trying to trick the viewer that you see a gem of those indie sea of cool, when in reality, we are dealing with a telefilm of desktop, sympathetic but full of clichés, with extremely stereotypical characters and moments of most forced and implausible.And I think that the problem of this small production, is that is created and conceived as a Hollywood film, if I not mistaken, so is designed, and if they press me much, intended for the oscars or the ISA, because it contains more than one section extremely academic and oscaril aftertaste (and that has crime in a production that gives them groundbreaking indie).Also wanted to remind, that fabulous music from the film, is not properly a score (the part of M. Danna if), rather a virtually calcada variant of a disk of the fantastic Russian band DeVotchka, something like what did in his day Yann Tiersen with "Amélie" and his album previously released. The fact is that, Liev Schrieber already made use of this great band's music in the highly recommended "Everything is illuminated", with Elijah Wood's character.Apart from the tremendous and numerous failures that one has seen in a first viewing, not everything is evil in this small not great work, because it has characters geeks, poorly built and very untapped in some cases, but with some charm. They are not credible, their reactions are forced and not give the pego as "family dodgy Yankee of those that are broken and destroyed that there is little to do", but they fall in sympathy, that Yes, little else. The right end, gives a bit of hooliganism to the tape (already you needed after some mediocre 99 minutes) and resorted to a completely unexpected musical number that gives a touch of quality to the tape, because, with it, it calls into question all the previous footage and clearly expresses the nonsense of the trip itself, but you have served for many things (including rid of grandfather cocaínomano, or which the Nietzschean silent, after talk and already it can express and "discover" horrifying is the world and how bad that everything goes. what a novelty, dude!).Most remarkable of the film, the only thing should be, is so curious metaphor of the van, which should go up is all torn once, because they are all characters that are always at the limit of losing the last "train of life". They have up to life, must adapt and above all be accepted as they are. Self-esteem is the solution. It is the only success at level plot of the film, along with the final majo.Following in my zeal to discredit works tremendously overvalued, see my 'beloved' "Infiltrated" by Scorsese, "Little Miss Sunshine" squeaking me, and when something squeaking, as they would say here in catalunya, Malament rai!. Characters not be the cree or the Holy Pope, the role of the mother, so lacking in importance, adds absolutely nothing to the set, the roles of Kinnear (Incidentally, portraying if same as always) and his father are very poorly taken, badly constructed and inverosimiles. The rest, more or less on this path, therefore leads me to say that the small is that I most has fallen by grace, the more natural of all and that gives an overview to the rest, although without going clear and that pass in an indie film, sends eggs!.Something that surprised me very negatively, is untapped which is the character of Steve Carell, thought that between him and the boy would be a link of education or of deep reflection, and I find banal conversations and moments disappointing, and that Steve does not hurt, but of course, when you have a character so poor when could be very rich in nuances, and with less details a Seat Panda, little can be done.Formally, have not found me anything out of this world, what is more, I think that it follows the line of a cheap telefilm, but with actors in A series (or I think xD), because convinced me only the scenes of the trip with the bridges, which is not too original if we see some other roadmovie or video clips and little else.Anyway, little more can be said, only what I think child, therefore, nothing adult, nor in their approach or in their characters, and the worst is that it claims to be it and there is nothing that I remove more than proportion that a work has one iota of pretentiousness to achieve depth of absolute emptiness. That is something qualitative infimamente, wanting to be politically incorrect so gullible shaped, fails to fairly commendable results.Message for the defenders of the film: Lapidar me or take me to the stake if they want to, but these are my humble and incendiary views on film so justito. I want to tell you, I did not like and uds the over-value, feel me fabulous, this year plays this year that comes as another garbage of Ron Howard. This is the life.Luckily I always we remain Solondz, Payne or PTA among other true masters of the indie film, which make truth, not telefilms film.</body>
</review>
