<review author="Luna" title="La banda nos visita" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The directorial debut of Eran Kolirin has already achieved many awards but the most important award that has already garnered is the give the viewer something what thinking and a history of which enjoy.</summary>
	<body>The journey of a band of musicians of the Egyptian police to Israel serves as a pretext for telling us another trip less concrete and more profound: the journey through the life of each one of the characters. We discovered on the experiences of each one of the characters that many times our history is parallel and similar or can serve as a help to others that we are on the road.Lost in a small Israeli town by various avatars of fate, the charity of some locals make them to spend the night indoors. It happens more in history. Apparently. Because after this surface as simple Eran Kolirin, also author of the screenplay, has managed to count much more in his debut as a film director. With the mastery of the domain of small things, Kolirin tells us about how these musicians influence and feed to the parishioners, and as the lugareñs also influence and make it evolve to these musicians. Ultimately Kolirin focuses on the richness of human relationships and gift us with a small moral: every human being has something to offer us.The actors are well chosen and embroider his interpretation, filled with life sentences of a realistic and careful script.KOLIRIN has opted for a sober realization, without technical fanfare, and with an abundance of flat media and Americans to make more realistic and close this story. Its stylish get hilarious moments and other truly emotional and tender.Hard and rough picture of Shai Goldman that compels us to deepen the apparent harshness of characters to discover his inner garden is also particularly good. It is also very successful (and some truly memorable moments) music composed by Habib Shadah, which immerses us almost without noticing and without stridency in the history.No doubt it's a film that we must not miss in 2008. Not only the viewers are able to appreciate its beauty but that criticism and the juries of many festivals has already awarded numerous awards in this co-production between Israel, France and EE.UU. It has garnered awards of the Academy cinema in Cannes isrealí took the award "A certain regard", its director took the prize for best director revelation at the European film awards, has been the award for best film in Tokyo and in our country got done in 52 international film week of Valladolid with the prize Novel the best director and best screenplay. They are certainly not the only awards that will reap. But from my point of view, the most important award that has already garnered is the give the viewer something what thinking and a history of which enjoy.</body>
</review>
