<review author="José A. Peig" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is, again, one of those movies that possess great strength and narrative force that hide a weak look.</summary>
	<body>Atonement in times of war and peace. Images and words that draw a process in three registers Visual and audible. Since the beginning the pounding on the keys of the typewriter (that reinforces the visual rhythm) insinuates us nature metafílmica of the story. Frustrated that only lives can redeem himself in an act of imagination. Remorse subdues with literature (and film). Joe Wright film is valuable in that it is a concise description of a weak soul which seeks to clean his conscience based on literature of (fake) good feelings; seek refuge denying reality. Here is invoked the power of the imagination without having this noble human quality authentic purging category, at least as we have it in the epilogue that echoes to detail the meaning of the three previous segments. If anything, literature of despair. All development is consistent, no doubt, but when we arrived at the end of the alleged purging we realize that there has been film to tell a truly complex story, use the history to offer an overwhelming array of Précieuses, though this is only appearance. See descriptive (and not devoid of psychological depth) beauty of the impressive flat sequence in a circle. The conclusion of the story tells us that it is not a whim of the filmmaker. The formal structure predominates over the content. Content, on the other hand, that can be summarized in a vital process fragmented into three levels: origin of evil (the mansion of the Tallis, gardens, family photography light and bright colors), consequences (landscape of war, interior of a hospital, chiaroscuro), review and recognition of the meaning by the elderly Briony Tallis. Seeing this scheme, we identify the smallness of the project to develop and are, again, one of those movies that possess great strength and narrative force that hide a weak look.Not pretentious movie, but yes, certainly too concerned to be witty at the visual level, without backbone a strong speech from expiatory confession that, ultimately, resembles more a selfish cry that a true selfless consideration towards her sister and lover for whose love was jealousy. In a few words; Atonement is a spiritual concept that goes far beyond the plañidero gesture. Atonement is a film that is taken too seriously herself to not repair the concept that defines the content and intended to last.After discussion, it was tempting to placing it on the level of mediocrity. But no one can deny its internal consistency (while the concept to develop is simple of what he believed in principle), the magnificent use of photography, the emotional soundtrack, the construction of characters so versatile and strong, and that vigorous and playful narrative describing characters and parallel times (sometimes describing the same scene from the omniscient narrator and)(at the same time, the malevolent perspective of Briony) feelings in the distance and grudges seeking the last chance even in the most desperate stronghold: art.</body>
</review>
