<review author="Jesus David" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good film, that keeps you connected to it from beginning to end, with great actors and a great handling of the camera by the director, I was surprised in that aspect. And already, more only would it destripara you the film.</summary>
	<body>Álex de la Iglesia, one of our best directors, is back to give a class and not of mathematics, if not on how to make good cinema and, above all, what comes of the balls. Much I have read about that isn't his style, or that it has lost its label, it seems as if a director had the obligation to follow exclusively in a single style and thus fall into the routine. But Alex is clever enough to offer us in each of his films a different point of view that sometimes it succeeds and sometimes not. A great success, for starters, is to include two of the greats such as Elijah Wood and John Hurt. And another great success is certainly include other large two breasts of Eleanor, lest be we forgot that we we have a Spanish film.History will speak little that in the end I just putting the leg and I tell you something that I should not. Martin (Elijah Wood), an American student, arrives at Oxford with the intention that Arthur Seldom (John Hurt), a famous Professor of logic, directed his doctoral thesis. The two will be involved in a series of crimes that have to be solved through logic, philosophy and own mathematics.We have a good film of intrigue, with small ups and downs, but that keeps you hooked to the Viewer from beginning to end. And it is not for less, because the beginning is commendable, and is where the master which has church with an incredible level camera sequence that unveils the first crime. After this, well it is true that there is much dialogue and can be quite tiresome, although the protagonists thrive well in their roles. In reality it is like watching an episode of House, you do not know that Devils are saying when they try to know which disease is the patient, but keep you hooked.But if the Viewer is slept, Alex, once again, he has been ready and said: there seems to be much dialogue here. as put here tits and an ass there and ready. And responsible for providing us with such images is none other than Leonor Watling. I had not seen the eyes of Elijah Wood as open as it was in possession of the ring. With regard to the role of Eleanor (Lorna) little cabe highlight apart from these scenes. Not because to do so bad, quite the contrary, but because just it appears throughout the film, except for those blessed scenes.I can not forget the soundtrack carried out by Roque Baños, which is exceptional, with all the words. A real luxury. Anyway, in short, for those who do not want to read all the rollaco to loose: A good film, that keeps you connected to it from beginning to end, with great actors and a great handling of the camera by the director, surprised me in that regard. And already, say something more only would it destripara you the film. Last thing I will say is that as soon as he finished the film came me a desire to mad to eat spaghetti.</body>
</review>
