<review author="Heitor Pan" title="8 mujeres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>See the Deneuve move the arms in an attempt to sensuality to the rhythm of a song plumbate is a rarity as worthy of witness as to forget.</summary>
	<body>Her had postponed an infinite number of times by laziness or carelessness, but at the end, the recommendation of a friend has given to an end with a verdict expected: Although we agree in a comprehensive film, something proven taste in our trips to the cinema, will continue to have our particular irreconcilable dark sides. This film was an event in France, because it brought together for the first time to a number of the great ladies of French cinema in a strange film, mixture of the heir to the novels of Agatha Christie film and musical melodrama. Great performers of several generations as Catherine Deneuve, Isabelle Huppert, Fanny Ardant, Emmanuelle Beart and Virginie Ledoyen and Ludivine Sagnier composed a filmed play, in which 8 women try to discover the murderer of the only man of the House.In a mansion isolated by snow, eight women discover the corpse of the husband of one of them. So this woman, as his mother, his sister, his daughters, his sister-in-law or the maids of the family can hide some reason for having killed a man in cold blood. Between surprises and musical numbers, women will seek to clarify the mystery by discovering the miseries and secrets of a very unusual family.Each one of the actresses gives life to a female character, all full of eccentricities, dark secrets and hidden desires in a plot that begins a classic, recalling such films as "negritos 10", but as it progresses begins to be possessed by the spirit of a screenwriter of telenovelas. The story is complicated by setting impossible relationships among women or giving rise to unexpected turns of script that I missed the characters to some Luis Alfredo or to hear the actors speaking with the classic Venezuelan accent.If that wasn't enough to impress the public, to the actresses of the draught of the of the film, typical of a dense and dramatic film, see navigate in a script as psychoactive, every time it occurs before the bewildered eyes of the spectator a musical number that brings little to the plot, without any musical interest and choreographies arriving at times cause the embarrassment. See the Deneuve move the arms in an attempt to sensuality to the rhythm of a song plumbate is a rarity as worthy of witness as to forget.It is possible that there who take everything as a parody to this kind of movies and enjoy with the showcasing of some actresses are able to fill the screen with the dialogues in other mouths would lead to flight, but I was unable to see the screen with that perspective. Just as I enjoyed with the musical numbers on "The other side of the bed" or with the hilarious detective intrigues of the classic "A corpse to the desserts", I bored in a sovereign manner with the comings and goings of characters without spark, incapable of drawing a smile or involve me in a story too marciana for my taste.I don't know how the script on paper, would be it is impossible to deduce a priori the success of a film, but it is quite complicated to me thinking that all these actresses have been in a similar story a good movie, unless they access under duress or under the weight of a lot of green billetitos.</body>
</review>
