<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A pity, because the actors - except an Elijah Wood which still not can be cleared his fronted of hobbit - do their work with ease (Julie Cox excels in a role that Hitchcock Bachelor), and the camera falls rightly.</summary>
	<body>We have some certainty? Thus begins the last of an unknown Alex de la Iglesia. Yes, we can be sure that you can do better, Alex, much better. And it seems, if you recuperaras a little even the bad milk (black, than non-white) that brewed your previous achievements (except the insufferable 800 bullets and indecent daughter, dead of laughter). You don't feel well make you cold to the Eastwood or the intellectual to the Allen, or at least that is what demonstrates this experiment (I hope!), a boring simulation of philosophical mecano with dyes of Cluedo, spiced with the salvific presence of Eleanor, that if it fails to get the temperature with your apron we would have died of sudden freeze.Please, Alex, what more bad screenplay! One just by importing a damn if you see one dead and how so unfortunate incident occur. And is that the Oxford murders are forced the Viewer to raffle narrative gear with weak lighting of a chaotic and forced logic which eventually reveal itself for what it is, pure smoke. It is not that the Oxford murders want to make a thesis of the metaphysical gaming - which also-, but that she herself becomes this indeterminacy through the constant exercise of fidelity to this inconsistency.A pity, because the actors - except an Elijah Wood which still not can be cleared his fronted of hobbit - do their work with ease (Julie Cox excels in a role that Hitchcock Bachelor), and the camera falls rightly. But this evocative soundtrack of Roque Baños (heiress of a Hermann hitchcockiano) does not deserve such absurdities of script, not. Perhaps faithfulness to the text of Guillermo Martínez (Premio Planeta 2003 in Argentina with this novel) the essential such disruption reason. What role of insurance will be an intelligent exercise of intrigue stained by the seductive falsehoods of labyrinth logical fallacies, to pass it to celluloid thing blurs in a quagmire has pretentious dialogues rather than look to the armchair, we escuecen without thrill.Alex slips when gets carried away by the excesses which populate his imaginary film lover, so if you do walking down the freak underworld as if you decide - as this is the case - emulate the labyrinthine intrigue of the angrosajón of the 1970s cinema (the footprint). Why the community is still his best creation, because without betraying his imagination, it offered a contention that denoted maturity without losing their non-transferable style.I guess that everything is to be patient and wait for your next.We will always be the Watling.</body>
</review>
