<review author="José Córdoba" title="Superman returns" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The result is disappointing. The intention to recover the spirit of the original has been on its surface, in its aesthetic, but not in the fun, adventurous sense of the first.</summary>
	<body>For me, the Richard Donner Superman is the best superhero movie that has shot because it combines two essential things for me: showmanship and entertainment. In recent years the genre has taken a turn towards darker areas, which have ended up making him a more serious than fun genus. This is not really bad, and films like Batman Begins or Spiderman 2, seem highly recommended, but it does not mean that you take less fun, entertainment and humor that distilled Superman, increased in their increasingly worse sequels.Bryan Singer, director of this new version of Superman, has stated in many interviews that his objective was to continue the work done by Donner for the first and second parte(que_fue_rerodada_en_un_70%_por_Richard_Lester), not wanting to be a rupture in the style of Batman Begins. In addition the original music composed by John Ottmann was going to include themes of the original soundtrack composed by John Williams, among them, how not, the departure of Superman. A movement upstream taking into account recent heroes like Batman have changed of representative item up to three times. For all this, he was eager to see the film, despite my maxim of never see anything with expectations in mind.The result, in my opinion, it is disappointing.The intention to recover the spirit of the original has been on its surface, in its aesthetic, but not in the fun, adventurous sense of the first. Thus, from an aesthetic point of view, the film is a very faithful continuation of designs that made John Barry for the film by Donner. This aesthetic moves even to the choice of the actor who plays Superman, the unknown Brandon Routh, of astonishing resemblance to Christopher Reeve and that comes, surprisingly, well standing in comparison. Unfortunate funny tone has been left aside. We have a solemn film, extremely serious, focused, especially in the recreation of characters and their relationships, see how it feels to Superman after returning to Earth and see his beloved Lois Lane (a gorgeous Kate Bosworth, which is less aggressive than Margot Kidder from the original) has one son and is in love with another manto demonstrate why the world needs Superman. Plot in general much resembles the original and is dangerously close to the remake. The villain of the function is provided by Kevin Spacey as Lex Luthor, and complies with the actor, but he notices, to the film, limited. Singer who did not want any actor rubbing histrionic, even Frank Langella as Perry White. Therefore all reactions are smaller and the villain is less fun/threatening, Gene Hackman in the original light years. Luthor also appears rodedado of some henchmen devoid of any personality and that become worst film, making me miss Otis or Tessmacher.En Miss balance positive direction of Singer, elegant as always. Also the scenes of action, just a couple, also they are very well shot and involve, though all CGI. The picture manages to recreate the original, turning it a bit darker and is really remarkable. The soundtrack only say that Ottmann isn't Williams and, despite not being a bad music, only manages to make you vibrate when inserted flashes or develops the original themes from Williams, that Yes the new theme of love is really beautiful.The film also seems made for the sole purpose of laying the groundwork for a follow-up once already we have all presented characters and pointed, somewhat conflicts as the first part of Spiderman.Un detail, the film, as it has already happened other times with Singer (see X-Men), appears to be much cheaper than what it has cost (about 200 million dollars)which makes it less spectacular than expected.In short, Superman Returns is a decent film that is taken too seriously to itself, resulting in solemn and therefore, away from the spirit of adventure and entertainment pure and simple that guided the original Superman. A penalty.</body>
</review>
