<review author="Luna" title="Es un mundo libre" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A round film in sum, with the quality in terms of accomplishment to which we are accustomed Loach. If you want spend a time of good cinema, with history and social background, do not let escaapar this film.</summary>
	<body>Ken Loach has always been characterized by telling stories with a marked social trend and in this his last film will not disappoint his staunchest followers. In this case it tells us the story of a woman dedicated to hire immigrants as temporary workers in England and its history serves as a pretext to narrate and deepen in another topic more important, more real and in which many people have submerged today: immigration, illegal immigration and all the issues surrounding this sad social reality. Numerous small dramas are those who tells Paul Laverty, which has become one of the writers Ken Loach collaborating lately (hers was the script of the previous films of Loach as "The wind that shakes the barley", "Happy dieciseís" or "bread and roses").The gaze of Loach not only focuses on the characters, who follows and described the diseccionadora precision of a surgeon, but that also covers the city of London which runs the story and which becomes another character, silent witness of what happened. Loach focuses in this case in London that tourists don't see, from the dirty alleys of the parking of caravans as home and the factories dirty work dangerous that nobody wants to do and that only the unhappy poor who come seeking to improve their situation dare to carry out. And is that you as the protagonist says "is a free world.". A free world in which each receive benefits to hands full with the sweat of others while most malvive working too many hours a day in ethically questionable jobs.Ken Loach addresses the issue with sincerity, and the viewer understands but the reality shows the director is lasting and complicated, the real world is sensed even more thorny and contentious. In this case, as in other films by the same director, the plot of the story is important, but the role of the characters is also relevant, and we can see how they evolve. In other films, Loach works with actors looking for naturalness and realism to compose a few truthful and real characters. In this case most of the acting weight rests with Kierston Wareing, a little-known British actress who before this film had worked in some video and in a supporting role in small television clamoring. The actress who was thinking of retiring from the world of interpretation when, as they say, Ken Loach called on your door with this role and upset their plans and their world so bad saw the panorama. Despite being his first role protagonist Wareing well supports the pressure and every time appears in full screen it with truth and the roundness of her character. They have been slow to discover it but sure that it won't be the only role as protagonist to interpret (and won't have to leave the world of interpretation) in fact shortly we can see it in "Rise of the foot soldier" of Julian Gilbey.El rest of the cast also has been chosen with great success and achieve a very credible composition of his characters which, in many cases, you forget that you are watching a movie and it seems that you immersed in a documentary hayes, or in life itself.The fact that most of the film is narrated camera in hand, with a hard and realistic picture of Nigel Willoughby who does not lose in embellishing the image also contributes to this. This is to be welcomed because it is not a pretty story. It's scream from the rooftops what is telling is real and is happening. And the Précieuses here does not take place.A round film in sum, with the quality in terms of accomplishment to which we are accustomed Loach, and perfectly wrapped by the soundtrack to George Fenton, one of the last regular contributors of Ken Loach (theirs are the soundtracks of recent films of Loach, "The wind that shakes the barley" or "Happy sixteen"). If you want spend a time of good cinema, with history and social background, do not fail to escape this film.</body>
</review>
