<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="This is England" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Raw, honest, organic, emotional: This is London is an uncomfortable film, which do not forget...</summary>
	<body>Despite what the advertising, poorly reported, counts, This is England is not about the origin of the skinhead in England movement. Even he recreates in excess illuminate our ignorance with cityscapes burned by unemployment, racism, drugs and the tedium of endless not never know what to do. Also informs about the way in which youth lost innocence and hocica your discomfort in permeable, warm and fraternal membership of a group. What makes This is England is to offer a rough and sincere, emotional and realistic portrait of affection or love or friendship. And it does so with the reliable packaging of the skinhead and their heads to zero, his boots and his ignorant, learned nationalism at foot of birra, proceedings of Foundation without bureaucratic committees that estabulen. Little emotional interweaving people, but who share strong codes based on a slight incline to the violence, street hedonism and similar patterns of image.Tony Richardson, Ken Loach and Mike Leigh, Michael Winterbottom Danny Boyle already before prefijaron an English tone of proletarian class and handled stories of simple people, asphyxiated by unemployment or mental anorexia of a gray, prudish, society doomed to fail in the management of their own happiness and devoid of horizons outside the neighborhood, of the industry on the outskirts, bar with generous pints and folk on the radio, but Shane Meadows makes a more modest exercise initiation, has a voice of their own, shedding proudly all influence of classic British realism (those illustrious names in greater or lesser extent) and offering a more modern style model, giving psychological keys (the father died on the front of the Malvinas or Falklands) or even historical (the skins of racism)(, but is the extreme right which manipulates and became what we know today). And in addition Meadows paints a few skins wanting to fun, colleagues of his colleagues, little interested in afear life more than it is. In fact, the gang splits in two: those who seek good vibes and beers Saturday night under the vacilón pace of Jamaican ska and those seeking to assemble camorra, stone pakis and paint rhetoric that do not understand in the underpasses of the grey city in which they live. Both factions live, however, in the orphan, deprived of family ties strong and thrown to a hotbed of violence where fanaticism burrow into mediocrity to remove fear.The oppressed working class (the working class heroes of Lennon) lacks glamour, they drink in the third bottle and they walk dresses with style (believed to be) while the city collapses and crushes them. Their children are confessed losers: Meadows attaches to these anti-heroes humanity others denied, it gives them humility, a heart almost. Gun salute, cheers and cannons to the interpretation: characters that give life actors in State of grace, acting almost effortlessly, impregnating of faith life routine, grey and toxic of these losers of quarter.Thomas Turgoose, the kid of twelve years which opens and closes the function, leave the noqueado Viewer. If they can see the film in English, subtitled. Hence wins more integers even. The score of the film is prodigious (Ludovico Einaudi) and its soundtrack is a generous compilation of ska, soul, funk and folk rock (Toots and The Maytals, scraps of Soft Cell, Dexys Midnight Runners.) The eighties were screwed, were ain't they?</body>
</review>
