<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What else would like to I have enjoyed. Even by the Church, with which so many good times I passed, but not convinced at all by these crimes. There are, however, very good film inside, and would be a shame not to enjoy their successes...</summary>
	<body>«What we can not talk about should be shut up»(Ludwig_Wittgenstein,_Tractatus_Philosophicus) - partly, only in part, the Oxford murders refers to a classic film, inspiration hitchckoniana, tiling with such technical cleaning that strike others. The disaffection towards the end result and what makes this chronicler of his vices condemn it to oblivion is his film little spirit, bearing in mind that the novel by Guillermo Martínez, premio Planeta in Argentina, is a thick, go thriller where the philosophy of Wittgenstein, the problematic of language and considered killing nature as a game between Pythagoras and Moriarty are assembled as chips fundamental in the construction of the plot. As you do not exactly know what to think about these macerations and disquisition of pure philosophical mind, the film of Álex de la Iglesia weakens that verbal flank. It stuns the continuous Lair by Kabbalistic, by the cryptic. It endures one the torrent of sophistry, the unquestionable intellectual root of the project - both the literary as the visual - but it is hard to assimilate the nomenclature, sounding phrases, all these dialogues operatic, perfect some, jerks others with whom writers (the own of the Church and his inseparable Jorge Guerricaechevarría) lead the mystery, merely detective part into the realm of the academic thrillerinvested the pomp and the patterns of the novel to the Agatha Christie or similar. The laudable business of Basque director sinks by the arid texture of the spot, by the bizarre sequence of coincidences and brittle ground of mathematics, are not (in my short opinion) claim attractive enough to lift a film narrative. It overwhelms this brutal tsunami of concepts that the lego Viewer sound you to validation of the COU, a sort of intensive master of philosophy to five euros and a half. You can ignore the detail, that commitment to fill all of mathematical culture, say, but something is lost then, something beautiful, not put in doubt. I read the novel murders, here the Oxford murders, when they left in Spain. I enjoyed the way in which enjoy the puzzles, the entanglements, the cluedo game. I also enjoyed the terminology China shop of the enrevasado world of equations and unknowns despejables only at the end of the day, but a good writer, in its own way, is a semantic filmmaker, a kind of demiurge of the verb which puts scenes mental onscreen who read. Kind of.The American whodunnit is a genre in itself and Garners legions of followers, public accomplice to the challenge of invest Cap a Sherkock Holmes here nihilistic and depressing (Absinthe and hobbies outside) and navigate complex waves of clues, corpses and all the classical paraphernalia. Church is respectful to the extreme meet ex officio and talent certain commandments inexcusable, but ignores master Hitchcock, who said have had in mind in the shooting, and placed too many implausible or unnecessary elements for fluid during the forced plot. Here we advise commercial smell of the director, which strained two or three scenes of high erotic voltage (a Leonor Watling carnal and explicit, suffering the onslaught of a golosísima camera that will rotate to focus with voyeur delectation an ass so morbid as disposable for the "serious" tone of the film). Elijah Wood is also willful and warns an extra enthusiasm, but do not squeeze the potential dramatic of his character or transmits credibility. Not the Church strives to get his deadpan vein, the coarse humor that we bienacostumbró, and instead displays academic ways, Orthodox, alien calligraphy altogether lines to what truly motivates his creator ego. As this is not the reason why the film not curdled. It seems more like an assignment (which I doubt reading the wonderful blog of filming and what there counts) than a whim of director already fully aware of his master in the craft. And lacking humor, especially that the humor of yesteryear, in one of its many variants. Is it missing lack harmony among the exposed pieces are wished a freer driving of the mystery, which is always corseted by the fallible instrument of language. That, at the end and after, Wittgenstein was talking and that just the poor Church falling. They say the good languages that Manchu awaits you. Veremos.A this cam except burning, some scenes of undeniable talent: the Museum of counterfeit parts, the aforementioned plano-secuencia and some memorable phrases halfway between the enigma and poetry that permeate as gold dust in the memory and us afanamos because not end up forgetting their very short text.Perhaps only remember these Oxford murders by a scene in which the camera literally sweeps the scenic space and in a plano-secuencia dinánimo brings together all the protagonists of history and by the presence of Leonor Watling and the flamboyant apron that puts everything in its place. Or alters it it already hopelessly. It is a pity that the actress not be him has demanded more or that its role does not possess more semantic chicha. The other does not you have any discussion and this review aims to ignite the libido of the staff. Elijah Wood in the arms of the voluptuous Watling is a muchachillo with luck and one fears, to force much open our eyes, that the woman engulf it or will make it a poor bag of bones. Anyway, he didn't finish I there, but the language has forced me.</body>
</review>
