<review author="Moebius" title="El halcón maltés" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Maltese Falcon, one of the final films of classical Hollywood.</summary>
	<body>When one faces a script where memorable phrases are so many that you can hardly one remember them all or choose one to open an entry like this, and when that script presents a story whose plot keeps you in suspense until the end, and rhythm works like a Swiss Watch and the characters interact among themselves in such a way that one comes to think that reality is on the screen and not in What we feel and touch, no doubt we can say that it is not only one of the best works of the genre, but that hardly could leave something unworthy of a job well. If add to the talent of one of the best American directors of the history and a hardly surmountable sharing, there is no doubt that we are talking about one of the greatest classics in the history of the cinema. Ladies and gentlemen, join me in the search for a rare and beautiful statuette that was once a gift for the Emperor Charles V: the Maltese Falcon.Before a work of this caliber it is always difficult to write without having the feeling that everything you say is going to be short. I even believe that anyone who loves cinema can speak of the Maltese Falcon without be carried away even a little. Anyway, about to begin somewhere, say I think not mistaken if I say that the film is the best remake of the history of the cinema. And it is that if it sometimes seems that Jimi Hendrix has composed "Hey Joe", it is also sometimes difficult to remember that the Dashiell Hammett novel had already been made into a film in 1931. Ricardo Cortez had been the first Sam Spade, and we had everything a Dwight Frye making bully serving El Gordo (what a pity to not repeat the role under the orders of Huston!).John Huston as several writers participated in the writing of the screenplay, and director worked two days in the storyboard, but it seems they were quite faithful to the novel. Until then Huston had debuted doing small roles but soon had converted in writer. As it is well known, we are talking about one of the best debuts in film history, since this was the first film by Huston as director.And it is that Huston helped lay the foundations of the American noir film, and created a lasting image of the detective's hat and raincoat. Although I am not very placed in detective fiction, it is assumed that this figure already existed in the black own Hammett novels and other authors of the genre such as Raymond Chandler, but at least film regards there we have the final characters, Humphrey Bogart, such interpreter marking an image that still currently influencing filmmakers to fire in the history of the cinema, writers, cartoonists of comic, etc.I certainly think that Bogart him much due to the mistakes of the actor George Raft in their transition from villain of the films the hero and tough guy that made him a superstar. Raft had already rejected the role that would later interpret Bogart in the last refuge, where the drinker friend of actor John Huston was writing the script. Another film after the fuse was prepared, and only needed a spark to launch the career of more stars Bogart. And since the Raft contract stipulated that it was not obliged to act on any remake, and poor George considered that the Maltese Falcon would be another film more of series B, rejected portraying Sam Spade. And finally, as you say, the rest is history.And I don't think there is doubt that Humphrey Bogart was born to play this role. The history and the role were there, just for a little talent to make Sam Spade a legendary figure, and Bogart knew what it was. A tough and shrewd, detective idealist in his own way, loving and cruel with women at a time, a romantic stranger misogynistic, knowing when to speak and when hit, smoker and drinker, and always done with great style. I think that even Dirty Harry was not a similar revolution in a police character from the side of the law.Well, let's talk a little about the history. A woman (Mary Astor) attends the Spade &amp; Archer detective agency that you returned to your side to his sister, who has allegedly fled home to accompany a bad guy. Miles Archer, fascinated by the beauty of the Lady, undertakes to personally follow the bad man, but is killed. His partner, Sam Spade, then takes charge of the case. The gross which had followed Archer dies shortly afterwards. Spade becomes the main suspect, and while police followed closely discovers that the woman he has lied, and his alleged sister there. Behind the mysterious matter is a statuette of great value, and a deferential although viperino man named Joel Cairo (Peter Lorre) will go to Spade to help get the precious object. So Sam Spade will be trying to desenmerañar a murky issue in which will be stuck to the hilt, and where will gradually discover that nothing is what it seems.Disturbing and also magnificent actor Peter Lorre was at the height of Bogart portraying this small albeit dangerous man who does not like being touched, and whose appearance is as elegant as twisted its methods. Few things are more threatening on a screen than a villain of scarf and cane. It is just give him his fair share of gloria. In addition, one of my favorite moments of the film is the first encounter between Spade and Cairo.Como is also the interview of Spade with "Fat Man" Kasper Gutman, who ceaseth not to utter a sort of strange proverbs praising the vital attitude of Spade, man who likes talking and likes to go to the grain and is also quite unpredictable. The character of Gutman is one of the great characters of roundwood has given the film. He was played by the British Sydney Greenstreet, an actor who had spent their lives on stage and which debuted in the Maltese Falcon passed the sesentena. They say that its physiognomy served starting point for the creation of the viscous Jabba the Hutt. Detective Tom is Ward Bond, a regular for several years of the films of John Ford. I also like that, rather than Secretary, women for all of Sam Spade, the intelligent and full of resources Effie, played by Patrick Lee. Incidentally, dying type that delivers the Falcon to Spade is the own father of Huston, making a brief cameo appearance.Perhaps he was lying as one Mary Astor any to say that it was impossible to stay with a phrase from the film. I think that probably all have heard of one in particular. One of the policemen asked to Spade on the composition of the statuette. "Of the material with which they forge dreams", responds the detective. Great contribution to the script, who was inspired to turn Bogart (imagine that it should not be too surprising, there is a better writer than him?) in a sentence of a work of Shakespeare.El Maltese Falcon, one of the final films. It was so good that he apparently served to baptize two terrible mechanical devices that ended with the second world war.</body>
</review>
