<review author="Moebius" title="Perros de paja" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Civilization against ignorance, the city opposite to the field, roots that accompany us throughout life, fear of the unknown, the other "I" hidden after our typical face... Straw, a great work of Peckinpah dogs.</summary>
	<body>Neither Heaven nor Earth have feelings; they are the things of the world as if they were dogs of straw (Laozi).Civilization against ignorance, the city opposite to the field, roots that accompany us throughout life, fear of the unknown, the other "I" hidden after our typical face. Straw dogs, one of the films most violent of Sam Peckinpah (although most of this violence is not on-screen) revolves around these issues and their interpretations can be varied. Everything depends, obviously, eye with that look.A young American mathematician David Sumner (Hoffman), moved with his wife Amy (Susan George) to the home town in Britain to escape chaos and violence of the United States. However his life will not be as idyllic as they could have expected, and they will soon have to face the attacks and abuses of the townspeople.Peckinpah knows very well build the image of a young man sobered to whom his wife accused of cowardice, to then turn the character. David is the human citizen, is the civilization and the law, but wrapped in a dangerous and hostile environment and under an extreme situation is displayed as a predator that defends its territory. It is no accident that your home becomes a fortress, a position of strength from which to defend themselves.If David is the mind, Amy is the body, attached to life, and with a system of values that clash with her husband. When it is attacked by Charlie, it will use its own methods and their own weapons out of the trance. Also represents a sort of duality: he escaped from his people to seek other life, and married a man not handsome, intelligent, but on the other hand you can not escape their past, their own codes of honor and her own education. Asked David to fight for her, that faced with the killers.In the midst of all this gunpowder only need a trigger, and that will be Henry Niles (my dear David Warner), a sort of diminished psychic that he has had problems with the law by harassing some girls, and whose encounter with the daughter of Tom Hedden will end up causing the siege at the home of the Sumner.En those first moments again emerge the confrontation between two different worldsthe David and Amy's. He appeal to justice, what most of us would have in mind in this case. She, much more pragmatic, is like a harassed animal, and asks David to give what they want to the Hedden. "Really you do not mind, isn't it?", says David. But how far you can trust one act? Isolated from everything and everyone, it seems that the only law that can survive at that time is the primary law of retaliation.</body>
</review>
