<review author="Sara Rodriguez" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good atmosphere, good start, good performances... but in the end everything was deflated with a last intrascedente section and let the viewer cold.</summary>
	<body>Each time I am more and more convinced that going to the cinema with expectations is the worst there is. But what it does when you're with a promotion as the crimes of Oxford? It is not that I am a big fan of Alex de la Iglesia but I like enough to want to see any of his movies and much more if you leave my beloved Eleanor Watling.eso without Fro.digo to mention Elijah Wood and John Hurt.Basada in the book of Guillermo Martínez "Murders", the film tells the story of Martinan exchange student who travels to Oxford with the hope that the brilliant Professor Arthur Seldom help you with his thesis. When it already gave everything for lost, the mysterious assassination of his landlady - intimate friend of Seldom - becomes Martin and Professor fellow detectives in an attempt to solve a mystery that seems specifically designed to challenge them.The film begins with force with that plane sequence in which you presented the characters think: well, after a movie that is worth what I paid! It moves at a good pace, featuring John Hurt so sure of himself that seems that you'll reveal all the mysteries of the universe and Elijah Wood right, but with the same face of scare of Frodo. The character of Eleanor, much to my regret appears without coming to story and the rest of interventions in the film are stuck with shoehorn (that not to mention costumes.)Yes, Yes, it is set in 1993 but that does not mean that they will cease to view a color blind xD). The script is not bad, but this mathematical gibberish and the verbiage about series logical blablabla that initially are as well giving pace and they get scheming in the end become against distracting us from the crux of the matter.Basically you could say that I was a little disappointed. Generally is not bad: the actors are correct, despite better function separately; It has a couple of winks very to the Hitchcock, but even so at the end it is deflated and loses all interest that had been keeping from the beginning making even more evident the lack of originality.</body>
</review>
