<review author="Moebius" title="Tiburón" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A stunning film, beautifully shot, and whose recognition was slow to arrive. Spielberg in its purest form.</summary>
	<body>During the first two weeks of July of the year 1916 the coast of New Jersey, a place where many people chose as a holiday and in which a budding tourist industry was creating was terrorised by a series of shark attacks that resulted in four deaths and one injured person. The wave of panic was such that the summer was in the American collective unconscious. between 1974 and 1975, United States, and soon the world would again feel that atavistic terror, although this time the only victims were pockets of spectators and the true nature of the great white shark. At the beginning of the 1970s the writer Peter Benchley came barruntando a story about shark attacks. Your editor encouraged him to write a novel on the subject, so said and done, Benchley returned with a book without a title. Considered many names, some, slap rimbonbantes other, titles such as "Stillness in the water", "Leviathan rising" or "The jaws of the Leviathan". With time running out, Benchley and his publisher chose the least worst: Jaws. The book was a great success, and the Universal producers, who are interested in history, were made with the film rights for 150. $000. Years later the producer David Brown has stated that if they had read the novel twice never would have bought the story because it was clear that it would be very expensive to shoot. But they loved the idea of a shark terrorizing the quiet beaches of the Atlantic. The agency that tried the Universal demanded that her directed a director member of your company. Producers, eager to obtain the rights to the novel, accepted. Somehow, what happened then is the Universal disbanded as he could that poor type, and began to search for a director to his liking. Producers David Brown and Richard D. Zanuck, who had produced the first film for the cinema by a young and talented director, decided to put in front of the project. The young Jew had a long television where a big truck pursues relentlessly a poor type in your car. It seemed the ideal candidate to carry Jaws screen. His name was Steven Spielberg. Spielberg had read the novel he liked, and seeing parallels between the story of Jaws and the history of the truck in the devil on wheels, and not having any other project view, it seemed that he had nothing better to do. The writer Peter Benchley made a first adaptation of his own novel, which Spielberg added some scenes. For example, I wanted to present the sharks Quint Hunter in a cinema laughing out loud as he contemplated Moby Dick, by John Huston. Can you imagine something like this? It would have been worth seeing. But Gregory Peck, who had the rights to the film, not seemed good idea, so the scene could not shoot. To complete the story for the film the script was revised by Howard Sackler, winner of a Pulitzer Prize and an expert diver. His contribution was that Spielberg had just deciding to shoot the film. Sackler requested specifically not included in the closing credits that it did not have time to be in the shooting. Another problem arose shortly thereafter. At the beginning of 1975 a contract with the Screen Actors Guild about to expire put study in trouble. The bosses of the Universal decided that any film shot if he could finish by June 30. With a hyphen without finishing, Spielberg objected some logic to the issue. A new writer, Carl Gottlieb, was hired as a kind of "boy for everything", which he worked on the script, he would attend trials, it would help in the improvisations. In short, would be there for any problem that could arise with the history. Spielberg wanted actors unknown to the film, but the producers insisted that you would with a great name. Roy Scheider, who had worked in The French Connection and was popular at the time, was chosen to play Chief Brody police. For the role of Hooper oceanographer, and after considering several names, Spielberg, on the advice of George Lucas, offered the role to Richard Dreyfuss. The actor loved the story, but he rejected the film. In his own words, the reason was that "he would prefer seeing her to shoot her, because the shooting will be a pain in the ass". Later Dreyfuss attended the premiere of his latest film, The Apprenticeship of Duddy Kravitz, and, after being horrified by their action, decided to accept the role of Hooper. Finally, for the role of the Hunter Quint, Spielberg attended Lee Marvin, who declined the role. Also is barajon names like Sterling Hayden (the police bastard of the Godfather) or Charlton Heston, although at the end the paper was awarded to Robert Shaw, with whom the producers had just work in the coup. The other important roles were to Lorraine Gary as the wife of Brody and Murray Hamilton as Mayor Larry Vaughn, and it is undeniable that such has Mayor face! For the fishermen on the quayside scene he thought to have Joe Spinell, which would have been great, but in the end it was not possible. The next step was, of course, get a shark. The artistic director, Joe Alves, began to meet with designers of special effects without great success. The people of the Guild could not stop tell you make a mechanical shark from seven meters was virtually impossible. Finally Alves gave Bob Mattey, which had built mechanical animals in the past and was retired. Mattey responded that he could do so, he got the job. To recruit the rest of the effects team special Alves searched which he compares with the magnificent 7, it was gradually finding those needed. A new problem arose when looking for a suitable foreign. The place turned out to be Martha's Vineyard, a picturesque place and tourist whose had a sandy bottom up to 12 miles offshore, with what mechanisms could function properly without that land would be nowhere. That was the main reason for Spielberg to choose that village. However, the people there did not want a crew in the full season. The people in the studies had to convince the larger forces of the people that everything would remain as before that came the people of Hollywood. A villager named Craig Kinsbury played one important role both inside and outside the film. According to Spielberg was the local version of the character of Quint, and the director encouraged him to participate in the film, writing their own phrases. He was also the inspiration for phrases of other characters, such as when Quint said "this is not how to get out fishing perches or COD". The shooting, which began around the beginning of the summer of 1974, was to lengthen the unimaginable, emerging problems everywhere. Many had to be filmed on the high seas, thereby placing cameras, calculate angles, prepare boats and actors was an odyssey that nothing remained in place, and not stopped cross boats and sailboats on the horizon. Another problem was the mechanical shark. A great full shark (which Spielberg called "Great white zurullo") and two biased sharks had built to shoot planes from the left or from the right. Although the sequence initial Spielberg had decided to hide the shark so that only see the shocks of the victim in what was a great success, the pure truth turned out to be the shark didn't. In the first test of the mechanical doll in water the piece went to the bottom of the water and had to be rescued by a few frogmen. Remember Richard Dreyfuss in the documentary inside the shark, by radio of the crew not Macaw of heard the phrase "the shark is not working". In what is already a legendary history of Hollywood, the bug with the shark ended up benefiting the film, that have the monster on screen all the time would have made shark in a horror film with Monster to use. Following the old axiom of the character of Kirk Douglas in captives of evil, people feared that that does not see. And shark is a good proof of that. It was decided that it would be amazing to have screenshots of real sharks in the film. Contacted a couple who had worked with white sharks to shoot underwater scenes. The problem was that normal sharks measured 3 or 4 metres and were not so huge as in the film. In a decision quite Spinal Tap was built a small cage and the Universal commanded a fairly quietly type that didn't even know dive so to mess inside the cage. The best scenes were shot when a shark became hooked with the cage and made pieces. As the shots were so good, and there be no one in the cage, changed the script to take advantage of those scenes. In another moment of filming the ship of Quint, "Orca", nearly was scuttled, and while all concerned save actors nobody seemed to remember the sound technician. It is the system of classes Hollywood!While filming was lengthened and the shark just does not work, the relationship between some members of the team wasn't too good. Robert Shaw and Richard Dreyfuss not were supported, which resulted in their respective performances in the film. The tension between Quint and Hooper was more real than it could seem at first glance. Robert Shaw was a guy with charisma, not always easy to treat, and his character was a nasty type. Hooper, Quint and Brody loaded things in the "Orca", Spielberg asked Shaw to try to harass Lorraine Gary, who played the wife of Brody as far as possible. For fifteen years she kept her virginity; not a bad record for this vicinity. When Spielberg, concerned about the rights of author, asked where had taken it, Shaw replied that he had seen on a tombstone in Ireland. It was not only happy improvisation. One of the most popular phrases from the film, "We're gonna need a bigger boat", was improvised by Roy Scheider to shoot the scene. Practically already is a phrase made in the U.S., which demonstrates the great impact of the film. One of the most famous scenes of shark was a mere product of the script. Special effects nor shark through. It is the famous story of the sinking of the USS Indianapolis Quint. The scene had its origin in a small paragraph written by Howard Sackler. Spielberg wanted to extend the discourse, so contacted John Milius to adding more phrases. Milius Spielberg sent him a lot of pages that gave a summary. Then that part of the script was given to Robert Shaw. The actor was also a writer, and his work included novels and a play. Shaw rewrote part of the script, with what the fabulous story of the USS Indianapolis was the result of the work of three great writers. It is not surprising that for many this is the favorite scene of shark. According to lengthened the filming, the "Department of special defects" (as so dubbed Spielberg) wanted to stop filming to refine the shark and other effects, but the producers feared that you scrapped the entire project. With all the team up the walls, at a charity gala dinner Roy Scheider began a war of food which ended with food thrown through the air in a pitched battle of food among the team. Luckily at the time of filming the final scenes the shark began operating, which attacks the shark from the ship in two and up above, and the final scene where flies through the air could complete. For the death of Quint had designed in a similar to the of the captain Ahab of Moby Dick destinations, with Quint speared the big shark and being dragged by him to the depths of the sea, perishing drowned. Spielberg did not like him and changed it to the end that we all know. The shark flies through the air and as it sinks we heard a strange roar is nothing but a roar of dinosaur of an old film that the director had already used by the end of the devil on wheels. Many scenes on the high seas were filmed camera in hand, but as says the director of photography, the camera often relied on the legs, arms or other parts of the body. Spielberg said of trying to always shoot at the same height of water, to give the impression to the Viewer to be bathing in those bloody waters. On the other hand, before you start shooting it ensured that the artistic director will not use the color red in any design. The only red that Spielberg wanted was blood. They are small details, which may seem stupid, which can reach the viewer in a subconscious manner. In another great scene, while Chief Brody monitors the beach seated, Spielberg wanted to have the shot in one take continuous. Finally developed the scene from the point of view of Brody, following an observación-reacción approach: as bodies of swimmers cross ahead of the camera, the level is changing and we see what he sees Brody then see their reaction. A really brilliant execution. When the sheriff finally realizes what is happening, Spielberg gave back to an innovative trick of camera by Hitchcock in Vertigo, moving the camera while expands the zoom level. Along with the Assembly of veteran Verna Fields, who the director called "mother Assembly", and of who probably learned some other trick, it is no doubt that much of the success of the film comes from the soundtrack. The acclaimed composer John Williams, which seems that you long it resting on its laurels, shot to fame for his work in this film, winning a well-deserved Academy Award. Although when taught him at the piano for the first time Spielberg who had composed the director thought he joked. The score of Williams has two functions: join the shark, as if somehow he would show his State of mind in every scene, if you move fast or slow, or if it rises to the surface or moves away, and, on the other hand, announce their presence to the Viewer. With it last had a dual effect, that if we see the movie soon we associate the presence of that disturbing music to the appearance of the creature, with what when it emerges without prior music the shock is even greater. The composition of Williams has been on the popular imagery associated with horror film, as it was in its day the music of psychosis. And is that if this tape Hitchcock revolutionized the genre of horror in his day becoming fashionable to the figure of the psycho, with Spielberg shark marked a before and a later in the films with creatures terrifying, being copied endlessly. All the films that have followed are daughters of shark. The film, released in the summer of 1975, swept the box office around the world, and became the film highest grossing of all time until the arrival of Star Wars. And not only that, is also an impressive film, beautifully shot, and whose recognition was slow to arrive. Just that happened you to Hitchcock in his day, the success of the work of Spielberg among the public has subtracted credibility, but for me his best films resist the onslaught before almost any Classic you can remember. </body>
</review>
