<review author="Moebius" title="Grand Hotel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Grand Hotel was without a doubt one of the best works of Irving Thalberg and one of many classics that have arisen from the MGM factory. Essential.</summary>
	<body>An ex-camarera who had worked in Berlin luxury hotels raided the German literary scene with his Grand Hotel. In 1929 Vicki Baum achieved a great success of sales with a description of the events and characters that can be found in an establishment of such characteristics. On the other side of the Atlantic, a young flacucho and sickly put his eyes in this work even before that it was translated into English.In the young producer Irving Thalberg MGM Studios, infallible creator of both critical and public success, was looking for a new project. Through a synopsis Thalberg gave to what I was looking for, but there was a problem: a small Broadway businessman had done with the rights to the novel. But one businessman looking for investors for his work, and Thalberg took his pportunities: gave $15,000 to do the work, and paid other 20 thousand for the film rights. And incidentally already had an adaptation of the novel that the dessert would have a great success in theatres around the country.After polishing the script producer put hands to work. The first thing was to put a face to the main character of the work, the Ballerina Grusinskaya. Thalberg immediately thought of the most glittering star of his time, Greta Garbo. In the beginning, the Swedish actress turned down the role, because he believed that he was too old for the role with 27 years. But finally the producer convinced her, and "La Divina" would be the dancer coming to less. With the approval of the Garbo, Thalberg made after cameras Edmund Goulding, with a reputation of being a good director of actors.And it was what was needed, since Thalberg had in mind a very strange idea for its time: bring together five of the most important stars of Hollywood in one movie. So strange was that the producer had to convince the Almighty Louis B. Meyer that was a good idea.Grand Hotel would then have five big characters interacting among themselves, each with its own problems and interests. Apart from the aforementioned dancer, have a ruined Aristocrat converted thief, an anxious magnate by finalizing a merger, a poor stenographer to the orders and an empleadillo of the magnate who is left with little time to live and decides to spend their savings to big living his last days.For the role of male Heartthrob, the Baron Von Geigern, Garbo loved John Gilbert, who had already worked in the past, and with whom he had a short romance. But Gilbert had more and more problems with drinking and his career was going downhill, so Thalberg suggested him that he changing his mind. Who did not change was the usual cameraman of the Garbo, William Daniels.Buscando Heartthrob and the sick man, Thalberg thought Buster Keaton for this last character, but Meyer vetoed his proposal. It was in another production of Thalberg, Arsene Lupin, where the producer gave with his gallant: John Barrymore (grandfather of Drew). Barrymore accepted on the condition that his brother Lionel would also participate in the film. Thalberg agreed, but made John sign a contract of three films with MGM. Lionel Barrymore would be terminally ill Kringelein, and John Barrymore (known as "The great profile", if you see the movie know why) the Baron Von Geigern.El cast was completed by Wallace Beery as Preysing businessman. Beery initially turned down the role, but Thalberg convinced him assuring him that it would be the only character to talk with German accent. The challenge appealed to the actor and accepted the offer.For the role of the sensual stenographer Flaemmchen decision could not have been better; Thalberg was signed to another great female star of MGM, the actress of great talent and beauty of Tiger Joan Crawford. To avoid clashes of egos, avoided the characters of Garbo and Crawford coincide in any scene. In addition, set out Crawford shot in the morning while Garbo would do so in the afternoons. A small role would be for Lewis Stone, former silent film Heartthrob.After saving some reticence, Barrymore and Garbo were very good during the filming, to such an extent that Barrymore alongside actress Noll Gurney subsequently organized the funeral of John Gilbert to the satisfaction of the Garbo. Lionel and Beery was going to yours, and Crawford, typical therein, was concerned about highlight somehow. Certain Crawford day feigned illness filming in the afternoon to coincide with Garbo. What could have been a disaster was a brief greeting. Even throughout a Joan Crawford finally intimidated in the presence of "divine", but the Garbo was friendly with her and asked him as he was. A rarity in the psychotic history of the Crawford (famous was his eternal battle with Bette Davies).However, with similar distribution and a good story behind it, nothing could fail and nothing failed. Grand Hotel is a watchmaking machine where everything fits, pace is so perfect as a well greased engine, and the characters entering and leaving in a totally natural way. The Garbo shines once again, with their own light, and deep voice captivates the Viewer, leaving a phrase for the story, I want to be alone. Perfectly complies with John Barrymore, although at first it might seem already too old for the role, being able to be romantic and hard at the same time. His brother Lionel makes us laugh and cry at the same time, while the gross Beery intimidated by their presence. Finally, Joan Crawford, wonderfully sexy, reminds us that it was also a great actress.Grand Hotel was without a doubt one of the best works of Thalberg and one of many classics that have arisen from the MGM factory. Essential.</body>
</review>
