<review author="Moebius" title="La ventana indiscreta" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Rear window could be a perfect summary of the work of Hitchcock.</summary>
	<body>You ever been surprised themselves snooping by the window, watching the neighbor that watered the plants, the boy dancing, the child who plays? Have you regodeado at the sight of a beautiful and young human specimen stripping is? Have you been embobados looking a couple give kisses? Come on, not deny, their eyes are faster than their moral restrictions. You, friends and friends, are observers, volunteers or involutarios, but onlookers to the end and Cape. You are a voyeur, as I am. Come, come, they are not shy. Leave out the small Alfred Hitchcock being inside and take a look through their window.Rear window, based on a small story of Cornell Woolrich, has become over the years one of the great classics of the orondo Hitch. If I had to do a top ten of their best films rear window would occupy one of the top without a doubt. The film is not only a prodigy of cinematic technique, but that is also an ode to the healthy pleasure of "voyeurism", an ode by Hitchcock to the prying and harmless onlookers.J.B. Jeffries is an intrepid and award-winning photographer to the Robert Capa that after suffering an accident convalece in your room plant and in a wheelchair in the Hot New York summer. His only consolation are the brief visits of biting nurse and his elegant girlfriend Lisa Fremont. The greater part of the day Jeffries solaza staring out the window and watching the daily activities of its varied neighbors. Everything will change when certain day begins to suspect that a murder has been committed in a floor of the building from the front. Although limited by his broken leg, Jeffries will not stop to unmask the murderer.After having shot a film as the rope using a single flat continuous around 1954 Alfred Hitchcock sought a new technical challenge. The British found what I wanted in the old history of Woolrich. After interview with screenwriter John Michael Hayes and the shadow of a doubt as his favorite film of the director, tell you Hitchcock (outside or not for that reason) hired him to adapt the short play It Had To Be Murder. The director invited him to the filming of perfect crime and told him that you happen with Grace Kelly a pass from weeks to know it and then write the draft of history. Hayes did so with what the final portrait of Lisa has traits of the character of the actress, although Lisa is really a fusion between Kelly and the woman herself of Hayes, who had worked as a model and knew that world of designs and Couture.After raising first as a challenge, history was trapping Hitchcock, and along with Hayes gave us one of the kaleidoscopes on life à là stronger Hitch that left us his work. If I had to submit to the most innovative Hitchcock perhaps choose Vertigo or psychosis; If I had to show to the Hitchcock technically mature and commercial perhaps I decantaría by with the death on the heels; But if you had to sum up his work and his life in a film only think I decantaría by rear window. If not all, there is almost everything that surrounds the work of British director par excellence: superb flat technicians, old suspense inspired by real crimes, and the smooth rhythmic Cadence of their stories. We also have the blonde of ice that hides a volcano of passion in its interior, the passion for observing the world from a safe place and hidden desire, one of the big leifmotiv of the director. And in this strange courtyard of Greenwich Village we have a picture of love in its different phases and types. First we have the protagonists: Lisa, the perfect woman to love, and Jeff, prototype of the man that is shy to engage more in their relationship and lose their freedom of action. And we have the neighbors: the newlyweds they mate relentlessly, the mature spinster who seems condemned to solitude, the composer solo and drinker, the young dancer by which all men long marriage without children who have resigned themselves to pamper a dog, and finally, the old marriage where love out the door long ago and have only been fights and grudges.Hitchcock returned to the idea of filming in a single closed space that had already developed in the rope, although this time set aside to focus on what the director (and many others) considered the essence of cinema the single level in the rear window: action and reaction. Good Hitch speaks in the famous book Truffaut on this theory with which he experimented Kulechov, the master of Vsevolod Pudovkin, and has points in common with the use of the flat contraplano. Virtually all the window indiscreet is based on this principle: we have a map of James Stewart looking out the window, then a map of what he is watching, and then have a third level of Stewart where look at their reaction to what you see. This is perhaps the film principle par excellence.Hitchcock was originally going to shoot really in Greenwich Village, but considering that the results were not satisfactory decided to lift some bulky decorated life-size in the Paramount Studio 18, the largest that had ever raised in the producer. Even so, the director needed more flats. Given that the height of the study wasn't enough, Hitch decided to disassemble the soil and build the patio at the height of the basement, while the floor of the photographer Jeff was at the level of the soil. A complex lighting system (called team to other studios and rented all kinds of lamps and bulbs) was able to simulate day and night, dawn and dusk. The demand for energy was great, and the warmth of the old lights stretched to actors and technicians. One day they jumped the antiicendios sprinkler and everything was flooded, so the set was in the dark. The old Hitchcock left in the dark to a study!Action and reaction are put aside in few but decisive moments. One is the scene of the death of the dog, where the point of view of Jeff is omitted. In this special drama mento mo we can see the scenery in all its dimensions. On the other hand, during much of the film the audience becomes the eyes of Jeff and sees what he sees. Hitchcock, which is called the master of suspense for good reason, just breaks that trend to make us partakers of something that the photographer is not seeing. Remember, directors of the suspense that you are outside: the public always a little more than your characters.Another element that accompanied Hitchcock during his career and emanating from its formation in the era of the silent film era is the display and report without using any dialogue. In the scene that opens the film after the titles of credits came to know almost everything about Jeff: his name, does, if it is enjoys prestige in his work and the reason for his convalescence, all without that have been handed down to a single word. Today it is difficult to shoot as well.The distribution of rear window has which have probably been the favorite players of Hitchcock: Grace Kelly and James Stewart. The actress shot one film before leaving the film and move to Monaco, something that infuriated the director. Stewart continued rolling with Hitch until both realized that the actor was already too old for exercise of protagonist Heartthrob and action scenes. A Thelma Ritter graciosa excels in his role as nurse of the photographer. Raymond Burr (the famous Ironside!) was elected for the villain. They have that Hitchcock chose to Burr because it could resemble the producer David o. Selznick, who the director was not a pleasant memory.Said Hitchcock if one placed a story in France should appear the Eiffel Tower; If one filmed on Switzerland should have mountains and chocolate to be used. If you wheel in Holland characters must pass through a mill. The place or objects should serve as support to what is narrated. How you defend the villain a character photographer who lives in Greenwich Village and spends the day in a wheelchair? Those who have seen the film to know the answer. Those who do not, look in the rear window.</body>
</review>
