<review author="Jesus David" title="Viaje a Darjeeling" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If at the end the see, so if you like it or not, you do not say that I have not warned. The film is the kind that housewives or hate them. I like hate it have not been blood and love I leave it for other things, so fu nor fa.</summary>
	<body>Funny comedy of Wes Anderson, which brings Adrian Brody, Owen Wilson and Jason Schwartzman (health), in a film that seems to trip is nowhere, that lacks only sense and. come on, rarely of balls. Premieres January 4, it would be because the first comedy which premiered in 2008, although I would recommend that you for a laugh, and if still in poster, go to see Hot Fuzz (whose criticism I still have pending). Why, laughter, or grace nor ná de ná. Perhaps I do that I like uncouth humor and not I understand the comic vein of Anderson, but it seems he has made the film for himself and his gafapastas chums. I better tell you a bit of will and already decide you, although I do not think that you draw no conclusion.Before the start of the film issued us a short that starred the character of Jason (I refuse to write his surname again) and Natalie Portman, if the producer to the end not decided to issue the short before the movie so you can search on youtube or similar. You can also see Natalie Portman nude.Which I still continue reading after say it last, say that the film is about a trip he organized three brothers (of blood) to the India, in search of spirituality in their lives, although the trip then take another sense I do not desvelaré to not spoil the grace. for one that has. Although I am not going to be bad, we are at Christmas, the film itself is very entertaining, in addition, Owen Wilson comes out, is the best of the film, the majority of points, and blows, fall therein. Adrian Brody is also correct, but still no consigo quitarme his character in the pianist of the head, which is why I is still difficult to accept his comic side.Then. What is it? I spend the peel to see this movie or I better call a pizza and see the repetition of the 1st new year's Eve special on a Sunday afternoon? Therefore not be I worse. With the mess of Christmas, Kings and others, go to take refuge in the cinema to see this movie isn't a bad option. Indeed it is the only good option of the first batch of releases of 2008. If at the end the see, so if you like it or not, you do not say that I have not warned. The film is the kind that housewives or hate them. I like hate it have not been blood and love I leave it for other things, so fu nor fa. FUA.</body>
</review>
