<review author="José Córdoba" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There is no substantial changes in tone with respect to the above, returning to repeat the same mistakes and others are accentuated.</summary>
	<body>Jack Sparrow is back and with the whole his troupe pirates, in this successful continuation of the film directed by Gore Verbinski two years ago. If one has to define it in one sentence, it would be "more of the same". There is no substantial changes in tone with respect to the above, returning to repeat the same mistakes and others are accentuated. His greater burden is excessive length for so little history, moreover, has no conclusion because he has shot together with the third party, who will come to be the piece of history that lacks it. Thus we have a film of more than two hours to which could perfectly remove him thirty minutes, because its central section becomes eternal, the not happen nothing really. It is a pity because the film starts well, with verve, with a scene in a really fun Cannibal Island, but from there, put the brakes to the rhythm and the plot and enters the monotony, that only leaves in its final stretch. Johnny Depp is fun, even more last lap than the first, but is what he asks his character so perfect, Orlando Bloom and Keira Knightley are as dull as of custom. However, best of the function, as already happened in the first, we found it in the villain role played by Bill Nighty, although it is an infographic creature half human half squid, perfectly created by ILM. Its action and the work of ILM is so perfect that we can distinguish in a fully digital creature to the old rokero of Love Actually. In an era where already nothing surprises us this turns into something very remarkable. The direction of Verbinski returns to be very effective and adequate, away from the excesses of all factory Bruckheimer productions. The script with very funny moments suffers from the problem of having split down the Middle, stretching the plot for two films, but lacks it content to fill the two and a half hours which takes the film. The worst aspect of the film, as well as in the first, returns to music excessive 30metre, out of tune, overwhelming, aggressive, too, that only manages to find tone in the comic scenes, but in general can cause headaches. It was composed by Hans Zimmer and five or six others in auto pilot mode, being the antithesis of the great work he did for the code da Vinci. Really little else to say, if you liked the first this you will like depending on the degree of requirement you have, if not you do not try. I enjoyed the first with nuances and this also, but with more stick still. The structure of the trilogy has as a clear model of the original trilogy of "The wars" but, unfortunately, is light, never better said, hehe.</body>
</review>
