<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="La Sombra del Reino" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If the personal taste is to see 100 percent action without paying the necessary attention to the characters and the story, this film is the ideal.</summary>
	<body>Lead to the big screen real conflicts which has submerged the war policy of the United States.UU and treat the espinozo subject of relations that this country has held with Saudi Arabia, can be somewhat heroic, something intimately personal such as we saw last year with Lions for Lambs or finally a small, medium or large disaster. This tape of the actor, screenwriter, producer and director Peter Berg was approached by my last option and what little I will talk about this tape so will show it.If the personal taste is to see 100 percent action without paying the necessary attention to the characters and the story, this film is the ideal. With a writer almost unknown built a story simple, already known and without many pretensions. It makes very clear that the intention is not to take party for one country or another, but for the cotrario reflect the bonds of friendship and humanism while in adverse situations. But although this sounds nice and well mounted, the truth is that history fails to impress. And this eagerness to remedy these relations and the way in which certain Americans are all those of the Middle East is almost failed of its director, giving thanks to the (s) friendship (en) with babies in those regions.I can tell you that the start is very good, in fact it is better with another great scene of great action that occurs on a highway, but from there onwards his pace is slow as they are given a unnecessary extended to certain scenes and so passes between history and bullets until it reaches its end without anything exciting happen. An ending that leaves the plot into nothingness, in a zero point.Actions also liked, Jaime Foxx makes a common role, although admittedly, had no where to take to be able to show off. Its interpretation is equal to others already seen by him. What could better describe their interpretation is when the word "transaction" is mentioned. And definitely not liked anything performance of Jennirfer Garner a role that I think was not for her, or was not the time to accept it because it is very little credible. Lead a woman to the war, a country that little accepts the presence of women in such conflicts, turned out a very forced and element that made the desire to not leave absent this "resort" female film notorious. However and again them, the arguments for the character of Garner do demonstrate.</body>
</review>
