<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting film of intrigue, targeted at the technical level by the Bilbao Álex de la Iglesia.</summary>
	<body>nteresante film, especially on paper, targeted on the technical side by Álex de la Iglesia, although not convinced at all in their exposure to images.It is based on a good novel by Guillermo Martínez, and its translation to the celluloid was no easy undertaking given the argument, where numerous dialogues and situations have to do with mathematics and its derivatives full.Read it is a thing, and see it on screen quite another. Alex has tried, but the printed pace and the irregularity of situations make interest come and go in a vague way.The beginning is really good, and their first 20 minutes or so are displayed with agility, showing great dialogues and a presentation of the characters, especially the mother and daughter, perfectly explanatory of their psychology.However, little by little the film glides towards an undefined territory, with dialogues and scenes that extend more than due (many scenes with the police inspector), struggling with the pace and making the interest was diluted somewhat, though, and this do not know if it comes in the novel or is the product of the imagination of Alex and George, writers of the film, occasionally enriched with truly subjugating sub-historias, as in the old criminal case of the tailor and his wife. A fascinating story, I do not know happened in real or invented life, but in any case has great strength and no little black humor, if it reflects.And this is perhaps what we miss you less to this film, being directed by Álex de la Iglesia, not have more humor. Probably because the original story does not, but it would have not been bad insert fun sometime, although the perplexity shown by the police inspector before the reflections of two mathematicians, seem to be going by that site. But the truth is that they do not laugh (do not know if it is what is intended).Anyway, it is an appreciable, not inconsiderable, film that entreteniene at all times and one always wants to know what will happen later, how will finalize everything. And this end is not to be very beyond. The movie ends somewhat abruptly and with some coldness. I guess that the novel has more force but in screen could even leave a sediment of disappointment.Excellent interpretation of John Hurt and the music by Roque Baños.</body>
</review>
