<review author="Berto" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Correct film by Alex de la Iglesia, that although it doesn't have the personal seal of the director manages to entertain and play with the Viewer, without having a spectacular script, the looser of the film as a whole.</summary>
	<body>I confess that Álex de la Iglesia is one of the few names of cinema that is able to move me to a home movie, and I guess that the main cause is that the Bilbao has clear, above many other laudable functions, cinema is entertainment. The Oxford murders is faithful to this principle, and that is well appreciated. Martin (Elijah Wood) is a Ph.d. student from Arizona reached very Oxford University, which expected its thesis is directed by the eminentísimo Arthur Seldom (John Hurt), a Professor of logic a bit skeptical. Despite the fact that they soon realize it has both have conflicting views, not them it will be forced to join their bright minds to discover who is the serial killer who tries to capture the attention of Seldom using mathematical games.Said out there that this is the least personal film of Álex de la Iglesia, and to tell the truth, here and there is no great action sequences, nor is there the black humor that often permeate the Filmography of the Basque director. Moreover, if something is the Oxford murders is you need long speeches and dialogues in which the process logical characters, no simple thing, post that combines philosophy, logic, mathematics and even quantum physics can continue while in dose light enough to not cause irreversible brain damage to those who have suffered the ESO. The hand directing of Church has its own merit in that, also in two magnificent sequences (the false flat sequence that precedes the first crime and the concert in commemoration of Guy Fawkes) which are undoubtedly the best of the film.That Yes, the way in which the characters interact is sometimes a little strange: Martin arrives in a new city where not known to anyone, and after 20 minutes, after only exchange a few words with Beth (Julie Cox) and Lorna (Leonor Watling), already it has the two in the pot: laugh you the Axe effect. By the way, seeing the disaster that often happens when an actor bends himself, is thank that to Leonor Watling also her have doubled. That Yes, everything else that appears on screen is yours, and well appreciated that, although their role is undoubtedly the weakest of all, above all by profiling bad that is. Obviously John Hurt shines with their own light, and Elijah Wood is also good, although those porcelain doll eyes distract theirs.In the end occurs as always: twists, recontragiros and other stunts fatal to finish with an end that, if well within the strange logic of the film not clashes too, it is so complicated and so unlikely that one is left with the feeling that have spared you something along the way. That Yes, if the Sudoku will fall short, this is your movie.</body>
</review>
