<review author="JLO" title="Soy leyenda" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Happy compassionate ending fails to ruin I am Legend although she makes it unfinished and they also told me that the end of the book by Matheson is more lucid, solid and recordable.</summary>
	<body>Speaking of I am legend, the first film tank of the year, is not only outline details of its strengths and weaknesses (though then do so). It is to speak of a film succeeded and failed, an experience found sensations and is to speak first of its director.Many times ninguneada the work of the filmmaker for the importance of other factors such as a famous book (of Richard Matheson's 1954 of the same name), a box office actor (Will Smith, more mature here than usual in its prolific FX tapes) and even other previous versions with Vincent Price and Charlton Heston in the leading. Speaking of Francis Lawrence is speaking of hits in a genre that is prone to excesses (Director of the also successful Constantine). His desolate New York is oppressive, his camera in hand provides nerve in its first half and not wallows solving subtlety with the death of the protagonists empathetic of the film. The good use of the flashbacks give the necessary information and they do not complicate the plot, religiosity does not bother by the naif of dialogues (God loves us us so we love him?) as if did it at times in his previous film. It is just also thank that patriotism is not present despite being a military the protagonist and on black top (not proliferate the classical flags starry wind). The story is simple and reminds others, a lone hero in fight with beings vampirizados where the epidemic unleashed, here and now, translates into a clear allusion to HIV and its current expansion. They are all cliches (calls by radio in search of survivors, search for supplies, pet friendly, etc) even the cartoon symbol Argentina El Eternauta trafficking a similar event with more strength and height if you want to. And here we reach the comparisons with extermination (28 days later), 2002 become inevitable because of too many characteristics in common. That WINS by desolation, the proximity of bodies infected without any digitization, for its elegance and its end. Now we understand Danny Boyle and its multiple endings, as if they were necessary for sincerity and as if he understood the business to all leave happy. Happy compassionate ending fails to ruin I am Legend although she makes it unfinished and they also told me that the end of the book by Matheson is more lucid, solid and recordable. But the Chief merit of I am legend is returned in good shape the film of genre (does science fiction? do Thriller? do suspense?) into a film to flow, which is honest, that achieves both and perhaps unwittingly, the pleasure and the desire to see cinema in the film (which is not little).PS: There is No bombastic music that remarque climates, only the story of Bob Marley and his legend CD used as leiv motiv of the film and the references to the comics are delicious (posters of the "future" Batman/Superman and another of the Green Lantern movie!)</body>
</review>
