<review author="José Antonio Bermúdez" title="Los Simpson: La Película" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The life of a family in cartoons has become a cultural reference of (our) Western society. Again, what do they love us so much? Let us be more precise, what does Homer (Homer) that we want to both?</summary>
	<body>What are the Simpsons? Became one of the most awaited movies of recent times. Yes, Yes, anyone would think that you it's an advertising phrase of the Hollywood industry. Nothing to do. It is the first film of the most important family of the last decades: the Matt Groening Simpson (s). Now that we're drunk of mass media, internet (youtube), television content (garbage) are criticized above all &hellip; what have the Simpsons to have remained so long in the cathodic screen? They have marked, continue marking an era. The life of a family in cartoons has become a cultural reference of (our) Western society. Again, what do they love us so much? Let us be more precise, what does Homer (Homer) that we want to both?The epicenter of all this is a generational issue, represented by the main figure. The vast majority that they identified a few years ago with Bart, they have now become Homer. At least they understand Homer. They identify with Homer. Empatizan with their everyday problems with the way of life, whether or not they agree with its decisions. Homer is a honest character, transparent, sincere towards the audience. Homer, there is secrecy, beyond drawing strokes and becomes a character of flesh and blood. More real than other attempts in television and film, with recognized actors, directors trying to tell us important stories (remember American Beauty).For so many years the television series has been consistent, renewing the fair and maintaining a theme according to the situation. So, within the Simpsons should be everything: madness, surrealism, the constant reference to cultural icons. The Simpsons have been with us so long &hellip; logical, demanded it the public, it was to see the family on the big screen. Necessary, by way of homage. The result, an enlarged chapter, a giant Homer. It could not be otherwise. Introducing the digital animation of how accurate, as required it an adventure of such a scale. Fun and ecological message, according to the times we live. The Simpsons could not escape such responsibility. And Homer (by way of redemption) the save his family, his world, his everything.</body>
</review>
