<review author="José Córdoba" title="La joven del agua" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You can enjoy more if you like adult fairy tales, if you enjoy with the completion of one film rather than with the robustness of a script, if you can overlook certain details by the enjoyment of some memorable scenes.</summary>
	<body>After his controversial film "El Bosque" is here the new job of director of Hindu origin, M. Night Shyamalan, "The water boy". Before analyzing the film I would like to point out that the Director seems to me one of the more interesting now, able to give real personality to their works, something that, unfortunately, increasingly is less abundant. His style of shooting, paused, avoiding the levels of very short duration in the Michael Bay style, makes a rare bird, especially working for a large Hollywood Studio. Her first film of renown was "The sixth sense", a habilísima film, which redefined the horror genre and that has had numerous imitators. His next project, "The protected" was not the commercial success that was expected, although for me it remains the best of her films, a parable about good and evil, with atmosphere of series as more beyond the limit or the limits of reality, that also ends up being the most original and best film on superhérores shot so far. Her two subsequent films end up being less interesting, both "Signals" as "El Bosque" wasted great part of its achievements in a final stretch oriented towards a final turn nothing compelling and that too requires the Viewer to be credible. The latter should not be a problem a priori, multitude of films presented impossible worlds filled with unknown beings but always from a fantastic point of view. Shyamalan always makes an approach to the fantasy that surrounds us from a strict point of view realistic, so any behaviour or illogical thesis is rejected by the Viewer. One more thing, taking a fully identifiable style, Shyamalan is approaching each movie with some new resource that can fascinate or irritate or, simply, leave indifferent. Serve as examples the levels through reflective surfaces in "The protected" or roll back to the characters that hide something, most notably William Hurt in "El Bosque", latter somewhat irritating.After this brief tour we reached his last film "The young water", a project that had problems to see the light, mainly by the refusal of the regular study of the director, Walt Disney Pictures, submitted by Shyamalan screenplay. Finally the film has been produced by Warner Bros. animation. and a new failure for the study has been this year, after "Superman Returns" (which will get the money just to cover expenses) or "Poseidon" (which, hopefully, will cover 50% of the budget). "The girl of water", that tells the story of a vigilante of an apartment building that receives a peculiar visit the swimming pool of the complex, it is narrated from the start, like a fairy tale, narrated in his foreword in original version by David Ogden Steirs, prestigious actor cast that, curiously, also narrated prologue of "Beauty and the beast". Since the initial level of the film we know we have a Shyamalan film, by the unusual duration of levels, its 1. 85: 1 aspect ratio, which it always takes a great party, his choice of blur the fore in several scenes, which perhaps means that you want the Viewer to see beyond the obviousthen this stylistic ideas always have a justification in the story he tells. In a plan merely carrying out the film is impressive and demonstrates once again that Shyamalan has personality, although he also notices the footprint of Spielberg (the favorite film by Indian director is "In search of the Lost Ark") in photography, reminiscent in some respects to E.T., as well as the choice of using "normal people" as protagonists and certain aspects such as always shoot from a slightly less than the actor point of view. The film falters in the script, very simple for the duration of the film, and that, practically, presents nuances for a character, that of the caretaker, played by Paul Giamatti. And, however, a moment which should be key in the film, which is when it reveals a fact about its past, which explains its current situation, goes almost on tiptoe, lacking the necessary strength. The other characters are traces or outlines of something else, just of a writer, vital to the plot, played by Shyamalan, in a way quite bland certainly has a little more development, but it is burdened by scant interpretative skills of the director. The rest of the multiracial cast is perfect, i.e., each is perfectly suitable to its character, being a great success the casting, which also extends to the strange character that disrupts the tranquility of the neighborhood, played by Bryce Dallas Howard, who already starred for Shyamalan his previous film. Also director, committed to his narration of a fairy tale forgets the reactions of disbelief that may have the characters against what is happening, nobody raises doubts, something essential to bring the film to the audience, his absence causing estrangement and this occurs from the beginning of the film, which is why the people not entering that game fails to appreciate the film. The rhythm is right, but deleting or making more fluid by mounting some scene, in particular that of the protagonist looking for a writer in the apartment building the film would win. But Shyamalan seems so happy with its own script that has failed to rule out totally incidental to the plot scenes, although on the other hand, some of them are very notable in its implementation, something that makes it even more irregular pass of the film. Anyway, should be emphasized its great end, above all the very latest scene, shot, mounted, performed and, above all, musicada in an exemplary fashion, and that if you were really involved in the film, it is very exciting. By the way, special mention to James Newton Howard that composes his best score in the film plane for a film by Indian director, to which comes working from "The sixth sense". His score is a masterpiece, a real example of how put a movie, while in disk, something common in the composer, loses much of the force that has with the images.In short, "The girl in the water" is a film that is best enjoyed if you like adult fairy tales, if you enjoy with the completion of one film rather than with the robustness of a script, if you can overlook certain details by the enjoyment of some memorable scenes. If not, this Act of onanism film of the director is not for you, because make no mistake we Shyamalan has shot a film of 75 million dollars for if same. A pity, because the film with all its shortcomings has moments to remember.</body>
</review>
