<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Las dos y media y ... veneno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about swindlers who want to avail of a few newbies undertakers to perpetrate a scam. Opera prima of Mariano Ozores, which surprises us with a very nice mess comedy and really hilarious moments. Highly recommended</summary>
	<body>Director: Mariano Ozores. duration: 77 minutes.Release date: December 10, 1959.Espectadores: 10.484 human beings.Conversation in the mansion underground of the family of Chinchan of the high peaks and the flowered valleys: I: could see the directorial debut of Mariano Ozores.Ella: of tits the time with your son.Me: That no, that is not tits.She: do the book says of cinema?Me: That is a comedy light, insubstantial, but with a bit of freshness.She: It puts it to give birth, I do not see it.Me: Maybe he had read regarding Ozores is "by-product of inexplicable commercial success" she: accept ship as they are small.Roque (three), had been in no less than 40 minutes but with a smile on the face. Glory to the Almighty, have seen a movie together Ozores. Aleluya.la film is about a guy (Jose Luis Ozores) who works at a gas station and his girlfriend wants to stay with the business of the father (a funeral home of new creation). With the help of a veterinarian (Antonio Ozores), they attend their first assignment, the death of a rich man of the people, very dear. When they arrive at the House, things do not seem to agree at all.If not tell me that it is the first movie as a director Mariano Ozores you would think that it is a great movie, but this finding explains to me why this man came to be what it was. And no I said I, if not my girl (the same that is capable of skinning a film without disheveled). It is a comedy film you mess with a great Jose Luis Ozores (if you had been born in that country which repeated its acronym, we would see him as a genius among the classics) very well supported by his brother and a great King Ferdinand. Situations are of American comedy, even the atmosphere, making many times to think it not be watching a Spanish movie. I laughed a lot, despite being a mood of 50 years ago, there is nothing.In short, film about swindlers who want to avail of a few newbies undertakers to perpetrate a scam. Opera prima of Mariano Ozores, which surprises us with a very nice mess comedy and really hilarious moments. Highly recommended to do with love.Essential viewing for anyone who likes the Spanish classic film.Besitos.P.D: Data from the Ministry and the pussy of the Bernarda appear on wikipedia as synonyms.</body>
</review>
