<review author="Bruji" title="El amor en los tiempos del cólera" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mike Newell uses an unbeatable international cast to reach the heart of the most beautiful romantic story ever written.</summary>
	<body>Intelligent and faithful adaptation of the novel by García Márquez. Mike Newell uses an unbeatable international cast to reach the heart of the most beautiful romantic story ever written. In images, a song of love for Colombia. "It was inevitable: the smell of bitter almonds always reminded him of the fate of the hindered loves". Much rain has fallen from that afternoon of August that by chance, as happen the big findings in life, I discovered "The love in the time of cholera". The passage of time managed to blur the memory of a woman of strong character that I never understood. It is not easy to understand that concrete façades are sensitive hearts safe haven at such a young age. Much to my regret, also evaporated the romantic ideal of pure love that survives only in the difficult art that captures the soul in the role. But twenty years were not enough to erase the image of a courtyard in which grow endless tropical flowers, or the freshness of sunset often soñadas on the Magdalena river, or the smell of the market of my retina in which Fermina Daza iterate the end of an illusion. Without knowing it, forever, I had fallen in love with Colombia.Joe Wright, Atonement director and one of the promises of the current film, knew how to sum up the challenge posed by the film adaptation of a contemporary classic of literature in an accurate sentence: "each novel has as many versions as readers". A reflection that turns into miracle chance that viewers, critics, writers and filmmakers - all readers - coincide in the same vision. The controversy is served and my question about the degree of infatuation of Mike Newell, satisfactorily resolved. "Think about love as a State of grace is not a means for nothing, but an origin and an end in itself". The indent of Ronald Harwood, winner of an oscar for the Piano, can be described as intelligent and faithful. Fidelity, so often promised the author with the solemnity of the oath of Florentino, entails the realization of an almost literal adaptation, which starts by the end of the story and back in an intense flashback, which is the crux of the plot, to return to the first sequence and address the outcome. Within the development, imposes a linear narrative structure to give consistency to this "go and come from hell" which are subjected to the protagonists. The phrases memorable novel they transcribed to the screen with absolute devotion, and try a fanciful characters flirting and stage to overcome the latent of postcolonial folletinesco saga threat which could be reduced the search for love throughout life in time of war and epidemics, when he is stripped of the complex internal travel that recreates the prose clean award Nobel. "It is life and not death that has no limits." Intelligence, for its part, is perceived in two cinematographic licenses which are incorporated into the story. Firstly, the presentation in dialogue - never occurring - a romance that is collected by the pen of steel and the typewriter in endless letters of round-trip; Unfortunately, written in English. On the other hand, bet brave to offer a change of actor for the main character. It passes from very interesting Unax Ugalde to Javier Bardem always effective, not attending for reasons of age, but the purposes espoused by Luis Buñuel in his last film, that dark object of desire. You need a Florentine I bet, emerged from the eyes with those who only know look at the heart, with a diffuse physical traits that are lost among the multitude of the midnight mass, and that it does not correspond with the real Florentine, the meat and bone, which Fermina sees for the first time face to face, in the market to become convinced that everything has been an illusion, the infatuation of a soul without a face. Impeccable production design invoice, his elegant Court, the exquisite work of makeup and costumes, the successful international casting, the art direction that remains attentive to the most insignificant details, such as which fixed his attention on the cages in which carry babies for River trips; and the sensible implementation of a craftsman, Mike Newell, far from being brilliant, is always correct, make love in the time of cholera in a film of unforgettable moments that stifle the fear of the writer, which took several years to be convinced to accept this Anglophone version. "Fifty-three years, seven months and eleven days with their nights". Intimate talks at the lighthouse, the eyes of the satyr who knows that the evil of infidelity is not if only perpetrated with the body, the excessive love of a latina mother (the impressive lady of Brazilian theater, Fernando Montenegro), the icy gaze and outbursts of wrath of the excellent Giovanna Mezzogiorno, and the unmistakable voice of Shakira visiting places of Cartagenaweed in the jungle, the mighty river, the port city of Barranquilla. they cause a shiver that cloudy look. And is that, admitting the impossibility of doing justice to the insurmountable works of Don Gabriel, it is not less true that the human quality of the Colombian people, the colorful spirit of their land, the atmosphere warm and fragrant, passionate, who now live in the novel, too, finally, do so in the film.</body>
</review>
