<review author="José Córdoba" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Having interesting notes in his mathematical dialogues, a good interpretation of John Hurt and a good Bill, cannot cover the expectations by the unrecognizable direction of Alex de la Iglesia and his screenplay that promises much more than what he gives.</summary>
	<body>The Oxford crimes involves the return of Alex de la Iglesia to the address after disappointing at the box office of their last two films 800 bullets and crime Ferpecto. His new film, clearly commissioned, shows that the director is able to renounce their identity signs and make a film away from his personal universe for good and for evil. The film tells us how after the arrival of a young mathematician at Oxford, a prestigious Professor to make his thesis director, death begins to make Act of presence to her around. A serial killer begins to pose a series of logical puzzles only student (Elijah Wood) and the Professor (John Hurt) seem to be able to resolve. The film clearly has a target commercial, no objection in this regard, is in fact a very decent film in that sense. Its duration (about 100 minutes) not weighs in the viewer and the mathematical burden of history is interesting, even though the director not it tries too hard to make it more attractive. Álex de la Iglesia, so committed work is surprising in this sense seems to evade his style the result is a film so impersonal that you could have led anyone. The address is so sterile that seems worthy of a movie of desktop, with the exception of a flat sequence well resolved, but out of place by its inconsistency with the rest of the film. Essentially dialogue film, Church solves almost all of the dialogues with the classic plano-contraplano, arriving tired by his insistence on the resource and the large number of scenes dialogadas between the character of the teacher portrayed by John Hurt and the student played by Elijah Wood. In this aspect the film was disappointing, while the Basque director leaves his mark on the character of a mathematical genius obsessed and prostrate forever in a hospital bed, only in this tortured personaje(interpretado_por_Alex_Cox) and, perhaps the daughter of the first victim of the serial killer (Julie Cox), seems to have left their record label director. The screenplay adaptation of the novel, the first thing that must be indicated is that it sins of literary. With a start too forced and incredible (what it says, by both the situation and characters), then begins to take flight despite the stereotypical characters, but is discursive, too many "intelligent" dialogues between mathematicians for a resolution so poor and force relations, here is unbelievable the relationship that arises between the characters of Leonor Watling and Elijah Wood. As regards interpretations, the result is irregular John Hurt is great as a teacher, in a role very grateful, everything must be said. Elijah Wood well hold the weight of the film, but unfortunately his chemistry with Leonor Watling is null. The latter in fact, because of its role whose unique sense seems the equip cargo sexual narrative based show Anatomy (especially her generous breasts), it is the weaker. Special mention to Julie Cox, a genuine robaescenas of first category. Elsewhere in sections the film is very correct from its cold photography to his artistic direction, passing by herrmanniana music by Roque Baños, with cameo included as conductor (how not!). In this sense the film proves its amplico budget with a very good invoice technique. In summary, the crimes of Oxford despite having interesting notes in his mathematical dialogues, a good interpretation of John Hurt and a good invoice, fails to meet expectations by the unrecognizable direction of Alex de la Iglesia and his screenplay that promises much more of what's on offer. A pity.</body>
</review>
