<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite the successes (that is), it is obvious that is an undoubted lack of hook. The principal of this blame the plot.</summary>
	<body>Not few occasions where films with an overwhelming promotion, they turn out to be a real fiasco. And is that the objective is quite simple: attract the masses to the cinemas. This translates into a major fundraiser in taquilla.pero also, although not always, in a true disappointment: is this the outcome that we this time? Much depends on the expectations that have previously this production, but probably for many Yes has been the case.Blockbuster, the most expensive film in the history of the Spanish cinema, actors with international prestige. 'Alatriste' we presented as a film epic and called to create a before and a later in the national cinematography, but is no doubt that it has not happened: it has failed take an adventure story, nor print excitement and interest. And it is that despite the successes (that is), it is obvious that is an undoubted lack of hook. The main blame for this is the plot, storyline lacking any: everything is based on capturing scenes, often without any determination, on the comings and goings of the 'Captain', in an effort to useless by summarizing the five books of Arturo Pérez-Reverte in a history that has home, no knot or outcome. And although this should not be always a problem, in this case Yes becomes all a problem, with the result of a failed product for many, or worse still, a failure of the current Spanish film.The portrait of the century of gold, the 'Golden and dark' time of our history, is probably the highlight of the film: decorated, photography, somber tone that surrounds permanent tape maquillaje.el is fantastic. But otherwise, the vacuum is obvious. Quevedo, count-Duke of Olivares, Philip historical IV.personajes, despite being not at all bad portrayed, lacking depth in their roles.Viggo Mortensen, one of the main attractions that was a priori, not disappointed: despite the fact that her accent collides a bit at the beginning, one is just getting used. In fact, the weight of history (and the film) falls on him, and despite making a commendable performance, fails to make the film to take off. The rest of the actors, better or worse profiteers, do their work properly, or at least mostly: Javier camera, Juan Echanove, Enrico Lo Verso, Elena Anaya, Ariadna Gil, and Pilar López de Ayala (in a very short role) meet, although he could not say the same of Blanca Portillo, that does what it can in his male role; and Unax Ugalde and Eduardo Noriega, who they note too 'cool' to the 17TH century.The soundtrack and sound effects seem to be a true reflection of what the Viewer is found before: good ideas and purposes, but totally unused long, have as a consequence an inappropriate positioning of the music in the scenes of fighting and a lack of emotion in other passages of the film.Thus, we find the fundamental problem of this title, and that it well serves as a summary: an attempt to have something big and not knowing how to do it. This time not are you can blame the failure to the lack of means, as 24 million euros given for something else. much more: Agustín Díaz Yanes, has been half way, possibly collapsed. Even the battle scenes have the force: why not some flat better exploited, or larger? What happens with emotion? is it that he could not count with more extras?Good luck to the next.</body>
</review>
