<review author="Sandavito" title="Beaufort" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Even if you have many common places, Beaufort is a film worth, with an extreme situation in which soldiers, only can resist vain until they give you the order to leave, while they consolidate their ties of friendship.</summary>
	<body>Taking advantage of its nomination for an Oscar as best foreign language film, let's talk about a little bit of Beaufort, Estadounidense-Israelí Joseph Cedar.Beaufort, (from the French, strong bonito), it is a castle of Arab origin occupied by Crusaders in the 12th century. As a point of interest, strategic, and located in the territory of the Lebanon, it was taken by the Israeli army from 1976 until 2000, year in which the last troops withdrew. Beaufort, the film tells the life of these last Israeli soldiers entered a part of history.Joseph Cedar signs a formally correct tape, with an abundant cast, and giving more strength to the characters and their relationships that the historical and political environment in which they are framed. In fact, such a situation of war no longer a mere abstraction, an enemy completely invisible, and often nonexistent, with a castle considered sacred to go to soak up the Sun, and, ultimately, with a handful of kids playing to be greater.Ron Leshem, Israeli writer of great success, which we saw in the last week of Experimental cinema in Madrid, wrote his book Im Yesh Gan Eden (if heaven exists) that is based the film, and has also collaborated in the writing of his screenplay. Journalistic source, he was awarded in 2006 the highest existing in Hebrew literature, the Sapir Prize award. Focusing mostly on the relations of these kids that, necessarily have to perform military service of three years, Leshem develops a claustrophobic argument, in clear parallels with the labyrinth of tunnels that make up the Israeli fortress. Nevertheless, and despite a great turning point in the first half hour of the film, these relationships are seeing reduced to a succession of give-and-take between a novice and immature, obsessed official to comply with the orders, and his group of soldiers and friends who think only leave the place as soon as they can. The official, finally, will be redeemed and will return as the prodigal son to the Israeli home.Beaufort is a film that makes long, because it has a huge flaw: the pace. Halfway more or less, everything is going well, but then it breaks down, taking in some character development that we deem, they knew before all were already friends before, or were neighbouring or something similar. Because everytime a new soldier arrives at the detachment, all are treated with great naturalness, leaving the Viewer to doubt among if all are truly colleagues long ago, or in the army Israeli all are as well, or, as seems more likely, he plays with the time of the narrative in a way so sharp in every scene can have gone weeks without that nothing and nobody will so indicate.We have also, of course, present the typical aspirations of the sub-plots: the soldier who wants to be a musician, who has a girlfriend in New York and will go see it when licencien you, the soldier who attends volunteer place because their relatives perished there.But let's talk about technique, which is where this movie stands. The realization, without being a great display, is quite adequate, achieving the desired effect of claustrophobia, thanks to a décor that fulfils its role perfectly. After the initial level to the Cube, we will be immersed in a maze of oppressive metal tunnels that represent security, while open spaces to symbolize the danger, because the enemy can bombarding with artillery at any time. Photography of the Israeli Ofer Inov, fairly realistic, encourages and emphasizes these two aspects. Yishai Adar music accompanies the perfection throughout the film, performing that role, so reviled in latest major productions, escort and support the image and the plot, rather than fight to see which is superior.In short, we can say that even if you have many places common, abundant in this kind of films, Beaufort is a film which is worth. It presents an extreme situation in which soldiers, hands tied, only can resist vain until they give you the order to leave, while they consolidate their ties of friendship.As a final note, a social curiosity of the film. Apparently, it raised controversy among relatives of the dead in Beaufort because some of the actors had not fully completed the period of compulsory military service. With a part of society is thus not surprising that situations such as which presents the film have given, continue to give and give in the future.</body>
</review>
