<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="The Nines" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A daring film, not bright, and with the ability to suggest highly interesting reflections on many occasions, and fall at the same time in other many extremely superficial</summary>
	<body>John August acquired reputed fame writer with that perfect youth film (one of the best in recent years) directed by Doug Liman, named "GO", living without limits (1999), which became the deliciously frivolous on par with Homeric epic of a group of young workers of a common supermarket, a product fresh, original and full of quality as a filmmaker. Then was in charge of the libretti of any animated film ("Titan AE"), on the ill-fated remake of Charlie's Angels, and especially ivory turning by the good scripted way three works of the great director Tim Burton ("Big Fish", "Charlie and the factory..." and "The corpse bride"). In "The Nines", August faces his first work as director of the function, in an attempt that despite the partially failed proposal, stands by its own merit, even with its flaws evident in one of the most daring materials operas of recent years. Failed but exciting, his mental game proposed in such intricate history will awaken passions or rejections in equal parts, but of which there is no doubt, is that it has an interest beyond doubt.The plot of the film, so tangled and complex to describe, shows us three stories with lightweight links in common, by removing the three by the same actor-personaje, Ryan Reynolds being performed. In the first, title "The prisoner", Reynolds embodies an actor frivolous and given to drink, slightly hinting the story that this reason is basically due to the fragility of their emotions when your partner leaves him no reason apparent. In the second, "Reality Tv", embodies to Gavin, a gifted writer of a pilot program of television and its vicissitudes to suffer in the form of setbacks to hire actresses, technicians or your unit tests prior to the antenna of its programme output, all this being recorded in turn by a program reality, with the intention of bringing the creative process itself through a TV live. In the third and final story, Gabriel is a hard-working husband who spends the day outside with his wife and daughter, having to resort to the help of a woman on the road to be able to solve the problems of your own car, taking into account, that this own life is the one shown by the previous writer of the program in its argument.The nexus of the three stories, as characters, Ryan Reynolds in this triad of characters Gary/Gavin/Gabriel, an amiga-amante always present one way or another in all three stories, Margaret/Melissa/Mary (embodied by Melissa McCarthy), and the threat which lurks in one way or another about himself, the actress Hope Davis and his three characters are Sarah/Susan/Sierra.Cuando a film begins with a note so deliciously ironic as the scene of the mirror and the navel, in which Reynolds, or rather his character Gary, makes a call to the nearest hospital to inform them that to look in the mirror has seen that gone his navel, a brilliant metaphor on the self-centeredness of every actor, and his tendency to literally look at the navel and believe the center of the universe, everything that comes below part already in advance unusual due to such successful first scene forward.Once runs the story, failed decisions abound in all the footage, being all the work extremely irregular, lacking a link no longer plot, but metaphorical sometimes, ideological or with a minimum sense of coherence and connection. This does not preclude that despite such shortcomings, the film arises as a risky proposal, as I have mentioned earlier, and is enjoyable to 100% by the lovers of the cinematographic rarities.Of the three stories, undoubtedly the most interesting is showing us the daily evolution of this writer bent on taking forward his pilot television show. It is the story with more depth, more ability to be interested, and Excel with their puns on top of the other two, more illogical and empty in its symbolism. The pressure from his superiors, having to give up the ties of friendship to take forward its work and the grinding work of the creator, come together in such wise proposal, which also has one of the best scenes of the film, that in which Gavin go lost on the street and is only able to see numbers above the heads of all the people that populate to his aroundby way of seeing the world as an impersonal audience, ignoring any emotional attachment and humanist.In this intermediate story, the role of Melissa McCarthy sticks to friendship, to the rupture of friendship, caused by the choice of Gavin become numbers throughout his life and a constant reality false and devoid of emotions. On the other hand, the role of Hope Davis is his boss in the chain, just the step above his work, giving rise to a heartless Harpy capable of anything for his work.The first and third story are quite more loose, and would come to be something as well as dependence on the first and the last love, concepts which together with the friendship of so successful history of screenwriter, make up the trio of feelings that mark throughout the film.In the first, the conclusion to drawn August through the institutionalization of the actor thwarted in a house under house arrest by his addiction to alcohol, it is that they are emotionally unstable beings, insinuating that they are unable to dispense with worship and the constant attention, in this case in the form of Melissa McCarthy, being his friend faithful that helps you overcome bad drinksstill Hope Davis as a threat in the form of spirited neighbour and active sexually, Amen little reluctant to avoid a good drink of any BREW. This first story is shown quite failed, not so much by the proposed symbolism, but by the way of carrying it out, too academic and little transgressive to be believable, more leaving the sense of metaphysical reflection of manual than anything else.In the last story, which supposedly gives meaning to the story, we have the worst of all the film, because despite the fact that the proposal to show us the frustration of a few characters that are part of a fiction upon hearing that everything is unrealistic, idealized and created by another exceed seemed interesting, August doesn't know to conclude the story in a suggestive way, and used to treat Gabriel (the new character of the third story) of divine Envoy (something that on the other hand not reveals anything unusual argument because in the first story, in less than 30 minutes of footage, it has left in the conversation of the actor in the first episodic story). On this occasion, Melissa McCarthy is the wife of Reynolds, who with her daughter spend the day in the field, again finding the character of Reynolds with Hope Davis, which takes you along a path without output with the intention of convincing him that should return to the place where appropriate, assuring him that everything that is living is unreal. Without disclosing the end of the film, only to say that it is a resolution incomplete, inconsistent and more full of absurd modernez new age that a successful symbolic vision which ended rightly the history.That is why reflections such as compare to the creator of any artistic manifestation with a demigod able to decide the fates of his characters, by way of divine yoke exercised by a superior body, not just materialize at all to mingle with unfinished allusions to the wishes of random, the destination or the parallel paths (as these chips placed in its correct order which alludes the girl in the last story). Also referred, quite rightly, that Yes, the number nine on multiple occasions, giving to understand the frustration that causes in all creator "almost perfect" posed by this assessment, in a display place imposed by every artist in achieving their maximum value.A film that although to be failed in much of its footage, excels above other products with regard to interest. A daring film, not bright, and with the ability to suggest highly interesting reflections on many occasions, and fall at the same time in other many extremely superficial. It is all commented in previous lines, despite irregular of the proposal, it is a film to see, a story which despite its appearance of film study, risks, and that is worthy of praise always in all new director that reaches the middle.</body>
</review>
