<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Mortadelo y Filemón: Misión Salvar la Tierra" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The new film adventure of Mortadelo and Filemón will go down in history not only by the great box office that can be done, but for being one of the worst films of the Spanish film in decades.</summary>
	<body>Many of us believe that good commercial cinema is in danger of extinction, such as the Iberian lynx, and give with a decent film that appeals to the masses is very complicated. One of the more memorable cases in the Spanish film is La Gran Aventura de Mortadelo y Filemón, in which Javier Fesser was able to collect and convey the essence of the characters of Ibáñez, his humor and his surrealist point.So good and funny memories contrast with the feeling of anguish and despair which leads to any lover of cinema second Mortadelo y Filemón RAID on the big screen. And is that having a reference so clear, the question that nobody manages to answer is why Miguel Bardem has done it so badly wrong? In its effort to copy the style of Fesser, Bardem has passed three villages, and what they previously were small and subtle details of the surreal world of Ibáñez, have now become grotesque imitation that populate each frame. The spirit of the characters is trampled and denigrated to unimaginable extremes. The humor of Fesser, simple and great ingenuity disappears at the same time here by complete for a set of bad jokes and gags in a bad taste, allowing that Yes the showcasing of its two protagonists téorico. And it is that there are sequences created with the sole purpose of providing an excuse for the display of Eduard Soto (real catastrophe burricalva) or Pepe Viyuela. But not fearful and dear reader, there are still more, and that if there were not enough the pathetic spectacle that is the film from start to finish, Bardem dares with a couple of winks moviegoers. Certainly Billy Wilder must be now turning in his grave by so horrible desecration.The new film adventure of Mortadelo and Filemón will go down in history not only by the great box office that can be done, but for being one of the worst films of the Spanish film in decades. And it is that on the 50th anniversary of these endearing characters, not be could have devised a worst celebration. Poor Ibáñez should be pulling their hair, of the few remaining clear.</body>
</review>
