<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Un taxi para Tobruk" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Well-meaning pacifist allegation, which is the best thing that goes for it, as well as the interpretative quality of its actors, all of them excellent (Lino Ventura, Charles Aznavour, Hardy Krüger).</summary>
	<body>"Close to Tobruk, where is one that has waged a bloody battle between Allied troops and Germans, with heavy casualties, four men, allies, manage to escape, through the desert, with a hilarious jeep." This is attacked by aircraft and they should continue on foot. When they are exhausted, they are initiators with a group of Germans, who kill. All but one who take prisoner."It's a captain, decorated with the cross of Hierro.Al principle your relationship will be clear enemies, but little by little will be known and becoming, increasingly, comrades". "- Is that you are insensitive to nostalgia, brigadier Dudu? - No, but I don't like to think about the past." "That is I leave the limpets and crabs".Well-meaning pacifist allegation, that is the best thing to say of it, as well as the interpretative quality of its actors, all of them excellent.Although the director has worthy films, here happens from conventional, but well it is true that it is carried compentemente and dialogs are worthy.The development of events, not too many, is credible and the spectator gets involved in history thanks to the clear anti-war critical intent.It is therefore positive and only for this reason already worth their vision.Even views the two with perspective, it can be said, at least I so I appreciate, that is a clear antecedent of the great "hell in the Pacific", by John Boorman and Toshiro Mifune and Lee Marvin's protagonists.In the order of the curiosities, the copy I saw on television lacked strangely in its original form, that is, to full screen. Strange to the broadcast a chain that takes care of this aspect, but on this occasion, once again had to settle, in many scenes, hear the characters instead of seeing them. In this regard, I can say without riesto to mistaken that saw him just 25% of the times you get on screen to the always excellent Hardy Kruger.</body>
</review>
