<review author="Caty" title="La joven del agua" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do it may not be his best tape, but in these times, where the biggest hits of the year are increasingly less movies? personality?, is up a break.</summary>
	<body>It is curious as many directors or writers used the film to project their fears, their insecurities, until your wishes more intimate. Do Woody Allen explores their neuro as anyone, Peter Jackson makes films that the has always wanted to see made its way into the big screen? M.Night Shyamalan, in "The girl in the water" is, in my opinion, of the fear to grow. Criticism in general has been relentless with it, the first commercial "failure" of his career, it will be his first film in invoice less than what it cost. But Shyamalan only defends how the knows: is the fault of everyone within the. A gigantic ego can be up good: Stanley Kubrick, for example, said that it was quite difficult to bear in the shooting, but as Kirk Douglas said: "He is a bastard?" "but a magnificent bastard", but in this case the film, in my opinion, has problems. Several. It is one thing to write a fairy tale, another is to tell a story using nothing narrative appropriately to fairy tales: the problem is not to make an adaptation, good or bad, the problem is that it is an adaptation. The director here has a practically written history, where images, on many occasions, even redundant. Unlike other of their películas(incluyendo_a_"El_protegido",_la_cinta_que_menos_me_gusta_de_toda_su_obra"), I see no consistency in the essential idea of the film.By other side and fortunately, the director continues showing us that even has that capacity that characterizes him to create good characters. Get the shy janitor of a building, Cleveland Heep(el_siempre_genial_Paul_Giamatti), transform into a hero. The visual, elegant style and discreto(teniendo_en_cuenta_los_cánones_más_de_moda) of Shyamalan, transform it into a true knight errant; as well as the character of Bryce Dallas Howard, new musa of the director, which fits quite well.Unfortunately, at the end and after, the ego gets in the middle of everything. Shyamalan urgently needs a competent producer to have as a friend, someone who listen you to and respect their opinion. Although for me is a director with a boundless talent, which not is as manages me to catch everytime it launches a film that has "something" that makes it different from all the others, is a really bad actor, and his presence in the movies increasingly becomes greater. Of illustrious helper becomes co-star with enough weight in the history.In short, "The girl in the water" may not be your best tape, but in these times, where the greatest successes of the year are increasingly less "personality" films, is until a break... Let us hope again that Director that we dreamed many shaped so fresh in directing in his new film.PD.-New trailer, as happened in the poorly translated "the forest" is totally misleading. As always, distributors, her trying to sell as the umpteenth part of "The sixth sense"? If you oyerais the times that the question "Is of fear, truth?" me has been made, you quedaríais really ballpark.</body>
</review>
