<review author="Moebius" title="Zulú" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>On 22 January 1879, 139 Welsh of the British army defendiron a base located on a mission against a Zulu force of 4,000 warriors. The film "Zulu" is based on the events of that day.</summary>
	<body>She is what I said. I only came to build a bridge.The British defeat at Isandlwana shocked an empire, but that same day, 22 January 1879, at Rorke's Drift, 139 Welsh (including wounded and aggregates, and a Scot) marked a milestone in military history defending a base located on a mission against a Zulu force estimated at 4,000 warriors. The Zulu film is based on the events of that day.If dawn Zulu focused in the main battle of Isandlwana and presented (if somewhat briefly) the reasons that led to such a conflict, Zulu focuses in the gesta of Lieutenant John Chard and his men and terrible round-the-clock that lived facing massive tribal force.The film opens with a massive Zulu wedding in the Royal camp where the Reverend Otto Witt and his daughter attended as guests. A few words of the Reverend we know that the conflict between British and Zulu is about to explode, although any other reference to the cause is obvious. A Messenger interrupted the celebrations to tell the jefeCetshwayo of the victory at Insandlwana. Before the alarming news and seeing his Church in danger, the Rev. Witt part with her daughter to warn the British detachment occupied by the mission. In the following scenes we have the main characters of Zulu. The first is the Lieutenant John Chard, of the Corps of Royal Engineers of the army, which is raising a bridge over a river. The second is the Lieutenant Gonville Bromhead, in charge of the military post of the mission. Initially Chard appears as an efficient military, while Bromhead, who returns from a hunting expedition accompanied by a few native servants, makes a first impression of being the typical military arrogant Aristocrat. As it is seen below, the richness of nuances that are both characters will cause that our first impression deBromhead and Chard (as well as which the own characters saved each other) changes as the narration. Bromhead comes from a family tradition of military, while Chard is an engineer without the combat experience. When Witt informs them of the imminent Zulu attack, Chard assumes command since his appointment in a few months preceding the Bromhead. Generally speaking, in any film a fact so predicts disaster, as it may occur in the same Zulu dawn without going any further.The initial clash between the two officers will be developed at the same time carried out preparations for the defence of the mission.Bromhead to comply with the orders but refuses to provide any other assistance to Chard, whose ignorance of the Zulu tactics and terrain is evident. In first thing is aided by a Boer added, while in the second it is left guided by their instinct. The director of the film, Cy Endfield, manages to carve out an interesting interaction between the two characters. The decision of Chard to stay to defend the place first make a kind of arrogant officer in search of glory. Later, while Lieutenant dictates some in principle sound provisions the oficialBromhead seems to act at all times with some flippant. As it was traditional in the war films of the era, the first part of the film serves to go featuring a gallery of characters with which we can identify ourselves and through whose experiences can get to know different moments of the battle and understand their reactions and feelings. Between the Group's different side stresses especially the soldadoHook, an ex - inmate dealing with nursing faking sick and seek initially avoid any potential risk or participation in combat. As it could not be otherwise, you'll end up behaving like a hero. We must also mention the sargentoBourne, typical veteran martial and impassive, and several soldiers of different condition: an ex - farmer who seems more concerned about animals than by his comrades, the novice unnerved, the typical drunkard, or the head of the Welsh choir, which takes leading role in one of the strangest scenes delfilm. In one of the brief lapses of the battle Welsh and Zulu they do a musical battle on to see who sings best and highest. Welsh advantage to drop one of the best quotes from the film: "these malditoszulúes have good low, but we have best Tenors". Priceless. Finally, I cannot comment on the strange evolution of the character of the reverendoWitt. Restrained religious of the beginning of the movie will witness a strange evolution that will end up with a desperate Witt imploring carried the wounded there, dropping verses as a fan and, ultimately, (can't find another way to describe it), giving ass to all those who are trying to save their lives.Witt will end up totally drunk locked in a warehouse. If you have to applaud the construction of characters as the two lieutenants believe it is also fair to note queWitt gives the impression of a blurred, almost parodic, figure in the middle of a full film of solid portraits. The best part of Zulu technically begins at the dawn of the battle, highlighting the travelling and the use of the crane with the Endfield adds intensity and a sort of 19th century elegance to the action. Previously director us worried about strange rumors and distant sounds appear to a train of footprints, and although logically assume that they are loszulúes, never cease to seem me disconcerting. They startle the scenes where the horizon is covered of warriors, especially towards the bottom, where Endfield, once already has us biting the bait, he surprises us by pulling on the line and leave us breathless for a moment.Together with the composition of key scenes and the wonderful portrait of several characters that make up the film, the director keeps in suspense to the viewer with the continuous comings and goings of the Zulus and the development of the battle throughout a day. Those who enjoy war history enjoy double contemplating the different Warrior Wiles and the tactical counterpart of the tenienteChard, in what has become a long and agonizing chess game in which the black pieces have an overwhelming infinite number of pawns.Another interesting aspect of Zulu is that his heroes are flesh and blood, and emotions and fear, something which is not usual in this type of films. If initially Bromhead boasted of ancestry military, he later confess to having felt panic. As the battle progresses Bromhead will change mind on Lieutenant Chard, and in a moment of weakness he will come to his aid. At the end of the tape, in a memorable dramatic moment, Bromhead shared his feelings with Chard, who closed a great dialogue with the phrase that opens this criticism.Zulu was a project by Endfield and actor Stanley Baker, who plays Lt. Chard sober but effectively. Both put their pocket money to finance this interesting war film, and in fact Endfield deepening in the británico-zulú conflict by signing the script for Zulu dawn, where the famous tribe charged more prominence.Michael Caine, which was her first role protagonist, runs with his usual accuracy the interpretation of the seemingly impassive tenienteBromhead. James Booth, with its image of quarrelsome player fits perfectly as the soldier Hook. Finally, Jack Hawkins, the unforgettable captain of galera of Ben Hur, portraying the Reverend maniac Witt. The film closes with a tribute to the fallen (other than as many as it might appear in the film) and eleven military personnel awarded the cross of victory, a precious award that has never been as high number for a single action in that distant battle of Rourke's Drift. I would like to close this post by recalling a comic scene of Zulu, that in which the undaunted military surgeon requests some soldiers to reject a few warriors seeking to enter through a window of the Chapel while it continues to operate as if such a thing. British phlegm in its purest form.</body>
</review>
