<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Juno" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Juno interspersed acid humor with moralina shift through what we might define as a 'everyday tragedy', in an efficient but non-explosive recipe whose main appeal lies in (some of) their characters.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Canadian Jason Reitman and starring Ellen Page, Michael Cera, Allison Janney, JK Simmons, Olivia Thirlby, Rainn Wilson, Jason Bateman and Jennifer Garner, Juno was nominated for three Golden Globes and opts to nothing more and nothing less than four Oscars, best film, best actress, Best Director and best script Original.La movie, second in the Filmography of the Canadian, relates to mode of comedy indie history of the young Juno, of sixteen, who becomes pregnant after their first sexual relationship and decides to give up his son in fostering a couple who has spent five years trying to have a child.Some years ago, the electronic Academy Awards left aside their prejudices for small productions and began to nominate the quehoy day we all know as indie films, so titles of low budget (compared to the rest of its competitors) and forget about me! or little Miss Sunshine gave the pitch in recent ceremonies, winning the Oscar for best script Original.Por, unfortunately, when a novelty becomes habit, the original spirit is terjiversa and denigrates in an election almost by default. And it is not that Juno is a bad movie, au contraire, but their four nominations were you seem to a server something excessive, most still bearing in mind the scant originality of the product. As well as believe that forget me!, American Splendor, Ghost world or the previous film from Jason Reitman, thank you for smoking, are more than notable products, I think that little Miss Sunshine is one of the films more overvalued for years, and the truth is that Juno uses exactly the same formula that the film directed by Jonathan Dayton and Valerie Harris. still with the echo in our minds of embarrassing messJuno is served from an unwanted teenage pregnancy to make the portrait of coming enough characters as so the Viewer is identified, or at least feel some affinity towards any of them, and win this its blessing. With an Ellen Page which stands as absolute epicenter of the film, Juno interspersed acid humor with moralina shift through what we might define as a daily tragedy, in an efficient but non-explosive recipe whose main attraction is, precisely, some of his characters.Thus, Ellen Page, to its twenty years old, takes almost the entire weight of the film, portraying a responsive and always sarcastic teenager that nonetheless remind me an affable version of Ghost World Edit but that, instead, it does not suffer any evolution, it addition to discover true love. And it is that Juno has always something to respond, always has an ironic phrase, a hurtful, precise comment, cool and calculated mathematically by his screenwriter which makes it pretty incredible. do sympathetic, endearing? By alleged, but not credible.In the same way, the young Michael Cera is a completely irrelevant and bland character with the exception of the final stretch, similar to j. k. Simmons, just a cranky Jennifer Gardner and Alison Janney, incredibly condescending parents, and an absolutely brilliant Jason Bateman avoid that Juno is a monologue of nominated for Oscar. so young and all, I insist that Juno is not a bad film, and is worth the trouble to see her, but is not the eighth wonder of the world that many seek to see it. And is that the label indie happened because some time ago to be a sort of patent, and from there, anything goes.</body>
</review>
