<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Sweeney Todd" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tim Burton chooses everything with perfect care, so even the minor role is brilliant. It close to perfection.</summary>
	<body>There are few filmmakers who wake up so many passions among his followers as Tim Burton does yours get put the willies. He said. And that happens when up to a trailerTim Burton on the wheel press that the film can be for children &hellip; "But rare children" and is to get once more create that magical atmosphere of tale that transgresses any narrative discourse that can develop on the screen. Benjamin Barker is a Barber who has been unjustly accused by Judge Turpin to steal women. While in prison the evil judge takes care of his daughter and keeps it locked up under lock and key. After leaving prison, Benjamin returns to London to plan his revenge. There he learns of the fate suffered by the two women in his life and plans to a macabre justice under his new pen name: Sweeney Todd. With him, the only person who knows his secret is a young Baker who will benefit from the skills with the knife of the Barber while trying to conquer it.Johnny Depp is essential for Burton in almost all tapes. It is true that he has collaborated with him on six occasions and that the outcome is usually quite bright and this case is no exception. It is not only able to act if not who sings it and does it very well. Something more modest but equally effective is the wife of filmmaker: Helena Bonham Carter (that equal that her husband does not know what is a brush) and is a fantastic surprise to discover the vocal talents of Alan Rickman or even Sacha Baron Cohen's (Ali G and Borat to the desubicados) which I admit that in his role of Pirelli has boot me more than one laugh thanks to his Italian accent despite the fact that I don't like at all as much less as a comedian and actor. Tim Burton chooses everything with perfect care, so even the minor role is brilliant (example in the child, magnificent voice and better actor than most of the players that populate the Billboard).Starting with the opening credits (great start) until the end of Burton recreates that grey and soulless aspect of the city of London but does something appealing and fun. Da essence red, a brilliant and bright red that contrasts with all the grim tone that permeates the footage, an almost theatrical red.His peculiar world is part of the protagonists of Sweeney Todd, the Victorian London is undoubtedly one of the most brilliant and gloomiest Burton creations to date and an ideal background for a brilliant film that deserves a place on the podium of honour of the Filmography of the filmmaker.It close to perfection. Notice. Sweeney Todd respects its original version, i.e. is a musical. Not is fooled by the first trailer as the majority of the work is sung and therefore stays in subtitled original version.</body>
</review>
