<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Juno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>'Juno' is a positive, entertaining, fable and with charming characters. Thanks to a brilliant script, Reitman Gets an immediate connection with the audience.</summary>
	<body>More or less once a year, the indie film gets fashion with the appearance of a film that breaks lockers and awakens passions beyond where treads. "American Splendor", "Little Miss Sunshine", or "forget me!" are just a few examples so fruitful cinematographic current, whose quality has been amply demonstrated in the form of nominations and awards of all kinds, as well as the unanimous endorsement by critics and the public.Now it is the turn to "Juno", which continues the path of its predecessors (has four nominations for the Academy Award, including best picture and screenplay, and is one of the movies more views of the current American box office) becoming the success (in) waited of the year.Directed by Jason Reitman, the film introduces us to Juno MacGuff (Ellen Page, rather than convincing), a sixteen-year schoolgirl who becomes pregnant from one of her classmates (Michael Cera). Deciding to go ahead with the pregnancy, you are looking for a couple to adopt the baby when it is born, and is as well as meet the Loring (Jason Bateman and Jennifer Garner), seemingly happy and perfect marriage. But that depends on the point of view that look.At this point everyone knows what a movie like "Juno" can offer. Because if something characterises American independent cinema, is the excessive resemblance between his productions, primarily at the level of visual and auditory, although never cease to resemble each other many of the stories that they tell.Thus, the three minutes from the beginning of the film by Reitman, one has already stylish indie through a couple of acoustic songs in charge of Belle &amp; sebastian or The Kinks, a few titles of entrance to the purest style "American Splendor", and a few levels so beautiful and austere as effective, impersonal.The same applies to the characters and the situation in which are involved. As in "Little Miss Sunshine" (to give just one example), no one in "Juno" stands out for its heroism or class, rather the opposite. They are normal and ordinary, nearby, people that happens to them something that could well happen to anyone, and any attempt to put solution.If outside, the protagonist can not remember Natalie Portman in "Something in common" (not only speak and think like, if not that up dressed very similarly), as well as the role of the could have played perfectly by Zach Braff.Entonces, what does this film for having received so much praise? Because, to date, the formula continues to operate perfectly. Because after all, what matters from a film is tells the story, and 'Juno' is a positive, entertaining, fable and with charming characters. Thanks to a brilliant script, in charge of (customer name) Diablo Cody, Reitman Gets an immediate connection with the audience, who immediately accepts the rules of the game and let it have fun and thrill in equal parts to the sound of a wonderful soundtrack.Of course much of this achievement is due to a few actors in State of grace, from the first to the last, with particular emphasis on the amazing Ellen Page, which shows that "Hard Candy" was not only a breath of inspiration, but especially in the prodigious couple Loring, a server is by far the best at all of the film.There will be some who complain of some depletion of the machine, but the truth is that more than one director would like to achieve so much, with so little. Simply exquisite.</body>
</review>
