<review author="José A. Peig" title="En el valle de Elah" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do great movie, honda and rich in dramatic records, depicted with sobriety and Cadence, without artifice vacuos that so often tends melodrama? Sung?.</summary>
	<body>In the valley of Elah is a film which refers to issues already mentioned in this booklet in relation to two films dissected and put your finger in the wound of our turbulent present: the creation of myths that subjugate and deform reality (flags of our fathers, Clint Eastwood), and in the consciousness disturbance caused by new media audiovisual registration (the strange there is en TI)(, Neil Jordan).The film opens with images of war in Iraq - reproduced on a computer screen - transmitting the disturbing feeling not to apprehend a reality evasive, misleading. Search for Hank (Tomme Lee Jones) runs two strata Visual and plot they build an x-ray of the lost son (the recordings and the data of the police investigation). Such a search involves a damning review and deconstruction of the values and myths played in Hank: Army, sacrifice, homeland, democracy, symbolized in the flag which reverses its position in that journey since the beginning until an end which is a declaration of defeatism, which is understood as a profound criticism of the foreign policy of the current Government USA, but transcends the easy use of the pacifist pamphlet.After a process of demystification, reality - always subject to distortion of the images and data - which we see through the TV or any of the modern audiovisual supports, ends up revealing their secrets. It is particularly significant that only Hank manages to be aware of the meaning of the recordings sent by his son when research data allow to know the real criminals. What we see on television or on the Internet is subject to our beliefs, a view backed by the set of dogmas that give a sense and a justification to the homeland. And yet there is no war heroes, because we all fear. Goodbye to the myths, ideological support that, undoubtedly comes from the hand of Clint Eastwood, collaborator of Paul Haggis, and above all because the message is the same as we saw in flags of our fathers.The pain before the truth has a great expression in the eyes of Tomme Lee Jones, actor who manages to handle each dramatic outline in a temperate manner and in accordance with the essence of the work: moral degeneration in a syncopated narrative that combines urban drama with notes pertaining to a pessimistic view of humans. The almost monochrome photography makes the same bleak austerity expressed in a script that gives voice to the characters and meaning to the silences is represented on stage. The greatest tragedy lies in what is not said. As we can see, great movie, deep and rich in dramatic records, depicted with sobriety and Cadence, without artifice vacuos that so often tends "toned" melodrama.</body>
</review>
