<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="4 meses, 3 semanas y 2 días" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>4 months, 3 weeks, 2 days is a good example of how a movie without too many resources and fewer claims can be a pleasant viewing.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Romania's Cristian Mungiu and stars Anamaria Marinca, Vlad Ivanov, Laura Vasiliu and Alexandru Potoceanu among others, 4 months, 3 weeks, 2 days (4 luni, 3 saptamini if 2 zile) won this past 2007 Palme d'Or at the Festival in Cannes and the Fipresci Grand Prize at the festival of San Sebastián, in addition to having been nominated for the Golden Globe as best foreign language film and nominated for the Academy Award in the same category, although has been out of both competitions.The film puts us in Romania, during the last days of Communism: Otilia and Gabita are students and share room in a residence in Bucharest. Gabita is pregnant, and young women agree to a meeting with a such Mr. Bebe into a cheap hotel that practice you an aborto.4 months, 3 weeks, 2 days is a good example of how a movie without too many resources and fewer claims can be a pleasant viewing: both Fund minimalist in form, this Romanian film has two great virtues that make it mercedora all those awards for which is guaranteed: firstly its realism, a relatively daily history we have and that I could locate in almost any space, and second, their impartiality.It will be better explained: when I speak of impartiality, rather I am referring to his lack of subjectivity, or what is the same, to its position before an act that still today can be taboo as it is abortion; Cristian Mungiu film does not judge at any time its protagonists, just plasma events into a sort of hyper-realist ' Costumbrismo ', which is to be welcomed, because its director leaves it well clear that his interest focuses on the characters, not in itself history and even less in an almost anecdotal context.But, without a doubt, the greatest success of 4 months, 3 weeks, 2 days, is the fact of erecting a character a priori secondary protagonist, increasing even more - if possible - his drama, because all the suffering of Otilia us strikes as unjust terríblemente, collateral from the mistakes of others victim: monetary problems, discussions of couple, and evils infinitely greater than I am not going to reveal here. The film rightly eludes the plastic harshness in benefit of the cruelty inside, to put it in some way, transporting us to a grey and squalid Bucharest where takes place a gray and sordid life.On the other hand, one must recognize that 4 months, 3 weeks, 2 days is not a round film: it is true that not it decays in almost no time, and its central character manages to captivate us with ease, but the minimalism of the film by Cristian Mungiu flirts dangerously with the atmosphere of the telefilm, label that falls on it, everything must be said, almost by default.</body>
</review>
