<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Killer Pussy" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about a monster that he settles in her cunt for a miss that forces him to go in balls all the time and eat the lovers and other follarines. For seasoned viewers are able to see all the programs of the washing machine.</summary>
	<body>Director: Takao Nakano. duration: the theme does not give for more than one hour.Premiere: the 2004.Yo I believe that there are films that roll bet for spectators such that gives them equal eight to eighty and swallow like a arthouse as a breaded milestone. If not, I do not understand these films succeed. Well looked, if we join porn movie title (Nacho Vidal rolled a few, but not surprise between their legs) a wisecracking Monster and gore scenes, have fine cinnamon, which they say.The movie not be nor of what trafficking, given that the copies are in Japanese without subtitles. At the beginning leave a few explorers and a magician makes strange things, to go directly to the girl in porretas. It is that some kids get into a country house to focus on what has been wear mineral salts and these are a girl that came with the magician stuck in a bucket of ice. He then unfreezes and it gets a girl a worm through the mouth (as disgusting announcement that the cocaine to the oldest remember where you entering a worm by the napia one) and becomes stronger in what comes to be the pussy. And ale to eat every male that here there to smell. what you want I say having read the summary? Reminded me a chapter of "The House of the drawings" where the Princess was a curse and when it lifted the skirt came out you a monster with tentacles. That chest to laugh. This is the same, but with fine offal, hear, as I bring the offal, which I moves, that is me mueeeeeveeeeee. I certainly understand not have translation into Castilian, although in the video store would well, next to Disney's one be called "Killer pussy".In short, film about a monster that he settles in her cunt for a miss that forces him to go in balls all the time and eat the lovers and other follarines. For seasoned viewers are able to see all the programs of the washing machine, even delicate fabrics.This does neither stars nor anything you like.Besitos.P.D: I'm dying of laughter thinking "killer pussy" and recalling history telling a friend envelope a girl that you linked in a bar. They went in the car, he lowered her panties and had to download the Windows of what came out of there. Jajajajaja, that thing more coarse!Pd2: The scene in which oozes the girl "flow" is the most disgusting thing that has been in the film.P.D.3: If this criticism not hovers me, not be what to do already, since nobody else has criticized Spanish.</body>
</review>
