<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Rec" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the most terrifying films of recent years, with a voltage that is on the rise, with the well dose Summit moments and an impressive final climax.</summary>
	<body>Finally this Christmas I have seen one of the great successes of the Spanish cinema in 2007. It is not that I fiase not liked by the public, that I I do not trust a hair, but the film has meant for me one of the great surprises of last year. "[Rec]" tells the story of a reporter and a cameraman of television, to conduct an interview, spends a night in a fire station. Everything seems to pass as normal, even in somewhat boring way, when a distress call become that night the most terrifying in their lives.Without disclosing anything about the causes of such terror say that the idea seems good and has sufficient doses of originality to be surprising. The film is shot from the point of view of the camera of the television crew. However, the action is not confusing even in the moments of increased agitation where, while images may be blurred or shaky, we always know what is happening and everything has a sense of narrative.The majority of viewers they go unnoticed the work of actors and that is because they are so well in their respective roles we have come to believe that they are real. Special mention for Manuela Velasco, that bears the weight of the film and plunges his character of program journalist television type "Direct Spain".As all good horror film fan knows, the hardest thing is not scare the viewer but an atmosphere as unhealthy as this film, transmitting a bad feeling to the viewer that is hard to beat. However, in "[Rec]" there are some of the best scares seen in a movie in a long time and without need of subidones of volume on the soundtrack, resource impossible helpings here by the absence of the same.All of the above in order to achieve one of the most terrifying films of recent years, with a voltage that is on the rise, with the well dose Summit moments and an impressive final climax. The truth is that I spent so afraid that I was delighted to be in a film with more people and not seeing the film I only at home.An example of how to maximize the physical space and the means available to make a not especially expensive movie that Spanish Cinema should draw many conclusions and not only the obvious of how well it works the horror genre today.Ultimately, the film by Jaume Balagueró and Paco Plaza is, in my opinion, the most interesting proposal of Spanish film of 2007. final assessment: 8.5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
