<review author="Vsancha" title="La joven del agua" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fable on as escape from the routine and sad monotony and find your place in the world.</summary>
	<body>Shyamalan is personally a director that I like, I think one of the authors of contemporary cinema, although he is a director that arouses many passions, hated and loved by equal parts and unknown to many more. If unknown and if not ask a known: "Have you seen the latest M. Night Shyamalan movie?", who will answer you, as well as launches a look incriminating, "I do not see porn" and your while contienes laughter you tell him, no man, is the director of the sixth sense, then and only then will be aware of whom you speak. To my personally I like his way of making films, and this water young being the weakest of his filmography is a good movie that gets a good time. Possibly with "The girl in the water" goes with the rest of his filmography, the exception to the sixth sense, i.e. to win with the reviewing which make all the juice and messages that Shyamalan leaves on their tapes. But first I found that a dot missing to get to the level of the forest or the underestimated signals. But again you can find many of the constants repeated in his earlier work, already not only in common elements that is often used when creating tension, if not in his characters, all try to find your site in the world, a role that develop in this life, whether a father who has lost the faith, a type that does not know that he is dead, or a man who discovers that he has superpowers and must learn to live with them. In this case is responsible for a block of apartments named Cleveland Heep, played by a brilliant Paul Giamatti, one of those actors who have an extreme ease to harmonize with the public, who one day rescues a mysterious young woman from danger. The girl turns out to be a nymph, a character from a children's story that seeks the way of returning to his world of Fable from our. Cleveland will attempt to help her. Shyamalan again to demonstrate that it has an innate to tell stories, brilliantly, which in the hands of others might seem ridiculous. The picture is adequate, the great soundtrack and the characters very good from the morbid nymph played by Bryce Dallas Howard, through the Group of hippies and their brutal talks until that great character that is the pedantic critical film that just moved to the block and course is not right nor a great mockery of Shyamalan critics often put to fall from a donkey. Girl with water is a supernatural story, a beautiful tale for children, a fable that many do not understand or do not want to understand, people still waiting for a horror film when you go to see a movie of this man, and do not realize that Shyamalan has ever shot a tape of terror, has ever shot a superhero movie, and he has never shot a tape of aliens, he talks about family, love, faith, specifically in this film of how magic can serve us to escape the monotony, the sad reality, or of a distant past which seemed already forgotten.</body>
</review>
