<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="En el valle de Elah" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The screenplay by Paul Haggis is a genuine Marvel and again, shows that we have one of the best writers of cinema of the present.</summary>
	<body>One of platitudes to talk about cinema is to say that the only thing that needs a director to make a good movie from a good script is &hellip; not to mess up. "In the Valley of Elah" (In the Valley of Elah) is a good example of such a good movie. And is that the screenplay by Paul Haggis is a true wonder and proves, once again, that is one of the best writers of cinema of the present. Everything fits, every small seemingly insignificant detail has its importance in the history and is not since there not by chance or to fill in minutes. In just a couple of scenes we perfectly drawn to the characters and their motivations. A joy.Perhaps aware that higher criticism to "Crash", unfair in my opinion, were due to the grandstanding of some scenes, just my favorites, here Haggis chooses to go unnoticed as director and let that history passes before our eyes without drawing attention. It shows thereby be able to direct without stridency and elegance which, together with its enormous capacity as a writer, predicts one of the most interesting races of the current Hollywood.Some be thinking that I'm missing a paw in my reasoning and are right. Despite having the solid pillars of an excellent script and good management, a film can unravel if the interpretations are not at the height. In the end are the actors that us has those emotions that the author has written for their characters.In this regard you can rest assured because "In the Valley of Elah" interpretations are at the height of his screenplay. All children, including Susan Sarandon makes one minor role that expected but that leaves a mark, are frankly well and you could not highlight Josh Brolin above Jason Patric or any other.Which Yes stresses upon them is Charlize Theron, which continues to grow as actress and you hold the type the real King of the function which is none other than Tommy Lee Jones. Veteran actor performed here one of his best performances and that, for him, i.e. much. Their close-up, their looks, we dipped in the emotional whirlwind lives his character. Few actors in the world can make a display like that he performs in this film. Only by him would be worthwhile seeing her &hellip; in original version, of course.Having said all that, I'd say that everything is perfect and finish my criticism by saying that we we have the first masterpiece of 2008. But it is not. There are a couple of details that I do not end quite convince. The first is a bit ambiguous to explain but can be summed up easily: the first hour and some movie I like and catch me more than the final half-hour. It is not that in no time it becomes boring, because only with enjoy the already it would be impossible to aburrise, but the end me does not come with the same effectiveness as the rest of the tape.The other aspect that not me convection at all has to do with two scenes featuring both by Tommy Lee Jones, the American flag-related and seem stuck with shoehorn with the sole purpose of sending a message to the Viewer. Especially enforced the second of them, in which the message becomes so obvious that almost annoying.However, the virtues outweigh the defects and I can recommend without fear "in the Valley of Elah" as one of the first films of the year you "must see". Although it is only for those who enjoy "Crash" can confirm the talent of Haggis and those who hated his previous film to discover if they condemned him prematurely or going you to hate forever.Final rating: 8 out of 10</body>
</review>
