<review author="Berto" title="Alien vs Predator 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film of remarkable entertainment, which exceeds in length to its loose first part giving the viewer what he wants and preached with the title of the film and that augurs a new series of films of this already new franchise.</summary>
	<body>Everything pointed relative disaster that was the first installment of what can now be considered a new saga would not get get a second installment of this confrontation between two of the alien races more deadly and at the same time most interesting film mythology of all time. The case is that although I do not like neither critics nor to public, above all by its zero resemblance to the series of comics from which drinks its sources, keeping more than any film of two sagas which it joins, or what is the same, if it gives sufficient benefits squeeze it until that is nothing to remove. For this second part already not told with the director of the first part, Paul W.S Anderson, immersed in the direction of the third installment of the Resident Evil, left his post to the Brothers Strause, special effects experts and promised to satisfy the fans with what all had expected, clashes between the two races, human dead everywhere and a story that could remind a bit to origin of the history of the comic.On the basis of these premises must be said that in this case the directors have right of full, because that is what we offer in this film, a small village in the deep America, full of bait for two races, and all this seasoned by fights between the aliens and predator that comes to hunt them.The argument begins exactly where just the top, although no need seeing to find out what happens. After the introduction to put us in a situation, the film focuses on introducing us to the protagonists, typical archetypes among which we will find the Sheriff of the town, the rebel of the people back after being in jail for something that did and trying to redirect to his younger brother, which follows the same steps. We also have, as no, aunt buenorra that at one point in the film you will need to remove clothing (foreground endless of his included rear) for enjoyment of the hormonado Viewer that clutter the room, and as opposed to this stereotype also have out there the military who returns to his home to try to continue with their lives. Obviously throughout the life of the people is threatened by the arrival of the Aliens, which camparan rampant at the city, eating and using to raise all the humans that are on the way, while the predator because there is only one, the alone is enough to put an end to all, try by all means to take forward an aberration created by nothing more start the moviea Predalien, fruit of the events of the first film.Starting from there to go to the movies knowing exactly what we are going to see, the film not disappointed in no time, has some very good special effects, and the truth is a joy to see how campan rampant land at these two creatures. The only bad thing that could highlight is that the action scenes are mostly very hastily shot and from very closely, which means that in the majority of the fights, you only get to distinguish a mass report of arms, blades, tails and braids, and that until that not a bit away the camera fails know what is exactly happening in the fight.Actors therefore quite Jessi, and that for a film of these features this pretty well. There is no any moderately known, with what is clearly the protagonists are exclusively those that give the title to the film.Ultimately, film of remarkable entertainment, which exceeds in length to its loose first part and that augurs well for a new series of films, under so well that it has worked around the world, and that if improve a little more formulates it can get a very interesting film especially for both Aliens and predators fansamong which I myself.</body>
</review>
