<review author="Ethan" title="Tener y no tener" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A lesson in how learning to whistle never had so many sexual connotations.</summary>
	<body>"Does Anybody got a match?". Those were the first words that spoke to the big screen actress who we remember today: Lauren Bacall. The star was born in New York, a month of September of more than eighty years ago and still continues to work at a good pace. The phrase in question belongs to the tape of Howard Hawks "Have and have not", and the appearance in a door frame of the young Bacall asking for matches that would be her future husband in real life is already legendary: Humphrey Bogart. "To have and to have not" born a curious bet between Ernest Hemingway - always reluctant to take part in a film project - and Howard Hawks. The director, to involve the novel Prize to participate in a film, threw a challenge. He said that he was able to make a successful film based on the worst of his novels. And Hemingway stung the hook. A few days Hawks managed to buy the rights to the book to his friend and got underway for what would be one of their best treadmills and, by extension, one of the largest ever made. With "To have and have not" they wanted to take advantage of the pull of "Casablanca". Thus, the character of Bogart was again a selfish who did not want to get involved in any war and resisted the charms of Slim (translated here by "Flaca", the nickname of Lauren Bacall in the film, the same that used Hawks to call his second wife); the bar, where much of the action was much reminded the film of Curtiz Rick coffee; but also the exotic environment of Martinique and the intrigues by the French resistance were suspiciously similar to those of Casablanca. Much of the blame that the final result had very little to do with the original, was a woman of. 19 years! -This was the age of Bacall when he withdrew the casting-. It is true that the director caused the situation because I was looking for a new Marlene Dietrich competed in coolness with his male opponent. So I needed the appropriate writers to make sprout witty and sharp phrases from his lips. Had: William Faulkner (another novel Award) and Jules Furthman - the latter had previously worked with Von Sternberg in a film of Marlene Dietrich ("Morocco"). But with what Hawks did was with the crush that arose the first month of shooting between the two protagonists. After the surprise, the director wanted to take advantage of the situation and ordered to rewrite the script. The result was spectacular: the sensual call of matches by Lauren Bacall was actually an invitation if Harry Morgan (Humphrey Bogart) to descend into his arms; or a bottle that ranged from a room to another was the perfect excuse for romantic encounters between the couple. The truth is that nobody has been able to match this complicity. One serving them to plan a robbery at a bar, only with the look; or to "play" the love in your room, where a lesson of how learning to whistle never had so many sexual connotations. Despite all of the above "Have and have not" is a film hawksiana on all four sides. His favorite subject, of friendship, was more than present. Thus, the cause of the final implication of the hero is the relationship between Bogart and his protégé, Eddie - great Walter Brennan - drunk and not the sex with Lauren Bacall. Only when his friend suffers an attack is when Morgan decides to act, but curiously does so in every sense: in the war, helping the resistance; and staff engaging with "la Flaca". This film directed by Howard Hawks was a real turning point in his career, but was also the discovery of a great actress. If there is a scene that I always associate with this masterpiece is a tall, thin woman resting on the proportion of a door. It takes a suit paintings, with shoulder pads. It has a slightly tilted head, with high eyebrows and insinuating look; and, with a deep voice, says: "does Anybody got a match?".</body>
</review>
