<review author="Pruden Rodríguez" title="Jóvenes ocultos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lost boys is a reference in the film of vampirism. Despite its obvious flaws of approach, it is today considered as a cult film for its innovation.</summary>
	<body>Lost boys (Joel Schumacher, 1987) could happen to oblivion as a mediocre movie that is, by its very simple structure, flat characters and their approach infantilón. The proposal by the American director, however, achieved some success in the long run. Bet to give a twist to the vampire subgenre and today is, for many, a film of cult and the propositions of big titles of vampire theme. Be that as it may, the truth is that in its attempt to attract adolescents toward this type of film, Schumacher managed to combine several elements that have made to remain in the collective memory as a different, special film.History, of course, is not one of its strengths. Lost Boys narrates the adventures and misadventures of two brothers that are installed with his mother (recently divorced) in the quiet city of Santa Carla. Soon echo the rumors that run on the existence of vampires and have the opportunity to check are not just rumors. Biker youngsters become his worst nightmare of the day in the morning. Michael, brother major (played by Jason Patric) gets seduced by the young Star (Jami Gertz) biker and puts in this way his younger brother Sam (Corey Haim) in a crazy fight to rid him of the "dark side".So what were those elements for which is today remembered? There were several (more or less wanted) ingredients blended to obtain the magic formula. One of them, undoubtedly, was his humorous, thug, informal, informal tone. Lost boys could be compared with the impact of "The Goonies" in the adventure genre (in fact Corey Feldman, better known as "Bocazas", comes in both films). It's films that have managed to keep the traditional elements and on the other hand give a fresh air. Thus, in lost boys can laugh with phrases as "my own brother is a vampire of shit, you'll see when MOM learned" and after a while spend a few tense minutes observing the gang of bikers led by David (Kiefer Sutherland). Vampires can no longer be in castles and, in addition, can laugh without giving up their dose of night terror.Another of the ingredients for success (their relative success) was aesthetics. Eighties costumes bikers, own motorcycles, to the latest fashion hairstyles (now obviously outdated), the nightlife, alcohol, girls, beach. they formed a mirror for many young people at that time and today are a pleasant picture which recreate. Add to this another ingredient: the impressive soundtrack (with groups such as Aerosmith Songs) and the less sought after of all the elements: the curiosities. Over time have passed to the category of legend players such as Corey Haim and Corey Feldman (friends with the same name, which were youth stars and then saw to fall sharply their careers). For both, it was the last film that gained some standing. The fact happened between Jason Patric and Keifer Sutherland was also known. After forging a close friendship during the filming, the first he "took" the bride from the second (was Julia Roberts) and things between them were not so well since then.In short, lost boys is a film bound vision, but at this point can leave indifferent. A note for the nostalgic: "Lost Boys 2: The Tribe", which premieres this 2008 is being prepared. In this sequel, and more curiosities: Corey Feldman ("Bocazas") and a member of the family participates Sutherland. By the way, not expect to see in our cinemas. Probably nowhere.</body>
</review>
