<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="4 meses, 3 semanas y 2 días" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hard Romanian film, embodying its young director Cristian Mungiu. It won the Palme d'Or at the 2007 Cannes Film Festival.</summary>
	<body>Hard Romanian film, embodying its young director Cristian Mungiu. It won the Palme d'Or at the 2007 Cannes Film Festival and once vista is not strange.The film is excellent because the script is iron, full of tension and intrigue, even everyday nature. Displays the Romanian social reality of the long and sad time of the dictator Ceausescu, where there were severe shortages of all kinds. Under these conditions, that a young man wished to have an abortion, shows the hypocrisy, injustice and cruelty of those with power over others.With few characters, but perfectly defined, a study of them superb psychological and some scenes, long, fixed camera, which literally acongojan viewers, as all those that occur in the hotel room and the exquisite and very difficult scene of the family meal, with the face of the protagonist and boyfriend fixed, while the rest of guests talk of baladíes things. Maximum stress and impressive storytelling that keeps in a fist to the respectable.Very good film.As a personal curiosity, when he finished the current of the movie in the past of San Sebastian International Film Festival, three girls, and MILFs, said that it was a crappy, poorly made and unpleasant film. And again, very bad.Anyway, they were also of the specialized press. The truth, I do not know how slip certain people to places where they shouldn't since the little film knowledge they have, especially in this case where relate, as it was the case at that time in Romania, facts that undermine the dignity of women and their lack of freedom to decide. The fact that precisely a women not knew to see "cutrez" of the prevailing reality, and that the sober realization, devoid of any artifice, thus show it, says very little of them, and I am not talking only in the section of movie knowledge.</body>
</review>
