<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="John Rambo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Incredible as it may seem, 'John Rambo' is the film splatter of the year; from Braindead he saw nothing of the sort.</summary>
	<body>Twenty-five years after his first delivery, and almost twenty years after its third installment, Rambo 4, or Rambo: return to hell, or John Rambo, as it will be called finally in these parts, comes to our screens on 1 February with more violence than ever before.Directed by and starring Sylvester Stallone, to whom accompany Julie Benz, Matthew Marsden, Graham McTavish, Reynaldo Gallegos, Jake La Botz, Tim Kang, Maung Maung Khim and Ken Howard, this fourth installment of the character created by David Morrell shows us a green ex-boina already veteran John Rambo who now lives a solitary and peaceful existence in the jungle of northern Thailandfishing and hunting cobras and then sell them. But everything changes when a group of Catholic missionaries need guide them to the border with Burma to provide food and medicines to some refugees besieged by the Burmese army, which has made the torture and murders commonplace. Rambo won't have no choice but to return to get involved. It will be forced to do what they know better, because although yours takes the war in blood.Novel company specializing in CGI want to promote is offering its new and revolutionary software specialized in bloody disintegration of human bodies to balance price. If you want to take advantage of this amazing offer, just should contact us at 555 - 12 34. In addition, if you call within the next fifteen days offer, completely free, two dozen of cobras. Exhausted the promotion of pythons.To this phone the teleshopping lamó Sylvester Stallone at wee hours of the morning to deal with the Visual effects of John Rambo, film funded, probably, with the money saved to take advantage of the offer 2 x 1 in Botox that promoted the branch of Corporación Dermoestética in Los Angeles.Y is that gods, often películón that is John Rambo.Aclaremos things: If we talk about in film termsJohn Rambo: return to hell, is one insult both to the seventh art in particular as any minimally rational intelligence in general, because its plot is practically non-existent (in short, the usual premise of all the sequels of Rambo), its completely archetypal characters, and deliberately obvious development.But, to my surprise, I found that it could no doubt catalog as best film splatter of the last fifteen years. Come on, from Peter Jackson's Braindead a server had not enjoyed both with similar dose of wild and free violence: tens of warheads that explode, hundreds of amputees Member violations everywhere, bodies vaporized in a huge cloud of blood after giving a mine antipersonnel, infanticide, ele crossed by arrows, massive desparramamiento of internal organs, mines that they trigger (almost) in Atomic explosions.All this and much more, in explicit key, is what John Rambo offers.As I said, the premise is indignantemente predictable, the archetypal characters over not being able, and Sylvester Stallone is passed throughout the film or killing indiscriminately or losing the gaze on the horizon thinking, one of two in which his circle of violence has been closed definitively, or have forgotten again buy bacon for breakfast, it is something that a server has been unable to decide.So, ladies and gentlemen, buy a bag of popcorn giant, a few soft drinks, left with the more hooligan chums who have, and be available to enjoy, laugh and applaud in this violent spectacle and gore without equal which is John Rambo: return to hell.</body>
</review>
