<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Amor en la tarde" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the less distinguished by their superb director titles, though, and it could not be otherwise, exquisite and elegant.</summary>
	<body>"Paris live happily a detective private already quite major and his daughter of nineteen years, who plays the cello."The father is following the adventures of a damsel that seems to be taking the horns to her husband. And indeed, it puts them with a handsome American, as an adult, very rich and handsome. As the vengeful husband wants to kill the American, the girl warns, beginning an affair between them.He does not know it or what it's called or who is actually. "She, to interest you, puts jealous making him see that many lovers has". One of the less distinguished by their superb director titles, though, and it could not be otherwise, exquisite and elegant. The first movie is with Wilder guionizara the great I.A.L. Diamond, who worked nearly thirty years with the Viennese.Wilder manages to give a patina of class, wonderful photography in black and white film, narrating a somewhat rugged story with hand silk thanks to some elaborate dialogues and some enternecedoras performances. However, it fails him, against all pronósitco, used pace and the character of the protagonist male, interpreted with some reluctance by a too mature Gary Cooper, which seems to be happening is it not very well with his role. But the film is winning as the history is twisted through the jealousy of the bon vivant.And then when I get the mastery in the staging of Wilder, with a simply wonderful ending that excites and moves really. Until then, removing their first twenty minutes, very good, is a hang out with Midlands and allegedly funny scenes, but only stay in Nice, as the Gypsy Quartet (truly Gypsy, because Wilder hired them to see them play at a Parisian cafe) drinking and partying are later going to the sauna to accompany the protagonist. The truth is that it is endearing, Yes, but little fun.In short, a film I think that minor within the Filmography of Wilder, which sets out how the virtue and innocence beats the Vice and evil live.</body>
</review>
