<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>How multinationals of the crime of the 21st century? The answer:?Miami Vice?, thorough and accurate recreation of the drug mafias.</summary>
	<body>Since the robbery starring De Niro and Val Kilmer in "Heat" gave me the heart to one hundred, I feel real veneration for Michael Mann, an admiration which touched the sky with its wonderful, deep and unique "Collateral". Why he hoped his film version of "Miami Vice" with the same anxiety that Carpanta was eager to dip a juicy roast chicken. The fact is that this summer that we have been seeing several different movie trailers, the "Corruption in Miami" has not been one of the most spectacular, nor much less. Not passes nothing why, the truth that the trailer for "Alatriste" showed great promise and, in the end, the announcement that the movie itself was more exciting.The case is that, still tired and without excessive desire, I dragged to Sacai cinema to enjoy in rigorous premiere this "Miami Vice" which both expected. And the first thing I wanted to see, rather listen to, was this subject that linkamos here.Viewers of my generation, to be sure, will bring echoes and memories of a good handful of nights spent with TV, in the company of Sonny Crocket, Ricardo Tubbs and, above all, mysterious and enigmatic Lieutenant Castle, which ended up gaining favor and affection of all of us.But the great song, that piece of item with which the sinister Total opened up all their powerful live performances, does not appear in the film. And although Sonny is ticking to any host, already not embraga with that decision of yesteryear, while he released and pressed the accelerator with their moccasins of design. is wrong all that? No. Because Michael Mann has gone from nostalgia and has decided to immerse ourselves in the most modern and current Miami, a Miami, as well as the fascinating Los Angeles which showed us in "Heat" and "Collateral", under the eye of her camera, looks like a genuine work of art of post-modernity, subjugating and stunning, images taken from aircraft and helicopters to aerial shotspespunteadas by an excellent soundtrack, you are happily printed in the retina.The visual talents of Michael Mann has no competence, today, the world cinematography. True that it enjoys very high budgets. Truth is that they allow you to do what pleases, but certainly the history aprovecha.¿Y? Direct, blunt and to the point. How multinationals of the crime of the 21st century? The answer: "Miami Vice", thorough and accurate recreation of the drug mafias, their connections and their springs. Without barely a minute to the everyday life of the life of the protagonists, only what is strictly necessary to define the characters and make that the pieces of the script complete fitting in "Miami Vice" everything takes place at breakneck speed. Operations are mounted on the fly, the decisions are stark and orders are fulfilled ipso facto.¿Los characters? Best Ricardo to Sonny, the truth, although it has more prominence. And, above all, Gong Li, magnificent. Up her love story, a priori the most dangerous of the film is credible, torrid and exciting. And also convinced me that Haggard and orondo Lieutenant Castillo.¿Y Tosar? Very well. Disturbing, magnetic, and very of the Earth, reading a newspaper of economic information with news concerning Amancio Ortega, Zara and Caixanova.¿Y action? It is not a "corruption in Miami" is not a salad shot, exactly, but every shot has the strength of a blow. Both the snipers of the principle and the sequence of child abduction are ideally solved. And the final sequence. only a master as Mann, with that narrative pulse for action sequences, is capable of shooting a transaction of drugs and money as if you were counting the Iraq Guerra. Fascinating. Epatante.¿Estamos, therefore before a masterpiece? Lol There are downtime, downs of pace and a certain general coldness that leaves you a bitter, metallic aftertaste. If in "Collateral", Mann achieved a perfect combination between design, sociology, philosophy and action, in "Miami Vice" premium formal on the emotional, the way on the merits. But nothing happens. Mann remains a crack and, of course, four or five sequences of "Corruption in Miami" worth infinitely more than 95% of the films currently on Billboard.</body>
</review>
