<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="John Rambo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The savagery which proposes Sly is so free violent entertainment as absolutely brilliant. Hour and a half of pure fun that Yes, very, very tainted blood.</summary>
	<body>After a long pause (over 15 years), Sylvester Stallone returns to tie the Red bow on the front in what is the fourth installment of "Rambo". As it already did recently with "Rocky Balboa", Sly is also responsible for writing and directing the roost.In a paragraph landscape of Thailand, Rambo WINS life hunting snakes to be sold to circuses and tourist attractions of the area. His life passes quietly until that a group of missionaries hires him to take up river to Burma, because they intend to distribute medication to one of peoples who suffer from attacks of the fearsome army of the place. As you would expect, the group is captured, so the heroic soldier, together with a group of mercenaries hired to do so, must return to take up machine gun and machete to rescue them.Few will certainly not be who come to this proposal with the few eyebrows were raised. What can offer at this point a fourth part of something so already by themselves exhausted and overcome by the passage of years? And lest we forget, the good of Sly has already sixty-two years, will not be too withered to these trotes?Well, the answer to the first question is as simple as opposed: everything and nothing.Nothing, because if what one expects from a film so is a minimum of plot coherence, or the slightest existence of a fairly elaborate script, you can go from long of it. It is completely impossible to take "John Rambo" seriously, because in that way it could be seen even an attack for the seventh art.Plot rather than predictable, flat and absurdly archetypal characters, deliberately Manichean situations, are just some of the constants of the film that will surely put the willies to anyone who contributes to this.But it is that this movie is aimed at those who also understand film as entertainment, those who know how to distinguish between art and entertainment, because ultimately embraces them both equally. Go, who know how to enjoy a good session palomitera.Because the savagery which proposes Sly is so free violent entertainment as absolutely brilliant. "Hour and a half of pure fun that Yes, very, very stained blood.""John Rambo" is a survival as in days gone by, with very good good and bad very bad, with incredible and exciting shot action scenes with strong pulse, and the is not perceived shame when it comes to decapitate, open channel, strangle, violate, or to blow up human bodies.For a long time that American cinema dared not brand new products so we (the most recent test are in the sweetened "4.0 jungle"), but it is that "John Rambo" does not stop to be an update of the 1980s action film, goes much further, becoming a show totally gore to meet even the early work of Peter Jackson or Sam Raimi as hemoglobin refers. Prodigy is achieved thanks to a few special effects extremely visceral, able to turn any extra who appears on screen (literally) in a rain of blood and guts.As to whether Stallone is capable of keeping the rate or not, suffice to say that half of dialogues with the other actors are reduced to monosyllabic with eyes glassy and lost in the horizon. But what more gives? John Rambo has become more explicitly violent and ruthless than ever, and that is what really matters.</body>
</review>
