<review author="Silvia Giner" title="La criatura perfecta" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The perfect creature is one of the bad movies you are going to watch this year. I believe that not even worth seeing or for those that are very very loving of the vampire theme or Gótika. It is slow and lacks any emotion.</summary>
	<body>Was when I saw for the first time the trailer for this movie, I touched a lot "another film on top with vampires and vampire baby". Clear que.en the film almost gives me the soponcio.The perfect creature is one of the bad movies you are going to watch this year. I believe that not even worth seeing or for those that are very very loving of the vampire theme or Gótika. It is slow and lacks any emotion. Narrates as live human and pseudo-vampiros in a retro-futuro in which these vampires are known as "Los Hermanos" and play a role similar to the Catholic priests in the society, that left the evident similarity for reflection. This co-production New Zealand - United Kingdom me has pulled out of my boxes for many reasons, as they are so many, I'll comment on the most relevant.Firstly, the decorated suck enough, it must be said that sometimes that is the cardboard stone, I have heard in my life almost a soundtrack so insignificant as this, not accompanied at all to history is descompasada and also for most I imagine that it goes unnoticed.Futuristic touch they have given to the film bristled me heart, God so ugly thing, that idea as vomit, God causes a sensation of constant repudiation towards what you are seeing. Also not be sustained because a minimally advanced society would never have whores streets unpaved, there are sequences in which is the ground of land and do straw?, we are going to run the horror. Not to say that they have black and white televisions, microphones that seem taken from DUNE coexisting with vans and airships, anyway.And as you would expect, I have here a good section of DESPELLEJE: Dougray Scott (the villain in mission impossible II) that we already entertained in Hitman and us alucinará in their next TV Movie Dr. Jekyll &amp; Mr. Hyde stars in "The perfect creature" and concludes in which will surely be the worst interpretation of his life. But let's see Dougry, do all the time why do is gesture by moving the head to the side as if you were a beast? Jo-der once is OK but all the time? I parce a pathetic way to build a character so rich as "Silus" and especially "Vampire" which has an infinite amount of possible registrations and siembargo the end result created by Dougray is impoverished.Well to finish with the I marujeo "could not leave me behind" to Saffron Burrows (the mystery Galíndez) aka "The fashion anorexic" because you know it because I've said it many times, I am up to the noses of the fucking look chupachúps and I think follow reivicando curves (Monica Belucci power!) this actress is that really give you some ganitas give a hot soupOh by God, is and perfect complement to spoil what could have been a great movie. It is also extremely bland and picks up the gun as a spaghetti, fatal, interpretativamente zero PATATERO.</body>
</review>
