<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Beowulf 3D" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Absolutely if it is worth going to see this movie in 3D. The effects are very well made and it is fun to enjoy them. You'll spend a while different and far from the typical bad film in 3D, this is different.</summary>
	<body>Absolutely if it is worth going to see this movie in 3D. The effects are very well made and it is fun to enjoy them. You'll spend a while different and far from the typical bad film in 3D, this is different. I recommend that you go to see the Kinepolis cinemas (which you can) or at least to a room that is enabled with THX (champion) and digital reproduction, that this is the best form to see a film in high definition. If you are going to a movie (and it is not the day of the premiere) coil will be reporducido already so many times that the quality will be significantly less.Beowulf is a hero of the eponymous Anglo-Saxon epic poem, which was written in old English alliterative verse. Its importance is comparable to the of the Nibelungenlied, Cantar de mío Cid, the song of Roland or Lebor Gabála Érenn. It has two major parts: the first occurs during the youth of Beowulf, and tells how comes to the aid of the Danes or Jutes, who suffered the attacks of a giant (Grendel), and after killing him, confronts his mother; in the second part Beowulf is already the King of the Geats and fight to death with a dragon.And in this fantastic adaptation to the big screen by hand of director Robert Zemeckis have a digitized Ray Winstone as "oh my God is good" making of Beowulf and which we will be able enjoy soon in Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull. Another that has been digitized is the beautiful Angelina Jolie, which have given a few pounds more and unsa very successful curves that make digital model a genuine esc ultura far removed from the original model closest to the chupachúps look.They have already long us than the actors we are condemned to disappear and be replaced by digital, much cheaper and less gourmet than flesh and bone models, I had my doubts but after seeing BeoWulf I think I begin to worry.</body>
</review>
