<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="No es país para viejos" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A deep and admirable masterpiece, endowed with intelligence, reflections and metaphors. Can not ask you more; any of it, sensational, is one of those movies that will endure over the years in the history of cinema.</summary>
	<body>Various levels of a desert area south of the United States, linked by a voice in off of the great Tommy Lee Jones reflecting on the passage of time, open that, of course, is the best movie of the talented brothers Coen, an absolute masterpiece that Captivate anyone who knows to appreciate it. If, in a superficial way, we analyze is not country for old men, we are faced with a simple story of psychopaths, police and money in the middle. But so are now simple filmmakers. Joen and Ethan Coen, which are of the great return to its heyday (of Fargo, specifically) to bring us a brilliant combination of literature and images (the film in question is based on the acclaimed eponymous novel by Cormac McCarthy) that several points in common has with the other mentioned and award-winning film. Loneliness, old age, the incomprehension, evil, or gratuitous violence are aspects to emphasize that they were also reflected in this film, despite contain, his last feature film, several doses of adrenaline, contained intelligence and anthologies reflections that will cost forget. And it is that the film itself is truly vibrant, while leisurely pace and sadistic content. It has an incalculable virtue only geniuses can reach, and is developing an apparently simple and topical history of virtuous way to give it abysmal intelligence, tragic scenes, and other truly violent and without leaving the Coens touch that makes visible that label that have marked with total security. Rarely are so risky film moments as those who are not is country for old men, moments in the heart is going a hundred and of which you never know how it will end. The narrative force possessing the film is therefore, not only admirable, but truly unusual.It is said that a masterpiece is that representation to which no missing or spare nothing, which is perfect. This film may qualify as such by precisely, not contain any failure. It is incredibly perfect, which scared many when they think that it is not possible to too. And it is that ladies and gentlemen, this drama is the most unexpected limits, is the best thing I've seen in years, and that is something complicated, very difficult to get. No doubt, with a tremendous pulse and a brilliant script, the film is develops an agile and realistic fluid reaching contain scenes in which the viewer will feel as immersed in the film that come up to terrorize is (most of them headed by Anton Chigurh psychopath). As discussed above, is not country for old men has an unforgettable reflection about the place in what live in ideal, of a present marked by violence devoid of meaning and a past that should be recalled. The film not only opens with an unforgettable introduction, but that his conclusion is even more touching and understandable in a way by killing witness a story containing, camouflaged between violence and a lost protagonist, all aspects mentioned, human and curiously moralizing. So this movie from the Coen brothers is not wonderful for well done is (which also), but to contain one of the most tragic reflections on today's society very rare in today's art. Spanish actor who has received all possible prizes and that soon we will know whether it rises with a golden statuette can be seen also as a cinematographic work of undeniable perfection, with daring and sensational one-way, an enviable literary adaptation and a few performances that deserve recognition of the great, especially that of Javier Bardem. His performance is simply impeccable, sadistic, funny, brilliant, wonderful &hellip; everything you want and more. It is stunning in its role of psychopath and interprets unforgettable sequences as the accident of traffic, the motel, the of the gas station, etc. This Anton Chigurh is, as well as a personality impossible, a brash man, which you you can expect any bad thing. Their motivations, their character, their coldness, their movements, his awful hair cut &hellip; everything is perfectly recreated by the best actor of today that deserves the Oscar without a doubt. Josh Brolin, the protagonist, is also great in his role of loser man found a suitcase full of dollars and has to flee from the criminal world in which has been involved. As well as the character of Tommy Lee Jones (magnificent as the police that manages to give meaning to the title and the work itself) represents the tiredness, old age and a clear vision of the world today, and Bardem the wickedness of a person living away from the normal, of Brolin is intended to symbolize the typical war veteran that hard to decide with clear evidence,, thus introducing another element is basic in No country for old men: that of consciousness. Key scenes as this Hunter when encounters the loot the money (with a map of him without knowing exactly what to do) or the most shocking and unexpected which takes place in the only telephone conversation that engaged with the killer who pursues him, Chigurh, when it has to decide between his wife and the money. I desvelaré not anything, because this is the essential element that carries all the fateful outcome. I've already said too much.The last film by the Coen brothers is nothing more than a deep and admirable masterpiece, endowed with intelligence, reflections and metaphors. Can not ask you more; any of it, sensational, is one of those films that will endure over the years in the history of cinema. We also never forget the performance of our Javier Bardem, from this moment, it is one of the best that have been seen in recent decades. So there is no doubt: must see is No country for old men. Is essential, the best in what little we have of the year.</body>
</review>
