<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Hacia rutas salvajes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In addition to music and careful photography of the film, notes in a resounding manner main actor Emile Hirsch, that bears the weight of the film magnificent way, makes us see life in a way much more clean and private prejudices.</summary>
	<body>I imagine Sean Penn as a visceral kind that is guided by emotions rather than the head. A man that acts by impulses, able to embark on any adventure if you it is filled with truth. So imagine as well by his way of acting, put on paper, often offering heartfelt, deep and extreme interpretations by its ability to transform, by his eyes halfway between the sadness of who has seen many things and the determination of who does not stop at nothing or to anyone.Also it gives me that image in his role as director, just embarking on those projects that falls, leading to the screen stories with which it identifies and choosing actors representing how clear his alter ego on the screen. It happened with the obsessed detective, played by Jack Nicholson in "The oath" and the same here, with the younger Emile Hirsch, in the evocative and ecological "towards wild"routes.Christopher McCandless is a young intelligent and bounced with the society in which he lives. Did not understand their parents, a couple obsessed with money and labour that are barely supported each other and also includes a system that cancels out the individuality and rewards the materialism. His rooted idealism will take you to change its entry into the University for the start of an internal search, breaking any tie of social conformism. To do so, donate practically all of its studies to an NGO Fund and decided, begins a journey that will try to survive on its own in the countryside.As I said at the beginning, the film shows that Sean Penn is in love with the story and, paradoxically, this fact lastra narration at certain times in a clear way. Penn tries to reach the Viewer as much information as possible, leaving nothing in the pipeline, adding to their images of an alive nature and wild and the adventures of the protagonist, a voiceover with the thoughts of Christopher and his sister that, in my view, slows down the narrative, becoming her at times too guided. His loyalty to the original novel prevents you from leaving the global vision in the hands of simple images and own intuition of the spectator, wanting to take it by the mental path that he himself had drawn up at the reading.At other times, however, the film runs fluid mode and then is when the director shows its full potential, in these passages in which simply leaves the camera observed the protagonist in his quest, without trying to influence or indoctrinate. In those moments in which words are not needed, it dazzles a careful soundtrack with the worn and powerful voice of Eddie irons, leader of the rock band Pearl Jam and composer of some topics in perfect harmony with the spirit of the film.In addition to music and careful photography of the film, notes in a resounding manner main actor Emile Hirsch, that bears the weight of the film so magnificent, portraying a character charismatic and charming, a type without evil makes us see life in a way much more clean and private prejudices.Also drew me attention to the sensual role of Kristen Stewart, the girl who we saw pass them straws with Jodie Foster in "Panic room", which has grown to become a teenager with a look of serene wild perversity.To conclude, in its two hours and twenty of footage, "towards wild routes" get the purpose of thinking to the public what are things that are worthwhile in a life that we we're losing sensations as atavistic as necessary. Although maybe that we also thought in less time.</body>
</review>
