<review author="Moebius" title="El mago (The Wiz)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If you want a lysergic trip without drugs won't see the wizard, it will not disappointed.</summary>
	<body>In that would think Sidney Lumet to get into a similar scrubbing? It seems that the man really worked with estusiasmo on the project, but I cannot think of worse way of closing a decade as bright as that signed there in the 1970s. The wizard is certainly not an evening dogs. The lethal power of this tape served to wipe all the blaxploitation phenomenon. It would be funded by the CIA?There was someone who had the happy idea of mounting a musical on Broadway based on the classic story of the wizard of Oz, but adapting it to the reality of African American and only with singers and dancers of color. The capo of the Motown, Berry Gordy, wanted to bring the musical to the big screen by Motown Productions, the film and television subsidiary of the famous black record company. Initially Gordy wanted the same protagonist of music to interpret the virginal Dorothy. But the manipulative Diane Ross got of medium and persuaded the producer Rob Cohen to offer a production deal with her as a top star. A thirty-something years making Dorothy Ross? It's the magic of the soul! The initial director felt that what had no logic and left the ship. Sidney Lumet, I do not know if I needed to pay off the mortgage or was clueless, was in charge of the direction.Apart from Miss Ross and some survivors of the cast of the musical was moved another great Star (already detached Motown) that perform the scarecrow. And what a star! Michael Jackson, when still not had become Wacko Jacko, co-protagonizaría the film along with the Ross. Mage was to Comedian Richard Pryor, and by long omnipresent Quincey Jones was in charge of the musical arrangements with a Pleiad of musicians and composers.I suppose that you to really enjoy with the magician is a black brother proud of their race that odie to Judy Garland, either or is a staunch fan of the funk, soul and music disc. Within the nonsense I cannot deny that I enjoyed the experience. There are some good songs, highlighting especially those in which Jackson takes protagonism, although others, especially ballads, they are quite boring. Then there is the collection of incredible masks Wacko Jacko and its antólogicas quotes from famous literally out of the filling of the body (?). To the decorated kitsch and black characters past acid added a few dialogs that appear to perjeñados by a schizophrenic (Joel Schumacher screenplay) and scenes unpayable as the persecution in the subway station, where bins and columns come to life and attack the characters! Not to mention some enigmatic taxis never take passengers and a long scene in the twin towers (Yes, the world of Oz merges with the of New York. worthy of a genius!) with colors and dances that stretches to infinity (and that which was shortened due to technical problems!) that leaves the best fill of Christmas Turkey at the height of a hamburger Mac.Las scenes intertwine as the sausages can entangle, and must be the music with less dialogue I've seen in my life. As the fish who drink, here they sing, sing and sing and return to singing. And when it already seems that Dorothy is going to return home, he gets to sing again! Spectacular, friends.I guess that it should be humor to enjoy with so strange film, but as I have already said I admit that I have spent good times. He would repeat the experience? I doubt it, but if you want a lysergic trip without drugs won't see the wizard, it will not disappointed.And that someone explain to me if you have any meaning that in a film where the protagonist all are black back home thanks to a white magician.</body>
</review>
