<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="El hombre con rayos X en los ojos (The man with X-ray eyes)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Original and risky (for the time), which includes several genera, and consisting of some moments of fun more fused with each other terribly cumbersome.</summary>
	<body>The classic debate of the topic of the superpowers: if I have them, do I take them to good, or just the opposite? In this film, Dr. James Xavier (Ray Milland) discovers a drops that give her X-ray eyes, and can thus see through anything put you in front.In his case, no doubt, you want to use the gift to see through skin and meat of their patients. It should not be forgotten that the film is 1963, and technical resources that were available at that time were rather more limited than now.As always, before a character equipped with benign powers that improves the human condition (at whatever level), is humanity itself who rejects him. It is something that the pupils of Professor Xavier (I mean this time Charles, of the X-Men), Spider-Man, or the very American Justice League, happens to them from almost the first moment of its existence. The causes can be many, but primarily tends to be out of fear or envy. Who wouldn't want be invisible, climb the walls, or faster than a bullet?The trigger in "the man with" is simple. A patient is about to be operated by one of the most renowned doctors of the hospital. However, when our James notes it, he discovers that the diagnosis is wrong, and that requires another type of treatment. He saves the life, but it is obvious that entering the brava in an operating room, making a cut where it isn't, having crippled the doctor to convince him, is not too well seen, and when called to meet with his superior, makes an unfortunate and terrible mistake. The Tin of Thunder is now open. From now on you will have to earn a living secretly, in circuses, and using false names ("pass and see Mentalo, man who reads the mind").But that is not the only problem facing our unfortunate hero. The human soul, full of good intentions, is still easily corruptible. Erotic power here takes all its meaning. With a drop of the drops (which by the way, the same doctor calls it "X", remainder of the beater) get to see through a role. Two, through the clothes. With three of the walls. And so on. So that what begins as an experiment just becoming an addiction without limits, until the point to destroy the pupils and turn itself into a genuine threat.In the final section of the film, the protagonist gets to see the insides of the universe, and is a vision that can not stand, so far as boot, in the last frame of the film, the eyes. There are things for which humanity is not yet ready.As for the film itself, "X: The Man with the X-Rays Eyes" is 1963 and Roger Corman (known as one of the most sparing directors to make films), therefore relatively poor visually (attention to the skeletons at the feast: does not move even one, while in fact they are in full and hyperactive bellacon). That Yes, the colouring is amazing anytime. It is an original bet and risky (for the time), which includes several genera, and consisting of some moments of fun more fused with each other terribly cumbersome. It is very short (less than one hour and a quarter) and is determined with solvency by a mythical and tanning director at Serie B.</body>
</review>
