<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="Halloween El Origen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The failures and successes of the remake of Zombie are respectively, due to their desire to pay homage to one of his idols and the use of an employment history for further digging in his personal aesthetic.</summary>
	<body>These hours will not be anyone who has not already come to Halloween (2007) by Rob Zombie, one of the most eagerly awaited films of 2007 (at least of the visitors of this page) and finally finished by brand new in Spain earlier this year. Treatment that this director has given to one of the most celebrated films of John Carpenter has proven to be fairly decent, although well below what he achieved with his two previous films. The failures and successes of the remake of Zombie are respectively, due to their desire to pay homage to one of his idols and the use of an employment history for further digging in his personal aesthetic.Because the best this new Halloween, is undoubtedly the first half, in which Rob Zombie used the story of the origins of Michael Myers and his insane psychopath to write another chapter in this great Chronicle of the white trash that already had outlined with their previous tapes. It certainly uses a lot of topics (abusive stepfather, unable to mother and an oppressive atmosphere full of violence and humiliation), but these never seemed exaggerated or explotativos; on the contrary, they are perfectly consistent with the thematic universe of the director, stressing the image of this androgynous child whose pleasure in the suffering of others is the only way of escape to a reality in which he is always the weakest and fool them that surround him. From there the film evolves to narrative pulse that occurs between Michael and Sam Loomis psychiatrist (character who is here much better used and developed in the original film), a man who, like the public, seek to understand the reasons for the behavior of Michael and what hides behind their willingness to kill. With the passing of the years this test be a sterile search, and after escape from the asylum where have locked you (in a very unpleasant sequence even by the standards of Rob Zombie), Michael returns to its former suburb of Haddonfeld to sow death among its inhabitants.In this second half is where the Zombie film loses much of its strength; as he has said on countless occasions, does not this second half of Halloween but summarize the original film except for slight differences (among them a greater number of casualties), with what, one might ask what has become of the delicate introspective look which the director had shown us. At the end, as Sam Loomis discovers, it is that the madness of Michael Myers has no explanation beyond violence as a unique expression of emotionality. But here the director has sinned a great excess, because I don't think they are necessary two hours of film to reach this conclusion. However, despite these flaws, should remove the hat before the way as Rob Zombie has dissected the slasher genre stripping completely and offering its most basic aspects to the extent that the same killer takes off voluntarily the mask to show veneration towards the final girl facing the. Also the relationship with sex typical of these masked psychopaths here has its explanation: this film girls use their sexuality as an element of humiliation and ridicule, starting with the unbearable sister of Michael and ending with the no less nerve-wracking friends of Laurie Strode. The interesting thing is that, with all this, Rob Zombie is not doing a tribute to the "myth" of Michael Myers, but on the contrary: it is destroying, in the same way that a child destroys a clock that opens to see how it works. This is the long prologue explícativo killing machine and the fact that, unlike the Carpenter film, this version not leaves open the possibility of a sequel (a key detail that the difference of almost all the rest of the genre). At the end, the Charter of love that Rob Zombie and his friends (is impressive the amount of luminaries of the terror and the B series walk through this film) have written to the original work of JC is burdened by excessive footage and also excessive reverence to the master (not only in what refers to the second half but also to the use of the original theme song)(, which here seem to not fit too well), but is without doubt one of those good remakes, one that is worth see to appreciate the work of someone who has not only been Halloween, but that it also understood. As always, there will be discrepancies in the final result, but the difference is that here appreciates the tone of a true artist.</body>
</review>
