<review author="Txapulin" title="Sweeney Todd" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We have a different movie that mixes several genres (musical, terror of psicokillers, Victorian drama, and a point of gore) in a way as only Tim Burton can do it, and certainly meets expectations.</summary>
	<body>Notice that my vision about this film is completely deviated by the fact that two of my cultural passions come together: Stephen Sondheim and Tim Burton. The Sondheim Broadway musical is a musical masterpiece and has the strange point in its favor that is a musical of terror, with the apparent contradiction that this entails. When many years ago (more than ten) started the rumors that Burton wanted to make the movie, I thought there was no one better than him so, and when it really began to make and began to leave the news about the cast (Johnny Depp, Helena Bonham Carter, Alan Rickman, Sasha Baron-Cohen), all tallied perfectly.And yesterday I saw the film, and all block perfectly. Any expectation that I could have met in the film. Refers to all expectations, except one: the surprise factor. What had I given yesterday by to enter to see the film without knowing anything about it, without having previously seen the musical, without knowing me the Catalan version of the songs from memory, without even knowing nothing of the plot, or unaware even that is a musical. For whoever comes to the Virgin film about the film, the shock must be very strong, and that so much envy.I wrestled at the moment against the temptation to write in this review a comprehensive study on the small differences between the film and the musical theatre. First because the majority of those who read me have seen none of the two things (missing three weeks so they release the movie in Spain), and second because it is a futile exercise, the musical and the film should be treated as different though in my head things have tangled. In any case, that you may know that there are some small details that I liked most in the theater and I think they improve the story and the characters and in the film are not so well treated.Step directly to enumerate all the good things we find in Sweeney Todd, and to see if I encourage you to see it and contéis me. First, the cast is exceptional. Johnny Depp, superb, as always, his interpretation is at the height of the character (all is said is a caramel character for any actor). Helena Bonham-Carter in general I dislike, but here is exceptional, his Mrs. Lovett manipulative, interested, but fragile and blind love is the perfect counterpoint to his partner, his impossible love. As I am in love with Alan Rickman and his voice, I cannot be impartial, as neither the immoral Judge Turpin, his character is. The rest of the side, including children and this so different from his Borat Sasha Baron-Cohen, are great.What Tim Burton always leaves more footprint in aesthetics, but it is what more I have been fascinated here is the costume. These dresses and costumes Victorian and somethings that are incredibly beautiful. And then there is the apparent technical "carelessness" in two other fundamental aspects of the film: the sets and makeup. Of the sets is also typical of Burton, is that since you're using models, you notice that they are models. The same goes for the makeup; It is deliberate that note the makeup of the characters and you notice that it shows his mood and his inner torment. And the same is true with, call it "bloody exaggeration" of the movie, which seems out of the films of Dario Argento. I am sure that Burton had the means to do the blood, make-up and much more realistic sets, but then had lacked several homages to the film kitch and naïve than her own film is product, including autohomenajes to his own movies (about the mock-up is mark of the House) and the musical that originated the movie (where the blood sprinkled literally to the public of the first rows).Total, that we are dealing with a different film that mixes several genres (musical, psicokillers, Victorian drama, and a point gore horror) of one way in which only Tim Burton could have done it, and certainly meets expectations.</body>
</review>
