<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="OSS 117: El Cairo, nido de espías" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A surprise any fan of the double zero agent should be lost, but also anyone eager to spend a bit of really nice.</summary>
	<body>Cairo is a real pressure cooker. English, French, spies and Soviets populate the city while the family of the deposed King Farouk and the sect of the Eagles of Cheops will compete for the power of the city. In the midst of all this hubbub, the French Republic decides to send the agent Hubert Bonisseur of Bath, aka OSS 117, to put a little order and step Jack investigate the mysterious death of the spy Jefferson.Toda a real mythology surrounds this gala film, that a delay of almost two years finally premieres in the Spanish charts. The character first appeared in the novels of Jean Bruce, which followed a series of film adaptations during no less than two decades were appearing in European cinemas until his disappearance probably by exhaustion of a character which could not compete against the Almighty 007.Por do so, return to the big screen of the French spy needed a changea wash of image that he would highlight in a time when action cinema is saturated as exhausted. Thus, "OSS 117." "Cairo, nest of spies" chooses to enter the ground also quite overused of parody, and becomes a scathing attack at the same time that charming homage to the James Bond Sean Connery who embodied forty-five years ago.But unlike other crude attempts, this time the proposal cannot draw attention for several reasons.First and foremost, be sensed that this great joke comes signed by a truly passionate team of the genus to which homage. Everything in it reminds to the mythical "Goldfinger" or "From Russia with love": the actor protagonist, Jean Dujardin, is a calque of James Bond, extent to be at times difficult to distinguish him from the Scottish actor: nail, literally, his grimacing as his surprising capacity for enarcar eyebrows, but it is that is surprisingly similar complexion (see the sequence of the sauna). More importantly its design and visual style. Not knowing that he made in 2006, the film could strain perfectly by one of the first in the Bond series. Photography, costumes, hairstyles, scenarios, and even movements of camera (these zooms) and levels, dress the film under a guise of mature flavor that makes remember with nostalgia times past.Another important card account the film is the humor employed away from easy jokes and thick brush, is mainly based on ignorance of the French to close to other cultures alien to yours. Because in fact, "OSS 117." is not simply a parody of 007, if not also the individual's French (and in general, West) as well as certain aspects of Eastern religions. Therefore, however much that is set in 1955, Michel Hazanavicius film no longer cutting current in your background, satirising rightly about the problems present today.Course, it is not the perfect comedy, and hold any downturn in pace can it against him (in the same way that happened, by the way, with the films of Sean Connery), but still continues to be the premiere of the week, a surprise that any fan of the double zero agent should be lost, but also anyone eager to spend a bit of really nice.</body>
</review>
