<review author="José A. Peig" title="Rambo: acorralado" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite the little visual care by the filmmaker, is a film that knows where it wants to go, good pace and a few very bad grape-laden dialogues and raised points of view with respect to concepts such as hypocrisy, survival and the law of the strongest.</summary>
	<body>The hangover which is detrimental to a film as genuine as it is First Blood is the impersonal and telefílmica management of director Ted Kotcheff - which does not prevent it in a very fluent narrative and in which the information is very well detoxified - and from here started to value a product than for a long time it has been very poorly valued and interpreted by traditional critics, and that never reaches the masterpiece that must have been because of the imbalance between the magnificent writing (screenplay) and the mediocre pulse of the filmmaker (realization). Following this, round up some nuances: the story about a disturbed than sowing chaos in a small town montañés possesses some attributes more akin to melodrama or independent cinema with pretensions of social criticism which action film pure and hard. From this angle, say that work Kotcheff is not at the height of the content, although the picture of Andrew Laszlo helps create a staging absorbent and the hostile atmosphere (mist, storms) that characterizes two strata of the scenery and the same theme: nature versus civilization, the savage against the representatives of the law and order.First and foremost, we need to find out what the causes or the features that explain a priori insubstantial icon but that - you despite who gets upset - has withstood the passage of time. And a film that 26 years later it has not lost validity with regards to their intrinsic values and its impact on popular culture. As it could not be otherwise, the center of attraction is the archetype represented in John Rambo (Sylvester Stallone), the timeless figure of the wild that threatened the established order, and which has its optimum expression in images that open the film: a lonely man that moves along a path from the interior of the forest and in direction to the cameralooking lanky and slightly desvaída look. Essential musical accompaniment of Jerry Goldsmith, which warns us about the elegiac nature of the film, tears for a soul destroyed in the brutality of war.That scruffy profile, progressively discovered us as a mad man is a victim of past circumstances and present (attention to the used flashbacks). And this is the trait that best defines the uniqueness and the narrative First Blood claw: make the viewer feel empathy for the wild, and aversion to the forces of the order. We refer to an archetype that has its roots in universal history, from the Amorites in times of Summer and Akkad, passing by the barbarians that undermined the foundations of the Roman Empire, and the Taliban on our immediate present. All respond to the archetype of the wild native mountains (or inhospitable desert), those who hate civilization, threaten to invade and destroy the order. Therefore, the scheme of First Blood this built on this same mythology. John Rambo, the savage, and sherif, played by Brian Dennehy, defender of civilisation, which puts morals and customs that govern the lives of the people to the Rambo style, thus personifying the intolerance against some modes of life (in this case, the tramp) who are on the fringes of social conventions (is laughable to read some critics who see in this film a ultra-conservative speech)When Rambo is actually a countercultural icon of anarchy and rebellion against the majority speech. (Anyway, they are not born stupid, but they do). The viewer feels attraction by what fears him is unknown. Therein lies the key which explains the magnetism of this character: the disturbed facing illustrated law using the laws of nature. This profile of intelligence based on the domain of wild nature, the ancient survival instinct coupled with skill in the dirtiest guerrilla military strategy. There the law is you, but here I am the law. Rabidly anti-war film is the x-ray of a disturbed, a victim of the system that ends up rebelling against the order that has created it when - after his escape through the riddled with underground of rats and aided by the light of a torch - attends the people and destroys the electricity of the population with shrapnel, while recreating the sounds and the fear of the war with the burning of gunpowder. Following the metaphorical game, it is the savage who has come to destroy civilization.Ultimately, John Rambo is the icon that responds to an archetype of savagery, hostility, alienation, and not devoid of a romantic look. Yes, that classical romanticism, of the marginalized and the Bohemian beatnick of the loser, and although here he alludes to those who failed in vietnam, the spirit beat is somehow part of the character. First Blood is a fierce metaphor for American society that fears to the wild but creates it in order to defend the civilization of those wild peoples that threaten it, to finally pursue it and condemn it to madness. And despite the little visual care by the filmmaker, is a film that knows where it wants to go, good pace and a few very bad grape-laden dialogues and raised points of view with respect to concepts such as hypocrisy, survival, the law of the strongest minority against the law of the weakest despite being most.</body>
</review>
