<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Alemania año cero" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A snapshot in movement of the time which represents the end of an era and the beginning of another. The zero fact history.</summary>
	<body>Adolescence: age happens to children and which runs from puberty until the full development of the organism. RAEEstamos in Germany in what is known as the zero year, understanding the concept of zero not as a synonym for vacuum or nullity but silence after the bombs of peace after the war, pause after the waste of movement. The zero as a synonym for turning to a country that takes time to think, stop and breathe. To create, in short, an identity resurgence which Phoenix from the ashes. Germany has to reinvent, taking from the past that will serve but looking to the future. Looking askance at what was at other times with the intention of not forget that their actions had consequences, and making use of the value to face the natural evolution which hangs above him.Placing already from the title the place and time of the movie, Rossellini makes clear his intention with a double semi-documentary home through a text and a voice in the form of Declaration of intent. Germany year zero takes the hand the young Edmund to continue their passage from childhood to adolescence with him in a constant metaphor about the zero point in which the country is undergoing. This maturation process that is adolescence is the time in which Edmund must begin to create their own personality leaving (or being left behind by) everything that was part of the child that was before, whether they were innocent games with girls or ball games. That moment in which Edmund begins to cease to be a child (something that visually is accompanied during the film with a change of costume and some darkness at the levels of the second half of the film) is reinforced not only by his actions (such as killing his father in one shows teenage confusion Oedipal or denying a caress their families) but by the treatment by others. The girls see you as a child as well as his family, but some and others are calling to do adult things. This intermediate world where Edmund is subject is the world of doubts he lived Germany during the period of confusion, when nazis and allies should live in a State in which no one knew already what was the North and what the South. "before we were National Socialists, are now only Nazi"the Professor tells a character at one point in the film. Before and now. Take what was to assume that no are longer. Reinvent itself, ultimately. Edmund does it, or at least try. Germany should do so, or that is what thinks Rossellini. In this constant it immerses US Germany year zero. Life re-emerging among the ruins, the evolution not expected and there are these trains, constant throughout the film, which appear to remind you to an entire country that time passes and not expected. A snapshot in movement of the time which represents the end of an era and the beginning of another. The zero fact history.</body>
</review>
