<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Classic films in the 21st century: Atonement is a copy and passionate love for a wonderful book (Ian McEwan). Again we see literature and the cinema caught the hand. Long...</summary>
	<body>There is a predictive cinema: one moves ahead of the plot, reasoning that the characters are always more runs later and gives with the distress key with astonishing ease. It is not that one is a prodigy or that you have already seen so many films that the talent and the necromancy have partnered their causes to our benefit. There is another puzzling anomalous film: one is misplaced and not right to find a point in the plot from where to take interest. Experimental film or terrible film disguised as experimental film. Then there is good film, inspired, that when one contemplates the serene harmony of classical proportions and has the certainty of that years later will be recalled when he saw the film, who enjoyed that so enormous pleasure and what bobo face (the side with which one admires the intelligence and beauty) we stayed when darkness disappeared and peopleoverwhelmed, happy, abandons the seats.Atonement rummages in the Christian concept of fault. Slowly (perhaps excessive in its premioso and almost infuriating boot), it enters the lives of those who grew up around a lie and how that lie determines its existence to the point that can not escape their infinite capacity for destruction. Fascinating from the point of view of go by lifting the formidable building of his argument from a simple premise (the idle and boring life of a teenage girl from high society forced to formulate an entirely false testimony) and a commendable plasticity, Atonement is a love story. Perhaps an unorthodox but love (to the end and Cape) is what moves the small plot knots that McEwan and Hampton (novel author and screenwriter of the film respectively) set out to offer emotions, a huge flow of them, emotions that impedes a sharp study of the hypocrisy of society which portrays, but even that is forgivable given of the (almost)(, now let me explain) satisfactory outcome of the film.The English aristocracy does not support heat: up a diner says that the haze exacerbates the nature and encourages losing the bonanza of the spirits. That the temperature rise detonates the tortuous and preciosista plot: the absolute molicie of whom everything has sometimes requires new toys that engolosinen your boredom. The rich girl used to invent worlds (because from the outset warned the eminently literary character of history: pure metaliteratura) can not resist the temptation of writing in the reality rather than in the invisible limbo of the folio blank. What his mischievous prose get is that an innocent (a kind of lacayo, a member of lower caste) loaded with the guilt of a sexual abuse. That informing aborted what could have been an extraordinary love story between the accused and his sister. Then Joe Wright begins with their temporary stunts, their intelligence and their more than sensitive sense of music, which takes over the tempo of the film and brand with concise noise key typewriter the upheavals, the connection between what is happening and that happened and that, in some arcane way, governs all the fringes of history. Without exception.Blame mingled in the spirit of the girl child, secretly in love with the man who smashes with his unhealthy niñería, is the common thread: everything is left to caress by this Atonement slowly 75º–82ºf, silent hatred regalada, swaying by pain, transmutada in one war instrument in this World War II serving as wild props.The typically English melódrama does not affect deeper meanings: Atonement moves away from the picturesque table of customs to the return to Brideshead or James Ivory tapes because what he wants is to show the Viewer (to the reader, first) a very simple purpose: we live to slopes with our sins, grow with them and we bury. The only difference, the element that the girl of delinquent imagination stipulates as an antidote to pain is literature, pure fiction, writing as grab that overwhelmed the infinite sadness. That is what makes success writer Briony Tallis: relive their convicted in the always overstuffed Kingdom of imagination. There, away from wars and injustices, errors and excesses, let them grow in his house next to the beach and there, in the book that grows in its interior, is where writer deletes the scene that dynamite his capricious and hedonistic, teens that that future lovers recognize his idyll with a sourcein an english garden Victorian packing and smell of tea and conversations galantes. The poetics of this image holds the entire subsequent history. Somehow, then chains the lives of many people. We learn in atonement that the destination is a bug bastard, one able to silence the splendor of a life based on whispers to levísimos tics of chance. We also learn that romance is left to contaminate of tragedy or that it may be impossible to define passionate (a brief moment of burning of a library before the eyes burnt by the curiosity of a child) of the fatality. All Atonement emanates fate, fate and moral misery. Impossible happiness becomes inevitable. This story of redemption is supplied from a formidable budget, how not. It is not enough to be a good movie but it is bound to more. This whirlpool of the industry is that recreates one of the most fascinating scenes these mine eyes have seen on a screen in a long time: the beach of Dunkirk, the neat and Baroque and delusional scan camera by an amazing landscape, devastated soldiers, los locos, which look at the horizon and sing hymns which hermanen them in the tragedyof the acrobats of their destiny mock death doing a few laughs from the sea while all around collapses, literally. And is not (also) free this Baroque visual style: everything we see, this lavish guignol, pushes the story where its creators wish, providing useful material to make what we expected more closely assimilated. Here there is no happy ending: it is not possible that there is. Betraying the spirit of McEwan could pull an extra viewers (Word of mouth is sometimes a gun loaded with nasty) but the precious history is its final stretch, the triumphal entry of a disarmingly full Vanessa Redgrave, which explains how his novel (which have seen on-screen in the last cent and peak minutes) is a farcean invention seasoned to expiate the guilt and Sin and the weight of all the demons that eat you heart when you know there is no way to return to the State of innocence that we was given.It is not a masterpiece. Here comes the corrective I have for not losing sleep tonight and sleep. It is not because the narrative material is so magnificent that his conversion to frames creates irreparable losses. There is also a bewildering gelidez moment. Cold and cunning, so seemed the film when there were after his exquisite and fundamental part. This coldness is worth, fits the purpose that guides his simple vocation of love story like glove. Truncated love, broken love, love turned into pink Novella melodrama, but the Fund is what matters, the impressive fresco of the human condition. I heard in a radio conversation, a not overly prepared to withdraw charm to the taquillazo, which Wright sinned of ersatz. I do not get to both, though I effort. I see artifice in everything that is fiction. Inevitablemente.hay much beauty in the movie. My prose needs an inspiration I no now have to deal with doubts of the gentle reader that creates me exceed and that I am simply selling personal emotions in excess. Atonement has the sumptuous elegance of classic cinema, part of a simply magnificent book (the Ian McEwan novel) and has enough support from the industry so nothing the ballast, and yet something depart me from considerla the jewel that is likely. To the best lack David Lean in command.</body>
</review>
