<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Orgullo y prejuicio" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A work to discover, that it is not flagging in their 2 hours of footage.</summary>
	<body>I'm not a fan of this type of film, moreover, do not know why the films produce me a unsustainable sense of sopor, although it is also true that as we left the cinema to see "Atonement" 2, almost to the time (we know that "Two sleeping in the same mattress become the same opinion") entered us an irremediable desire of seeing the first film as director Joe Wright, the (umpteenth) adaptation of the works of Jane Austen, "Pride and prejudice" and how the are putting on canal + each 2 by 3 (six) than better movie to see a Saturday this afternoon.On the other hand, once again, I refer to the evidence, it seems that Joe Wright has also become, not only a precedent, but also a style when it comes to his films, and is that compared with his next film you notice certain parallels that range from (quite similar) levels to the careful selection of music and it is that both are composed by Dario Marianelli. Another obvious dominant note in both is the absolute presence of Keira Knightley which I slowly managed to separate from "Pirates of the Caribbean"; and sights that cost me, because sometimes get me the stupid habit of setting a character to an actor and there is no way to take him off of him. Important also interpretations of Rosamund Pike, which knew of many films, Donald Sutherland, who do really well, as "father of the creatures" and above all Matthew Macfadyen, an actor to which known really little but makes credible and justifiable, his role as Mr.Darcy. Apart from the costume, ambiance and especially photography, with these landscapes that leave one with his mouth open and eyes as dishes, I have to say my wife will love it and after a couple of viewings made with special DVD, quite careful editing and it emulates the original book of Austen.Una work to discoverIt is not flagging in their 2 hours of footage.</body>
</review>
