<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Sweeney Todd" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not lost in nonsense, and from the first minute as we dabble in flour, translating the arrival of Todd to the mundane landscape London, under Tower Bridge. The best of 2008, with difference.</summary>
	<body>For all those who I usually read well know and know my passion towards Tim Burton, is why I could not (or known) hold the time remaining until its premiere in Spain (February 15) to see this MUSICAL film, one of the most famous musicals of Broadway, Sung almost in its entirety (little dialogue spoken there)(to tell the truth) and that, once again, starring Johnny Depp, along with Helena Boham Carter, Alan Rickman, Timothy Spall and Sacha Baron Cohen, in his first dramatic role, and is that Baron Cohen only have seen him do comedy. Note that Burton dreamed for years with the realization of this film and it shows, it shows in what has taken all care to make the Ribbon round from levels that separate the Ribbon entirely on an exercise fully theatrical, until the actors, even the effects and makeup, everything perfect, perhaps, the only negative note I see, and from there in that incapie over and over again that it is a MUSICAL is sometimes arriving tired so long singing by actors, is missing a little more dialogue, and is that both "Chicago" as "The fantásma of the Opera" or even "The producers" were partly spoken and partly Sung.The actors, all, without sin excepción exception are impressive, from Depp, who sings really well, until Alan Rickman, who takes to boot, but too it (bridging the gap) quite well, I leave aside to Timothy Spall, which frankly has much to learn to power "a little" sing good, given that his character everytime he opens his mouth it shows that theirs is not singing.Saving this and knowing in advance, are forgiven everything to the film, that it is not lost in nonsense, and from the first minute already us gets into flour, translating the arrival of Todd and the mundane landscape London, under Tower Bridge, or the final moments in the House of Todd.De best of 2008 with difference, hopefully uncle Oscar is good with Burton.</body>
</review>
