<review author="Caruco" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a great film, but if more than acceptable and interesting. That Yes, we must first save the pitfall of initial minutes pulling to bland.</summary>
	<body>I give a point only by give the opportunity to take a leading role and allow us to enjoy so many minutes on screen of a so great like him actor John Hurt. And I continue with the score. Another more so by the presence of Elijah Wood, proving that you can do something to break his image of hobbit. It is not a great film, but if more than acceptable and interesting. That Yes, we must first save the pitfall of initial minutes pulling to bland; presentation of characters and situations, and where Álex de la Iglesia shows us what will be its realization: pulling rather flat and television, abuses of close-up and disappointing levels and contraplanos in the sequences of dialogues, as if it were delighted with the retrieved distribution and want to be more respectful to him.In general it is very difficult to find any identifying mark of the style of the Community Manager, read black humor, bad baba or personal gender twist. We will have to wait a while to break the tone with any technical or formal virguería and this will be a flat sequence from the interior of an auditorium, going out to the street and entering a bookstore, moving... culminating with the discovery of the first crime. A plane sequence that most significant characters are going through.And most, not all, because as a good tale of suspense that boasts, in the style of Agatha Christie, the screenplay is truffled of side and main, characters about which do fall inevitable suspicions about his possible involvement in the facts or not. Also proliferate the winks to the Hitchcock master: level sequence cited with trick rope type; the presence in the distribution of Anna Massey, actress of frenzy; or an overhead plane under a staircase, forced reference to Vertigo. And all this seasoned with dialectics on philosophy versus mathematics as possible methods to arrive at the truth of things, or slight flapping of a butterfly can cause a hurricane in the place and most unexpected moment.And if not I've counted wrong, hence wore added two points on 10. Would add you another: one more for the gorgeous Leonor Watling in leather, and only covered by an apron, while a clever side travelling in general level discover us your buttocks. Scene that will make ready is Álex de la Iglesia!, not a few male viewers to the film.I will now go to SAC and will put three more points by, adapting the novel murders of the Argentine Guillermo Martínez, offer us a film with a plot of intrigue which, while not will go down in the annals of the genus (another thing is what will happen with the rear of Leonor Watling!), or the Mise en scène, prove, is &hellip; elite and entertaining. Without more. And they are already six points. It is not bad!</body>
</review>
