<review author="Jesus David" title="Mortadelo y Filem칩n: Misi칩n Salvar la Tierra" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A hodgepodge with capital letters in which are saved, perhaps, the principle and some gag of the protagonists and Todoquisque, played by Alex O'Dogherty. Boring, child and do script? that it verges on the absurd.</summary>
	<body>You can see the poster? What do you think? Shit is not it? Because the film for the style, but expected. A crappy capitalized which save perhaps the principle and some gag of the protagonists and Todoquisque, played by Alex O'Dogherty. Boring, child and do script? that it verges on the absurd. I am going to defend Pepe Viyuela and Eduard Soto because the poor do what they can to such nonsense. Nothing to do with its predecessor, is too noticeable change of director and vision "peculiar" about the humor that they follow the comics. Reminded me the time of Benny Hill, which ran the police and caco fast camera, in fact here use it on several occasions, is known that you made them grace to the writers.The argument, see. the plot is about a very bad bad who wants to leave the planet without water to sell its substituent of the same product: the botijola. The case is Mortadelo y Filem칩n will have to stop them and blah blah blah. I'd like to tell or you apetecer치 read it. The truth is I am imagining the writers, among which is the director, writing the script and mondando of laughter. I imagine them all three discussing on what to put in the movie:-Hey! I have an idea. We could do some scenes in fast camera so that people retuerza of laughter in the seats. And abuse she nauseam.-If Yes, good idea. Although I have another better. I call my nephew that handles this of the photochop and do us a dog than punching, juas juas juas-great! We can also get you the voice of Bart Simpson, the people will fall exhausted at our feet. And the dog will be called Bush, juas juas juas what evil I am!-about punching me gusta. We are going to do is to give all Campion throughout the film. And now, we only need to write the dialogues of the characters-Buff that lazy uncle, mira, improvisen, to pa' that paid. We Let's go to the bar.Because that, shameful. There is no where take it. Most jokes give embarrassment and the dog, truth, regrettable. We will, quite contrary to the movie that made Fesser, many criticized in his day, but that seems to me a vision very successful comics, is well written and well directed, and you laugh, that is what matters. But cannot say the same of the film by Bardem. In short, as I have already said, regrettable. I stay at home reading the comic, in truth, is the best thing you can do.</body>
</review>
