<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not to be wrong... not good. This is simply one bland thriller more, right, but those who fall into oblivion hopelessly as just its projection. A penalty.</summary>
	<body>After four years away from the big screen ("Crime Ferpecto" was their last release, as "The children's room" premiered on television as part of the "movies for No sleep"), Álex de la Iglesia returns with his more orthodox work to date and, therefore, more impersonal. Counting with renowned actors such as Elijah Wood, John Hurt and Leonor Watlting, "The crimes of Oxford" is a thriller based on the eponymous book by Guillermo Martínez. Mucho leads talking of "The crimes of Oxford", movie that finished awakening so much expectation before its premiere as views contrasted after him. On the one hand are those who defend it with the best work of the Church to date, while on the other are those who think just the opposite, it is one of the worst (if not the worst) film director.I, honestly, I dare not say that it is as below, for example, "Perdita Durango", although yes I can say is that I was more disappointed.And it isn't because the peculiar director has shelved its personality filming a thriller quite vulgar and current. The fact that sometimes a director to part their hallmark and roll something completely different from what we are accustomed does not have to be negative (as did David Lynch in, for example, "A history true").The problem of "The crimes of Oxford" is that it is not a good movie. It has many elements that certainly avoid that it becomes a failure total and absolute, as they could be a design of sober and elegant production, the performance of John Hurt, or some specific scenes that seem to Álex de la Iglesia tries to put something on their side (the long sequence that follows different characters without cutting planes, while distorted by CGI)(, it is the most remarkable), but many others who condemn it inevitably. Let's go by parts.For starters, the story than the movie planet, by very attractive enough in advance (discover the murderer through tracks and mathematical tricks), just proving basic, very simplistic, and with just a couple of mentions of the science of numbers. If were not enough, these winks are absurdly simple to solve, but despite this the characters seem to take eons to resolve them, no one would say that they are mathematical geniuses (forgive the bet of the mirrored numbers as an example).On the other hand, the script (with really sonrojantes situations) is unable to move at any time. Even at the time of the final resolution, everything is cold, distant. Nobody cares and know who is who, and even the same director seems to have more desire than anyone to finish.Nor is it saved from burning Elijah Wood, which continues with the aura of Hobbit beyond where treads, and fails to make its too credible character, always being Hurt below or the same Leonor Watling. Character of this, who quietly could have been eliminated of the Assembly, as its sole purpose is the heat staff (although also admit that had not been for her surely neither would paid for the film).Finally, stresses adversely mounting in general throughout the film. Everything happens too quickly, despite the relative tedium that follows continuously, with scenes happening in zacchia and atragantada manner. One floor of the bus because he sees his girl walking down the street, and to the tenth of a second already are fused in a fiery Kiss, despite that time before had appeared discussing. Read more: a character embarks on a plane, and with little time to move the finger, as appears the transport flying over the airport without there having been a temporary cut of medium. Almost gives the feeling that "the Assembly of the director" was originally more than two hours, and then in the production room they had been used and misused of the scissors.Thus, small flashes, "The crimes of Oxford" prevents that you can define bad, but unfortunately we can not say to be a good movie. This is simply one bland thriller more, right, but those who fall into oblivion hopelessly as just its projection. A penalty.</body>
</review>
