<review author="Jefe Dreyfus" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good movie, great director. If Mr Joe Wright continues with this evolution awaits a very promising career. Wish to get, will certainly be a very good sign.</summary>
	<body>Good morning, I am elputocriticón, today is Friday and plays a movie premiere that, moreover, is news for being in the list (that beautiful word) of the Oscar for best picture of the year. So today: Atonement: beyond passion (takes shit sticky subtitle, which makes you want to trallar only to see it and on top is a couplet, which we have released the manga in this country of ready) &hellip; started!They are not going to believe. The movie is a love story! and on top she is upper class and lower class &hellip; and works for her family! (my mother, my mother, never seen, by whole body goose bumps). Total that the two pipiolos one day discover that their bodies react in a jovial manner when they are together, but just when love begins to be in the air, the whims of fate (and a bitch girl) will play them a dirty trick and eventually separated.Holy God, that can I lead to the cinema to see a (not pornographic) film whose subtitle is "Beyond the passion"? Therefore without doubt the fact that part of the team already collaborate together in the previous film by the director (and opera prima): pride and prejudice, film that I began to see a Sunday morning, on the couch at home, without whores desire, but that I loved and managed to draw a smile on my face (a Sunday morning!!)(, remember!). So when I learned of the existence of this film not hesitate even a moment go to see her and visiting drag elprimerhombre with me.Atonement is a film that is very well, largely because its director Joe Wright makes more history that history itself (which is the adaptation of a Best seller superfamoso pela me, the plot is nothing out of this world), getting more of what you might expect, but that, nevertheless, not just getting the Viewer (I) to the same extent that if managed in his first film)(Yes, already is that this is what has been said throughout the world but is I think equal, they want to make him). And is that the main problem that I see is that after a brutal first part of film (with a great soundtrack tying the scenes to perfection and a treacherous flashbacks) the thing falls quite in the second part (is the war lords) where unfortunately, despite the hardness of what they are tellingnot just hook and the thing loses pace. And all this despite the fact that this second part the director marks a flat sequence of who-you-shit-pata-down-from-good that undoubtedly will delight young and old. Towards the end, the movie tries to recover the pulse of emotion, but the thing comes late and not very conseguida.¿Y to all this uncle Oscar who said? Because (surprise gentlemen) her has been nominated as best film but has not nominated the Director!!! But if it is the best fucking movie!!! Not I (God frees me) give any credibility to awards, but is that these things do not stop amaze me (and scare me at the same time). Overall, we have the nomination for best foreign film, but the Academy has not nominated the Director, actress (Keira Knightley, who seem to be only well in the movies of this man) or Act (James McAvoy). How do you eat this? You will know. The safe end that will end up winning the adapted screenplay (more than novel adaptation) and one as the picture (does not fail, if you hear any comments regarding a snowing out of the film saying: "that good photography", this is what in the end will take the Oscar).In short, Good movie, great director. If Mr Joe Wright continues with this evolution awaits a very promising career. Wish to get, will certainly be a very good sign.</body>
</review>
