<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="American Gangster" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not the masterpiece that is intended to be, but neither is it an interesting proposal which boasts a beautiful setting and a huge cast.</summary>
	<body>Denzel Wahington gets on the skin of Frank Lucas, one of the most powerful gangsters in the 1970s. On the other side of the coin, Russell Crowe is Richie Roberts, the police who try to stop him at all costs. Ridley Scott leaves the intimate tone of "A good year" and directs the mammoth "American Gangster", stylish production of old Court adapted by Steven Zaillian (Oscar winner for best screenplay adapted by "The Schindler list"), and produced by Brian Grazer. The race for the Oscar gives the starting signal with a film that certainly will have much to say.Because certainly merits to be nominated to several statuettes has. The first and most important is nothing less that it double, since both Washington and Crowe are in State of grace, and conducted some performances superb, making only elect one of the two a capital sin. In fact, almost seems the same Scott wants to recognize merit, because the first time that they face is face to face, in a clear reference to the encounter between Pacino and DeNiro in a bar in Heat, great movie of Michael Mann.Otro distinctive feature of "American Gangster" is his photography. From his sobriety, the film is eye-catching and elegant, while remember again to another of the films Mann (in this case another genius, "The dilemma" with Russell Crowe), get give it some personality to the tape.And luckily, because unfortunately, one of his main problems is precisely an appalling lack of personality which is not achieved find at any moment, doing that what should be a new bet with, Yes, tributes to great films, not differs from a simple medley of them. Therefore, despite being an intense drama about the moral duality of a character that leads to the climax the Machiavellian phrase of "the end justifies the means", "American Gangster" not comes nowhere near to that once offered "The godfather"; and the same applies to others regarding the film, "French Connection", "The price of power" or "Casino", for example. And perhaps the reason is that Scott is not Scorsese or Coppola Mann, and never will be (indeed, even begins to be surpassed by his brother Tony).Another problem that drag the film is its excessive emotional linearity. From the first (and powerful, by the way) until its final climax scene script and Assembly are so meticulously studied to not giving standing to any alteration or lack of control, either for evil or good. When it comes to the truth, this results in the complete absence of times of real tension, pain or emotion in general. And that, is a film of more than two hours and half, just missing it too. "Everything flows with excessive uniformity, and the only thing that reaches the Viewer to alter are painful junkies take explicit close-up scenes.""American Gangster" seems ultimately as the godfather of the year, and is always well have films in this style around by our billboards. It is not the masterpiece that is intended to be, but neither is it an interesting proposal which boasts a beautiful setting and a huge cast (with the exception of Cuba Gooding Jr are all impeccable, and are easily identified a couple of side seen in cutting news series). In addition, play with another major asset in their favor, and is that it demonstrates that even can be (too many) tricks of computer and film without special effects. And that is laudable.</body>
</review>
