<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Those who go to see?The Oxford murders? forgetting who is the director, just ready to be carried away by the game, you will enjoy a first class, with surprising twists and delicious characters Cluedo.</summary>
	<body>"The perfect crime is not one that remains unresolved, but that is solved with a false culprit".The great (in various senses) Alex de la Iglesia change log, thematic and country to serve us a product of pure entertainment, in the style of the Dan Brown novels, with a strange crime related to mathematics, a few suspects enough freaks and dialogue laden with conspiracy theories, pseudo-filosóficas and strokes visions of humor mark of the House.Martin (Elijah Word) is a brilliant student of mathematics that flies from America to London that Professor Seldom (John Hurt), a recognized eminence, oversee his doctorate. Although at first, their different views on the science and the life separated them, the murder of Martin, intimate friend of Seldom home, they will join them in the search for the guilty.The successive deaths and some notes left by the killer with obvious mathematical connotations, seem to relate to the old teacher in crimes, initiating an intellectual battle between the persecuted and their captors.The different visions of reality of the two protagonists, the plot become a dialectical game in which each tries to convince the other of his ideas. The romantic and idealistic vision of Martin, who believes that there are absolute ideas, immutable universal truths from which we can understand both nature as human behavior collides frontally against the cynicism of the Professor Seldom, convinced that at the end random is one of the bases of life, which you can never trust or get to analyze. Can the flapping of a butterfly cause a hurricane on the other side of the world?The movie kept me almost unblinking throughout his life, sometimes by rapid dialogues, with mirrors and linked contrarréplicas, others by trying to discover the tracks of the Church it is leaving, who committed the murder and few others, by the overwhelming beauty of Leonor Watling, who left for posterity a scene in apron that happens to my Gallery of fetishes of for life.Alex de la Iglesia puts a breaking point for its cinematography, regardless of almost all their characteristic ICT to serve a film more academic, to put it in some way. For me this does not imply nor much less a step backwards or a betrayal to his film, but a search for new ways, new challenges, new images.In addition, serves as "The Oxford murders" of the Church for some feats at a technical level, as the false flat sequence (usease, a flat long, seemingly uncut sequence) that reminded me of how it is filmed "The rope", Alfred Hitchcock, in which the director presents the characters related to a wonderful choreography.Perhaps the only time in which the film squeaking is in relations of Martin with the female characters, too TThe, perhaps in an attempt to not distract attention to the central plot and not extend the footage unnecessarily in a work that is pure entertainment, without more pretensions.Anyway, those who go to see "The Oxford murders" forgetting who is the director, just ready to be carried away by the game, you will enjoy a first class, with surprising twists and delicious characters Cluedo. Who aims to solve the mystery?</body>
</review>
