<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I stay with the feeling of having seen an exceptional, original film (though it is sometimes go by the branches of the topical) and with a pulse Ripper, being the second film by Joe Wright, a director of which, I am sure that will provide us with a real masterpiece very soon.</summary>
	<body>There are films that, despite its visual elegance retailer, fail to reach the depth that would touch them to become great. Atonement: Beyond passion (go added title so admirable to have been here) it has an absolutely stunning visual section, with a truly outstanding photography and an atmosphere of more accurate, but also has one of the best scripts seen in time (despite being based on the aclamadísima novel by Ian McEwan), incredibly deep and with some touches that end up to round out this captivating story. While we went through all this, we might suppose that this film seems a masterpiece. Pity some excesses by director Joe Wright, that despite this, manages to carry out scenes which we have to get the hat. Where more lacked passion this Atonement is probably in its middle part, when the protagonist is in the war, his girlfriend awaits you and while the girl of discord, and age of majority, is dedicated to caring for war wounded. This part, as well as topical, is where the filmmaker is left take a pulse so far never seen showing scenes that we know of memory (with the exception of the master flat military sequence and Briony visit the serious wounded) and somewhat boring. Despite this, Atonement: beyond the passion contains a first time bright, respond and majestic, which leaves the viewer with a tremendous desire to see what will happen afterwards. A complex, entrevesada and ambitious plot of love, loyalty and jealousy starring some stupendous Knightley and McAvoy, while continuing to ignore the vision of an imaginative girl, excellently played by Saoirse Ronan. And after those slow and almost inconsequential three quarters of an hour, Wright returns with his harrowing expiation of guilt, with several magical and memorable sequences as Briony visit to the apartment of his sister or the epilogue with an impressive Vanessa Redgrave. Unfortunately, this last part is shorter, with which we have a film somewhat irregular, although it never becomes bad, quite the contrary. My opinion may not be the same as others, and perhaps what to my seemed great to others will have seemed it incredibly tedious, and vice versa. Nevertheless, the film is full of emotion and complexity, it is adult at all times (no, not treat us as naive children) and contains one of the most sad and at the same time brilliant endings ever seen. All of it, cannot be forgotten, accompanied by a melancholy and wonderful soundtrack to Dario Marianelli. so therefore, this magnificent film deserves be acclaimed and seen by anyone who appreciate not only the technical aspect, also writing and the nuances in which must be set to end to understand the abysmal final sentences. I stay with the feeling of having seen an exceptional, original film (though it is sometimes go by the branches of the topical) and with a pulse Ripper, being the second film by Joe Wright, a director of which, I am sure that will provide us with a real masterpiece very soon.</body>
</review>
