<review author="Patri" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film by Alex de la Iglesia, despite its flaws, is entertaining until the end and is the best that has been in theaters lately, especially for those who like this type of movies and the homages to Hitchcock.</summary>
	<body>Alex de La Iglesia is one of the best filmmakers we have in Spain, since mutant action or the day of the beast bashed by critics, to the community or even 800 bullets, but that it was not so bad, has been the only Spanish director who has made movies full of black humour, unconventional in the cinema in our country. The crimes of Oxford tells us how an American student (Elijah Wood) arrives in Oxford to ask for help with the doctor to a Professor of Mathematics (John Hurt) who admires, a series of strange deaths and a nurse (Leonor Watling) it pues everything. The beginning of the film is rather disappointing, with a few dialogues really topical and boring, however, the thing is encouraged when we find a flat sequence in the purest style of the rope of Hitchcock, serving to lead us towards the first death, where begins the true history and will lead to begin the relationship between the teacher and the studentto embark on a full of puzzles and mathematical philosophy research. Everything is resolved at the end of a rather twisted and manner difficult to understand for who has not been very attentive throughout the film, the typical end makes you to be thinking for a time in the film to see if all the pieces fit and here it seems that they do, although slightly adjusted. Elijah Wood and John Hurt are perfect in their roles, to Leonor Watling saw something out of place, though it may that outside by dubbing, their presence serves to provide the female point and the love story that seems that his character need entire film aimed at the general public, in fact does not appear to provide nothing more, unless a conflict between the two main characters and either interprets enthusiastically, something that can not hide or with its charismatic beauty.The other woman in the cast, Julie Cox plays the character perfectly more hitchcockiano that has seen in recent years. But the film by Alex de la Iglesia, despite its flaws, is entertaining until the end and is the best that has been in theaters lately, especially for those who like this type of movies and the homages to Hitchcock.</body>
</review>
