<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="Dicen por ahi" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Second part of the graduate with sufficient merit to be viewed</summary>
	<body>Yesterday I went to see say (2005), better known as the new Jennifer Aniston movie A good girl (2002) and the come back of Kevin Costner (dance with Wolves, 1990). The problem is that still I am debating me internally each other I liked or not. Hmmm. In short the film is nonsense, but has its moments in which you kill of laughter, especially due to the brilliant performances of Shirley MacLaine (in their shoes, 2005), who is more than regia and an ideal role for her. Lately Shirley MacLaine is hitting regia Royal granddaughters grandmother.If they don't know what it is, in short, the film is the story of a woman, yes woman Jennifer, since you're not a girl but you do 30 juvenile roles (please, accept your age with dignity, recalls that the public you followed a decade of Friends and we know add), well said, a woman confused and undecided on his life and relationship, who suddenly is indecisive and confused when he discovers that her grandmother and her mother could be the true protagonists that first inspired the novel, and then the classic film, the graduate, 1967, and that his father could not be his father.Kevin Costner is the possible father and the man who shakes up the three generations of women and as they say some friends: the guy puts. Really opaque to its rival in the story, Mark Ruffalo (how if it were true, 2005), the correct lawyer noviecito without more emotion, or chemical with Jennifer. Frankly, he looks so little thing, which is well understood the indecision of the protagonist. Up flat seen actor, which already is becoming favorite galan of the romantic comedies made in Hollywood, others, not this.Rescues the performance of Mena Suvari (American beauty, 1999), who acts as the surface, carefree and jumping (literally) sister of the protagonist, who on the other hand, is unfortunately trapped by his own face of "Rachel waiting for Ross on Friends", limiting his acting register.I think this "second part" of the graduate has sufficient merit to be comfortably viewed on video or DVD, more isn't as good as so it is worth paying the entrance of the cinema. Finally, if her come si la ven go with encouragement of seeing something good light.</body>
</review>
