<review author="Natalia Eseverri" title="Alatriste" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I do not know if with another director's vision had come to enjoy more, but if I was lacking that spark of seeing something spectacular and at the same time have reflected to the Spain of that century.</summary>
	<body>My recommendation is one of the films most anticipated of the year which has also been able to count with the largest budget that has been granted to a Spanish film.The truth is that I really liked, much respected all the details of the book of Perez Reverte and I believe that the work of the director, Diaz Yanes, in gathering the most important arguments of the three books in the film has reflected great. The landscapes and the work of rebuilding the 17th century Spain has been an outstanding job to which I can not get any hits and also with any touch could also be reflected in some of the paintings of the time, a perspective that has seemed quite original.In history, tells us the life of Diego Alatriste, is not a film with beginning, intermediate, and final as the usual let's see. Narrates his adventures in various battles and at the same time looking at people of her around and also the lives of each one of them, but always focusing on Alatriste as main character. Not be if it is something appropriate to have focused so or on the contrary have sought a story the protagonist that easily could have continued, but guess that try to include important details of the three books, the only way to achieve this was so. To my at least gave me that impression and I see it right.But the essential, although repeat a lot but it is truth is Viggo Mortensen Alatriste, also without any shred of doubt. You see even in their manner of walking, have you got an extremely complicated character and he has it carried its terrain with ease. He and his magnificent interpretation is based that the movie will work.And now comes to me has been able to crash the movie and if it is true that it tells the Spain of the 17th century and as Diaz Yanes said, tells it you better than a school history book, also it's truth that tell in the way that has done it much loses the rhythm of the film and sometimes makes you weary and also tell a story of the Spain without having that reach the roots but also have to think a little in the viewer and offer something to make you enjoy the movie, because my feeling to leave has been to see a good film but without reaching excite me. I do not know if with another director's vision had come to enjoy more, but if I was lacking that spark of seeing something spectacular and at the same time have reflected to the Spain of that century.In any case, in addition to Mortensen, want to highlight many of the side of the film that although they had very few papers have been able to give their own personality and they were fantastic, especially Javier House as count Duke of Olivares and Juan Echanove as Quevedo. In films of this kind should highlight the artistic direction and costumes because they are that more is it curran and his work have made perfect in "Alatriste". Note the very exquisite taste that they have had in choosing both scenery and costumes of each of the characters and that is to be welcomed.And not is because gives me that we are going to hear much Alatriste in the upcoming Goya. I, without hesitation, gave it to Mortensen.</body>
</review>
