<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La quinta del porro" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Anti mili pamphlet with the word truño which fits perfectly. It has three funny expressions, a type that looks like Eugene and a girl in pelotas. And even so, I has repugnado. Fuck that bad.</summary>
	<body>Director: Francesc Bellmunt. duration: 107 minutes.Release date: 21 January 1989, although authorized in the 1980s, with what we have another errata, or it is that so great shit there was no güevos to release soon.Spectators: 1.237.461 human beings, since is this data, I have frozen pussy of the scare.In life there are films that a person may be called truño, being so wide. But when that Word mentions it a server who has swallowed cagarros and the size of a trolebus Cairns, it takes another dimension. So great is the truño, I'm going to inaugurate the truñoteca for those movies worse than bad. Of those that you are sure that the director is is starting laughing at home saying, "and people are viewing the kidding this I did for everyone laugh".The film is about a fifth (rather than beer) that have to be incorporated to the mili from Barcelona to Morocco. So a train is with all future soldiers, chosen motifs among the stereotypes more absurd that you can lend to the face. And then some arkhan, others makes it crap and you think incredulous "do so little worth my time so I am losing with such truño?".Poor Álvaro de Luna, of hardship that had to happen in life to accept this "film". The script is a total and absolute nonsense. But not a funny and absurd, if not a shit boat nonsense. The actors are the worst of the worst, '' embutidos '' in tontísimos stereotypes. The plot is non-existent, and the worst comes when approaching the end. It is they breaking us an anti-war pamphlet that to me, a declared military anti me stirred the guts up to almost convince me to enlist me. But if I was not able to move couch to turn off the TV, as to go to hit shots. Than more bad laziness.In short, pamphlet anti mili with the word truño which fits perfectly. It has three funny expressions, a type that looks like Eugene and a girl in pelotas. And even so, I has repugnado. Fuck that bad.Besitos.P.D: I have the doubt to see that more than one million people have seen the film. If someone from the time her went to see the film, I would ask your opinion. It is that I can't believe that someone you may like this.Pd2: Another question, why such monstrosity needed five writers? Me he surprised when I saw the credits, but has come me to mind now.</body>
</review>
