<review author="Jokin García " title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An interesting film of mathematical puzzles for a thriller of good invoice, that without being the best work of the Church, still shining at a very high level.</summary>
	<body>The new film by Alex de la Iglesia. It is not his best film, but in the case of a director that I have totally on an altar, and which each of their films seems a masterpiece, "The crimes of Oxford" manages to not detract from the average level. And if we add to this that he was waiting this movie since I had news that was going to do, the fact that has not disappointed me one iota is quite eloquent.The argument is on simple principle, a serial killer leaves clues in the form of logical sequence of what will be their next step, and the Duet Elijah Wood (I am unable to look and not see Frodo) John Hurt (which eats the screen) has to investigate to discover the terrible truth, in a scene full of colorful characters and mathematics and philosophy as a backdropfor a more or less surprising outcome and through it also crosses the torrid romance between Frodo and an explosive Leonor Watling (making the joke would say that it is not the only explosive character of the film) in "The Oxford murders" philosophy is the true protagonist, through the ideas of Ludwig Wittgenstein, and above all the message of "there is no universal truths"in an interesting thought about if the abstract ideas preexist or are mere tricks. The "2" concept exists in nature, or is simply that we call "2" everything that fits in our idea of duality?To some but I would say that some of the equations are very tricky, as skips some steps or are slightly pulled their hair, somewhat "Deus ex Machina" but at least allows the Viewer to play to discover the intermediate steps. But we will, which ultimately is a highly recommended film, and not it is the best of Alex de la Iglesia, and don't have that "Alex" style, continues to be a movie of the Grand Master.</body>
</review>
