<review author="Javier G. Pasamón" title="Hacia rutas salvajes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although they apasionen me this kind of stories and films, it does not remove Penn to go in search of an exorbitant bombast using your camera getting create an underlined and unnecessary entromisión with the filmed reality.</summary>
	<body>One, after viewing the last film of Sean Penn, inevitably comes to the memory a sympathetic and, in general, unknown film of James B. Clark, entitled by these lares "the boy and his mountain" (1969), based on the work of Jean Craighead George (1), which was of a boy who runs away from the wealthy life known to spend a summer (and any) to another station in the mountains living what the nature given, accompanied by the Thoreau master literature and getting through food algae care and hunting provided by the good do their Peregrine Falcon. "Wild routes" would be the older sister (and serious) "A boy in the mountains", because while in the B. Clark film, there was some pretentiousness (if everything a little Disney and sweetened), the tape of Penn, there is a certain excess, and not just of footage.We might well say that Penn makes the same mistake, although not at equal level, as his good friend Mexican Alejandro González Iñarritu "we love so much" on this website: the search for an exorbitant bombast using your camera getting create an underlined and unnecessary entromisión with the filmed reality.There is a clear willingness to interfere visually to the spot. And Penn, to tell us the story (and be noted as a filmmaker) interferes in the formal section with mechanisms of dubious taste and effectiveness as the abuse of air, rotational levels (around a topic in this kind of stories) and slow motion. However, the use of split screens is right for me, not so the letters on screen that they disfigure the set and assume a little subtle mechanism to describe it's a newspaper.As in "Babel" of our "esteemed" Iñarritu, Penn seeks impossible postcards, films the sky, look rebuscadísimos levels and ultimately seems to try to say: "Hey, look at how good I am!" or something like "I am indie and cool me be it", but unlike the multilingual tape of the Mexican, in this if there is a sense to show landscapes and its spectacularthat is to say, that something less than it because if you have the man, because nature is one character.Of course, Penn has not had the subtlety that is Malick on how show nature.Another negative aspect - very in fashion today - and that he shared, unfortunately with the works of Iñarritu, is unjustified acronológico Assembly, because the novel is completely linear.As an adaptation of the novel by Krakahuer, say that it is quite acceptable and decent, in addition to faithful. Although, for a server, the most notable of the tape are the remarkable photography of Eric Gautier, usual first operator of Olivier Assayas, the exceptional soundtrack of Eddie Vedder of the Pearl Jam and notable interpretations of Emile Hirsch, which carries the entire weight of the film, and Hal Holbrook, with a brief but memorable contribution.Although "towards"wild routes contain elections in film that I have not just convinced, personally, and for reasons beyond reason, I love the road-movies of lonely characters with a self-improvement and challenges, and it not going to be less. And is that the film of Penn has an end of a beauty and so heartbreaking message as true. Life is unpredictable, all survival requires preparation and prior in-depth study (which the protagonist clearly lacked her), but above all, and most importantly, is there need to accept yourself as who is. His ideals were exciting and exciting, but utopian. At least he had courage to prove it.But although they apasionen me this kind of stories and films, does not detract from what was said already above, Penn goes to the search for an exorbitant bombast using your camera getting create an underlined and unnecessary entromisión with the filmed reality, and that removes many integers to the film.(1) Author who not only wrote the novel that would give rise to "the boy and his mountain" entitled "My side of the mountain", but also a kind of second part called "On the Far Side of the Mountain", not adapted for film.</body>
</review>
