<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cloverfield is a spectacular divertimento, which unlike other get uncomfortable with hyperrealism which entails being recorded by way of home video. The penalty is that we have already seen "[Rec]" and "The Host"...</summary>
	<body>On the occasion of the Rob (Michael Stahl-David) trip to Japan, his friends decide to prepare a party surprise of farewell, which come to among others his recent ex-girlfriend Beth (Odette Yustman), his brother Jason (Mike Vogel), or his best friend Hud (T.J. Miller), this last charge in addition to record everything in his video camera.Suddenly, a shock paralyzes the feast. The average Manhattan lights turn off, a few seconds a terrible explosion in the city stands.Thus begins a struggle for survival, something unknown, hungry to escape. monstrous.Mix between "Godzilla" and "The project of the Witch of Blair" (as well his producer, JJ Abrams), "Cloverfield" is a more than interesting proposal that despite return to the (outdated) attack on major cities in charge of monsters of all kinds, for the umpteenth time brings breath of fresh air to the genre, creating a turning point that for a server would have been much more impressive of not having seen "[Rec]" and "The diary of the dead".Since then, it is not at the plot level where the revolution. Matt Reeves film through all clichés of movie monsters, the argument, the truth, therefore rather predictable and simpleton.But being shot in camera in hand, as with the fantastic film of Balagueró and Plaza, provokes in the viewer a spiral of sensations more intense, as the monster in this occasion is delegated to a background, and is much more important what happens to the Group of protagonists. Indeed, images we have of the creature are quick and confusing, tenths of a second in which the camera, while running looking for refuge, focused upwards and lets us see a shade, or a profile, but never (until the end) we have a detailed image of your body. In the same way that "Signals", for example, the feeling of insecurity causes not knowing very well what it is attacking. This is what we hear and, therefore, imagine, what frightens us.But without a doubt, the most important achievement of "Cloverfield" is realism which emerges despite the impossibility of the situation as of the plot. Unlike "The Host", or the aforementioned "Godzilla", on this occasion no heroes or epic moments. Engaged with the protagonists (and everyone in general) is simply to help each other escape unharmed. In fact, even one could say that it is quite anticlimática, avoiding at all times impossible scenes and americanadas gestas.They certainly help its spectacular special effects. For example, the fall of buildings after the initial attack are a realism that cannot fail to recall the collapse of the twin towers.And is that in the end, "Cloverfield" is not if not a metaphor, a personification of the terror with which us (and the world) live after that fateful 11-S.Es precisely the monster itself which has just disappointing. Is not that it is wrong, it is not much less, if not that has been both him and is his mysticism throughout the film (as they pass the minutes are seeing it with a little more detail, down to the last minute, that we can finally see a map with all luxury of details) and what has preceded himjust knowing a little, resulting in a simple hodgepodge between "The Host", "Godzilla", and "Starship Troopers".Even so, and despite a last scene something free and shameful, "Cloverfield" is a spectacular divertimento, which unlike other catastrophic blockbusters get uncomfortable with hyperrealism which entails being recorded by way of home video. The penalty is that we have already seen "[Rec]" and "The Host", because if we would not be talking about no doubt a real before and after in the genre.</body>
</review>
