<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Under its apparent novelty and its tremendous viral promotion, 'Monstruoso' continues to be entertaining but typical story of 'boy saves girl from the monster' filmed with a camera in hand hyperrealism something sickening.</summary>
	<body>This weekend comes to our screens the film whose viral promotion has been of the most spectacular in recent times. Directed by Matt Reeves and stars Michael Stahl-David, Mike Vogel, Jessica Lucas, Lizzy Caplan, OdetteYustman, T. j. Miller, Margot Farley and Theo Rossi, undoubtedly the most recognized name of this Monstruoso, aka Cloverfield, is its producer, j. j. Abrams, creator of cult series like lost or Alias.Monstruoso has a monster attack in New York City, in the heart of Manhattan, narrated from the point of view of a group of young people who the filamrán everything with his camera of video with the intention of preserving his testimony.As I said something above, Monstruoso can boast of being the film with one of the most aggressive internet campaigns ever: dozens of rumors, title changes, its enigmatic creature, videos of all kinds. And, as it was to be expected, similar campaign has emerged effect, because in a few weeks Monstruoso has rentabilizado loosely production cost only at the American box office.In a mix - argued by own producer - Godzilla and Blair Witch Project or if moved it just to the previous year, [·REC] and The host, monstrous is an entertaining tape mix of action and terror that plays so brazen with everlasting echo of the attacks of 9 / 11. You must only take a piece at random from the film produced by j. j. Abrams and any video posted on YouTube of some testimonial videoficionado during the attack on the twin towers to give account of this.Thus, Monstruoso uses the panic and confusion of the hasty camera and a few credible Visual effects and sound to tell, in a seemingly innovative way, the same old story. And is to make a monster film to plague New York City poses discover gunpowder, precisely, and as I have said on more than one occasion, the resource of the mockumentary begins to be too recurrent.As well, however, one must recognize that Monstruoso is a film ideal for eating popcorn, if one is not too prone to dizziness, and the action is pretty well worn, despite remind us to a host of films, from the aforementioned Godzilla, The hostname or [·REC], to Alien or Pitch Black at times.As usual in this type of production, the first third of the film is completely irrelevant, with a preview of his characters totally irrelevant to what the viewer has come to witness, followed by a supposed history of antiheros - or heroes of a foot, according to taste-, which in fact conceals a story of boy saves girl from the monster. As always, the monster of the day is not what one expected us much reminding of The host and, as is also often common, left over the last ten minutes of footage that does not reach the hour and a half. On the other hand, one of the great successes of the film is the fact of not showing the monster clearly, if not in a progressive way, following the pattern of Alien and Ridley Scott dictum of causes us more terror what we believe that we have seen, to know that we have seen.But, again, Monstruoso is a film entertaining, certainly tense moments and that will no doubt delight of good palomitero cinema fans.</body>
</review>
