<review author="Victor Bilbao" title="Cold Mountain" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Cold Mountain" is a pleasure for the eyes as well as ears because there are precious of great lyricism dialogs, although they alternate with the brutality and cruelty of the war, any war.</summary>
	<body>It could Mountain is a small but beautiful place of the South of the Unidos.Todo States the world is very attached. One day arrives a new pastor with his daughter, a beautiful woman. He falls and is met by a young handsome and hardworking.The hardly speaks so not given well.When they are about to reach more, he must go to war that has occurred between the North and the South. Before leaving, she gives her a book and a photograph of him. It will always take it with him. "Wounded in the war it desertará to return with her, who is undergoing economic hardship because of the damn war."You've told me that barely days after he remembered his name. "Oh, Inman, more than three years have passed and I still remember his name."Beautiful and unforgiving film anti-war framed at the time of the American civil war, although it might well have happened in any other place and time.Renée Zellweger fell the Charles Frazier book because there was many twigs to make a great film and endorses a role Bonbon. Moreover. And Anthony Minghella has done so.Directed with master hand, with a spectacular mise en scene thanks to a beautiful compositions with great depth of field, a superb photograph that highlights the rugged places in Romania where shots were filmed foreign (most), and some brilliant performances, especially intense of Jude Law and Renee Zellweger, without forgetting to Nicole Kidman.El film walk with steady at all times handstopping when you have to stop and being strong and agile when the situation requires. Thus, one might think that it has an irregular rhythm, but it is not true.It has the pace at which the various events that will occur when the protagonist ask and even require. "And if it is long, that is more defect that can be found, because it tells the long and difficult journey of a hamano until you reach home, and that requires time to tell.""Cold Mountain" is an excellent western with elements of various genres within it, not little recalls to the quest of the hero Ulysses on his trip to his beloved Itaca, where his beloved Penelope awaits. "In addition to all of this is appreciated the large amount of excellent actors involved in the film, even in very small roles.""Cold Mountain" is a pleasure for the eyes as well as ears because there are precious of great lyricism dialogs, although they alternate with the brutality and cruelty of the war, any war (in this sense is particularly significant the episode of Nathalie Portman).An excellent film that never ceases to be an impressive story that leaves honda footprint.</body>
</review>
