<review author="Darthz" title="La joven del agua" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that runs along the inner world of each spectator. a more open way of seeing life and the roles that each develop or could develop; a message written in the subconscious of a beautiful music and a great beginning.</summary>
	<body>Originality is always short, and even more ingenuity. And this happens with Shymalan, that we are going to see a film, and even though we know his tricks, know as his characters and his inner world always drive to questions that it has to be done covering the show, we are surprised. And at least to me, held me captive. They are simple stories told of how at first glance may seem complicated, and not is more than a Union of small details and references on our world and the other, the largest, the imaginative, which recreates in his films. With "The girl in the water" it brings us to Earth a story, a legend, a nymph and his rocky road to return to their world. A film that runs along the inner world of each spectator who really gets into the role in the film, which accepts that more is a philosophical way to film a horror film, as the majority of the people to know the main thing believes. It is the eternal return to the question of who you are, or what role do you think that you have in this world; the enthusiasm of knowing the world boring and stereotypic can change through the imagination and the desire, the desire to make good movies, show the world what you want without being drawn by the unbridled and stupid mass. We will bring this time, the director, a more open way of seeing life and the roles that each develop or could develop; a message written in the subconscious of a beautiful music and a great start, and likewise with the end of the film, a message that does not come rather than say how to evade us ridiculous flatness of the world, with this final message, the Seagull flying above all, slowly losing by the mantle that covers us day and night: while there is life, there is hope.</body>
</review>
