<review author="Ethan" title="Callejón sin salida" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not the most successful or the best of film noir, but yes it is containing all the elements that characterized this type of films in the 1940s.</summary>
	<body>It is not better or the best of film noir, as her possibly exceed the Maltese Falcon (The Maltese Falcon of John Huston, 1941) or El Sueño Eterno (The Big Sleep of Howard Hawks, 1946), by say two of the most famous, but yes it is containing all the elements that characterized this type of films in the 1940s. 1. A confusing and ambiguous plot. Indeed, gives equal the times you see her, at the end you do not clarify in who killed whom and why. I have always believed that the blame that the mind is us nublara had Lizabeth Scott. You can not stop looking at her when he get on screen, and it is at that moment when tend to clarify some dark point of the trama.2.-quick and witty dialogues. Very close to Screwball Comedy and evolve into a perfect complicity between Bogart and Scott against third parties - see the "Jerome" word used interchangeably the couple protagonist when lurks a danger, or the resemblance between women and bottles. All the style of the novels of Dashiell Hammett and Raymond Chandler, in turn the most prestigious black film writers. A curiosity: the name of the character that makes Liz Scott is Chandler. It is a coincidence or is a tribute of the writers Garret and Fisher? 3. A Fatal woman. The blonde Liz Scott. At first us strikes as a replacement of the great Lauren Bacall, but then we see that behind won't you. It is the archetype of the femme fatale, platinum blonde, voice grave - highly recommended to see her Original version - appears singing a song very sexy in a slum where plays clandestinamente.4-darkness prevails. It could not be otherwise, film noir is the eldest son of Expressionism and it is characterized by the incorporation of light and shadows - more shadow than light - to reflect the State of mind of the characters. Here is appreciated even better. When the characters returning from the war to be decorated all the action it is day; the illuminated faces reflect joy for the return home. But the thing is complicated and someone is killed everything becomes dark and the action takes place at night principalmente.5-A spectacular start. A man who barely can keep standing flees from thugs and the police. Sufficient tension so the Viewer does not move seat until the end. 6 Flashback and feature voice-over. As in Doom and so many other negruras, the narrative structure rests on a long flashback narrated in first person by the protagonist. The voiceover, serious, deep and sarcastic most of the time, accompanies us along the 100 minutes that lasts the film. Again in the see it in V.O.7.-the "good" is not so in reality. Humphrey Bogart is a captain of the Army (Rip) that does not hesitate to contact friends gangsters of St. Louis, where he worked as a taxi driver, to help him steal some letter. This typical ambiguity is what makes the genre so attractive.Anyway, I do not think that a film that meets so many black ingredients like this film of Cromwell there is. Including one of the most characteristic: the presence of Humphrey Bogart. Do not fail to see them and. Jérôme!</body>
</review>
