<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El espía" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In a way, and although it may seem a simplistic printing, the Spy is the typical story of revenge of the nerd to the most handsome and popular class.</summary>
	<body>The glamorous encouraged spy image machaconamente by the film already seems obsolete, excessively exploited. The latest productions with spy agencies workers as protagonists come to corroborate this trend with examples such as Syriana, the good Shepherd and even, though not renouncing the exaggerations of the saga, the last Bond portrayed by David Craig, much more earthly and vulnerable than its predecessors. This is also the case for the spy (Breach), second work of director Billy Ray, who debuted with the price of truth (Shattered Glass), notable film funded by Tom Cruise.Y find it curious that, for both works, Ray had been based on two popular scandals: in the case of the price of truth, a journalist with an excess of inventiveness for his stories, and the spy, as it puts forward his elocuentísimo Spanish title in the history of a secret agent, considered the greatest traitor/topo discovered in the bowels of the FBI. Judging by the theme of both works, Ray you must interested much the characters cheats and double life.The approach of verismo of this sober tale is noticeable from their initial credit titles, with the television images of John Ashcroft, Attorney general of the first Bush administration, announcing the arrest of Robert Hanssen, an agent of the FBI who sold secrets and American spies to the Soviet Union for more than 20 years. His case, perhaps the most significant public known to date, was considered one of the greatest disasters within the U.S. intelligence.But the tape does not deal with the way in which this man could filter secrets to a rival Government for two decades, the possible reasons and reasons of Hanssen. So the Spy is, above all, deepen in the strange and contradictory personality of an agent specializing in management systems information whose grey task, a far cry from the glory predestined for the field agents, it was never subjected to severe scrutiny.Excellent work of Chris Cooper, a regular from the third line of credits, giving it complexity and depth to the contradictory character of HanssenPara guide us on this trip to the mind of Hanssen, another character far removed from him, the young Eric O'Neill, effectively portrayed by Ryan Phillippe, agent will be who we want in the complex world of this character with great richness of nuances for the excellent Chris Cooper, actor usually relegated to the third line of the end credits. O'Neill will be assigned the task of 'hunting' Hanssen in one of their betrayal to avoid retiring from the FBI without even having stepped on a court by his countless list of offences. So, during much of the film, both are measured in the typical pulse between the gifted student and the old Fox who is knows all. The always splendid Laura Linney in the role of head of O'Neill also appears in the cast.Ultimately, the simple proposal for the Spy is the explain how an agent of acrisolado patriotism and apparent honesty was able to 'sell' his country to a rival power. Why could strange intersection of cables in your mind make decisions as prejudicial to the security of their country. Many of the arguments put forward in the film hint at continuous contempt shown by the superiors of Hanssen towards his work, considered to be of Office mouse, but as he showed with his betrayal, was much more crucial and required much more dedication and effort to safeguard sensitive national security information. In a way, and although it may seem a simplistic printing, the Spy is the typical story of revenge of the nerd to the most handsome and popular class.</body>
</review>
