<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Familia" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Opera prima of Leon de Aranoa that shows a bearded man and his family. Extremely original, at times funny, at times emotional, at times it lasts and sad, is obliged vision for anyone who likes a SIP of good cinema.</summary>
	<body>Director: Fernando Leon of AranoaDuración: 97 minutes.Release date: January 23, 1997.Espectadores: 151.333 of human beings.If you have not seen this movie, I recommend that you stop reading this review right now. It is not think reveal nothing, is that better see her virginal, how maiden of the harem of Ataulfo manso, that warped how Pamela Anderson in pneumatic dreams of millions of anonymous onanistas. Warned you aloan. The first time I saw this movie, I caused much impression. To begin with, for the first 10 minutes that you caught so of surprise that you do not know or think. And then this is a dramón, camouflaged in a curious way of comedy but a tragedy that leaves you rather squashed. That if, between mean you laugh.The film is about the celebration of the birthday of a father. And here I can read without muss nothing.The directorial debut of Fernando León de Aranoa (is not the cousin of Ferdinand to make Opera, as I pointed the other day) turns out to be a very funny movie, and above all very original. That I don't forget, many years ago, one of these bipedal vipers of the programs of the heart attacking this director that had gone with the same shirt as in the previous gala of the Academy Awards. There is the cultural level of a country, what we change clothes (if not tell him now, then I forget). Total, than the actors they do very well its role, history requiebros you put again in the movie if you sales at some point, and the end has apotheosis moments. To see a Sunday afternoon calmly.In short, directorial debut of Leon de Aranoa that shows a bearded man and his family. Extremely original, at times funny, at times emotional, at times it lasts and sad, is obliged vision for anyone who likes a SIP of good cinema. It is not the best, but it stands very much among the rest.kisses.</body>
</review>
