<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="American Gangster" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will delight all amateur movies of gangsters, Russell Crowe, Densel Washington, the biopics and good film, because if something can be said of this product is that it is a great movie.</summary>
	<body>It's nice to start the year with a proposal like this. Mechanical Scott back on the path of the great films, and "American Gangster" is a good proof of that. Surrounded by great actors (Russell Crowe and Denzel Washington) immerses us in a true story, the life of Frank Lucas, puzzled the Viewer, to show us the corners and methods of the underworld of New York and New Jersey. Everything in this movie is sensational, starting with the address and ending in any technical department. It is incredible that the Oscars have forgotten it in many of the major categories. Denzel Washington (Frank Lucas) returned to build a character of those that leave footprint, and presents us with the way and the brain need to have to become the most important person in the drug trafficking and the mafia, beating the Italians and showing us how was murky the army and police enforcement. Russell Crowe is the polar opposite in terms of roles, it is the honest police which is responsible for the operation to dismantle the Organization of Fran Luke and company. The director of "Blade Runner" returns to give us a lesson in cinema with this proposal, that well could be equated to the great titles of the genre as "The godfather", "One of ours", "Once upon a time in America" or "Casino". Despite its duration fails to make heavy, with a pace and a superb, charged performances of realism that help shape all the aura of veracity that distills the new proposal from Scott. In short, "American Gangster" will delight all amateur movies of gangsters, Russell Crowe, Densel Washington, the biopics and good film, because if something can be said of this product is that it is a great movie.</body>
</review>
