<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Hacia rutas salvajes" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Towards wild routes is a film with many philosophical and moral aspirations that sinks by pedantry and inconsistencies of the discourse of Penn Sen.</summary>
	<body>After nominations have been made public to the awards Oscar, as well as making pools about what and who are the Favorites, must also think of the defeated. Perhaps the clearer is this wild routes towards, Sean Penn, who many gave as a clear candidate for the most important Oscar Awards.Sean Penn, it must be said that it is one of the finest actors of the current scene, but that his forays into the address have not been very fortunate. Towards wild routes is another movie to add to that list of busts, and Penn used the adventure of Christopher McCandless to perform an ode to freedom of the human being, anarchy, and cruel and heartless that can reach the society. And do it without losing any time a true filosófico-religioso halo, also of trying to justify acts of the character, so is more pedantic and pretentious. Penn focuses more on relationships that McCandless is setting in their adventure and there are times where the leaves aside the own adventure in itself, and rarely is transmitted to the viewer that struggle of mankind against the wild nature. If the story itself is not very much, the pace and the way in which it is told (who are you think go alternating fragments of the final scene with the rest of the story?) make even less attractive. Penn also happens with the excessive footage, and is two and a half hours duration rather than excessive for a story that could have resolved in little more than ninety minutes. All the actors are correct, although the nomination to the Oscar of Hal Holbrook resembles more a recognition throughout his career than to his portrayal in the film.Towards wild routes is a film with many philosophical and moral aspirations that sinks by pedantry and inconsistencies of the discourse of Penn Sen. Little you can save from a similar film, the most notable being the fantastic Director of photography Eric Gautier.</body>
</review>
