<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="En el valle de Elah" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting proposal of Paul Haggis that probably lasts little in theaters. If there is possibility is highly advisable to visit the room to delight with such superb performances.</summary>
	<body>Tommy Lee Jones is going to win the nickname of iron man as follows choosing roles that choose lately. First start with in the Valley of Elah to continue with the tape of the Coen brothers. In both most of the time doesn't change the rictus. But in both cases it is brilliant. (Other that has crept into the two films is Josh Brolin, that this preserved a discrete second level but that has had a year round completed with American Gangster) and has become a fundamental part of the gear of all tape quality self-respecting.In the Valley of Elah a father looking for clues about the disappearance of his son after his return from Iraq. A fairly sympathetic father is because he is the second son who loses and Moreover the entire family has a significant military tradition so it will be constant and incisive in all stages of their research. Help a young police officer that after initial reluctance just seeing that truly the death of Michael looks more than suspect. Formal and informal research along with the videos of the mobile of the deceased soldier will be able to do little by little fit the pieces of a rather soulless puzzle of the cruelty of the human race.Despite his clear independent tone (exclusively in terms of investment) the solvency of script and actors get an almost perfect finish in this military thriller that leaves little rest to the Viewer. Alternate intimate moments of confession with the harshness of reality between war and everyday life which becomes difficult to fit. Interesting proposal of Paul Haggis that probably lasts little in theaters. If there is possibility is highly advisable to visit the room to delight with such superb performances. He dare not do advocacy of good and bad in a raked so as the war theme, or the goodness of man.</body>
</review>
