<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Skinwalkers" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A mediocre film, in which, no technical aspect superimposed on a very limited ability to suggest, a flat performance, lousy actors and child treatment of popular legends.</summary>
	<body>James Isaac takes the reins of a new project related to the topic of the werewolves, the argument that many films has given, and so unsatisfactory in most cases, removing specific inputs from the classic film ("The Wolf Man" (1941) or "The curse of the werewolf" (1961)), or worthy revisitaciones during the 1980s as "Howls" (1981), or "An American Werewolf in London" (1981). In this case the picture was not very promising given the charge of trying to advance modestly or not, so suggestive idea of the werewolf, is a director whose previous proposal was the horrendous "Jason X", and that previously in this film, only had shot one of the terrible aftermath of the estimable "House, an amazing House". Therefore, that is not too surprising the ill-fated final product that has emerged from name "Skinwalkers".The plot of the film, obviously absurd by the way, shows us to a new breed of human marked by a curse, beings that nightly transform into Werewolves thirsty for human blood, devoid of all morality by a group of Renegades, and controlling whether by another faction of such enigmatic race. The latter precisely, are responsible for protecting a child that will soon meet the indicated age of thirteen years, day in which, according to reads an ancient prophecy of the native American Indians, a change that will give a new meaning to their species. This constant struggle between protectors of a better future for all of them, and the Renegades who refuse to stop being what they are, is the basis of the story.Isaac, in his work as a director, not craves the gift of originality at all, and this is why, although it may seem contradictory, which boasts the only thing salvageable from the film, the inconsequential assumed by the director creates a referential visual style, without any notion of personality, but made way correct, functional and without claiming to never engage in more complex tasks. Say that this is more a film positivio, says quite the level of mediocrity that distills the film for all and each of its pores.Perhaps the acting work would have been a little more decent if they had had the opportunity to work with a hyphen rather more elaborate, as we face the clear example of script written in so radically referential way, in the bad sense of the word, which seems to have been written with the autopilot on, or failing that, during a night watching movies of genre, and shooting here and there. In addition, with the aggravating circumstance that was written at three hands, being so insane proposal which furthermore were radically distant in their approaches to writing and previous proposals, having worked some in films of police gender or thrillers and some other comedies of most vapid. Another nonsense which logically not has gone well.The acting level, helps too that the interest of the viewer rise much, showing the cast, and when I say everything is all, tremendously superfluous, apathetic and nuances that might give a minimum of interest to the future of its protagonists. Interestingly, is a tanning cast already the most fantastic Court productions, although that if any especially remarkable. Elias Koteas is perhaps the most gifted actor for the performance of the Repertoire of beautiful faces that adorn the history, although it is not able to overcome a poorly drawn character horribly described in his ambiguous personality and level as the music of the news. The carnal Rhona Mitra, little to say, taking into account that never showed the lowest level of acting ability (and hopefully to improve although it is a little bit on the expected "Doomsday" Neil Marshall), but that if, its spectacular beauty creates an inevitable symbiosis between instincts more primary of any man and his physique. The rest of the actors, so little to say, some familiar faces of American television (the also beautiful Sarah Carter and Jason Behr roswelliano), and an actress, whose choice of roles for the film has struck me forcefully, it's the Norwegian Natassia Malthe (another is actress? powerful physical presence), which in addition to this "jewel" before us appeared in the television behalf "Bloodsuckers" crappy, in "Dead or Alive" (the adaptation of the game, not the film of Miike adrenalítica) and eye, two sequels to tremble, "Bloodrayne II" and "Alone in the dark II". It must have courage to intervene in two sequels to films of Uwe Boll, which should be the ultimate in film shabbiness, as to change agent ipso facto.This referential aspect to which both referred in previous lines, left note clearly not only in the subject of the film, but even in levels or scenes side previous productions, especially in the 1980s for the fantasy film prolíficios. Influences of films such as "The night travellers" and substitutes (latter damage made to the fantasy film), visual aspect in the transformations debtor of films such as "Sleepwalkers" or "Wolf Howl" (which referred to the principle), or a tone supposedly camp in the bad sense of the word, are too heavy Remora to overcome his own autodelimitación and save this tremendously failed production.In addition, even the mythology of the native American Indians, is treated in a very superficial way. For more effective treatment of the subject, recommend the vision of a production television of the year 2002, of the same name ("Skinwalkers"), and directed by Chris Eyre, a direct descendant of the tribe of the Cheyenne, and who also has a very interesting experience dealing with issues related to its culture throughout its limited but productive filmography.Few good aspects has the film, perhaps missed requiring the story and mythology that appears only on very rare occasions, and some scene of effective action, as this confrontation in the town, with echoes of the more thuggish western and, again, general reference in history.Ultimately, a mediocre film completely, in which, no technical aspect superimposed on a very limited ability to suggest, a flat performance, lousy actors and child treatment of popular legends.</body>
</review>
