<review author="Jose Contreras" title="4 meses, 3 semanas y 2 días" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The history of abortion fires at the heart of the regime, and the atmosphere does not leave puppet head.</summary>
	<body>In the 1990s the rate of crime in the United States declined markedly. Many mayors wanted to attribute success to their police measures. But an economist, David Levitt, proposed an expliacion less jactanciosa and more controversial. Levitt said that the crime rate dropped 20 years after the decriminalization of abortion. There are fewer unwanted children, society had less prone citizens into marginality, and the curve is noticed when these individuals were adults, i.e., twenty years later. The assertion makes in his book "Freakonomics" that I recommend to everyone.Consider if a similar case can look for in Europe. Ceausescu forbade abortion (and contraceptives) from 1966 until 1989 when he lost the playoff. And the country has a significant crime rate. If Levitt is right, the curve noted Americans should note in Romania from the theoretical 2009.Menos Levitt, Mungiu extends for a college girl of 22 years needing an abortion in the last years of the Communist Romania. The film takes to boot. Mungiu wants us to know how many penalidades supposed in their country to get a brand of tobacco or a hotel room, before displaying the sacrifice was an abortion.The costumbrist fresco works like clockwork, joining the main story accusations. The history of abortion fires at the heart of the regime, and the atmosphere does not leave puppet head. If I wanted to give the coup de grace, Mungiu should have delved into what it leads to these two desperate housewives to put in the hands of a doctor without scruples. That tragedy was waiting to the pregnant woman with a child in a society like that.The friend of the pregnant woman, Otilia, supports the weight of the drama throughout the session. It handles the details, it gives the face, he sacrificed as needed. One wonders that it takes her to do something like this, one deconfía even of so much goodness until that birthday takes her to the House of the parents of her boyfriend. Then glimpse what inside. You want to know if someone will do the same for her.The flat sequence have become an occasion to dazzle the Viewer. The last flat sequence overwhelming that I saw, the "Atonement", shows an army of men who seek, sing and cry on a French beach. Mungiu used, at first to show the nest of a Communist student residence, and at the end to join the ups and downs of the protagonist in a suffocating approach. These two flat epics, the discussion with the doctor, and the stationary camera at the meeting in the parents House are the stylistic flourish to an undeniable work. A topic so excruciating he deserved a narrative talent as unusual as which has shown Mungiu.</body>
</review>
