<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Savage Grace" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Savage Grace is nothing more than a sensational melodrama of tiny quality that exploits the curiosity of the public, Avid of the great families of high society scandals.</summary>
	<body>There are families whose lives seem drawn from the imagination of some writer melodramas or clamoring, but as reads the well-known phrase, reality always surpasses fiction. And as often happens, there is always some avid producer exploit the morbid curiosity of the human being, and decides to undertake a project to tell the story.And here we have Savage Grace, which tells some of the facts that happened to a family of American high society between the 1950s and 1970s. United States seems to be a legendary family saga, almost of legend, and the circumstances the truth is that they are not for less. But in that film, stays in a tabloid, twisted and gruesome, story that only seeks to awaken the curiosity in the audience. All the elements are forced to give even more sense of cheap soap opera, with some scenes that could have been devised by the pseudo programs writers as here is tomato. Tom Kalinse is passed both thread the film becomes pathetically funny for those viewers who still have the courage and the fortitude to take everything to banter. The sequence of the airport is simply the most stuffed who have been in a supposedly serious film in some time, and just look at the expression of Elena Anaya, who is thinking about who would send her to embark on such nonsense. Something like this also should think Unax Ugalde, Belén Rueda and Simón Andreu, although their roles are merely witnesses. Julianne Moore has the excuse that the character was a chocolate, and that in the right circumstances, it could have been Oscarizable.Savage Grace is nothing more than a sensational melodrama of tiny quality that exploits the curiosity of the public, Avid of the great families of high society scandals. It is a film that does not offer any incentive for the unpleasant task of viewing your ninety minutes made eternal.</body>
</review>
