<review author="José A. Peig" title="Rambo (Acorralado II)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good film that preserves the values and the uniqueness of the character, strong in technical resources, but somewhat irregular and rough.</summary>
	<body>Pure action and also war cinema unceremoniously film. Let's start with a proposal and a reflection; We are subject to the discretion of the blog, here are not worth the personal tastes, but objectively assess (heh, laugh you, who writes this will take their idealism to death), if analyzed film has — or non - artistic and intellectual values, moreover, should be put them in their corresponding value. Action movies don't like very much around here, and we maintain that - in general - is the film genre in the US is more difficult encontrarle.valores, transcendence. There are film miracles as Die Hard, but the rest seems (seem, illusion, chimera) a thing of artillery, noises and stereotypical characters. Okay, still not we have explored to fund this genre. And this blog is intended to be a great adventure of knowledge. Adelante.First Blood was a drama of hostilities physical and psychological violence that eclosionaba in a crushing of American society, and strongly critical view against the military institution. Bad aren't the homelands (all have one, like Rambo, Bohemian Wanderer very reluctantly) but that there is no place for the wisdom and sacrifice of a human being in such patriotic. This second part of the saga returns to put Rambo in a world that may never be part. Happy dialogue that closes the story: love a country, Yes. Die for him, Yes (the good soldier), but always and when part of a country (read part of a society, this goes to the us who have problems with the meaning and the value implicit in certain words used in according to what contexts), then say so, always and when part of a society involves more than economic interestspropaganda, lameculísticos (sorry). The value of human life, the consideration for the weak, with the surplus marginalized. Does anyone still believe that Rambo is a "tough guy"?. Then you see this movie without prejudice and will realize the fallacies that beside the point of this icon have been said. Rambo is a totemic explosion of brute force and savagery in the service of worthy causes. In this film is dedicated to kill and/or scare military, whether American or Russian (while protecting the locals). No matter the nationality nor the color, but the moral principles. Perhaps in this lies the deeper critique of the Western establishment: do not want symbols, or technology tip or propaganda apparatus if they are not grounded in moral and spiritual principles.Forget the blood and the value and leave it in the hands of technology. There is no action without an instinctive mind to Rambo. Marshal Murdock controls the machine, times have changed. Rambo is back just in the heart of the jungle, and has to survive the war, a war of silence, there are no enemies declared in a game of interests between the capitalist and Communist machinery. Rambo contrasts his mind (and its spiritual values) to the cold cruelty of technology (attention to the sequence in which Rambo destroys the great computer of the Marshal, symbolic act in which the Warrior reaffirms its superiority and contempt on the machine). We return to meet the struggle between civilization and wild romanticism.And following the exploration of the features that explain the magnetism of the iconic Apollonian body and long hair, if in the analysis of First Blood we accusation to the archetype of the hostile savage claiming historical roots, the kinematics and the body language of Rambo reminds us the mysticism of the American Indian, the romantic idea as akin to the counter-cultural movements; in this sense, essential to the sequence of the hero armed with the bow and the arrow running next to a waterfall, and then appears from the right part of the image the Thai military that soon begins to shoot against the run. After hiding among the rocks, are witnessing the most fulminant gesture: taking advantage of the nervousness of his rival - has run out of shrapnel - Rambo emerges from the rocks, it rises with the arch and his arrow points and stares at his rival, and this want - and this is crucial - but you can not shoot at the goal: the serene lip of the hero that paralyzes the mood of the rival and nullifies all their defenses. What matters is the mind. Subjectivity?. Non merluzos, review the scene in question and will see that the magnetism of the hero is expressed in the same film material. And not confuse us. Rambo is an icon imbued with a terse Primitivism (potentially ridiculous depending on the mental patterns of each, or simple and plain indifference), but in no way it is pointless if we look at the image (an imperturbable warrior that dominates the opponent from his personal power) and words (the mind is more important than the machine). And in another order of things, we're before a movie at the technical level is almost perfect. Soundtrack, photography, ideal, while it is true that the first third suffers from the dispensable minutes Assembly and pace. But above all highlight the perfect choreography of explosions, strategies, succinct of a script in which the action and look are sufficient to define the tension, and to which he attended in their last 25 minutes approximately. War films and anthology action cinema. To put the character in the circumstance of absolute solitude, betrayed by the Americans, mistreated by the Russians, losing her only friend, return to find the loser and the lone hero who rebels against the world: the bow and arrow, instinct and intelligence, Mentalism and technology: hatching of the total Warrior and final expression of the icon. Supervivencia.para survive the war must be converted into war. This frasecita - sometimes causing hilarity - it wasn't a whim of the writer. The last 25 minutes of the film are perfect exposure in the potential speech act. Once again, it is the romanticism of the individual in the minority that manages to win over the majority, but it is not a representative of the institution (or the country), but a defender of the values, the oppressed, the forgotten.Crude and one-dimensional characters. Manichaeism?. No, let's see, here there is no American Russian and good Thai and bad bad. Here are all bad less Rambo and the victims of the system. Being a film action and built above the foundation of a lone hero, supposed Manichaeism is reduced to a minimum. Almost unavoidable, in addition. And if you why this film is Manichean, we take the "masterpieces" of John Ford or Howard Hawks (which often narrated stories about lonely and forgotten heroes in a bad environment very bad) and say it loud and clear. No doubt the boorishness of the characters is a hangover - like description and development of friendship between Rambo and his collaborator is pretty flimsy-, but recognize that since his scheme and essential intention was no place for too many acrobatics. Not ask del olmo pears. It is not a great film, the scheme is a repetition of his predecessor (here is punished much that the sequels repeated theme and scheme, by that of creativity.), and beyond the remarkable expression of timeless icon is a very simple war story. Anyway, this is action cinema, Paul Greengrass and Michael Bay could learn something. George Pan Cosmatos camera is the model of precision synthesis at the level that shows action, explosions, the faces of the characters (the emotion that arises in the battle), the appropriate tempo and the transition from sequence to sequence. And Yes, everything you knew about Rambo was definitely lie. How will Rambo live?. Every day. This is the free spirit of the beatnick. And in General, a good film that preserves the values and the uniqueness of the character, strong in technical resources, but somewhat irregular and rough.</body>
</review>
