<review author="Natalia Eseverri" title="Mortadelo y Filemón: Misión Salvar la Tierra" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A compendium of topicazos bulk that does not match the quality of the comics, nor is a well-deserved tribute to the author of these characters that have pleasantly marked many childhoods, like mine.</summary>
	<body>There is impossible to adapt things in the film or that the result is no more satisfactory. With the first installment of Mortadelo y Filemón, Javier Fesser managed to surprise me, traslandando this magical universe of endearing comic, who managed to hypnotize me in childhood, thanks to a good story well told and who managed to see those shots of comic, those characters that made me both laugh. Ultimately, he managed to see the comic strip across the screen.In this case, there is a principle in the indent bug history not hooked from the beginning and if above, what you aderezas with topicazos as easy jokes, sayings, meter andalusianism pure and simple because if and also exaggerated, and a question from when Ophelia originally was Galician?.The case is that during most of the footage, one is bored of not seeing anything interesting that surprised him, as he always did the comics of Ibáñez, and saved some extemely that you awaken a slight smile that serves to not sleep you in the armchair.And I prefer not to mention the new mort, because it hardly has any prominence and who has, nor is that it would be worthwhile. Pepe Viyuela line only lacked the gag of the ladder that memory of girl in which he got the head in the staircase and the sketch was trying to take it out, without success. And for me, only save Janfri Coronado, which makes effect, Mauritius Venacio, the Super, and Emilio Gavira Rompetechos, because they are the only ones that retain the essence of the first film and that do not fall in exaggerations with their characters.Anyway, seeing the outcome of this second part, I hope that not passes them through the head, a third, because now, in truth, they would end up with the Earth.</body>
</review>
