<review author="Sandavito" title="Caramel" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Caramel surprised by how easy it is.And however it contains that complexity of who knows how to do things well and to see it seem that, simple. But not simple.</summary>
	<body>I remember that I saw the trailer for Caramel and thought "How have the plot once". During the almost two minutes that lasted (trailer long compared to the rest), one could see the supposed protagonist work in a barber shop and flirt with a police officer. But, fortunately, the human being is wrong, and I'm not going to be an exception. And I am glad I made a mistake, because I could enjoy this simple but exciting film, costumbrista Court spiced with a pinch of suggestive sensuality (both to the eye and ear) and quite humor.Caramel surprised by how easy it is. Easy to tell the stories, ease in the evolution of the plot, ease of identification with the characters or the recognition of any of them as close to you. And however it contains that complexity of who knows how to do things so well that seem to see it to that, simple. But not simple.We started with the well-crafted screenplay with sufficient interest in the sub-plots as to give verisimilitude as a whole, but without the excessive importance which sometimes gives them under the umbrella of "Choral film". Characters who live and breathe, have his philosophy of life and their concerns without having to show it in an obvious manner. Plays with before seen things, but that does not bother to see again. Interpretations seem sincere. It is true that there are moments in which each character adopts a somewhat fixed role, but there is always something behind a Fund.The realization of the also protagonist, Nadine Labaki, won't be of those who switch to history, but at least allows us to see clearly and with a certain focus what is happening, from open levels (American or generals many times) to flat preciosistas detail of the preparation of the candy that gives its name to the tape, supported by the warm picture of Yves Sehnaoui. Music, as it is logical, clear North African aires and an oriental touch, is the perfect counterpoint to the situations of the film.But not everything is good, or rather, it is too good. The movie sins of too much of that "candy". Sweet and well-meaning, perhaps in excess, in my opinion is a film which is easily, leaving a light sediment, a smile out of the room, but nothing more. Still, recommended to have a good time.</body>
</review>
