<review author="Ethan" title="En un lugar solitario" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Violence becomes more evident, the point of view of Gloria Grahame importance and alternates with the Bogart until final resolution.</summary>
	<body>The tape is one of the two masterpieces that gave the director of devotion to excellence, Nicholas Ray, Humphrey Bogart and his production company "Santana" (the other is knock on any door). It is not surprising that Gloria Grahame - one of the big black ladies on celluloid - outside the protagonist since two years before he married the filmmaker. The marriage did not last long, but was very soundly its wedding with her last husband, Anthony Ray, the son of Nicholas then. It seems that everything remained in family. In a lonely place are multiple movies in a single, hence its enormous appeal for any film buff. First is a fierce criticism of the own Hollywood: the protagonist is a bitter writer who does not hesitate to confront the producers, directors and stars throwing them on face his lack of professionalism, whether by commercial interests or by simple arribismo. Somehow can be considered an autobiographical work that the own Ray suffered theirs to bring forward their personal projects. But it is also a tape where it appears one of the favorite themes of Nicholas Ray: the difficulties of the couple (a violent Humphrey Bogart and Gloria Grahame) to live your love story in a hostile environment. In this case, the pressure of the police - who believes that Bogart is the murderer of a Chambermaid - not let this co-existence comes to good term. "I was born when me besaste." I died when you left me. "I have only experienced the few weeks that I've loved" are phrases pronounced him as her throughout the film. The situation will be repeated in later works by the same author. Thus, in Johnny Guitar, Sterling Hayden and Joan Crawford were trying to live his love in the past and at the time of the action, but the social environment, the ambition and the dark background to Johnny as a gunman, made that it is impossible to live together. The same applied them to the characters that embodied James Dean and Natalie Wood in rebel without a cause, this time the pressure exercised her own friends and family. Finally, it is interesting to note as Ray uses different points of view in the plot. Not only that of the protagonist, as it is the case in most of the classic films of the time, but that as the violence becomes more obvious, the point of view of Gloria Grahame importance and alternates with the Bogart until final resolution. And it is the actress performed one of their best performances. Away from his tumultuous marriages and of its concern for their physical appearance - filled lips to give them enhanced so that more than one ended with his mouth full of cotton after having kissed - Gloria Grahame was very serious in her work and an excellent professional that garnered major awards, including an oscar of the Academy. In a lonely place is an essential film for all film buffs in general and for the lovers of the Nicholas Ray film in particular. It is a film that can be analyzed all the elements then Ray will develop in later films; but it is also a tape to enjoy the images of the plot and. Gloria Grahame.</body>
</review>
