<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Los olvidados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Portrait of tourist invisibility. At the end, and after that this film, make us partakers of a reality which we look askance planting in her to make her look at the face without hot packs that worth it.</summary>
	<body>The forgotten starts with images of different cities these screenshots making the banner of a form of knowledge of the places called tourism. Together with these images, a voiceover puts a real but invisible world of poverty and bad life that the majority of people who have visited New York, London, Paris or Mexico have ignored in your ride by the city after these great monuments. Buñuel chooses this film for throwing himself to the task of open your eyes and unknown to show a reality that exists just like.In a scene in which one of the young protagonists of the forgotten wanders alone a brickpit among ruins, feels after the skeleton of a building (recurring motif in the film) a train smoke as well as the characteristic sound of the contact with the tracks. It is clear that the reality of that boy is far from the modern reality of the cities, where a train symbolizes the evolution and well-being and a learned building is part of the truth of the world of the protagonist. The strength of this image leads us to understand the bipolarity of the big cities where the life of the poor has nothing to do with the of the richest despite being part of a local community. Buñuel is clear that they are two different worlds but not go away to the characters that make up. Urban single subparagraph which has the forgotten shows a predatory city where the need of the weak is used as a self-serving del Rico, depicted in an own silent scene in which the young Pedro is appealed by a pedophile after a showcase. One and others, therefore do what they can to survive in their world the only thing that varies is the goal: get food in the case of the young man and get satisfy sexual desires of the man.Finally and after both food and sex are two of the basic needs to cover and the second (or the sensuality in its less obvious derivation) is present throughout the film through different characters and very suggestive scenes. The ellipsis is linked to sexuality in the forgotten but the strength of the images of Buñuel does not require explicit scenes to get expressiveness. A girl hydrating legs with milk or a mother off plane moving arm suggestively aerating a cloth, are the high points of two scenes but the preparation that Buñuel made to reach them draw doubt the least lucid Viewer; and while the sex takes place he entertains us with some disguise dogs dancing and closing us--literally--the door.Through Gates and fences delimit spaces in the forgotten. The presentation makes Buñuel on the sites that make up the community shows packed with houses, without gaps for individuality, but at the same time, thanks to the dynamic of your camera, get that displacement in this world of chaos are fluids. It is precisely this aspect that most draws the attention of Buñuel in the forgotten: how the camera manages to follow developments in small places and make them rich scenarios thanks to the movements of your camera. Public places, on the other hand, occasionally are more overwhelming by the burden of the soundtrack diegetic and because they are the meeting places of the groups, that join together forming agglomerated spaces. These groups are so homogeneous that is clearly delimited who is part of them and who not, thing is not the case in the interiors being treated almost as public places to concede that almost ubiquitous presence to the eye of the Viewer. At the end, and after that this film, make us partakers of a reality which we look askance planting in her to make her look at the face without hot packs that worth it. And if we are not listed, Buñuel focuses on throw us an egg in the face. Who is fought now?</body>
</review>
