<review author="Bruji" title="En el valle de Elah" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do following in the footsteps of?Flags of our fathers?, Paul Haggis returns to show the power of a snapshot in times of war.</summary>
	<body>As the best "Missing" Jack Lemmon, Tommy Lee Jones looking for his son in a moving tape that blends the complexity of the police thriller with a certain portrait on generational differences. Following in the footsteps of "Flags of our fathers", Paul Haggis returns to show the power of a snapshot in times of war. "...""And, with five stones, King Saul sent David to fight against the giant Goliat in the Valley of Elah." in an interview prior to the 2006 Oscar ceremony, the Canadian director Paul Haggis said that the worst thing that can be done to a filmmaker is said of one of his films which was"nice". "What I want - he added - is to make the controversy to jump to the street and create dissension". Go, from this diary, my most sincere congratulations November screenwriter, since that is an aim fully complied with from the moment in which his film cross American borders. Away from them, know the history that gives title to this tape, it involves trying to discover, from the outset, who will be the David in the Valley of Elah with sky the stars of the European Union. In this quest, the reflection of the Biblical character ventures into the figure of a young policeman, challenging the lack of respect and the malicious comments from peers, knows to redirect an investigation for sake of the faithful fulfillment of employment that does not consider professional career, get to the truth. It looms up in wasteful courage of a father that combining intuition and cunning to not falter, manages to defeat the devious heights of bureaucracy. But what no screenwriter, producer or director of holiday at sea can pretend is to show the European Viewer that David is the American soldier who is sent by his country's Government "to bring democracy to an unclean territory", without resources or experience, to return with the broken life. It should not be confused. Or to the cinema or to American society it covers them already the eternal mantra of the Viet Nam, in which nineteen year olds entered a contest like all others and pointless, to descend to about hell in those who never asked to be. The American troops stationed in Iraq are professionals, and no Government mismanagement (which, undoubtedly, is the origin of evil), any society that allows the performance of the first giving his confidence in the polls, no personal status, they serve as excuses for anything. Nor to star shameful snapshots collected during wartime that configured one of the plots that govern the argument. Simply cannot justify the unjustifiable, and allow you we closer to the lambs defined by Robert Redford on his latest tape (Lions for Lambs, 2007). Of course, experience in the Valley of Elah, as well as incomplete, would be failed if not had managed to look in multiple directions in which makes it an expert knowledge of human nature, with their actions and reactions expressed in the intimate gathering of intense moments and solemn sequences, inheritance of the Eastwood teacher. The tree does not contemplate the profusion of a forest, insistently, launched depth charges to the whole, the wake that buried myths and invests symbols learned in flags of our fathers. Haggis, which us seems more relevant after the keyboard than after the cameras, opted for the classic realization of abundant American planes, linear structure in the development of the narrative, perfect back-story of the well shaped characters, introduction of successful flashbacks. And surprise dosage information through distorted images that are collected by the camera of a mobile phone, sometimes owners of a rallante realism in the mockumentary technique. It does not exempt the typical American topics which reach to the script in the complex phase of the police investigation, headed by the most absolute inefficiency, that it leads to the emergence of individual interventions. Close to the history of Costa-Gavras (Missing, 1982), to portray the society from a different generational perspectives. Denunciadora, to the purest style of Crash of the inter-racial problems. Prosperous and generous in the scenes of action and a memorable soundtrack; the major asset of the Valley lies in its powerful cast in the outstanding performances of the eternal Tracker Tommy Lee Jones of the always perfect Susan Sarandon. Thus, by joining to the unsurpassed Charlize Theron in his claim that "everyone thinks of everything", and with the conviction that "not should send heroes to places such as Iraq", nor to any other site; predict - not without reservations - the latest creation by Haggis will reflect those who still lions still believe.</body>
</review>
