<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Juno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great movie as a patchwork of life daily, sweet and sour at the same time that tender, with as good as sharp reflections, a nearly round history, that only light bumps pace prevent achieve absolute excellence. Essential.</summary>
	<body>During recent years has set a standard in the film American enhance small independent productions (which in fact are not so) in order to become the "sleeper" of the year, stories of great quality, with the help, that Yes, propaganda promoting posed the nominations for the Academy Award. So we have come in recent years films as "American Beauty", "Entre cups" or the more recent, "Little Miss Sunshine". This year it is the turn to the new production by Jason Reitman (after his notable opera prima "Thank you for smoking"), already known for half the world due to their nominations for an Oscar, including a well-deserved nomination as best film, it's "Juno", a film about teenage abortion, full of irony (that not sarcasm) and stands on their own merits in one of the most notable films of the new year. The great risk that this new film by Reitman, as they suffered in certain media productions previously named, is engulfed by its own propaganda paraphernalia in this error routine of being drawn by the impact of the film to expect the absolute end-all of gender, wrong that prevents really appreciate the values of such estimable film.This new film by Reitman, shows us the daily life of Juno MacGuff (surname quite revealing by the way), an insolent and associable teen amateur rock and drop insults and chascarridos for most sharp, that a careless becomes pregnant of Paulie Bleeker (Michael Cera), a deferential and esmirriado shy teenager passing hours training for their athletics competitions. So unexpected situation, Juno (Ellen Page) Decides to look for parents of rent, since that has not had courage to abort time. During the reading of a magazine ads, discover what could be the ideal partner to adopt his son, formed by Vanessa (Jennifer Garner) and Mark (Jason Bateman). But the feelings and the unforeseen loves the history of adoption will be more complicated.Before an argument as given to the work of direction of actors, Reitman shows a wisdom for the comedy beyond doubt, in one of those cases in which demonstrates that a good director does not have to boast of their expertise and stay above the action narrated, they should help you work out smoothly. In that regard, the Canadian director is like a fish in the water to get the best out of themselves of all the actors comprising his films with one simple setting, but always looking for the best framing to make more credible if fits excellent interpretations knows out of their "creatures".Obviously any glorification of the great work of actors wouldn't be possible without a concise, incisive, script with a few dialogues full of irony, sensational turn to tenderness. Keyword this last to describe the tone of the story, while in the majority of times there is an ironic distance events suffered by the characters, everything is covered in a sweet and condescending look, an ambiguity between irony and tenderness that works with the precision of a Swiss watch. Helped that if a distribution in the State of grace, able to give all to each of the characters of his own personality, know refine their ground not to exceed or be minimised by the other characters, although of course, Ellen Page as Juno is the main valuarte of the film. An actress to get very far with a performance throughout this film which shows that we we have the best actress of her generation, able to move from the more radical insolence tenderness more descarnada (special that flat end on the stretcher from the hospital) without apparent minimal effort. The rest of the cast, as discussed above is a high level, especially Jason Bateman in the role of Mark, a frustrated musician caught in a relationship so intense that it drowns you and not allowed to pursue a dream that may turn to feel through the rebellion teenage Juno (the catalyst of the emotions of the characters who star in the film). Perhaps should be an exception to such successful cast, an actress that never proved to be worthy of the position of privilege which has as an interpreter in the American industry. He is Jennifer Garner, whose role as Vanessa is very limited, and not because of the prominence in history, but by the own obvious limitations as this beautiful Texan actress. It is very evident throughout many scenes of the film, as Ellen Page, with fifteen years less and the retail experience that entails, sticking a feast of talent at the expense of the limited Garner.Juno has diverse influences both in its tone and its restrained bet as akin to the more reflective comedy multigenérica choice. In a year in which so successful as "Superbad" or "Embarrassing mess" comedies, gambled on occasions by a moralina prevailing in much of the American film (without therefore subtract them too many merits), Juno ran the risk of passing in the same directions, but in a display of expertise of that fantastic script, known succeed even of any execution moralist, that, although on the one hand the story denies abortion as a valid option, knows that camouflage with so much skill comic (the Asian partner fight alone against abortion in sick ridiculous way), that even the final reason why there is this fact is more motivated by the fear that by no moralist decision or reactionary. Even the final where becomes an absolute Ode to the dysfunctional family as as valid as any other option is a political incorrectness (soft, that if) obvious.The story advances through the characters, as it should be in a good human history, contrary to the great American production of the year, where the development of the action motivates or directs the human decisions of the characters that inhabit. This helps also to develop these wonderful characters, with reflections on love (there where one thought was intense and of strong ties are broken, and against where least expected arises in a latent manner), dreams lost in adolescence and the fear to be self-conscious in the decisions taken by a setback that ballast lives forever. With a great soundtrack, replete with songs of independent Court added rather than remaining, as that great start as a 70s video clip where Reitman gives clear evidence of the insignificant draught of a teenage girl pregnant in our society.Ultimately, a great film to scraps of life daily, bittersweet way while tender, with as good as sharp reflections, a nearly round history, that only light bumps pace prevent achieve absolute excellence. Essential.</body>
</review>
