<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Ahora o nunca" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Only notable performances by Nicholson and Freeman manage to save 'Now or never' from the boredom and the fussiness, in a sympathetic but relamida film.</summary>
	<body>This weekend comes to our bulletin boards, The bucket list, as always, faithfully translated by these lares as now or never.Directed by Rob Reiner and starring these two already Jurassic monsters of interpretation that are Jack Nicholson and Morgan Freeman alongside Sean Hayes, Rob Morrow, Beverly Todd, Alfonso Freeman, Rowena King, Serena Reeder and Hugh B. Holub, the film tells the story of two terminally ill patients, one of humble family and another billionaire, who decide to make a list with his last wishes a reality.Certainly, the golden years of the filmmaker Rob Reiner were anchored between the late 1980s and early 1990s, when between 1986 and 1992 lead titles account with me, the Princess Bride, when Harry met Sally, Misery and some good men. Since then, his career has been chopped, and the truth is that only these two actors with capital letters that are Jack Nicholson and Morgan Freeman fail to save his last film of the burning.Conceived as a drama with background of comedy (or vice versa), now or never works solely and exclusively by the good work of its two protagonists, able to get oil of an obvious script and some situations or joke or forcibly tear gas. And if now or never was starring two other actors, no doubt would be speaking a ñoña, simplistic, cheesy and quite vulgar movie in general terms.With a first third of footage in which now or never puts us in situation and in which we can enjoy of certain bis conatuses dramatic, turn to a thick film that is limited to a succession of totally predictable but not by them less funny gags and a sort of documentary of the wonders of the world, while the two protagonists are each roles already usual for all: Nicholson, the rogue ricachón and selfish, and Freeman, humble and full, besides being, how no, the voice of the Narrator.And, as you expect, you will learn each other. That's all.Luckily, the script passes to feet letter by the theological message, without claiming lecturing us (at least, not in excess), but does not escape the situations of easy tear. On the other hand, it should be insisting that the good work of its protagonists to now or never becomes a film pleasant view, entertaining and exceptional locations, managing to convey to the viewer the latent buenrollismo over your footage.On the other hand, one cannot complain that the Union of these two great actors has not produced a higher quality product and that, with a minimally original screenplay, the movie had given a lot more than itself.Entertaining movie to pass the time.</body>
</review>
