<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="4 meses, 3 semanas y 2 días" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>4 Months, 3 weeks, 2 days is a good film showing the agony of the regime of Ceauçescu but that is far from being the great masterpiece that gives to understand his Palmarès.</summary>
	<body>4 Months, 3 weeks, 2 days may perhaps be the most award-winning movie of all 2007 worldwide, and is that in all the festivals or awards that has competed, it has devastated. To this great success, which will certainly benefit greatly the development and promotion of Romanian Cinema, it must be added the great reception from international critics.All of this creates great excitement around the film, and it may be very counterproductive, because it tends to be difficult to match expectations. It is almost impossible to not be influenced by these sensations, and consciously to the film of Christian Mungiu is required more than we. That feeling is soon replaced by a slight disappointment, and is that the rhythm to which the story is told difficult which the viewer immerse himself in it. History it is also true that it takes to boot, and the initial half-hour goes unsuccessfully engage and excite the Viewer. However, when Mungiu makes it clear that the issue of abortion is a mere pretext to show how it was Romania's Communist regime, the film is gaining in height and film quality. Mungiu portrays very well the double standards prevailing in that society, the fear and the desire for freedom of a people, the oppression and monitoring continuous of a regime in the last sentenced to a disappearance that would still take a couple of years. In his eagerness to seek the realism, the film is sometimes explicit, and loses intensity with the long and questionable levels sequence in which they go to the protagonist wandering down a hallway or streets desiertas.4 months, 3 weeks, 2 days is a good movie showing the agony of the regime of Ceauçescu but that is far from being the great masterpiece that gives to understand his Palmarès. He would have won more if Mungiu had chosen another pretext to an illegal abortion.</body>
</review>
