<review author="Bruji" title="El Gran Combate" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A song of infatuation by North American indigenous community.</summary>
	<body>Around 1860, some three hundred cheyenne Indians are forced to live on a reservation in Oklahoma that are dying of hunger. Deceived by a Commission of the Congress of the United States, - which ignored their demands and their most basic needs-, the leaders of the tribe decided to return to his true home, to their homeland in the grasslands, located over two thousand kilometers. The American Cavalry will not hesitate to pursue them and give them capture, but the noble Indian people never give up without a fight. Autumn Cheyenne (real title of the great match) could be defined as a song of infatuation by the American indigenous community, embodied in a beautiful poem that narrates the pain of the Indian people, persecuted until the extermination by the insatiable greed of the "white man". Not only stripped them of their territories, they were also forced to leave their natural environment and practiced with them a shameful policy of ethnic cleansing; clearly doomed in this film. It is, therefore, an atypical Western, (remember that in films such the good are always those of the Seventh Cavalry, which save their chaste maidens from the clutches of the Indian savages that start scalps), in which the admiration of Ford by the culture of these peoples succeeds in creating a film beautiful, chilling in many of his scenes, with the creation of images of an unusual beauty on the screen; and - as all runnings of the acclaimed director - it does not exempt any anecdote that release their folly by the perfection. On this occasion, we have received that in a famous sequence in which Richard Widmark (the protagonist) with other civilians expected output of an authority of a House of postas full Monument Valley, Ford forced them to stay standing up more than three hours, to the Sun, until the shadows of their bodies reached the length as, in his view, it was appropriate. With this film, more November director of the history of cinema, would show his detractors that was quite uncertain rumors that circulated around his person, which accused him of racist. Indeed, John Ford and Raoul Walsh were the only Directors of film hosted by the Navajo Indians in their own tribe, in appreciation of the work that both played to dignify the role of Indians in American history. In the navajo language, the Ford name was "Natani Nez", which means "the high Warrior"; and Walsh, "Etsua already apenta", much more beautiful and descriptive than the previous one, which means "The Eagle of the sky in the morning". With this work of author, farewell of the great filmmaker of the western world, many viewers will recall the famous dancing with Wolves Kevin Costner; a good film (undoubtedly good), but that no one should settle knowing the existence of the great battle.</body>
</review>
