<review author="Bruji" title="El Juez de la Horca" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A peculiar remake of "The stranger" of William Wyler, based on an approach unknown in his time.</summary>
	<body>Any classic film lover knows that the path of John Huston as director (he was a prestigious screenwriter and actor) was governed by the principle more absolute of irregularity. So much so that, without prior notice or apparent motivation, along with authentic masterpieces, - said nobody like him managed to rub the perfection to direct a film-, we find true bungling, worthy of an eternal mediocre beginner. Personally, I have always believed that this extremist trend was only another sample which showed his unquestionable genius, not exempt from certain excentricismo. It is easy to see how turned on projects that managed to inspire you and make you grow professionally, and how - with the same roundness-, only confined to sign other works that failed to draw your attention, either because they were custom or because, even as own creation, ceased to be interested. To honor the great filmmaker in this special, the safest bet would be doing so with the comment of a film which belonged to the first category, which admit no discussion about its quality. However, I thought interesting to address the only film of Huston that not can be kind in any of the two previous sections, simply because it is "something else", the exception to this rule that characterized his filmography. To begin with, "The judge de la Horca" even is has been able to catalog its gender. It is known that it is a kind of remake of William Wyler's the stranger, in which Walter Brennan made the role of the judge; and that, on this occasion, he plays Paul Newman. But it is also known that it is not one remake of any, but a highly personal work that part a little common originality, for a totally unknown at the time approach. In reality, is not a western per se, but rather a picaresque story about a man who manages to become judge, jury and executioner, only law (very often, arbitrary) of a territory without it. Talking about the judge Roy Bean (which, apparently, was a historical figure), haunted by a famous actress of the time, the exciting Lily Langtry, who briefly appears, played by Ava Gadner. The argument is structured in two distinct parts. The first one, bursting with sympathy, is characterized by the good mood that has prevailed between the characters, for the showcasing of Newman. In the second part, - less bright but more interesting than the first-, emphasizes the narrative of the supporting actor Nead Beatty, and a bizarre revenge starring Jacqueline Bisset, in which the humor disappears. Thus, in a field that does not ends be western, which can not be comedy, and never in his mind be a drama; Huston is beginning to move with some discomfort, that makes that this film does not reach the mastery of others of this era such as the Mackintosh man, the Kremlin letter or the great man who would be King; but that, due to the perfection of many of their scenes, nor fell into the bag of appalling mediocrity in which are blood Sabia, Fat City or the Phobia.Lo, the hanging judge... is something else. A very interesting experiment that lovers must be judged; and whose viewing is a wise choice.</body>
</review>
