<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Michael Clayton" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A simple film that uses distractive elements to tangle her, making it more complex and sobrevalorarla more than it really should be.</summary>
	<body>I have argued many times that I am going to see a film with the minimum information, with strictly necessary because believe to listen or read previous comments ago permeate your own discretion. However, only the fact of knowing the vast amount of accomplished nominations generated high expectations. But I also recognize that things like being the directorial debut of Tom Gilroy recognized Hollywood screenwriter with significant works such as the myth of Bourne of 2004 and the Bourne Ultimatum of last year and the participation of excellent actors led by Tom Wilkinson, and Tilda Swinton they helped him further. Annoying most of Michael Clayton is the immense ability to tangle the plot through a high level language, with a libretto that becomes heavy and at certain points tiring, in what we can call a film whose plot is nothing innovative and whose plot can crumble easily. The strategy used was trying to create of already created, a "smart" script by a subject specialist for trying to reach some spectators with a more refined and exquisite taste. However in their background there such and the plot is simple and so easy presumably, that from the beginning part us the importance that would have the role of Karen Crowder played by Tilda Swinton.Michael Clayton uses part of the complex and heavy, dialogues time as tool to increase a simple intringülis that begins in the deselance of the sameIt lies in a flashback larghissimo back to its point home to trigger what from the beginning with those first images of a big Tilda Swinton, was assumed. Swinton throughout footage gives us a large sample of interpretation that make for my best of the tape and which make worthy just the nomination as best actress of Reparto.El beginning of the film is really good, as also the picture thanks to the excellent selection of scenery natural beginning with New York and Royal offices of the most important law firms in this city. But in flashback stories and moments distractive are used to lengthen his end. Halfway this becomes evident with a number of details that are no more than trivial and end up tiring to the Viewer. This is certainly a weapon of double edge because it suggests that the end will bring an explosion of vibrant and definitive moments, but the truth is that none of this happens and more than "elegance" as many have called the end of Michael Clayton, for I do not is more than a simple finish that stands out again repeat, the performance by Tilda Swinton. Not taking game by one side or the other with a calculating end, is the least that can be expected of a film over his footage stands out for this typical feature of thrillers that are wrapped in the world of law, its laws and the ambitions of those who handle them. I can hardly recognize brilliant in this aspect that some critics have pointed out.Although all of the above, the film no longer interesting thanks to lucid moments that save it notoriously. It is initially quite promising of this writer that ironically failed in his script precisely, but forgive by being his directorial debut. In addition it became clear the desire and ambition for showing us a risky and modern film that although he failed it is totally and absolutely valid.</body>
</review>
