<review author="Plissken" title="Sweeney Todd" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are so many virtues of 'Sweeney Todd' the result is a spectacular musical returns us to the Burton more wild since the 1990s.</summary>
	<body>They have out there that Tim Burton took much time behind to adjust the most macabre musical by Stephen Sondheim, ' Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street', and seen the result one cannot deny that the waiting was worth. Above all to the director himself, that puts all the meat in the grill to sign his most gross film since its already brutísima ' Mars Attacks!'.The story is faithful to the musical almost at foot juntillas: Benjamin Barker, formerly a naive Barber, returns to his native London after fifteen years imprisoned for a crime he did not commit under a new identity: Sweeney Todd. Returning to his old barbershop, discover everything you had him has been snatched, and machine a vendetta against the corrupt judge that led to his disgrace. With the help of Nellie Lovett, a dark panadera, and its knife razor silver, Sweeney Todd will trigger an orgy of blood that will become more and more ruthless, reaching guilty and innocent alike.With 'Sweeney Todd', Tim Burton shows that it is one of the few Directors of Hollywood can leave aside the timidity and moral or family conventions that dominate the contemporary American cinema. The original work was an example of how evil, cynicism and amorality campan at ease by modern society, but the tricky thing was to bring that feeling of rot to the big screen in times of political correctness and self-censorship. The small miracle has acted so the Californian director, that will have happened it in big filming the degollinas of the deranged evil Barber and his repulsive accomplice.And speaking of accomplices: if John Carpenter has Kurt Russell, Tim Burton has Johnny Depp. His alter ego on screen since the days of 'Edward Manostijeras' is at home playing Sweeney Todd, brilliantly with his obsession to slopes. A new freak to add to his long list, with the exception that it can be which will serve in tray Oscar who is persecuting his entire career. And along with Depp is Helena Bonham Carter, facing the mirror perfectly Depp with a Mrs Lovett in the fine line that separates the unconditional love of the mass murder (of bread). Also include Alan Rickman and Timothy Spall as the villains of the function, and an unrecognizable Sacha Baron Cohen and a very young Ed Sanders effectively underpin the very high level of adaptation.Closing the chapter of praise, stresses (once again in the Burton film) the gloomy and oppressive atmosphere of the nineteenth-century London in charge of the legendary Dante Ferretti and the grim picture of Dariusz Wolski (see their records and tell me if Tim Burton did not choose well to his collaborators). All elements will be joining the original music of Sondheim, and the result is a spectacle of luxury at all levels.But not everything in 'Sweeney Todd' works. The big problem in adapting a musical film consists of correctly measuring the percentage of "musicality" that will have the film, and in this case Tim Burton has sinned to be too faithful to the original. For a long time that it did not see a musical so musical (easily 90% of the role is sung), and although most of the numbers are bright and are perfectly engaging in the plot, there are times where it is inevitable to feel out the sinister and hooligan spirit of the same. In particular attract attention the moments in which appear the other couple protagonist of the story, that in the musical must fulfil the role of "lyrical moments" and as a counterweight to the black adventures of Todd, but appearing in the film as downtime that, to make matters worse, result up irrelevant to the main plot.Even so, there are so many virtues of 'Sweeney Todd' the result is a spectacular musical returns us to the Burton more wild since the 1990s. Pity about the tasteless couple co-star. A 8'5.</body>
</review>
