<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Monstruoso" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Monstrous is a film of disasters which enjoy all those seeking a cinema without pretensions and spend a fun time that can give rise to a new way of dealing with a much-needed fresh and original ideas of gender.</summary>
	<body>A great and calculated strategy of promotion and marketing can work miracles, and become a taquillazo a film of low-budget (by American standards). The best example is the project of the Blair Witch, although Monstruoso is not far behind. Drawing the pull that are homemade videos that proliferate like mushrooms over the internet, the idea of Monstruoso, that besides original offers a special commercial hook, I had to translate sooner or later.And it is that it isn't more than a film of disasters in which the action is through the camera with which a few characters are recording the facts (as [REC] go no further). The truth is that the film is quite entertaining and decent, that is all a merit if takes into account the level of Hollywood palomitero film. The principle makes very long to introduce a few characters that are basically going to devote to running from one side to another throughout the city. It is obviously made on purpose to go creating the viewer curiosity and some anxiety to see the bug that gives title to the film and that is capable of causing destruction. Anyway you must concede that the protagonist is hexed, and that we must be very bad suertepara your girlfriend is going with another and a monster attack the city hours before travel to Japan and be appointed Vice President of something. In some of the most spectacular action scenes, the fact that the film is shot with the camera on his shoulder can significantly stun. The Visual effects are of good quality, and the monster, while little seen on screen, is very accomplished and is not disgusting or unpleasant.Monstrous is a film of disasters which enjoy all those seeking a cinema without pretensions and spend a fun time that can give rise to a new way of dealing with a much-needed fresh and original ideas of gender.</body>
</review>
