<review author="Ethan" title="Grupo Salvaje" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Peckinpah will give them a clue of what is approaching, you need only look to play some children at the start of the film...</summary>
	<body>Grupo Salvaje is a film that has not done but grow with the passage of the years and today can say, without risk to wrong, that it is the masterpiece of Sam Peckinpah and the most representative of the so-called western twilight; Maybe it's because the controversial filmmaker film fit perfectly with the elements that defined the genre. Some of them are as follows:-the characters, eternal adventurers, belong to the Wild West and outside site with the arrival of civilization. They have no other way that fight to death, more than anything because they can't do anything else. Thus films as two men and a destination (Butch Cassidy and The Sundance Kid of George Roy Hill, 1969) are calcadas in its resolution to Grupo Salvaje. -The players are old cinema glories (Holden, Borgnine, O'Brien, Ryan, "indio" Fernández, etc). It is calling a crepuscular tape. Peckinpah did something similar in duel in the High Sierra, for some the first feature film of this genre. -The "tone" of the film is nostalgic, pessimistic and, above all, violent. The good times have gone; "romanticism" of the western, duels and justified by the absence of law violence no longer exist. Now prima violence by own violence. In Grupo Salvaje "good" are worse than the "bad", such as birds of prey. To highlight the harshness of some sequences Peckinpah used slow and don't think to do so by aesthetics. I think the claim of some critics naive when referring to the scenes of the shootings as if they were a "dance"; what the director intended was to get images from barbarism to remain in our retinas--and in our memory - the maximum time possible. It was a new form of complaint and there is no doubt of the close relationship that exists between what counts in the film and what was living in Viet Nam at the end of the 1960s. The viewer who has not yet seen Grupo Salvaje to be prepared for a new experience. Peckinpah will give them a clue of what is approaching, you need only look to play some children at the start of the film.</body>
</review>
