<review author="Plissken" title="John Rambo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In an exercise of honesty and consistency, Stallone directs nerve and simply the last Rambo slaughter without half measures.</summary>
	<body>We must not forget it (I write, of course, to not forget what I): Sylvester Stallone is possibly one of the most limited of Hollywood actors, but certainly not one of the most stupid people. In 1982 she played one of the two roles that will always be remembered: John j. Rambo, a tormented veteran of Viet Nam responded to violence with the Armageddon himself. After two sequels that exploded the myth of the machine killing a human, then against the worst enemies of the USA, the Soviet Union collapsed, communism disappeared as a major threat and Rambo ran out of enemies that massacre. Stallone is dedicated to make stupid comedies and action of second row, and we all started to take him by bobo ("do not feel legs").Well well, Rambo returns to the fray twenty years later. And when how easy it would be to check a divertimento light in which the perfect soldier trashed Muslims, Stallone is in charge of the project to return us to a character morally crushed beyond of any redemption and more violent than ever. And what they want to say, may even catch by surprise.After the bloody escabechinas in Viet Nam and Afghanistan, Rambo becomes to remove middle and is dedicated to hunt snakes in Thailand. Some missionaries seeking to alleviate the suffering of the raw Burmese civil war are captured by the army, and Rambo decides to return to hell, after finally accepting himself: he's not going to war, he is the war.In an exercise of honesty and consistency, Stallone directs nerve and simply the last Rambo slaughter without half measures: bodies that exploit, cercenadas heads, crossed by arrows, violations, INCI skulls, gaps of the size of a fist. lejísimos the trivialization of the war who were 'Rambo' and 'Rambo III', 'John Rambo' uses the "post 11-S style" and scratch at high altitude in the action scenes. Furthermore, the solitary nature and almost a psychopath of the main character is underlined by two details: the absence of his mentor, Col. Trautman; and the comparison with the crude mercenaries, appearing at his side newbies. A military spectacle at the service of a figure who, in this fourth installment, reaches an almost legendary dimension.Thanks to the common sense of his actor and a right and crude visual wrapper work of Glen McPherson and Franco-Giacomo Carbone "Hostel", 'John Rambo' is a notable war film despite black spots such as the lack of charisma of the actors accompanying Sly on the cast, that first half hour too redundant or that end missed in part. At the recent press conference, Stallone said that with 'John Rambo' it intended to say goodbye to the character shaping the brutality of war. Objective fulfilled, since then. A 7.</body>
</review>
