<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="La Escafandra y la Mariposa" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Diving Bell and the butterfly is an ode to the tenacity of the human being, which is able to fight the largest of adversity and win it without more aid than the own force of will and the desire to live.</summary>
	<body>Long French cinema not obtained many awards and recognitions at the international level, and is that there are three French films nominated for the Academy Awards, and the three are added a whopping eight nominations, including some to the most important such as address or adapted screenplay awards. And that Persepolis failed candidacy for best language film not Inglesa.En the neighbouring country perhaps still must be wondering why not selected to the Diving Bell and the butterfly that represent them at the Oscars, given the nomination of Julian Schnabel for Best Director has won among others. With similar ingredients, there is no doubt that we are facing one of the most eagerly awaited films in these first months of 2008. The first impression is that you it's a sea inside French, most by an innate Association of ideas than by real similarities between both films, which are very different. The film is first and foremost a singing strength of will of human beings, and the brave fight against adversity. It is a touching, and emotional story that does not fall in the easy sentimentality or melodrama. Since the beginning of the tape, Julian Schnabel transmitted to the viewer the feeling of being trapped in the body itself, although this can also take in entering the story altogether. The pace is perhaps too slow, as well as the duration, which is excessive. All actors, especially Mathieu Amalric, who signs a honest, sincere and extremely touching performance with the only resource of his voice, play some brilliant performances.The Diving Bell and the butterfly is an ode to the tenacity of the human being, which is able to fight the largest of adversity and win it without more aid than the own force of will and the desire to live.</body>
</review>
