<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Inugami" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Disconcerting, extravagant, surprised at not being able deslavazada and what is worse... quite tedious film Court, at least allegedly, fantastic.</summary>
	<body>"To a little town, comes the new secondary master."There he meets the particular family Bonomiya, falling for Miki a woman's youth, although quite older than his appearance. They fall in love and begin a secret affair.But it will not have easy because, apparently, the Bonomiya family is a family secret: from many generations ago, women are affected by a kind of curse: see a series of spirits of wild demons, which are deposited at the bottom of a few jars. At night they must have them to check that none of them has escaped. "If this were to happen, they would attack human beings".Disconcerting, extravagant, surprised at not being able deslavazada and what is tedious peor.bastante film of court, at least allegedly, fantastic.I have to agree that it is very interesting. Throughout the film prepares us to attend at the last minute to a fireworks of who knows what, but interesting, strong, imaginative, spectacular, violent, exciting. But nothing of the sort happens.All is shown at the end that is losing the time, resulting in a "mocho toco" film.We are it promised much and is going prepared for us to do so, but in the end everything remains in a pure and pretty boring fire of artifice.In addition, its director is in a rather embarrassing way, pedantic to the, suddenly, and without that nothing explain it, remove the color at the bottom, no one knows for what Earth. He is supposed to highlight the fire that is suddenly turned on in a scene is vital?. But it is quite sloppy Amen for free.Someone could say is that I did not understand the philosophy and Oriental keys of the film. And may well be true, it had done so maybe I would have liked more, but the truth is that I think "Inugami" as a small joke, whose vision does not lead to anything.It is also very long for what has (rather little).But not everything is negative. It has a good photograph, the landscapes are simply wonderful, and actresses do it well, getting the protagonist give his character a halo of mystery really achieved.</body>
</review>
