<review author="Plissken" title="H6 Diario de un asesino" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>That the success of the carnet is proven by points, they should move this concept to other areas, as the film. Sad, sad, that a film is thus carried out.</summary>
	<body>That the success of the carnet is proven by points, they should move this concept to other areas, as the film. As it is seen that anyone can be reached with a script or whatever under his arm, even accessing the ICAA (upon the recommendation of some buddy) aid and direct a film, what less than that perpetrated a fudge remove a few points, and not let him go two chestnuts followed. And if you do, remove it from circulation. Cinematically speaking, of course.This delusion comes to the thread of ' H6: Diary of a serial killer ', the directorial debut of the young Majorcan artist Martín Garrido Baron, who as in the web of the film indicated, "with only 9 years he began to paint, and at 17 already exhibited his first work in a gallery, which makes almost a prodigy of the image".Viva humility.'H6: Diary of a serial killer ' premiered with a Conatus of controversy to renege friend Garrido of the final assembly of the film, throwing pests of producers for not having included the 45 minutes long testimonials of doctors, guards and you go to know more about the character. From here I thank the producers in question that I avoid 45 minutes more of ordeal, because the film lasts 90 endless, dull, absurd, old and at times hilarious minutes, more than enough to get an idea of the prodigious Mr Garrido.El argument is simple: Antonio Frau (hilarious Fernando Acaso) kills his girlfriend and spent fourteen years in prison, after which he married a woman vase, inherits his aunt Encarna pension (insane scene dedicated to receive inheritance of his lawyer) and begins to do the work for which has been "elected" by a "superior being" (Florentino Pérez?): kidnap, rape, and cut prostitutes, leaving everything collected in a meticulous diary, as it did at the beginning of the 20th century his idolHenry Landrú. SPOILERS (as if someone were her to see) the first problem is the script, perpetrated by Martín Garrido, Sr. on the basis of a character that mistreats and kills her partner after just three minutes of footage, jumps to that same character, fourteen years later, become a psychopath who says himself in the voiceover, is called to be "the chosen" to purify and sacrifice some few women of dissolute life. Someone said "character development"? For what, if you've already shown that he was a murderer at age 28?Later makes it happen, again and again, by the same situation: I draw someone, I would like to eat, I kill. Invariably, all their victims go through this modus operandi. The third intimate dinner you get loose laughter.But there's more: marries it an (laughable Mª José Bausá) jamona of 35 tacos which leads years pulling a married doctor, and that by leaving the House of his parents is ready to marry this element out of the bag. The jamona also spoke in voice-over, has three scenes of bed and they do not kill. Live at the boarding house with her husband and tortured prostitutes without knowing anything, and his best phrase in the movie is:-this Board makes me bad of the nervous system.More: when it comes to film, appears a police inspector (played, so to speak, by the very same Martín Garrido, Sr.) of which knew nothing, which also speaks in "off" and discover the murderer with a ticket of the first victim of Fernando Acaso (absurd Alejo Sauras, lasts three minutes and says six phrases). The "case" resolves to the first row that make the Board, already takes criminal mind.And to end with the hyphen: the murderer, in the end, is that he had devised a plan to become a psycho-killer superstar, covered with the proceeds from the rights of his diary (halfway with his wife jamona) and get to Venezuela as soon as they soltaran you from the asylum. The one chosen was a humbug! When he spoke in "off" with himself, it was autoengañando! A twist of worthy of Bryan Singer screenplay, will. Pathetic writer and actor, this Martin Garrido, Sr.Y I have left to the end to this artist, this "prodigy of the image", Martín Conectado, Jr. kid, for my part three tips from my humble knowledge of the environment:-when you desnivelas the frame, usually get sense of confusion, imbalance, Madness (test to see 'Dogs of straw', Sam Peckinpah, for example). But when you desnivelas the framing in 75% of the levels, get sense of that were shooting with a tripod without bubble, or drunken-rhythm in a sequence does not mean to put plans for a tenth of a second in a conversation of the kind "would have worked much?" Likewise, if you will display the number of five murders, five of a total of 18 who committed the element, at least varies a bit of House, that the third bored already a little-if at the end you are going to copy to other (Lynch, Fincher, McNaughton.), or attempt to position it at least, don't go by the life of "prodigy of the image", man. All copy, but when we artistillas give penalty.Sad, sad, that a film is thus carried out.A 2, for some time in some of the prostitutes and give less would be to give him notoriety.</body>
</review>
