<review author="Plissken" title="This is England" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Shane Meadows is a film small and sad in the background, but told with rhythm and color, especially in the first half.</summary>
	<body>The eighties. That decade that, fortunately, leave of glorificada within a couple of years (played 1990s grunge and the makinote will be fun), gave to much in all senses. And in the bad sense, gave rise to the radicals claimed national symbols to revive old ghosts of hatred and xenophobia throughout Europe. Also gave rise to the new romantics, but that's another story. 'This Is England', the award-winning film of Shane Meadows, the novel is set in the coastal England and lower-class of 1983, stuck in the Middle thanks to its unwavering leader, Margaret Thatcher's Falklands war. Shaun, a boy of 12 years who had just lost his father in the war, leads can be orphaned and poor. And one day, finds a group of skins that accept you as more than one group. Its entry matches the back of Combo, one of the more radical members of the group, which will try to drag them to the darker side of the movement. Shaun must choose between staying with their new friends or honor the patriotic values for which his father died.Shane Meadows is a film small and sad in the background, but told with rhythm and color, especially in the first half. This helps that from minute one, the star of the function is the young protagonist, Thomas Turgoose, which eats the screen to bits next to who you are, and that gives the story a tremendous power. Beside, the endearing 'Snatch', Stephen Graham, Tommy is great in the role of the violent Combo, and a good handful of unknown young give life with much success to this peculiar gang of skinheads.Other aspects to be highlighted are the cuidadísimas photography and ambience, that as soon as we put fully at that time as heterodox (if not tacky) as we move to the more sordid part of the life of Shaun. The inclusion of hits of the time as the mythical 'Come on Eileen' of Dexy´s Midnight Runners or the "Tainted Love" soft Cell contrasts with the intimate music that accompanies the more solitary moments of the Shaun small or the selection of music ska and soul these skinheads hear in their small revelries. Because one of the keys that handles Shane Meadows in which we identify with such extreme characters is different which was the skin movement in the early 1980s, before characters like Combo become it cannon fodder for their nationalist Crusades.On the negative side, outline the short route which has the history itself; When Shaun process could understand months, or even years, to travel from one end to another of the ideology skin, the feeling that remains at the end of the film is that the protagonist has spent a few days with a group of people and then gone. Gives the impression that time required to make sense of the evolution of the characters, or what is the same, this evolution is somewhat hasty way. Against the same is relapse in some cliché of the genre.Moreover, a remarkable example of how having a small history of neighborhood and to reach any audience. They call it universality, and it is a pending issue here. But of course, this is Spain. A 7.</body>
</review>
