<review author="Ethan" title="El perro rabioso" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is closely related to the black gender American, but narrated in the purest European Neorealist style.</summary>
	<body>The nature of the human being is configured as the years pass and successive experiences within a changing environment will be acquiring. The personality of the film director - those who have - also evolves and so interesting is to look out of his recent films, where you can see your style with all its complexity, as remember past works made in the "cooler" period of his career. This second is what we do about Akira Kurosawa and his dog Rabioso. Indeed, Nora Inu belongs to his first stage - second after the initial tapes of court for some more nationalist-characterized by feature films close to what I was doing in the West; in fact the film is closely related to the black gender American, but narrated in the purest European Neorealist style. All this under the particular point of view of the great Japanese director. Let's see it: the dog Rabioso is structured in three very distinct parts: the first tells us a chase between a young policeman (Toshiro Mifune, actor fetish of Kurosawa) and a thief of small-time just steal their regulatory gun. The second part, the core of the tape, acquires a tone of learning very Hollywood to recount the investigations of the newbie and bitter detective with one serene and experienced agent (Takashi Shimura, another of the usual film of filmmaker). The conclusion, as to the form, is almost a copy of the introduction, which gives a circular nature to the very interesting plot; However, although it's the same persecution, the character played by Mifune has evolved from their despair, to occur the crimes caused by seven bullets from his own colt. The blackness of the film is no accident. Kurosawa takes some sequences to denounce the situation that was Japan at the end of the second World War: disoriented female characters, to which more materialistic; the despair of the policeman and the thief - not sure who is more "rabid"-the two; the Manichaean treatment of some characters ("there are two kinds of returning, and soldiers who had suffered the theft of his backpack, those who were content with the situation and those others which in turn also robbed it"); and the suffocating environment, where the heat is one character and the night the main decor. The approximation to European cinema is also evident. When Mifune decides to mix with low funds, to keep track of the thief, Kurosawa stops the action and is dedicated to contemplate the slum dwellers and people which there survive. At that time, it is inevitable that come us to the memory films as the Bicycle Thief (Ladri di Biciclette by Vittorio de Sica, 1948) and Eastern cinema feel increasingly more international. Really it will be a year later, after the premiere of Rashomon and the successive awards at Venice and in United States, where took an oscar of the Academy. Among all these influences - that seem very appropriate - appears the personal hand of Kurosawa when, by way of documentary, filmed a baseball game or the camera wanders the sweaty bodies of some dancers cabaret just act. It is the same which based its implementation on scene in depth with a three-tier structure, so that when the characters converse among themselves, which is firstly talk with which is situated at the bottom of the stage or someone placed between the two. It is the same that synchronizes the credits with a first class level of a dog gasping with few friends face. And is the same as to find that boot had been censored in United States, where suspected that the animal had been mistreated, said something like: "is the first time in my life that I have come to wish that Japan had not lost the war".</body>
</review>
