<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Pozos de ambición" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Wells of ambition is a hyperrealist spiritual involution inversely proportional to the social evolution of atmosphere kubrickiana for total showcasing of an immeasurable Daniel Day-Lewis.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Paul Thomas anderson and starring Daniel Day-Lewis, Paul Dano, Kevin J.. O'Connor, Ciarán Hinds and Russell Harvard, There will be blood, translated here - this time Yes have been taste - as wells of ambition, is nominated for eight Oscars and already has in his possession a globe of Oro.Basada in the novel Oil! Upton Sinclair, the film is an epic story about family, faith, power and oil, which takes place on the border of California at the end of the 19th century. Wells of ambition is a chronicle of the life and times of Daniel Plainview, happens to be a miserable miner who has to bring forward a single son, an oil magnate. One day a Plainview comes a mysterious murmur on a city to the West where a sea of oil oozes towards the outside, and there goes with his son, H.W. to try his luck in the dusty Little Boston. This paltry city, where the only possible fun revolves around the Church directs the charismatic preacher Eli Sunday, Plainview and H.W. give his stroke of luck. But now that the Fortune begins to smile les, nothing will ever again be the same: conflicts arise and all human values - love, hope, community, faith, ambition and even the bond between father and son - are exposed to corruption, deception and the flow of oil.Señor@s, we have before us the title should be the Oscar for best film and Best Actor by far, with forgiveness of this another genius of the Coen brothers that tomorrow I will see for the second time. And it is ambition wells, recalling some unfortunate comments lost by this humble blog, film is capitalized.Having previously directed titles as diverse as Boogie nights, Magnolia or Punch drunk love, Paul Thomas Anderson brings a mammoth production of 158 minutes for absolute showcasing of Daniel Day-Lewis. With a photograph austere although replete with beautiful and arid panoramic and with a plot that could remind us of a sort of dark giant, Wells tells ambition the degradation of the human being through the power, and makes it a doubly worthwhile way: firstly, because it shows us that corruption of the soul through several characters who evolve hand in hand, and secondly because achieves that, like the protagonists, the viewer not is knows the fatal consequences of such degradation unless it is already too late.Done and structured as a biography, ambition wells offers us an inversely proportional spiritual involution social evolution, as it said, reflected both the Reverend young from the Church of the third day Eli Sunday, whose different friction over decades are without a doubt the best of the film and the character of Daniel Plainview. Thus, wells of ambition stands as a cruel portrait of human greed, a heartbreaking all human scourges canvas framed in the extremely Puritan society of the United States of century.But, if there is something else that worth mentioning wells of ambition to separate its exciting although dense history and that, for a server, it is the best interpretation of Daniel Day-Lewis to date, it is the atmosphere kubrickiana that pervades the entire film by Paul Thomas Anderson: since the texture of his photography to his strident and disturbing soundtrackuntil his unorthodox sequence end.Finally, for a server, a small wonder with aftertaste classic.</body>
</review>
