<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Hula Girls" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A more than interesting film, a film that appeals to the heart to develop a story that works beyond a topical and predictable development to become an effective demonstration of bold and good feelings</summary>
	<body>In dealing with a project in which the spirit of self-improvement to become the main focus of the story, all director runs obvious risks of falling into predictable or repetitive, being something very common in American cinema, but it occurs less regularly in the Asian cinema is irregular current Japanese cinema, either the pop-up, although over-appropriated, dramatic Korean cinema in all its aspects. Fortunately, the Japanese "Hula Girls" overcomes these platitudes to show us a positivist fable where emotion takes precedence over reason.The plot is very simple, a group of teenagers in a small mining town, rebel against the sad and predictable future that awaits them, working men like mine, and in addition, redoubling efforts with the housework. And this way of rebelling is involve in the imminent project undertaken by the mining company to create a Hawaiian honeycreeper Park in one appropriate for this so little place in appearance. Their personal histories entrecruzarán, giving rise to breakdowns that will make harder if it should be the goal of earning a living with it, and therefore help to revive the decaying economy of the town where they live.Before argument so predictable in appearance, the work in the direction and the script wanted as something more than transcendental, as a director without the appropriate narrative pulse ran the serious risk of falling into the absolute apathy, more pronounced and therefore predictability, contempt for the Viewer to the story. The Japanese director of Korean Lee Sang-il shows especially gifted to get the most out of all these scenes requiring go a step beyond the pure cinematic technique, those in which emotions makes an appearance, to boot a ravishing power that makes an appearance from the bottom of the heart with unusual force.His mise en scene is typical of the new Japanese cinema, one that sinks its roots in the film slow and contemplative of the classical masters of Japanese cinema (Shindo, Ozu, Mizoguchi), taking it to this present of Japanese society, always debated between tradition and modernity, usually finding a point equidistant balance between both currents. In his previous filmography (awarded in festivals), had already taken account of the constants which prevail in his films, and again has been able to get away with this tour de force of mixed emotions resulting from this story of self-improvement and good intentions.Say, against, that the script is extremely predictable in the flow of history, always resorting to scenes thousand views on both sides of the Atlantic, topics remaining merits to the film in a clear way, resulting in some really desperate sequences by their predictability. It is not precisely at this point where "Hula Girls" back the flight to become a more than interesting proposal. Lucky that the work of the cast of actresses not can only be described as brilliant, in a demonstration rather than when it comes to internalize feelings, no one makes it better that Asian performers, resulting perhaps simpler for its own cultural essence. Scenes as the fake farewell on the train, with the Group of teenagers dancing the "hula" while the feeling that has taken root in its interior are described with gestures made Professor, is effective absolutely irrefutable, it was touching in its simplicity and mise en scene.This successful group of actresses are totally credible effective film of contrasts involving this referential history. Contrasts that form the basis of the story not shown but allotments, which must possess every good movie. Tradition against modernity would be the most obvious, and which come to light the constants of this type of intimate and emotional film. That tradition weighs as a slab impossible to overcome at times for some of the members of the Group of "hula", instead being the trigger of his rebellion, his way of escape from a place sad, gray, and devoid of any future hope for others. Splashing in his mild complaint also other aspects so rooted in their society as the submission of Japanese women (tremendously effective scene of the beating of a father to his daughter bailariana), being a metaphor for liberation from the oppression of the tradition (patriarchal society) the Hawaiian dance Japanese.Mentioned in various circles, somewhat uninformed way, or at least devoid of a baseless knowledge about this type of production in Japanese cinema, to the influences of this film they came from Western as "Full Monty", "Billy Elliot" and similar films. And while it is true that contain obvious points of connection, no go so far as to find the main basis of this story (on the other hand, based on some facts true that today still have their fruit in a true Hawaiian theme park), influence final as predictable story. In 2004, a film of self-improvement, "Swing Girls", in this case in a musical environment, won the most awards of the Japanese Academy of cinema, and a few years later, in 2006, the great "Always", took us to a Japanese past sweetened by a condescending look by its director. The sum of both productions resulting "Hula Girls", which has also been multi by the Academy. In addition, leave see certain influences from films of similar theme of self-improvement, type "Linda, Linda, Linda" or the recent "Backdancers", in addition to the already mentioned clear.Once exposed the constants of the film, say, anything that saves the proposal and makes it stand out above similar productions, becoming a good film, is the ability of the director to provide the history of a clean, emotional look without artifice (something common in the productions of American of this style as I have mentioned earlier), resorting to more primary emotions to empathize with the viewer effectively, without needing too much cheap theatrics (albeit with a predictable development, that if).In short, a more than interesting film, a film that appeals to the heart to develop a story that works beyond a topical and predictable development to become an effective demonstration of bold and good feelings. Recommended for fans of the film as positive reverie.</body>
</review>
