<review author="Caruco" title="4 meses, 3 semanas y 2 días" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the films most interesting season, for its realization, for his performances by the wealth of their nuances, for free from ethical and moral discourses predictable. Although not round.</summary>
	<body>Gifted student of the extinct movement Dogma pushed Lars Von Trier, Romania's Cristian Mungiu delights us with a few frames as sober as attractions. And as a good dogmatic, strips of music to your images by limiting the soundtrack to the dialogues and the diegetic sound. His camera, curious and incisive, is entering the girls showers or inviting us to contemplate this fictional Odyssey, with all its harshness, but that it could be hundreds of thousands of mújeres during the dictatorship of Ceausescu, decided to abort clandestinely, takes us by the hand to invite us to take a raw journey, accompanying his two protagonists.In this chronicle of two college roommates room at the residence, the ups and downs of those times of the Communist dictatorship in Romania of the eighties, where everything is so precarious is obliquely as guarded. Its citizens are always under suspicion, or to register in a hotel to make their decisions freely. But above all it becomes a poignant story about female friendship. In a world governed by mistrust, its protagonist, Otilia (Anamaria Marinca), is precisely their enthusiasm in the unconditional help her friend, Gabita (Laura Vasiliu), the table of salvation where grab. It's believe to have someone that never betray us, that would do the same for us before the more cumbersome problems.And Mungiu tells us through the omnipresent Anamaria Marinca, not the teenager senseless (more than anything because their answers given to understand that he never knows the correct decision), which stars Laura Vasiliu, the young woman who has been pregnant and wants to rid of that fetus in advanced state. With Otilia will be living as if were in the first person, each of that chain of events and scenarios that leads the fact decide to abort in such a regime. Roads in which any currency goes, even the own humiliation.Not just tested or prefabricated, the frames of Mungiu, with abundant flat sequence, cease to be very striking visually. Even the Green jersey that looks Otilia during much of the footage could be defined as a visual revelation. Or his silent scenes in the mirror. or in one of the stronger sequences of 4 months, 3 weeks and 2 days, of these for leaving one stuck in the armchair, it occurs (for a fact that I do not desvelaré) while Gabita waits "turn" locked up in the bathroom of the rented room, until bursts Otilia, direct to the bathtub.The pity is that so good proposal and pace lose bellows in his final half-hour, where the interest and the rate decays; and where Mungiu, impeccable thus far, da symptoms of weakness, including introducing a flat completely unnecessary detail, which breaks with its suggestive, and by no means less raw, scene.Errors that no river one of the films most interesting season, for its realization, for his performances by the wealth of their nuances, for free from ethical and moral discourses predictable. And above all for its ability of fascination and immerse ourselves in this Odyssey (almost) in real-time with Otilia and Gabita with a naturalness and ease appalling, even though not a work is much less round.</body>
</review>
