<review author="Heitor Pan" title="La Escafandra y la Mariposa" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Schnabel manages to create a bright, honest, hopeful and sometimes film caustic and with certain doses of humor. It dispenses completely with the easy tear and manages to reflect the tenacity and the vitality of a man whose body is dead.</summary>
	<body>The first thing could one think when you see the lauded movie of Julian Schnabel is in a direct comparison with "Mar adentro" from Amenabar. Not in vain, they share part of the theme, that of a protagonist, in the fullness of life, after an unfortunate fact are doomed to live prostrate in a bed. But there just all their differences.While the film in which Bardem embodies miraculously to Ramón Sanpedro, was a plea for euthanasia, capacity of a man in full possession of their faculties to decide if you want to assemble lifetime, "the Diving Bell and the Butterfly" is an ode to the life of a type which is much worse, utter isolation from the world into a body that does not respondincapable of something as simple as asking to change the channel on the TV when they issued the letter of adjustment.Jean-Dominique Bauby awakens in a hospital bed after having suffered a massive stroke. As he regains consciousness realizes that is unable to communicate, while their capacity to think, recall or imagine remains intact. From here on, Bauby will have to cope with their new situation and decide if you should try to get in touch with the people who try to help you to the only visible action which is capable is the one eye blinking.Thus, the film chronicles the true story of the protagonist, who against any odds, managed to dictate a book poetic and stark, free from the prejudices of the writer, for the sole purpose of recounting the experiences of someone locked up in his own body, as if I lived in a Diving Bell hermetic, but able to let fly the mind without any limit. His relationship with those who wanted him and made him more bearable captivity and, above all, his inner voice. A thought which became their only existence.I admit that the movie surprised me. Knowing the topic, it seemed impossible that director could deprive it of the two characteristics which could more easily hit: the extreme drama and slow (also extreme). But Schnabel manages to create a bright, honest, hopeful and sometimes film caustic and with certain doses of humor. It dispenses completely with the easy tear and manages to reflect the tenacity and the vitality of a man whose body is dead.It took us a while to see front image of the prominence, following its evolution since it comes out of coma from the inside, as if we were caught up with him in those tissues and organs that do not obey our orders. For when finally shows us her figure, we're totally on their side, we have already shared part of their suffering and their change of aspect we hit with more intensity.The only parties that my commitment to the film was less were in the numerous flashbacks about the previous life of the protagonist, little or nothing to bring to his new situation. The vision of his previous work, the relationship with their children, with his ex-wife, or his father, not transmitted me that more desolation by his loss. In those moments I look forward to again display its constant in their new situation struggle, his sense of humor, his Narrator inner voice.After a movie as well, hard to tell someone, "my life is shit" (something that my optimistic nature prevents me from thinking). Perhaps, in many cases, be true the saying and not aware of what have until we lose it.</body>
</review>
