<review author="Victor Bilbao" title="El rey de los cowboys (Go west)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very good film of Buster Keaton, misunderstood in his time as contained more serious elements as humorous divertimento, or at least that not must take a joke.</summary>
	<body>"A young man not found work in his hometown, travels to New York in search of a future better, but within minutes of his arrival, is overwhelmed by the life of the big city and decides to try his luck elsewhere." It falls from a train near a ranch and becomes a cowboy very special. "Very good film of Buster Keaton, misunderstood in his time as contained more serious elements as humorous divertimento, or at least that not must take a joke." In reality, and thus have much thought / wear/ACE ACE, is not a pure western, because it would have by law, which included in the genre of comedy, and not comedy but the comic film, that is different. However, and because of that is also a western and this is a blog of this genre, I include it. Without more.Consists of three distinct but complementary, parts to each one better. It is said to have inspired beautiful poems Spanish great poet Rafael Alberti is a heartfelt work and with poetry in spades, which contains a smart dissertation, hilarious and imaginative, about the attempt of the human being for the realization of their dreams and the importance of the destination in the evolution and future of the same.The cowboy nice, absent-minded, but deeply honest and honored, timorous but determined to succeed in a world in principle very alien to its natural habitat, but that will dominate it for their perseverance and somewhat lucky.A film to recover, which meant an economic cost in the shooting far superior to the agreed in principle between Keaton and Joe Schenk, famed producer. The reason for the high cost of production was a cow!. The cow "Brown eyes", the Holstein breed, chosen between the herd by the own Keaton because he believed would be more ready than their peers. Soon they realized that it was as awkward as the others, but insisted teach tricks and to behave in a set. Thus, and in the midst of a blistering heat, not in vain were filmed those scenes in the middle of the desert of Kingdom, Arizona (USA), taking even careful to wrap the camera with ice so that the tape is not melted, I say so, Keaton gave him carrots to the cow and brought him first with a cable, then with a string and end with a thread.But this was not what made them lose more time, but the cow you entered the zeal and there was no way that "focus". "They presented" a nice bull but this was rejected. There was no choice but to wait to move to the hot and continued shooting.Joe Schenk, the producer, when learned what had made such filming exclaimed very angry: "That's Keaton" He will "If there is a way of making a film, find" it.</body>
</review>
