<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Fucking amal" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting film co-produced by Sweden and Denmark, made of rough and rather rudimentary form in the technical aspect (filmed in 16 mm), but honest and credible to 100 percent.</summary>
	<body>In a sad Sweden people live two girls who study in an Institute. Elin is a beautiful, rebellious, young that comes with many boys, although he dislikes none. It's not be like any other, and has dreams and hopes for a better future, will undoubtedly bring you the people.For its part, Agnes lives with her parents and is in love with Elin secret. She has no friends since he lives in this town, where he arrived two years ago.To establish contacts with other colleagues, his mother organizes a party at home, where it is not nobody &hellip; except for Elin and her sister, ranging more drinking than otherwise.Despite the difference of characters of the two girls, Elin and Agnes fall in love, but Elin does not dare to "come out" by fear to the rejection of the friend ACE.Interesting film co-produced by Sweden and Denmark, made of rough and rather rudimentary form in the technical aspect (filmed in 16 mm), but honest and credible to 100 percent.This succeeds Moodysson, director, thanks to a good script, with successful dialogues (the mother of the girl lesbian explaining to his young son what lesbianism) and great performances.The decor is simple but full of intense moments that mixed humor with sadness and despair, while that doubts and feelings of his unhappy characters.His existential void, product of the boredom of the cold and lonely place, full of despair, makes them start and end more sometimes even sexual relations by ending the boredom than by the possible love may feel towards their partners.The end, removing the excess epilogue, is good and want to applaud, partly because of the simplicity of its proposal and in part by the rightness of his speech, a speech at all times close to the Viewer, who feels that we you are talking about you to you and recognizes characters, far removed physically which are in them.Estimable in truth, won a lot of international awards, especially for part</body>
</review>
