<review author="José A. Peig" title="Rambo III" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Action film completely drowned by stereotypes, a flat script as a folio, devoid of inspiration at the time resolve situations or raise something that equal or exceed as seen in its precedents.</summary>
	<body>Home, the approach of this third adventure wisely pointed towards the development of the themes that best define the idiosyncrasies of this rebel Warrior, always towards the defence of the values that we humanize beyond brute force. Rambo seems to have found its place in the spirituality of the East, WINS life taking advantage of their physical qualities in the fight to body and silenced the concerns of his mind with the landscape and the spiritual symbolism of Thailand. Colonel Truman (Richard Crenna), who is a Rambo it definitively renounces his Warrior past travels there. Truman is a double-edged: the element still linking to Rambo with the past and the only friend that cling. Precisely, the hero returns to again without another real reason that friendship. Rambo III, however, is a slight variation to place the character in the battle between rival, that here, unlike their previous two, in which predominates the solitude of the hero against the world - it confraterniza with one of them. But, in response to this archetype of the hostile savage civilization, ends up being logical Rambo sympathetic with the Afghan tribes, that they correspond perfectly with this archetype upon which this built the profile of Rambo, and also here the mujahadeen do the role of oppressed who must save the Russian demon, as it could not be otherwise. (And because of all this, what evil has aged this film, and the hilarity that produced us all this in a world post 11-S.je).Moreover, action film completely drowned by stereotypes, a flat script as a folio, devoid of inspiration at the time resolve situations or raise something that equal or exceed as seen in its precedents. It contains some time of outpouring of the more or less worthy hero, and some segments filmed with success, as the assault on the Afghan fortress. He forgets his attractive approach and ends in a joke of spare parts, which crude imitation of the great moments of the trilogy.</body>
</review>
