<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Monstruoso" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An exceptional work, which reformulates the code generic and narrative, to offer us a catastrophic film with being antidiluviano of through, showing us the double readings of a society slave of new technologies.</summary>
	<body>After sweeping to victory at the American box office during its first weekend (46 million dollars in four days), the new sample of multimedia entertainment guru JJ Abrams, an absolute genius of binomial entertainment-marketing for the film and American television comes to our screens. A creator, that beyond the quality of their projects, which may like it or not (though to a server you earned from long ago), knows to build the paraphernalia and the expectation to create each new project he undertakes a sociological phenomenon. In its new proposal as a producer, which leaves the baton of leadership to his close collaborator Matt Reeves, introduces us squarely in an exciting game where the generic conventions of thinner, giving rise to a history that transcends beyond the screen to point directly to the technological obsession of our society in the 21st century.The argument, so cleverly hidden during the pre-production of the film, shows us the feast of despedidad of a young New York name Rob, since him has emerged a promising job as Vice President of a company headquartered in Japan. After showing us, camera in hand, loving squabbles between some characters at this crowded party, a mysterious tremor puts on alert all them, thinking that this is perhaps an earthquake, or even a terrorist attack. From that moment, his next few hours will be Vertigo, trying to leave with life of hell in which the island of Manhattan has become by the attack of a stranger be.As discussed above, in the Chair of director Matt Reeves, a director which only had as baggage above the direction of television episodes and some forgettable screenplay for conventional films of action ("alert maximum 2") sits. That is why it will be difficult to find out if the true architect of the final product is himself or his popular producer, moreover, after seeing some pictures of filming where it seems that the less, the film was shot two-handed. In any case, the Mise en scene of the film, contrary to what may seem due to the semi-documentary style of the story, is one of the great strengths of the film, where Reeves gets something that many tried to (and even justified) before leaving Midway, use this adrenalítico camera movement to interior of the characters and their anguish personal portrait mode. Here at Cloverfield (aka "Monstruoso"), this axiom acquires its absolute perfection, getting Reeves that confusing and dizzying scenes are directly related with that feeling of loss of characters, on the other hand, being clear and concise those which must describe attacks or flat General (not to mention master dramatic scenes in their intimacy as the reaction of Rob after the call of her concerned mother). This brilliant visual work is accompanied by a tremendously effective script, in which, by removing a couple of turns of dubious credibility as a military permit civilians head-on at your own pace through the affected area, each of the shares takes place with the narrative rhythm right, alien to any narrative debt that creates an obsession to lengthen the story (little more than their acertadísimos 80 min of footage)contributing therefore to make still more credible the agony and terrifying experience faced by our troubled protagonists.These protagonists are played by actors little popular impact the vast majority (perhaps Mikel Vogel, for her performance in the remake of "The Texas Chainsaw Massacre", the most well-known). Which does not mean, that demonstrate a solvency beyond doubt, resulting as real as life itself in its characterizations, and perfect when it comes to translate on-screen desperation or more primary emotions.On the other hand, it is impossible to deny the film effective and powerful help media possessing, thing that is perhaps the main reason for which certain American means, in a very superficial way, have been used as a weapon against this brilliant film. Creating even false indirectly related Web sites with aspects of the film, to how to create false clues, does more than increase the worth of the proposal, beyond the limited view of certain media retrograde, stagnated in the past that will never return, and which JJ Abrams knows RID to clear samples to accept the future of multimedia art with enthusiasm. Creating even false myspace places on the characters in the film (and logically, anyone can search for the network), or protective activist groups of the environment (which who knows if they will have relation to be shown in the film).Buried beneath that aspect of simple catastrophic film with Monster of through, hide multiple readings at the risk of pass unnoticed by less smart viewers. For starters, the film is the best ever shot sample on the paranoia of American society after the terrorist attacks of 9-11, penetrating by way of documentary on a metaphorical sample of reality within the fiction, not only for its visual style, but even because it must not forget that what we are seeing on the screen, is not more than the evidence of what has happened in the area formerly called Manhattanby way of visual testimony of the terrifying tragedy occurred. This fact is shown on-screen alternating personal recollections filmed in previous days by the same videotape, a tremendously effective trick to create the necessary contrast between quiet and superficially concerned life of these privileged somethings, and the stark realiadad who played them live later. This intrusion into the intimacy of this group of friends, leaves us another interesting reflection on new media that dominate our lives, where anything must be filmed to be a crushing credibility. Where "The Blair Witch Project" was looking for a notable analysis of the essence of fear as myth embedded in the popular imagination, or "REC" with respect to the power of the intrusion of the media in any area of our lives, "Cloverfield" (aka "Monstruoso") goes far beyond these two successful productions that come to mind of irretrievably (still lower than the new proposal of Abrams) (by far), resulting in one of the best fantasy films of the last five years without a doubt productions. A film whose growing tension is masterfully (unlike the two, where obvious pace gaps prevented them from even more transcend gender), with set truly anthology pieces that will go to the history of the genre, such as the attack of the residual beings of the big monster in the corridors of the metro, shot with an MBA who scares of the reached perfection (and reminds the master scene that we all remember the "aliens" of) (Cameron), or go no further, scenes of absolute macabre beauty, such as the scene of the ghostly chariot driven by a horse without fixed direction (a picture suggestive to say enough is enough). Mention apart in this respect for the scene of the rescue in that semiderruido skyscrapers and only holding in another which is still standing, a modern tower of babel which stands imposing with the intention that has always had the man reach the sky, and that on this occasion becomes death trap (with echoes of that popular film called "The Colossus in flames").In short, a work unique, at the risk of being misunderstood, he reformulates synchronizing codes and narrative, to offer us a catastrophic film with being antidiluviano of half as excuse to move double readings of a society technologies slave. Simply masterful.</body>
</review>
