<review author="Christian Sandoval" title="La noche de los muertos vivientes" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film is one of those found in that select group of films screening required for all those lovers of cinema.  and it represents a direct influence for a number of filmmakers who include John Carpenter, Sam Raimi, among others.</summary>
	<body>"The night of the living dead" (1968), is the first film by American director George Romero, which is considered a true classic of the genre of horror, which quickly became a cult film. The script was in charge of the same Romero in collaboration with John a. Russo, and is based on the novel "I am Legend", by writer Richard Matheson. Barbara (Judith O´Dea) and his brother decide to go to visit the grave of his father in a remote forest, but there they are attacked by a stranger. Barbara survives and manages to escape in his car to a nearby farm, where it is inside, is a partially mutilated body. While running frightened, he meets a man who explains to him that a group of strangers is attacking without apparent meaning people. Now they are surrounded by these strangers, so it will have to do our utmost to survive this macabre situation.George Romero began his career making short films and some commercial for "The Latent Image", a company that had been founded by John a. Russo and Russell Streiner. The trio eventually bored of making this kind of productions, and they decided to make an horror film. Based on the novel by Richard Matheson and other films of zombies, formed the script for his first tape about undead, for which got $114,000 dollars, through "Image Ten", producer who founded along with its two previous partners, more Karl Hardman and Marilyn Eastman.Obviamente due to the low budget that included, knew in advance it was quite complicated to make a film at the height of the classics of the genre with the the filmmakers had gone.In attempts to reduce costs, Romero had no choice that filmed the movie in black and white. This decision eventually gave good fruit at the level of criticism, since it provides a feature documentary type film, which denounces a kind of loss of social stability. Furthermore, the fact that this filmed in black and white gives a special charm, reinforcing the idea that we are dealing with a true classic. The counterpart of this decision, however, was that this represented serious problems to Romero and company, to find a study that would distribute the film. Columbia Pictures was the only firm interested in distributing the tape, but ended up rejecting the idea, because the film in black and white would disadvantage with the new TVs to color that existed in the market. The American International Pictures (AIP) also consider to distribute the film, but wanted that Romero shot another final and set more love scenes. Finally, the distribution ended her performing the "Walter Reade Organization", which changed the name of the tape of "Night of the Flesh Eaters" to "The night of the living dead".The construction of the script went through three phases. Initially, under the name of "Monster Flick", the film was a combination of horror with comedy, which told the story of a young aliens who visited Earth and made friends of some human teenagers. The second model of the script was the story of a young man having fled home, discovered that some corpses of people are being used as food plants by some aliens. The final script that was practically written entirely by Romero, already relates how some human corpses reanimated, feed on the flesh of the living.In an interview, Romero relates how this idea that a principle was a three-part short story, ended up giving place to this film and its two sequels which are: "Dawn of the dead" (1978) and "The day of the dead" (1985).Many people tend to emphasize the alleged socio-cultural background that has this tape, which is seen as a kind of direct criticism against racism. The fact that the protagonist of the film is an African American, played by the actor Duane Jones, in an era that racism was more latent than never, was a very risky move by Romero. Moreover, not content with this, the rest of the characters (they are all white) are pretty badly unemployed. The director leaves women as true hysterical, that do not contribute much to the defence of the House in which they are detained, but that rather they become a burden which makes more difficult things. Worse still is the character of Harry Cooper, played by Karl Hardman, who is outright racist, as well as being a rather selfish and coward, person which little cares about the future of the rest of his teammates in order to save his own skin. Despite all this, Romero has said on several occasions that the choice of Duane Jones as the protagonist, was only because he made a good casting, and not because of some kind of message against racism. Intentional or not, the message is easily percibible during the course of the film, in addition to the date of departure of the tape, coincided with the death of Malcolm X and Martin Luther King, so the parallel between the protagonist and the two men became more obvious.Much has been also the message against the capitalism that Romero has wanted to translate in his initial trilogy, is also possible to see in the fourth part of the saga "The land of the dead" (2005). Especially in the second part of the trilogy, is a critique of the consumer society, in fact the action takes place in a mall, while it seems to be the analogy between the zombie and the person average, moving to the beat of the rest of the flock, immersed in a system that leaves many real possibilities of free choice. Cannibalism represents the American Society of those years, that under such a system of competition, one can fall into attitudes, that for us to succeed, we must sink or "devour" which is beside our. That message is easily transportable to today's society, where the United States is the largest existing "Cannibal" today.The director has been argued sometimes that a film without a message, is not a film that worth.The tape was received quite varied form by critics that rejected by its effects sequences and gore cannibalism, while on the other hand, is praised as groundbreaking film, which was recognized by several critics as an immediate classic. During the course of the years, also the criticism that makes the film to American Society of the 1960s, stressing in particular the criticism towards the Government and both internal and external policies has praised.The film represents a direct influence for a number of filmmakers who include John Carpenter, Sam Raimi, among others. In 1999 the film was named as "significant culturally" by the library of Congress of the United States and was selected for preservation in the national register of films. Furthermore, also received recognition from the "American Film Institute", which placed it at place 93, in the list of the 100 greatest film of all time, produced in its hundredth anniversary.All the reasons given in this article give to understand that this tape is one of those found in that select group of films screening required for all those lovers of cinema.</body>
</review>
