<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not being good cinema, is not, it is very high level entertainment.</summary>
	<body>This wave of revivalism that runs us has, in a very personal and biased point of view, rope for a while. It would revise upwards (the current technique at the service of nostalgia) the milestones of the always glorious past. As the memory is greedy and like to return there where he was happy, cinemas will fill when start to fall, truffled of modernism, ñoños episodes of adolescence. Unstoppable machinery of the merchandising will be his army of creatives to find three feet to the cat and all shall acome, with gentleness, to the dictate of the box, that (as we all know) governs with tough hand the ins and outs of that, in principle, it could well call Arte.Bien, Pandora's box is open. And hopefully what comes (and much of what there was) like this Miami Vice Michael Mann.No still good movies, which it is not, is very high level entertainment. Not denied its frivolity, its decay in the strictly plot, but it shines powerfully when Mann, versed in police clashes from his Miami Vice television or from the very acceptable Heat strikes the filming of violence.The roster of stars do what they are told: put the gesture, given the size in composure, although neither have deep parliaments or tormented souls to redeem in ninety minutes of footage. I liked very much Jamie Foxx, who has already shown that it touches all the sticks, and everyone makes with dignity. Spare Colin Farrell, is not an actor with packaging still. and the boats? Don't expect the gentle reader of this page of film the boat vertiginous and series fatigando the Florida Keys dirty waters, although some there is clear. Nor the insistent rhythm of the tune of Jan Hammer. There are (and galore) intrigues Mafia infiltrates, shots, organised crime raids, drugs, prostitutes... As a C.S.I. but overfunded economically. Then there is the majestic end, an absolutely recommendable choreography of shooting in the streets, that leaves the audience breathless: literally.Miami Vice is a product of marketing, is a nod brazen to a successful product, is a long and expensive video clip, but we must not play down the effectiveness and sobriety, love of pointillism, some fondness for the craftsman work (this depth of field with night shots HD cameras).Very notable mimbres to be overly strict with what, for sure, not intended to nothing more than entertain. And do it well.After all, ochentera series was ñoña, abused Armanis and imposing cochazos without coming to story and Don Johnson was an advert actor, but mediocre... Or was the man worth?</body>
</review>
