<review author="Kiko de España" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Americans still do not have your Godzilla: the only thing they have done is put a costume to September 11.</summary>
	<body>Cloverfield has reached Spain just when the taquillazo has falter a bit in USA, but that is unimportant.Before you start a warning to all those who are "marearon" in [REC]: I non-hypocritical and recognize that if that bothered them to the Spanish they bear not the invention of the Abrams. At least in that right knowing the building out to tail and here the camera focusing on less, but that does not matter because we all know what we are going to see. Those who follow the blog know that The Host I did not like anything and that great Rob knows this better than anyone else, I had the honour (and nerves) appear live in your program and I have to admit that I like more Cloverfield, but neither is a movie of monsters and Americans still do not have your Godzilla: the only thing they have done is put a costume to September 11.SPOILER: at least in the of Bong Joon-Ho they explained the origin of the bug and not, do not bother me at all to not explain a hell in the movie end modest SPOILERRealmente, Cloverfield looks like Transformers and despite being little what we see is amazing, but always from the point of view of the camera that records the day in hell and clearIt moves quite. Level "credibility" has that must have a blockbuster (what is) pulling less (that level of the military launching a missile with the kids before dodging him and my mother), but take seriously. Too much. And that is because we have a movie "characters" in The Host, or as said the great Jordi Costa in El País this morning: a movie of love.Not counting the end credits the movie stays in 1970s and peak minutes (but staying to listen "to them", are wonderful) and the first fifteen and pico are absolutely inconsequential given the ellipsis of the tape, so that pulling an entire Act to submit to only children has a goal: sell (exquisite) soundtrack from the moviewith music by Gorillaz. dolls or Coconut Records, Kings of Leon will also sell.</body>
</review>
