<review author="Txapulin" title="Monstruoso" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie that perfectly meets the expectations created by the best campaign of marketing in recent years. Millimetric calculated to make us have a good time.</summary>
	<body>You are going to submit a tape which her we found at the site that was once Central Park. This is the shocking approach (although not so original, remember that the Blair Witch Project) from the film with the best promotional campaign of the past years. The result perfectly meets expectations. It offers exactly what the trailer promises: a giant monster destroys New York, while all simulates to be shot with a homemade camera and without mounting, with the result that would be if it were recorded in several shots in a single night.The result is completely calculated to be realistic and credible, and at the same time is able to maintain the tension and that the Viewer is not lost, telling us the history which is the case, with several plot surprises excellently stowed in the plot, including a secondary narration perfectly embedded in the Assembly and that offers a dimension added to the story and an excellent epilogue.I dare not say that the film is revolutionary, because I don't think he believed school (although there are [REC] Balagueró i Diary of the Dead of Romero to take me the opposite), but yes excellently leverages the latest advances in digital cinema to offer something never seen until now, at least not in this way. We also have a product that already input is more than a film. Thanks to the different viral websites that have emerged on the movie, we know where it comes the monster and other elements involved in the story (the oil company, the Japanese drink, the Group antisitema, etc.), things that the same format of the film can not be explained within the context of the same. Total, a very enjoyable film, that makes fit perfectly the commercialism with original, and approach accompanied by an interesting phenomenon of viral internet marketing.</body>
</review>
