<review author="Rafa Delgado" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is really entertaining and know create tension in the Viewer, but more based lightning and Thunder that no script.</summary>
	<body>The terrorist attacks of September 11, 2001 in New York marked a before and then in all the senses, that there no doubt. The infamous war of Viet Nam was the first unfortunate event in broadcast almost in direct on televisions around the world, but the boom in communications at the end of the 20th century and the way in which lived the nightmare and unfortunate attacks against the twin towers, radically changed the concept. Now everyone had the power to immortalize a moment at your fingertips: video cameras of all types, digital cameras that allow recording of video, mobile phones with camera. Therefore, when the whole world saw how over three thousand people were killed brutally live and live, while New York widespread panic, which were closer to the event not bowed to stay in front of the TV, but grabbed their cameras, took to the streets, and began recording.From this very personal point of view, the new creation of producer j. j. Abrams, Cloverfield is threatened. A disaster on a large scale from the point of view of one of those people that run to save his own life, and the most loved. Abrams wanted to recreate the atmosphere of sadness and confusion to a disaster as Dantesque as the 11-S in his new film. This new "" audiovisual culture that not only he explodes, but the vast majority of television news and news programmes, not to say all have realized that something with potential, and above all is a macabre morbid, it sells. The "we are live" to a monumental disaster.But fortunately Cloverfield is fiction, and narrates the "typical" attack on New York (how not) of a giant monster godzilliano (although of Cloverfield, Godzilla, little), from that point of view: from the eye of a domestic camera of a chavalada which the bug bitter them feast of farewell of his best friend. To as The Blair Witch Project. To the REC (is curious how two very similar projects have coincided in you time in this way without one having proof of the existence of the other).Unfortunately, Cloverfield is far from the excellent film by Jaume Balagueró and Paco Plaza. It is really entertaining and know create tension in the Viewer, but more based lightning and Thunder that no script. It also has a few visual effects, although discrete, met to perfection and are extremely realistic. Not to mention the wonderful sound effects, that if they are not the Oscar next year, would have to be something punishable by death. But despite all this, the script is bullshit, and (more or less correctly interpreted) characters, four subnormaloides whose decisions are the height of absurdity. No one in their right mind would accept entering in ground zero of a catastrophe, and more if there is a giant bug there milling, to save the girl in your friend whose state of health is unknown. In addition to fuck, which carries the camera not the loose while you have the bug before and go it to eating!Very little credible the film in that aspect, but you know, there's no business like show business, the show must go on, and all that stuff.Visually it is not bad, although us perdemos wonderful levels thanks to the ironic mode on, pulse surgeon that carries all the time the camera, ironic mode off. It moves, moves a lot, and there are times when despair. Now I would highlight a level of those that are for framing, if not because it is a spoiler as a cathedral. Good going, a track: Kiss.Confirmed Cloverfield II, by the way, that to know how call her (and will continue, because it is more closed than Lynn Redgrave at the hands of Woody Allen).And speaking of holder films, those responsible for that "translate" titles in this country, have once again demonstrated his incompetence: where is will get this monstrosity of Monstruoso muchachada, if the film is called field of CLOVERS? Very simple: is Monstruous was the phrase. promotional Word the tagline on one of the zillion American progress posters that came out of the movie (and all are equal), and one of these guys thought that it was the title of the movie, and the rest is history. is as if to Rec her they entitled in USA Living Fear!To piss and no echar gota. INCOMPETENCE, as well, in uppercase.</body>
</review>
