<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Alien vs Predator 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is shit on a stick, without argument, without effects, nothing worthwhile.</summary>
	<body>If I am sincere this second delivery nor called me the slightest attention, and has been a partner which has nearly pushed me to see her, he didn't have an excessive by the sequel curiosity, although it is true that although I followed the project, I've done almost of mere observer, without get involved therein, and want the most minimum see something embodied on screen.Without a doubt, make a sequel to a "Crossover" (mixture of two sagas) with two such emblematic characters of the FOX sci-fi film seemed a sovereign memez but friends, the box office manda. And well, repeats the same formula, flavored with cinema entertainment or action, so you can call both forms and it is very nearly the same, so we have the aliens without Lieutenant Ripley (replaced by a mother, military profession with a girl in his charge, hehe as "Aliens"), look at her I have been throwing less during the hour and 20 min. footage and on the other hand the predator, what happens, that more than one them was budget?In the middle to a bunch of suckers who wish that they loaded sooner are simple, stupid and mindless to the more not being able, go of those when you are loading you say!SIIII FIESSSTA! that look that stupid tiparracos made in this kind of films, there is never any that you feel more or less identified, apart that I do not know very well why reason, much of the tape reminded me to "Transformers" from Michael Bay, silly boy, aunt buenorra, bugs, and other crap, only missing the "Rubick cube".The argument should be in half page, also his screenplay (in the rest of surplus page), the actors are to kill them (hehe) and refiriendome to the "superoriginal" phrase of the poster, where if that could hear my screams (or almost) has been in the room, cursing, first to my companion, and then all those morons that spent their money to see the first part and we have punished with this second, as well as in the fight scenes, among so much darkness (perhaps to protect the tape of Screeners) fails to appreciate nothing, and one out of every scene more confusing fight that.In short: Is shit on a stick, without argument, without effects, nothing worthwhile.</body>
</review>
