<review author="Bloody Will" title="Hacia rutas salvajes" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that moves, moves and keeps your heart shrunk as a pass.</summary>
	<body>Sometimes one is easier to give its opinion on a film that has holes on all sides. A very bad performance, an infumable script or a story that has no where to take can be criticized. The trouble is when you find yourself with a film that excites, moves and keeps your heart shrunk as a. I would not know how to describe my reaction to 'Wild routes towards': I cried like a child with its history and I have not been able to take off the eyes to so much visual wonder. One of the best films Hollywood has released in the last half of the year and it has inexplicably been ignored by nominations to the Oscars with others who deserved it a lot less.Some will already have its Director as the main reason to attend its screening. Sean Penn is characterized by extremely intimate movies with palpable obsession towards human relations. This form of filmmaking tends to sometimes fall into excessively boring footage and stories that extend the drama, but in 'Towards wild routes' Penn has managed to avoid that 140 minutes become a nightmare with sincerity, simplicity and stimulating the senses to the maximum extent.Based on a best-selling novel of Jon Kracauer written in 1996, Penn gives form to a script which tells the life and thoughts of Chris McCandless, played by Emile Hirsch, a young man of 23 years who after graduating from the University decides to leave everything, including hiper-absorbentes parents (William Hurt and Marcia Gay Harden), to go slipping up to Alaska. Along the way you will cross with a pair of hippies, a farmer (Vaughn) and an old man (Hollbrook), to change the life. It is paradoxical that rebelling to the non-conformism into a default type of society is so sad consequences.Unlike other biopics, Penn uses a narrative structure that situated to Chris at his final destination, Alaska, and is interspersed with the different stages of the voyage with the voice-over of a delivered to form sister of the protagonist. This way of mixing so many resources may seem confusing but to me I found it more effectively. The past, present and future of Chris is joining as a puzzle to explain something so illogical as leave a life of money to live as a beggar backpacking. Those who hate both temporary jump course, will suffer a continuous torture.Another of the strong points of the film is his photography because as good road-movie landscapes are essential, and them here all together: the cruelest city, the most impressive beaches, more blue lakes and white whiter Alaska winter. The only thing that gives me doubts about 'Towards wild routes' is if its director not abused excessively from them, and the 140 minutes that lasts the history.Many spectators will seem pretentious way of drawing the most natural America, I've only noticed that some scenes are stretched unnecessarily because of both sky and forest, but never can tell the activist nº 1 for natural resources as is Sean Penn that he cut in the outer planes.The big surprise of the film, and something not expected is an Emile Hirsch is coming out, although the script by Penn has everything to make the kid look, as well as all those who surround him. William Hurt and the later Marcia Gay Harden left their mark as parents reckless and abusive, although his scenes are well few and leave without tying very well the theme of parents of Chris. Penn avoids show the agony of these to not interfere with the path of the protagonist, which is a broken link a near perfect plot.The side are luxury and there is where the movie has scratched its only nomination for the Oscars. Hal Holbrook displayed on screen and live the best 15 minutes of the tape. His dialogues with Hirsch produced a tenderness that transcends the screen and must confess that along with the farewell of the populous hippie, the relationship between elder and backpacking provoked an irrepressible River of tears that now makes my hair stand on end.I not forget the soundtrack and an Eddie Vedder that carries me next to Chris. For me, another success when put me the ball in the throat.Note that 'Wild routes towards' has seemed a peliculón, and is that who have passed that critical point where you upload more hopelessly to the wheel of life, see Cris courage and courage Fuera de serie, arriving directly at the head and above all to the heart. Excellent drama of a director so Maverick as its protagonist, but that many are them atragantará with both landscape made in USA.</body>
</review>
