<review author="Yul B." title="Mortadelo y Filemón: Misión Salvar la Tierra" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More fun than the first. For fans of Mortadelo y Filemón.</summary>
	<body>Change of director to this sequel it has sat well. I'm not saying that Javier Fesser is bad (because it is not much less) nor that wasn't the right director to address the first adventure of Mortadelo y Filemón in movies with real actors. This charismatic filmmaker was able to give his personal stamp (and for that they chose) to a first film foray into flesh and blood of these beloved Comic characters that came out of the bogeyman of Francisco Ibáñez and many hours of fun made happen to several generations of Spanish (and guiris) in other countries. And then the taquillazo.But precisely for this reason, for wearing that particular and characteristic touch that always accompanies Fesser his works, 'La Gran Aventura de Mortadelo y Filemón' escrow resembled too aesthetically one of his best-known works, and that to me I love, 'El Milagro de p. Tinto'. This small detail stripped somehow the prominence, the essence, spirit and personality Ibáñez has given to his most famous creatures.I believe that Miguel Bardem has been able to better capture that same essence, spirit and personality of mort and Phil, and has managed to direct a sequel more in tune to the aesthetics and the modus operandi as crazy with serving this pair of agents of the T.I.A. and company.This installment of suggestive title, ' Mortadelo y Filemón. Mission: Save the Earth ', it is more fun and entertaining than the first, and has more pace and is much more understandable on dialogues than the original (still I remember what I had trouble understanding the sentences of some actors such as Benito Pocino, Janfri Coronado or Eduardo Gómez script). A succession of comical gags enough good made public (mainly adolescents) will drop many sincere and spontaneous laughter in my session who had faith in that the 'facelift' directional had been for the better. But, in addition to the change of director, other factors make this patriotic film a pleasant entertainment. The plot that has fuck from here and there of the collection of published comics so far, well written and told, is one of them: the planet is facing a big threat: a great drought that end with all of us and that will try to take advantage of the evil Botijola (Carlos Santos) to convert the drink that bears his name in the replacement of the water. To do this you will have his henchmen to eliminate the water reserves left in the Tierra.Un attack in the MoMA, where the best undercover agents of the world met to try to expose the evil Botijola, which does not come (Edu Soto) Mortadelo y Filemón (Pepe Viyuela) because they do not speak, just with all of them. Two disastrous the T.I.A. agents will now have to put their differences aside and reunited again to save the land of the great drought and to protect your machine from the rain, invented to recover the lost water and teacher effect (Janfri Coronado).However, effect is kidnapped by Botijola, but soon get hide the pieces of his invention in different historical moments, using the time machine. Mortadelo y Filemón will travel to the past to recover valuable invention, with the invaluable help of Ophelia (Berta Ojea) and following the orders of the Super (Mariano Venancio).The film is arguably set with as much regularity, order and harmony that you passed in a sigh. And that desire to not end is a good sign in view of infumables tapes of endless end walk through our cinemas.The special effects are another point in favor of the tape. In 'La Gran Aventura de Mortadelo y Filemón' the FX were a very important element to move with fidelity to the big screen the implausible and fancy cakes, devices and other almost surreal elements that abound in this pair of agents calamities comiqueras comics. And, as I mentioned earlier, wore the label Fesser, they were the protagonists of the film, so any fictional character might have been victims of them, gave equal that they weren't Mortadelo and Filemón. However, the special effects of this sequel are, for my taste, better than its original, excellent, not only by your invoice, visibly different appearance, but by being more at the service of our protagonistsmaking this surrealism which I talked about appear up to normal and recognizable.And, finally, the change of actor for mort has been a brutal hit. Edu Soto gives a dimension and a few nuances to the role many broader and more likely than Benito Pocino. Pocino was a limited interpreter, who did not know (or could not) get the amount of juice that has the character while Soto so grab by the horns and manages to bring to light the true personality of mort, the master of disguise.Although not only Soto is you should congratulate on her work. As regards the main that repeated, Pepe Viyuela improves quite on his previous performance, perhaps because it is more mature as an actor and appreciates his chemistry with Edu. Mariano Venancio (the Super) and Janfri Coronado (effect) are more subdued and give the right touch to his characters, without exaggerations; Berta Ojea (Ophelia) continues his good online.New, Carlos Santos (Botijola), 'Los Hombres de Paco' Povedilla, makes a credible evil despite their possession of good people. And Alex O'Dogherty (Todoquisque, Arturo Cañas in 'Camera Cafe') represents a hilarious henchman. The appearance of Carmen Ruiz (Toribia) as the sister of mort is priceless.Only a drawback would be the film, good rather two, which do not depend on the work and effort of the director or actors from the rest of the technical and artistic team: first, that it is virtually impossible that the viewer can appreciate in the same way that makes it the reader of comic book series Mortadelo y Filemón the amount of details jets but ingenious Ibáñez left corner or at the bottom of their bullets.Bardem has worked in that I take account of them, but would require a double session of the same movie to capture details such as, e.g., the micro from one news presenter caught to the flap of the jacket with the clothing clip, a mobile phone with a raspberry as headset, curious signs as the 'Jilton' Hotel or all almost one hundred announcing ' 3000 bathtubs to 3 euros'all that is and takes the 'pescadillac', or a background vocals who answers to a seller top-blanket that offers precisely on a beach the pirated copy of this same film which we are talking about saying 'I me her have already downloaded'. And this is only 1% of other things that I have not mentioned and others that I have not seen or heard for sure.And the second, very obvious, that this film is for absolute stalwarts of Mortadelo y Filemón. If you are not I recommend that you spare you paste the entry because all she (I mean the movie) you will seem insane. PS: I'm still missing the two hairs of the head of the 'head'; and the real beard of effect, not those somethings pelajos given to Coronado.</body>
</review>
