<review author="Bloody Will" title="John Rambo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Rambo is 100%, an action of the earlier film.</summary>
	<body>20 Years have passed since John Rambo appeared for the last time on our screens. I remember perfectly that summer when everyone ran to the capital to see Stallone by pressing the tape of the hair and distributing wood on a single premise: was the best and the only one that could save the situation. 20 Years have passed, and for Rambo, nothing has changed. Let you in the door of the film claims of seeing a movie with deep script, with outstanding performances and an impeccable cinematography. Rambo is Rambo, and give us the opposite is to deceive us. With an aesthetic of serie B and almost camera in hand, Stallone dispenses with script to mount on three sentences a succession of massacres on innocent and the execution of the villains. And what we wanted?, then that. That is 'John Rambo'.The synopsis is simple: when a group of peace activists intend to cross the dangerous river of Burma to reach a village and distribute medicines take hand of John Rambo (Stallone), alone with his boat can guarantee a good trip. Does but once the evil guerrillas raze the village and capture the volunteers, Rambo will be the only one who can rescue them with a group of mercenarios.¿Os reminds something?, because Yes, igualita that 'Rambo III': the prota is the specialist, the prota is the only and there is no one else, why the army of go to know where, and from the hand of the actor Ken Howard, begs his speech. In this sequel to Rambo at least does not put any hits and shows that you will progress. A pity we lack Lieutenant Trautman (Richard Crenna), which is only seen in a flashback-dream of Rambo that puts the willies &hellip;.The nostalgic, which burst the video store to base rent hundreds of times the saga, it will enchant. It has everything for what you have cried over these years, and Stallone knows had to follow this same path, because that would of contrary the public is you lay on top. I must confess that a 'Rocky' they changed the life and evolved it in the latest installment, but John have not touched you or plush, that still retains.With script, direction and production of Stallone, character eats all the scenes of the film and with just three lines and a couple of memorable statements the film achieves its objective, and that is to entertain who goes to see the immortal Rambo. For the greater glory of the myth, the footage is so little that it is impossible to bore you: 1 hour and 19 minutes, in which does not rest more than 30 seconds and in which dialogs not going beyond 4 lines. Everything happens very fast, so that does not explain where the volunteers come from, does not explain the reason for the presence of villains military in Burma and not explained where Rambo has been, but gives more: bodies are falling one after the other.The great innovation of this sequel is without doubt the violence and harshness with which our protagonist gets rid of his enemies. I'm not saying that previous ones were a tale of Disney's, but you can check the amount of blood is multiplied by 10 and the images are much more explicit. If one of the bad guys gets too to the camera, do not hesitate: Rambo will open from top to bottom, and this time sees everything everything. We have one of the film more gore this year, and Jigsaw does not come out anywhere.I hardly speak of its actors. Stallone is who and the character is not going to now what Jane Austen. The girl is Julie Benz, and from that left 'Angel' only have seen in this type of roles it: inocentona and weak, as in the series 'Dexter', where currently lavished.What the hell, I liked and pretty. Not because it is a human or social background excited (that already saw him last week in Sean Penn), is that it is going bad jokes entertainment, a scene of almost 10 minutes with submachine gun and a girl to save Thai small cab ** s. Rambo to 100%, it is this action of the old movie to 100%. It's Stallone maintaining the essence of the character without touching one iota. It is as it would have been there always, in the jungle, waiting for what it brought again.Refrain addicted to the cinema and lovers of Wim Wenders. This is the opposite. This is &hellip; RAMBO!&hellip; and has returned!</body>
</review>
