<review author="Bloody Will" title="Juno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ideal characters, a round script and a plot that connects.</summary>
	<body>It is amazing how the simplest ideas end up being the most endearing films. As if it were already a tradition, every year we have veered away from the main prizes for the powerful hipermillonarias productions for the independent film industry. I remember that when 'Pulp Fiction' entered the nominations 14 years ago something made me frown. Now, the absence of a tape as 'Juno' could be considered a crime.Coup of heart and much dialogue, 'Juno' stands as the perfect this year, and no comedy because it makes you have you in the seat or saucy jokes are more clever. This synchronized combination of ideal characters, a round script and a plot that connects is far superior to a sound of laughter.There are two stars in this film, and that you be no doubt. The first is Ellen Page, whose performance is virtually of outstanding &hellip;, but the other Star comes out on-screen and is everything. Diablo Cody, the new sense among the writers, has drawn a world so round as closed, that of Juno, a young irreverent, maleducada, know-it-all but whose positivity connects it to the first with the Viewer. This debut earned him a nomination for the Oscars, and what you want to tell you: more than deserved.Juno (Page), a 16 year old girl passionate about rock discovers that she is pregnant with a boy that does not even have a stable relationship (Michael Cera). After announcing the news to his father (J.K. Simmons), Juno decides to give his son to a newly married couple with an enviable environment (Jason Bateman and Jennifer Garner), which retain a somewhat special relationship &hellip;.Stating that I think the comparisons are odious, but Juno is the teen version of what was his rookie season Veronica Mars. The girl is a real verbal submachine gun that has answer for absolutely everything, and the irony is much of the conversation. I don't know if there is someone aged 16 with so much maturity and personality out of series, but these qualities, which can lead to rejection of who sees it, has an unexpected result, and that is a profound complicity with the protagonist of unusual situation.Why not seem a boldness that says that the direction from Jason Reitman is basically circumstantial. I'm not saying that it is bad, is that simply it sticks flat to level in the excellent script for Cody, and think that not is has separate much of the way this has been checked. With a profusion of flat media and a technique more than acceptable did not lack that Reitman, should set itself too many frills for the film secured its place among the best. I repeat endlessly: the script is everything.Those that are unpayable are the cast of actors of the film, which seem to live the moment of their careers. Ellen Page went on tiptoe by ' X-Men 3 &prime;, and would come 'Hard Candy' to show that the girl is someone to take into account in coming years. In 'Juno' Page is just out. I guess to screenwriter and actress sharing nights in white and some that another Cup (the girl is already 21 years old) because the symbiosis between the two is impressive. His performance is paramount to wanting to Juno, and that the character commits more than reprehensible actions for some.The rest of side appear shortly, but good. J.K. Simmons is the compressive father of Juno, and tenderness between both players passed on the screen. Jason Bateman, very frequent to comedies holds the type, but Jennifer Garner is in the role of Vanessa Loring one of the best of his career. Not only end up loving Juno, is that above all the happiness in the world you want a character that could to be unfriendly. Michael Cera outboard what better do: be a lovable pringao.If home contaramos the decisions of Juno without knowing her, the character would be negligible. With simplicity, cotidaneidad and emotion with which Diablo Cody tells the story of Juno, it is impossible not to love. Perhaps some see a message with moralina USA in history, but for me goes unnoticed that I absorbed completely the protagonist. With a soundtrack lame ** da, 'Juno' is one of those few films that should be seen in this era pre-Oscars, when we know who is and who does not.If in the adjoining room shooting out of the submachine gun of tite Stallone, in this, the bullets go direct to the heart and the head.</body>
</review>
