<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="No es país para viejos" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A monster from the film, an almost perfect movie that stays in the retina hours after having been seen.</summary>
	<body>Reaches our charts a few weeks of the Oscar ceremony, one of the strongest candidates to win. "Isn't country for old men", the last genius of the Coen brothers, obviously boasts no less than eight nominations, including that of best film.Based on the eponymous book by Cormac McCarthy, the film puts us in a time of change. In this new West no longer bandits or outlaws, if not drug traffickers armed to the teeth, and the small U.S. villas are no longer peaceful places in which the Sheriff can walk unarmed, now need a gun for his own safety. In one of these villages, in the State of Texas, Llewelyn Moss (played by a Josh Brolin who lives its second golden age) is done with a Briefcase full of money which is among a handful of bodies caused by an unsuccessful sale of drugs. Without knowing it, thus draws the attention not only of the Group of traffickers to whom belongs this money, but also of the murderous psychopath Anton Chigurt (apotheosis Javier Bardem) and Sheriff Bell (Tommy Lee Jones). Thus begins a brutal persecution without truce, which will not stop at nothing, 8–10 of blood, pain, and death.Let me say before we start: very, very well have to do other nominees to snatch some of the statuettes at this authentic marvel.Because "No country for old men is" it is film with capital letters. The first minutes of the film already warn the viewer of what is about to see. The voiceover of a depressed Tommy Lee Jones accompanies a succession of various levels of the desert, real pictures of the sunrise in the arid fields in which shrubs are shaken by the wind. When the camera at the end moves, it does so slowly, to show us the arrest of a mysterious Bardem in charge of a police of the people. Continues playing the voice of Lee Jones mixing with ululations of the breeze, and the car moves away from the scene. All this at a very leisurely, without background music, elegant and sober pace. And so, one realizes that we are faced with a new and true colossal of the Coen brothers; that "Is No country for old" intends to join the group formed by the master "the man that wasn't there" or "Death entre las Flores", away from the easy comedies to which we were accustomed in recent years. There is no shortage which already doubted the ability of managers to return to surprise to the public. This film should serve all them to dispel doubts, which not only has sufficient quality to belong to this select group of works of art, if not even likely to overcome them.Because, I repeat, what has created the tandem of Directors is a monster of the film, an almost perfect movie that stays in the retina hours after having been seen.Just for its technical and artistic level, "Is No country for old" is longer with the label of masterpiece. The Coen brothers prove once more that make better use of the panoramic format, offering impossible levels in every inch of what appears on screen is essential to compose what are authentic paintings. All without exception, since the more bombastic level to the more intimate (Bardem washing their hands in the sink of the Police Office), are of great beauty. And obviously, fused together with a sophisticated and intelligent use of the camera able to almost become one secondary protagonist of the story. Pay attention to the sequence of the hotel.But even better it works everything is in their argument and mix of genres. Because "Is No country for old" is, after all, a film of the West (1). He is simply a thrilling Chase in which three gunmen (and any more that it joins the party) they seek to seize its prey, be it a suitcase of money, one death in the box, or one criminal less in the streets.What is surprising, is that on a basis so (seemingly) simple, the film achieves propose doubts and questions, and very difficult to answer (or is perhaps its title the best response?), both moral and social levels. What would you do? Who is really good? So how can you trust a stranger?. do something to prevent that crazy as Chygurt deambulen by our streets?Oh, and Javier Bardem outboard its role. Not only it is impossible to find out the true nationality of the actor (his English is much better than many Americans), if not his character of authentic AWE. See how decides if a person lives or dies, with that look of crazy thirsty of blood, gives authentic chills. The Acme, the gas station scene, with such terrible dialogue between him and the owner of the same.(1)The same Joel Coen says that "is as close as we are never do an action film".</body>
</review>
