<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Arma Fatal (Hot Fuzz)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Attractive, witty, and surprisingly entertaining and fun; an excellent and ingenious portrait and parody of the film police, much higher than the average of parodies that proliferate both today and are simply in an I want to and I can not.</summary>
	<body>Fatal weapon (Hot Fuzz): you have to see, that pleasantly surprised I took with fatal gun. It was time that I not laughed so much and so a taste with a film of these features. Hilarious - from start to finish - English parody of intelligent humor laden with references to the action-horror film. He paid tribute, and at the same time laughs at them and themselves. Difference with other parodies of the type Epic movie, date movie, or Scary movie 4. While these did you vomit and retorzerte in the seat (less evil that do not exceed the 85 minutes), weapon fatal glad see her. I had read good things about it, but did not expect me to see the crazy and hilarious comedy that would be. After the super hit had Edgar Wright with his particular parody on movies from zombies on Zombies Party, now comes the turn of parody over American cinema (than irony because the producing and directing is English) with the typical police film full of explosions and pyrotechnics so characteristic and this type of tape Hollywood. All minutes of weapon fatal, exude English humor on all four sides, in exposed situations, both the archetype of the characters created, all perfectly defined and interpreted. Escorted to the script by the actor in this story, Simon Pegg, both manage to form a perfect match when you enter the amount of gags and jokes abound in fatal weapon, and raise the adjective of prank to unsuspected heights. The film revolves around a British superpolicía who is moved to a seemingly peaceful London town. But much more the reality, the small town will become a box of surprises, with all kinds of neighbors and eccentric and most hilarious situations. The director and screenwriter, echoes of all topics and clichés of the genre of action for perpetrating one of the greatest tinker in 2007. We will not only find the more English humor, but that there is also room for the absurd humor (more common in the film of the couple Abrahams-Zucker), jokes, gags, surreal situations, and parodies of other tapes of action as called Bodhi or Bad boys II. Apart from being a blend of action and comedy, especially comedy, we have a good part of parody to horror, type Scream and be lo que hicisteis. So we will see the thousand times seen masked killer who is annihilating "poor" people of the town. And here is where the director pointing somewhat; as we already enjoyed Zombies party, Edgar Wright shows us scenes of blood and gore as they should be; well explicit. In this way, lovers of the genre, which I certainly am, see satisfied our concerns resolved with the murders will occur. Thus, we will have our good dose of offal and blood thanks to hack, desmembramientos, death and various crushing; all this seasoned a good comic basis. As for the script, eccentricities full course does waters at any time, keeping the expectation in the viewer despite two hours of footage that has the film. This is due largely to the frantic Assembly that has the tape, recalling moments (in the English and furious) to the works of the always controversial Guy Ritchie. On the other hand, everything bad lies those responsible for its distribution in Spain and the director of dubbing. Firstly, the Spanish title is overused and thousand times seen, HORRIFYING. If the head of marketing aims to attract the public with that title you ready. And then there is the awful dubbing that accompanies the work. If you have the opportunity to see it in g.w. don't hesitate. In short, attractive, witty, and surprisingly entertaining and fun; an excellent and ingenious portrait and parody of the film police, much higher than the average of parodies that proliferate both today and are simply in an I want to and I can not. With a very equitable humor, since some easy jokes even more intelligent, biting and satirical humor come together in fatal weapon; a film that leaves us an excellent taste in the mouth. It seems that the tandem formed by Wright and Pegg continues to operate.</body>
</review>
