<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Annie Hall" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>From the care and full script up witty dialogs laden with a brilliant sarcasm and subtle irony Alvy us spit, make the tape an overwhelming statement of intent.</summary>
	<body>Annie Hall: excellent x-ray about human behaviour and romantic relationships between men and women. Annie Hall was the Catapult enabling the rise to fame of the today master Woody Allen in the seventh art. Annie Hall turned out to be a film jewel unprecedented and Woody Allen was the kick-off of his extensive career and one of the tapes celebrated, award-winning and acclaimed of his filmography. For Allen, was his first Oscar as best director in 1977, as well as the Oscar for best original screenplay co-written with Marshall Brickman and with certain autobiographical touches. Allen was also nominated for best actor for his performance in Annie Hall. Nevertheless, Allen even went to collect the awards who had won his film, and still failed to attend until the 2003 no the Oscar ceremony on the grounds of a tribute to New York City. In addition to these two Oscar, Annie Hall also won the statuette for best actress, thanks to the performance of a splendid Diane Keaton; and the Oscar for the best film from 1977. Annie Hall, talks about the relationship between Annie and Alvy, their different stages of falling in love and passion, and the subsequent inaction and routine.Alvy is a comedian forties, neurotic and sickly, with thousands of obsessions and panic to compromise after two frustrated divorces. Annie is younger than him, is pretty and insecure, and not know he wants to devote his life. Through different temporary changes in narration, we discover what happens with his love story. Woody Allen is allowed the luxury of playing and break the canons established by the code of film and narrative, introducing dozens of flashbacks, interactuaciones of Alvy directly with the viewer thus seeking complicity, scenes of animation (tribute to snow white), a division of the screen for interpolation of messages between the protagonists, the physical and spiritual unfolding of Annie when you don't want to make love with Alvy, dreams, images with subtitles etc. The truth is that the viewing of Annie Hall is a delight. From the care and full script up witty dialogs laden with a brilliant sarcasm and subtle irony Alvy us spit, make the tape an overwhelming statement of intent. As always in the Allen characters, include obsessions and tics of the human being. He is a genius at capturing all the obsessions and neurismas of a maniac as it is himself, and knows how to combine perfectly the scathing and ironic humor in the style of Billy Wilder, with surrealism and brilliance of the film silent Chaplin. The work, narrates the difficulties of personal relationships, moral obsessions about love, sex, friendship and fidelity of the couple, the doubts to a reality that we do not want to arrive and therefore on the emotional immaturity. Annie Hall is reflected to perfection all irrational romantic relationships that may suffer the human being, recreating with appalling sincerity every day of a loving relationship, with all its phases; Because love is not always beautiful as paints it Hollywood, and Allen draw it in Annie Hall with a strength and passivity is concerned. After some thirty works in his filmography, Annie Hall is destined to become the cornerstone of his entire career, the pillar basic and most important of his films, and one tape key of the 1970s. The film was shot mainly in New York and briefly in Los Angeles. It is well known by all, the love that Allen granted to the city of New York and as always reflected in his films. In short, a romantic and dramatic comedy that will go down in history its structure and narrative and address resources by both the wonderful script and interpretations of the two protagonists. Finally, just me analysis with the last sentences of the film, which I believe condense perfectly all stated above: well. that's more or less what I think about human relations, do you know? They are totally irrational. and mad. and absurd. but. I guess we continue keeping them because most need them. Big Woody, large. Score: 8.5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
