<review author="Emilio Martín Luna" title="Los Crímenes de Oxford" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is entertaining, you do not get bored, it lasts little, but is a feeling of disappointment when sales of cinema, as if what you have been counting is irrelevant, you forget it that same night.</summary>
	<body>Murders, this is the title of the novel on which this film is based. With this title, this director and a good deal, it is conceivable that, the less we will see a good movie. If in my previous criticism spoke of the label of the Coens, Alex de la Iglesia has been characterized by give a style to his films, something Dantesque, ironic and with black humor. In this, his latest creation the crimes of Oxford, we find a Director who renounces his style and makes us a more formal film, trying to catch the touch of intrigue by Hitchcock and British mystery film. Although some characters are cartoony, it is a different Church, and this is the first big failure of his film. I say first, because it has many more, the second and very serious is the casting, Elijah Wood, Mr Frodo for friends, has the same charisma that Jesulín in Cannes, deadpan, little credible happens throughout the film with face of surprised (enormous eyes, seems to receive a sartenazo in the face), open a door I surprised, lame bus me amazed, open unyogourth. that scare!I think good actor, for more details see Everything is Illuminated Liv Schreiber, but this film does not provide you the type, and is not the most appropriate physical. In fact, when faced with their female partners, Leonor Watling and Julie Cox have the same chemistry that Mel Gibson and the Pantoja. Leonor is an actress as the top of a pine but its mission in this movie is tontorrón to Elijah, vase we are going, the script treated very badly, and his character is irrelevant. More importantly is Julie Cox but his character is very bad explained by a script that omits much information away from the day the morning Mr Frodo has two females mad for him, and by that he is worth. On the other hand, if a hit is William Hurt, who is having a bad age (although of young not.)but it is a sensational player that gives credibility, and if you see dressed as Guy Fawkes (makes you smile.)(V for Vendetta).The script is quick, nothing explaining, while all the mathematical thinking with reference to Kessler and other authors, it is interesting, can be confusing, and after seeing the end, you think that it could be much better film, perhaps treat the film as logical succession is a good approach, but I think that it gives you many laps things to confuse you and then the result of the equation does not fit you. This sort of thing only is given either to Christopher Nolan, any director malhucho could have done something similar to this film, and Alex de la Iglesia is a great director, for I think that is you should demand more to this film.Despite everything, it is entertaining, you do not get bored, lasts little, but is a feeling of disappointment when sales of cinema, as if what you have been counting is irrelevant, you forget it that same night. Maybe that expectations were high but seeing the director and the title of the novel, the following figure of the logical series would be good movie, and trístemente is not the case.</body>
</review>
