<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Entre copas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An intelligent comedy achieved its biggest trump card when not to fall in the uncouth and easy joke, but in a few dialogues very elaborate and mixed with surreal situations where it is impossible to avoid the viewer outlines a smile on his face.</summary>
	<body>Surprise with uppercase I had while watching sideways. The truth is that Alexander Payne had left the bar very high with the great concerning the satirical Election and Schmidt, but with his last feature film to date (not counting their mini history of Paris je t'aime), has managed to seal a magnificent tragicomedy with delicious dialogues sharp shaped darts Payne shoots relentlessly. With 2 Golden Globes and an Academy Award for best screenplay adapted from 2004 behind him, sideways (2004 indie film) is a breath of fresh air that is both appreciated given the avalanche of American commercial cinema where we left over shots and explosions. Simply with a brilliant script, and a chosen cast perfectly, it is demonstrated that can sign one of the best films of 2004. A smart and made comedy for intelligent people, achieved its biggest trump card when not to fall in the uncouth and easy joke, but in a few dialogues very elaborate and mixed with surreal situations where it is impossible to avoid the viewer outlines a minimum smile on his face. Through the wine spots in California, we are witnessing a road movie of unsuspected destiny. Initially as a singles trip fun and horny, happens to result in a tragicomedy of second chances, and these young people already lost, farewell trip with particular emphasis to true friendship. In between cups, director lodged two completely opposite characters and through the exchange of ideas or opinions get in a smooth manner and resorting to more ironic and sometimes black humor, close a bittersweet comedy really nice. From the first minutes, you acknowledge the strong magnetism of the film, which inadvertently you just you going hooked little by little and you want to only see that it is going to happen in the next scene, and as her will solve our sympathetic protagonists. The Quartet of actors is fabulous, protruding a brilliant Paul Giamatti as failed and divorced novelist lover of good wine Pinot, and seeking only elegance and good taste of a good bottle of wine, instead of a woman. Then we have his opposite Thomas Haden Church, an actor friend about to marry where you will use the trip as a last glimpse of freedom and simply conforms to a cheap Merlot in plastic cup. The female duo complete television Sandra Oh (of Grey Anatomy), as an expert of good wine, single and independent which will go to stop the arms of the actor. And finally, Virginia Madsen, a divorced and insecure if same waitress desperately seeking the attention of an interesting man. Alexander Payne, ironic and master observer of human behavior, get what truly matters: something as simple and always works as the stories and the characters they play, and signed a work about the friendship of two men lost in their respective lives, seeking only a last stroke of luck in life and very different. An excellent emotional story where search at any time the complicity of the audience and play with the sense of humor that most often arises precisely of some tragedy. Highly recommended. Score: 7.5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
