<review author="Dragon negro" title="Monstruoso" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The idea of show special effects through an amateur camera transmits this sense of reality long lost in the film, used already as we are to any type of digital effect.</summary>
	<body>The experiment Cloverfield, consisting of narrating the destruction of New York through the camera of an amateur and under the point of view of some young people who were at full party salda very gratifying way. After so many months of bombarding us with online advertising, the film had become one of the most anticipated of the season, with all that that implies, but this time if that has been at the height of so much anticipation.We are in a farewell party of Rob going to work to Japan the next day. This prologue of the action, although it may do something long, is absolutely necessary to know the characters, their relationships and motivations, and then develop the story once started the attack. Once it begins the destruction, the film progresses at frenetic pace without barely pause.The greatest achievement of the film lies precisely in this massive destruction, the idea of show special effects through an amateur camera transmits this sense of reality long lost in the film, used as as we are to any type of digital effect, it is becoming increasingly more difficult to surprise us and make us feel that what is happening is real. Cloverfield gets that same without having to show the destruction to detail, but with sudden and recuperated, camera movements although it must also be said that there are many more effects, and very good and effective, which in principle could be expected.In the script, one almost was has resigned to accept in every movie have to be the typical love story that moves to the main character and is the central axis of the script. But it is in this case not to bother too much and if something can reproach is as predictable as a dull finish. Cloverfield is a great movie, leaves you stuck to the seat thanks to his stunning images, and even tell us the same story of sacrifice staff in search of true love, at least is told dramatically and manages to achieve that this destruction is taken very seriously. That Yes, go prepared to film because the feeling of dizziness during the film there is no who remove you the.</body>
</review>
