<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Bosque de sombras" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great movie, that despite light bugs script and that constant feeling of "déjà vu", introduces us without problems in the history of these two couples and makes us spend a truly uncomfortable time, which is what you were looking for its director.</summary>
	<body>Again the letter of presentation of a novel director, and again a great movie despite you who gets upset, are faced with a letter for the commendable presentation by the director bilbaino Koldo Serra, which after surprise with his excellent short "The Witch's train" gives us a film full of interest despite some logical defects of an opera prima.The plot of the film we situated somewhere in the 1970s Spain mountain, where arrive two British couples to spend a few days in the middle of the nature and enjoying the tranquility of the landscape. The two couples are different, the older couple formed by Gary Oldman and Aitana Sanchez Gijon is described as the typical couple where the man takes clearly the weight of the relationship, even in a dominant and authoritarian way, instead the youngest pair formed by Paddy Considine and Virginie Ledoyen have constant relationship problems, show two people with little personality evenbeing the male character very deferential and lack of decision and character, something that will be key in the course of history.Everything takes place at a classic pace with precision of Swiss watch in showing us the small and subtle disputes between couples, without ever being embarrassing or forced, without why it no longer exists a latent threat in the form of inhabitants of the village, as that scene in the tavern of the people where the arrival of foreigners is greeted with some suspicion by the clientsespecially by the character of Lluis Homar and his brothers. The discovery by two couples of a girl in the wild in a barn enclosed with food and drink like any animal desatará the dramatic events of history, when the people try to recover the girl and the two couples turn protect it and bring it to the Commissioner of police.The best aspects that we can find in this film are many and varied, with small subtle details that I have said before, as when character Ledoyen wet his shirt leaving transparent its anatomy and enters the tavern in the town, in a scene that causes an uncomfortable feeling in the spectator, that manages to be smooth on the skin of the character of her boyfriend, and as his own lack of character and personality prevent him from dealing with this situation in a different way than shut up.There are brilliant staging elements, as in the debut of Nacho Cerdá, which function somewhat unusual in the Spanish film, and that some Miss, that normally in our country the synonym of good cinema is associated with a shabby appearance and walk at home, which I shall never take it. Its visual appearance is excellent, the Mise en scène previously commented and created by Serra is a formal perfection surprises, even in some complicated levels, where the outside field create a feeling of discomfort and constant threat in that forest that hides many secrets. The work of actors on the other hand is brilliant subtlety, which is creating unrest growing without seem forced or expresiveness, except for this lousy actress, almost always, that it is usually Aitana Sanchez Gijón. on the other hand, soundtrack, is also very remarkable with so few elements and so minimalist sound, as well complete with pictures from the filmanother success more and a are few. All the technical elements shine in this uncomfortable and violent film.The references that are based on this debut of Serra are so obvious that any film lover could mention them with closed eyes, progressive violence of the typical urbanite when found isolated and pressured by a situation to the limit of "Straw dogs" Peckinpah and the intrusion of an external element in a medium as it is the nature of "Deliverance (defence)" by John Boormana medium so as to prove extreme as when the character of Gary Oldman says in this life just what hunters or hunted. And in general a large part of the cinema of the 1970s, in which the hardness and dry and direct style created a certain fear of the Viewer without even borrowed elements of fantasy film, as some reference to "Visitors", the year 1972 film directed by Elia Kazan with James Woods of main character.On the side of the few aspects that do not just function in the film, that even if they are few, any, we find that the script occasionally is not fluent narrative pace that should get (well, or what was left of the script to move it to the screen), due to an excellent first half an hour, then occasionally force any situations in excess. Also some attitude and intentions ambiguous in some scenes, as the rape scene where it does not explain how a woman can leave that they violate to another without flinching, out of fear or for any other aspect, which logically only found one possible explanation on their more rational side of human attitude, without this being fully convincing.The other problem, and perhaps greater, in the history the fact that Serra manufactures his film from the cinephiles, i.e., chooses the path to film on the cinema, and that sometimes when you're too reverential, and not opt for the alternative of making films simply about life, creates an artificial feeling and a constant feeling that because you've seen that before, and I am not referring only to these two films mentioned above, because scenes such as rape or a character without personality or character to take a path so direct and violent already were clearly present in "Straw dogs" with the attitude of Dustin Hoffman, and that sees anyone in a blatant way.Anyway this attitude of violence in crescendo disagree with certain sectors that her have labeled violence without justification, term it carries of if two words completely contradictory to me, as if there were some way to justify any kind of violence. Violence occurs, occurs, there is no justification for anything, and this demonstration of good movies so testifies.In short, a great movie, that despite light bugs script and that constant feeling of "déjà vu", introduces us without problems in the history of these two couples and makes us spend a truly uncomfortable time, which is what you were looking for its director. A story with many crumbs and much more underground substance which seems at first glance. And above all, a sample Spanish Cinema should continue to create a truly interesting industry and not just for wealthy bourgeois and their cries when they see social dramones that are aesthetically and morally reprehensible in many cases.Great debut and a new hope in the form of a breath of fresh air for the film Spanish in general, and of the genus in particular.</body>
</review>
