<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Transformers" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With a job that only offers the scene of action as a source of flattery towards the film, or the interest that can cause the physical attractiveness of the actors, and above all, the actresses, nothing can save the product of the most resounding suspense.</summary>
	<body>On the occasion of DVD output to the new blockbuster Michael Bay today, I have encouraged me to take a look with some sweats cold that roamed my column before the atavistic fear that produce me the majority of films of the Sr.Bay (entire mediocrity except the sympathetic, and little more, two parts of two cops rebels). I have even done the purpose of evading any intention to seek a meaning to the film, and simply get carried away by a forgetful, passenger entertainment and make me disconnect a little both acting, technical analysis or any other type of trial of quality on the film, adding to all my doses of popcorn and coca cola, as it should be with a product as well. As well, despite my good intentions, and really promise that I've tried, again the cold sweat has taken hold of me, this new attack in the form of Michael Bay.Desde film visionando a good start rhythm of pure action, clear that any attempt to find a movie with a minimum sense of the narrative pace would be a utopiashowing Michael Bay with this Transformers what an aspiring filmmaker should never do to learn to tell a story. Everything happens at an abrupt, illogical and absurd, pace with several stories crossed in different parts of the planet just by crossing the most illogical way and impossible to view in recent months on a screen. A plot and narrative confusion which is absolute nonsense.We will never know nor if the script really exists or is a mere excuse for certain more limited than Stallone in a Shakespearean drama actors give rein to his shameful performance. All this is framed in a story that really is ridiculous, about two races of robots alien (the good and the bad, as simple as that) who seek on Earth an object that will give you the ultimate power to some, or will protect the universe to the other.With regard to those actors that teem by the film, say that of course, as good mediocre Hollywood blockbuster (and Yes, I think that it there are good, but not this one in particular) used different actors of various strata to satisfy all kinds of audiences, starting with the beautiful faces of television advertisement essential in any work (sic) of Bay as the beautiful Megan Fox and Rachael Taylor, or his male version with Tyrese Gibson, Josh Duhamel shedding testosterone by every pore of his body (to the delight of the girls), and adding young actors as the promising Shia Lebouf, in this film is perhaps of little salvageable, or actors of some standing that one wonders that demons do in this void, such as John Voight and John Turturro (simply painful East last). Mention apart for that irritating black actor named Anthony Anderson and their corresponding appearance in every movie of this kind. Truth that if Megatron I was going directly to this without think about me so.Little more than add, horrible narration, awful script, stupid dialogues everywhere, and little to save from such nonsense. If we add lasting exaggerated for the little story that counts, we have the most absolute nullity film.In an effort to find something positive, say that Bay is a virtue (perhaps the only), which is to create set pieces of efficacy proven in the action scenes, the best of the film no doubt those last 20 minutes in which the high budget sees really justified their investment, with a clash between robots that remove the hiccups in certain scenes.Ultimately, with a job that only offers the scene of action as a source of flattery towards the film, or the interest that can cause the physical attractiveness of the actors, and above all, the actresses, nothing can save the product of the most resounding suspense. All of this are analyzed from the prism of film as art, or at least decent entertainment, because of course is, there will always be who to a film that is limited to stun the Viewer to avoid that you or even ask what you are showing, you find some appeal. A server.NO.Little more than add, by budget, intentions, and excessive ambition, the worst movie of the year by far.</body>
</review>
