<review author="Illaq" title="United 93" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I have the impression that this is a great movie. I went to the cinema to see something "known". When I left the cinema, he had just seen something "new".</summary>
	<body>Today 5 years of terrible events which refers this film. Especially in North America, it has been discussed much about the advisability or not of the same. However, in view of the reception in the same United States given, it seems obvious that it has arrived in good time, the cinematographic work, both as a reminder of those who died in that sad, puzzling and unforgettable date. United 93 is a film whose outcome we know. There is, therefore, the game of the director with the Viewer to see if it hits the end. Thus, there are only two possibilities. The first, dealing with a sort of docudrama: a notarial acts that occurred dramatic story. The second, something similar to what I understand as the "essence" of cinema: telling a story through predominantly Visual elements. When turn off the lights of the room, almost without more ADO, we find ourselves in a hotel room in which some Muslims pray. They are young. Their faces express tension. Obviously, the Viewer, like them, knows the reason for the tension. But worldwide, the film world, not yet known. It is night. After dawn, young people are directed to the Newark Airport. The route, in a wall, is a great banner: "GOD BLESS AMERICA". "The other" also pray. In my view, the film revolves around a great contrast between the earlier and the later, between the before flight 93 and later, when, traveled the track, there is no turning back. The first scenes show men and women going to theirs. In the background, routines, comments without greater importance, the inner world of each one and that wishes to show to others. There are no heroes; There is neither good nor bad. They are not abstractions or cartoons; just ordinary people. Everything changes, but on the horizon of what predictable. Much of what happened on the plane that carried out this flight is unknown. It is known that at 9: 24 a.m. September 11, 2001, the Commander of the Flight 93 of United Airlines requested confirmation of an alert message that he had received. You know also that two minutes later, the hijackers beat in the cabin and took control of the aircraft, probably killing the pilots and a flight attendant. It is known that to the 03, once passengers broke the door of the cabin, the aircraft, a Boeing 757-222 crashed in a Pennsylvania field, killing all its occupants. Greengrass, based on various sources, including the official report and the testimonies of relatives, follows the course of the report, devoting most of the screen time to the period between the takeoff and the terrible moments immediately prior to the fall of the aircraft. If, at the time of take-off, the pace has been enough to keep the attention: jumps of characters to others, by way of presentation of these anonymous creatures, with their concerns, interests, hopes, more or less minor, by usual, pointing us already masterfully the nature of some of them, the takeoff marks the great transformation. Obviously, see us on the screen still do not know anything, but Greengrass and us Yes and therefore imposes a clear rhythm change. It is as if the race takeoff of the Boeing 757 indicate symbolically this acceleration to make vibrating. The viewer expects that "something happens" familiar, but the director maintains the tension of the spectator, inviting him to participate in fact, doing that you shelved what they know to enter into action, so that it transforms the question as to the "why" for the question "when". Not cease this new pace until the end of the film. The camera, which quickly jumps of characters to others, the natural dialogues, entrecortados, fragments that overlap each other, make copper narration a verisimilitude of reportage, without, however, losing its status as "film". But United 93 not only presents what happened on the plane; also shows the confusion, panic and chaos that attached to all those responsible for air traffic that morning, symbol - as it seems - confusion, panic and chaos which seized the "first world". Maybe the director thought that it would be too much lock ourselves in the aircraft cabin for the 35 minutes that mediate between the abduction of the apparatus and its end. Well because it difficult to maintain the narrative tension in a very minimal environment or perhaps because I would like to give us an overview of what happened that day, employs a narrative strategy always has given game in the film: the story of the "United 93" is the story of all those involved, through continuous and increasingly faster, cuts that come and go from the plane to air traffic controlsthe command of the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) post and the command of the aerospace defense of North America (NORAD) command center, where people that there are (as the first world) trying to understand what is happening. While the camera jumps from one place to another, there are some faces that stand out: Ben Sliney, the director of operations directed at the FAA command center on 11 September 2001, one of nine persons of the FAA and the armed forces of the United States.UU. that are interpreted to themselves in the film; mayor James Fox in the Northeast sector of NORAD, and again asking where are the Chairman and the Vice-Chairman, highlighting the lack of leadership that became apparent that day. Of course, there are images of the two planes that crashed against the twin towers of the World Trade Center, but, in my opinion, I think that marginal notes are that could have been dispensed. In summary, I have the impression that this is a great movie. As I said at the beginning, I went to the cinema to see something "known". When I left the cinema, had just seen something "new" to a certain extent, a sample of cinematographer: still important facts as narrated and maintaining a credible fidelity to the actual events, I have not had the impression of seeing a documentary, but a constructed play so that the viewer enters the function, side by side with those in it involved, keep the attention constantly and enter into the atmosphere of tension that surrounds all the work. United 93 takes 115 minutes and has been written and directed by Paul Greengrass. Barry Ackroyd is, in my opinion, excellent director of photography. Music, adjusted to action anytime, was provided by John Powell. Tim Bevan, Eric Fellner, Lloyd Levin and the director have been producers. A curiosity of the translation: in a scene for the NORAD command center (prepare for a fictional tactical exercise), an officer refers to the "Russian bears will enter by Alaska". Obviously alludes to the Russian bombers Tupolev TU-95, whose name in code which NATO is Bear. Recommended audience: it is easy, anyone who likes the film.</body>
</review>
