<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Supersalidos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A recommended surprise in the form of comedy teen, with a few players in State of grace, a few fun so far as dialogues despite to be based on the themes of always, with multiple references to this style of the 1980s comedies.</summary>
	<body>One usually has some suspicion when it comes to go to see a film about teens with altered and eager for sex hormones, more taking into account that in the vast majority of cases usually give monsters of the greater possible ilk as a final result. It is also true that a server is usually disconnected part of your brain on many occasions and is able to enjoy even the primary instincts posed the jokes even sexist times about sex, women or any other lindeza concern to most of adolescents and often portray these films.The only hope that housed find me before a decent product was who was behind this production, Judd Apatow, in this case as a producer, which is owed modern with considerable interest comedies as "Virgin at 40" or the commented recently in this blog "Embarazoso mess" (of imminent release also in rooms). So pleasant surprise that I have brought, despite find us with certain common productions such passages, would be an error be carried away by the superficiality in this laudable attempt to provide a true humanism to the characters in the story, despite constant talks of thick stroke.Greg Mottola, a semidesconocido director who has previously worked for television in various comedies, knows to create comedy almost perfect teen for the times, that point of view always the vicissitudes faced a few adolescents treated from a fearful of adolescence and realistic vision (and again, probably influenced by this new brand in the American comedy that already have become Apatow productions). Coarse comedy Yes, but always starting from a few characters with which any viewer is identified in several occasions.History shows Seth (Jonah Hill), Evan (Michael Cera) and Fogell (Christopher Mintz-Plasse), three losers, but why not especially schematized in a cliché precisely, at least not brought to the extreme, which found the opportunity to his short life of adolescents having sex or couple before the University when invite them a party with the popular people of the Institutea change of lead them with which satisfy both teen drinking left.Throughout the film, we follow the adventures of these three friends to achieve its objective, in any way during a long night that reminds the lived by Corey Haim in "Pope Cadillac", the popular ochentera movie. All this from a few dialogues that probably will be accused of swearing, bad taste, etc, but we should not forget, that while always considered so in most cases, they do more than reflect largely talks of a foot of every teenager, despite him who gets upset, realistic. It must be said, in this case in particular are really fun and cause more sincere laughter in the audience. But it is not the only aspect of the film positive, because underneath all that rude comedy hide much more serious aspects that run the risk of pass unnoticed for the absent-minded spectator. Fear to grow as a mechanism to internally fight nostalgia for youth represented in the attitude of the two cops (taken to the extreme, that Yes, almost close to slapstick), or other fears as losing your loved ones to grow and start a new life, represented in the film with the relationship of friendship threatened by the distance between Seth and Evan (both excellent in their roles along with the impeccable role of Fogell) and their emotional reconciliation final.The work of Mottola as director the truth is intrascendete technically, confined to be extremely conventional, without any notion of originality in the sunset scene, entirely predictable, as following a brand without leaving its conventionality or its marked guidelines.In short, a recommended surprise in the form of comedy teen, with a few players in State of grace, a few fun so far as dialogues despite to be based on the themes of always, with multiple references to comedies of this style of the 1980s such as "Revenge of the nerds", "This exciting course" or the aforementioned "Dad Cadillac", with more background than it seems at first sight, and a true humanism and candor of the characters in many scenes that create a hilarious solvent product and turns on their own merits in the best comedy teen years with difference.</body>
</review>
