<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Doce hombres sin piedad" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sydney Lumet does something as complicated as put the camera and ignore it, without incendiary rhetoric or elevated speeches, only a group of men current releasing ordinary phrases.</summary>
	<body>Already for a long time it not eating a serving of classic cinema, so on the desktop of the Sunday, I decided to dispense with the Technicolor and taste a jewel of trials in charge of Sydney Lumet and his political cinema film. This is the theatrical "12 angry men".To be a copy of cinema of convicts, rooms and presumed guilty, begins in unusual way, just in the last step of the trial, when the jury retires to deliberate if the accused in this case with a possible murder in first degree to their backs should be found guilty and worthy of the death penalty.It is to this jury who still camera will be installed next to them in a small meeting room on a sweltering afternoon, to passively attend its deliberations. What at first seems a mere formality in a case of course, with plenty of evidence against the suspect and several witnesses, is prolonged by the doubt of one of the members, reluctant to send the boy to jail if you don't see things absolutely clear and without a hint of reasonable doubt.As the film progresses, the only participant in the discussion that from the beginning raises the first question - a huge Henry Fonda - will try to reason with the other details of the trial. Various personalities will be coming to the fore portraying a small sample of the society. Prejudice, quick-tempered men with shy types, various social strata and different ages should be to agree on a man's life.In the middle of the 12 men, two stand out for its clarity of ideas and exposure of the same, each on one side, while to his around the rest is changing opinion, realizing that it is not so easy to send someone to another neighborhood where one must be completely sure of his guilt. Reasonable doubt starts to bite in the minds and the minds of the group.The film is almost a play, with a single scenario, a small number of people and dialogue who intersect, overlap, cut and fight around the life of a boy. Although perhaps over time it has lost some of its initial strength, it remains a calm and accurate plea against the death penalty, trying to demonstrate that even in the most crystalline trial there may be dark spots that send an innocent man to the electric chair.To do this, Sydney Lumet is something as complicated as put the camera and ignore it, without incendiary rhetoric or elevated speeches, only a group of men current releasing ordinary phrases. There is a hero who convinces them, nor nor a villain willing to cause death, but rather questions, experiences and little defined feelings that intersect.A simple movie in structure but with a great work of script, of those that were made by famous directors such as Robert Altman or (I hope not receiving death threats after this absurd comparison) the first films of the now somewhat desnortado Kevin Smith, full of dialogues on which slides narration. Perfect for taste unhurried a Sunday afternoon.</body>
</review>
