<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Todos al suelo" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film on four bank robbers beginners and their avatars in your first shot. I've not liked, that has few sympathetic moments, is too tontorrona and gets us a pufo moralist that sucks. And the worst, which is in administration.</summary>
	<body>Director: Mariano OzoresDuración: 86 minutes.Release date: April 1, 1982.Espectadores: 1.294.874 of human beings.The other day I commented with a digital dearest (which has all the fingers of the hands and feet) that this humble blog is doing a great deal by Spanish films, namely by Mariano Ozores. I think it is an exaggeration, but if it is true that I have not found any other review (rather than the who are beginning to read) of this film. Neither of the most critical. I will be a rare freak raaaroooo (which would say Papuchi)? Do I encumbraré to Mariano Ozores to the altars as this French magazine made with Hitchcock? Grow my son watching these movies mentally healthy? Do or tell at school "Ñiaaa, that riiiiica is her fuck" step away from their teachers?The film is about four gentlemen that come together to rob the Bank in which you work. Each has its idiosyncrasies, one which is a flirt (Pajares) is married, she is pregnant to a lover and you want to escape with another. Another is Ozores which has a workshop and is eyed (and a prostitua wants to live with him). Another is Juanito Navarro, that her daughter fights with her husband day if day later, while his grandson suffers. And finally Esteso makes cashier bundled with a woman of hipergordas tits. Comedieta of entanglement, which is usually decir.¿Me liked the film? I'm glad that always ask me you the same question. Because on the one hand, I've laughed, but nothing to do with other titles of this people. And on the other hand a number of things that happened to list to facilitate the understanding of my readers have bothered me: in the first scene leaves the only teat throughout the film. This is mislead viewers. As counterpoint, do not see the duo in his underwear (TAD to Esteso, but enough time to close your eyes) her comedita mess is for you rias, not to make mess you a tearing absurd and tontorrón. The theme of the son who suffers by his parents fight is pathetic.Finally, what the hell paints that advocacy against abortion in a film of these? I guess that for things like this they joined Mariano Ozores with the extreme right.In short, film about four bank robbers beginners and their avatars in your first shot. I've not liked, that has few sympathetic moments, is too tontorrona and gets us a pufo moralist that sucks. And the worst, which is in administration.Ozores comedy without tits and few laughs, bad thing, friends.Besitos.P.D: A salute to my faithful follower, the father of Chinchan sr, which makes me much publicity, that thing is I. It is not if it will know that I am referring to my parent, heh, heh.Pd2: Scene Juanito Navarro and Antonio Ozores priest, dressed in Pajares medium dress in nun saying to a girl that passes "Go ass to give injections" has seemed very good.P.D.3: Has another "tricky" critical moment "to something" that we could say it is surprising. This dark Office, with sinister character, that you move the wires leading up to the elections. Ains, Manolete, if you don't know what you get.</body>
</review>
