<review author="Christian Sandoval" title="Someone Is Watching Me!" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A Carpenter tribute to the work of Hitchcock, which sets out how dangerous that can be the loss of privacy.</summary>
	<body>"Someone is watching me!" (1978), is a film directed and written by John Carpenter. It is one of their least appointed films, not because of its quality, but because it was a production made for television, so it wasn't so mass consumption. It is perhaps the only film of the director that falls into the genre of suspense as such, noting a clear inspiration in some works of Alfred Hitchcock.En Los Angeles a woman named Leigh (Lauren Hutton) purchased an apartment on a high floor, which has a beautiful view. After getting a job as Director of television, he receives a strange call from a stranger. These calls will continue to receive them in his Department, which joined a few strange gifts that begin to leave in your door, end up worrying about her.Her friend Sophie (Adrienne Barbeau) advises him to go to the police, but as the harasser has not threatened they can do nothing. What Leigh does not know yet, is that his bully the notes what she does through a telescope from the front building.There are many similarities of this film with some of the work of Hitchcock, starting with the theme of voyeurism, which immediately reminds us to the film "Rear window" (1954), especially in the scene where Leigh is in the Department of his bully and begins to see what what happens in her apartment with her friend. A very similar sequence will be repeated later in the film, Brian De Palma "Body double" (1984). In addition to this, we can also see certain similarities in the style of the opening credits and the soundtrack composed by Harry Sukman, at times sounding similar to the compound by Bernard Herrmann.A despite the above, we are not dealing with a copy outright by Carpenter, who is responsible for printing their own label to the film. The director here deals than the headdresses by Hitchcock in his film. The theme of this production Fund, is how easy that can be invaded the privacy of someone by using existing technology, that the instruments used were quite obviously in that time precarious compared the existing instruments of the day today. These were limited to a tape recorder, a small microphone, a telescope and the phone which is the object with which the harasser is responsible for tormenting Leigh. Of course, now with the Internet and the existing technology is much easier to access the privacy of individuals.Another feature of the film is that the bully is not shown until the end of the film. He is dedicated to psychologically torment Leigh, especially through constant telephone calls to her apartment. Here is where the sentence uttered by Sophie in the film takes on a special meaning: "Rape is when a man consciously frightens a woman". Leigh during the film is gaining a growing phobia to the phone. Everytime this sounds, she is shudders completely submerging it in a State of despair and helplessness.However, is portrayed as Leigh as a triumphant, independent woman in a race led by men, a symbol of the reigning women's Liberation at the time in the United States, in a determined moment, she decides to confront the person who insists in harassing her, by what he tried by all means find out the identity of his bully.Carpenter does a great job after cameras, making the viewer becomes one "stalker" more, following each of the movements made by Leigh. On other occasions, we see through the eyes of the protagonist, which helps to feel their anguish, as for example when it is trapped in his Department, seeking desperately to her stalker in the darkness, that thanks to the movements of camera is achieved in better shape the desired effect.This is a very good director film, full of suspense, which manages to keep interested spectators during the course of this. The end is quite abrupt, very much in the style of television productions, but not why it is bad. Unfortunately for this film, it is difficult to avoid comparisons with the masterpiece of Hitchcock, situation ending overshadowing a little to this film. However, it is a good entry to the Filmography of the director for both the genre of suspense.</body>
</review>
