<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Alvin y las Ardillas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although fun and reconciliante with the kid that lives within us, is a bit disappointing, you know the saying, to where you were not you should return, better remember it as it was, to not annoy her on his return.</summary>
	<body>Already many years perhaps 20? I continued on television (the canal which is now called "intelligent channel" which is the 2 TVE), an animated series that used to put many Sunday afternoons, starring 3 sympathetic squirrels with strident voices that he wore to the poor John (his caretaker and "father") and their adventures and misadventures, once again, and perhaps thanks or not, the lack of ideas in the Mecca of cinema has brought to the big screenreplacing the original Chipmunks animated characters in CGI.I admit that in my case Garfield, despite having seen 2 movies as my wife loves the cat, not called me the minimum, and yet this film and moved by a bit of nostalgia, has led me to see her knowing, in advance, what was I going to find.On the one hand have to Jason Lee (already mayor man), that here portraying the legendary role of John, then the 3 squirrels in CGI, sincerely well recreated, do 3 bugs "with charisma" through a Pc isn't feat, then we have David Cross, secondary in countless films, that here is the villain of the role andof partner Lee bellisima Cameron Richardson, to which we have not seen too many movies, but that I bet that will be a face (beautiful, beautiful) we will accompany from now onwards.Honestly, when I heard about the project I thought it was a joke, and was not until I saw the first trailer I record that this was "serious", and that has worked excellently well in box office will have sequel? Squirrels will return to TV as when I was small? Big questions unanswered.The film certainly does not give much, it is clear what is going to give a tape where 3 squirrels are the protagonists? That's normal, sincerely did not expect to see Macbeth, Romeo and Juliet, nor a remake of Citizen Kane, but, however at the end of viewing have a feeling that it has missed the characters, were much more charisma in his animated series, and here are dull, desdibujados and firmly poorly aimed, besides the fact that I do not remember that squirrels obsession because John (do era John not?) was his fatherrather, until where comes my memory were devoted to bitching you and make your life impossible, within the rules and coexistence, given that we are talking about a series of drawings for children, and you know that everything you see a child, like a monito, copy.On the soundtrack I was lacking the main theme, something that is completely unforgivable, and that many thirtysomethings had no illusion have recovered, although the Chritsmas Time sounds me that also went in any episode of the series.Finally, although fun and reconciliante with the kid who live in our interior, is a little disappointing, because we know the saying, to where you were you should not return, better to remember it as it was, to not annoy her on his return.</body>
</review>
