<review author="José A. Peig" title="John Rambo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It exposes brutality without nuances or euphemistic valuations, what makes it a harrowing film both in its subject matter and the Mise en scène, especially due to the magnificent photography that collects all the infernal impulse of the Burmese jungle.</summary>
	<body>Sylvester Stallone has done his small and personal masterpiece without repair in sensitivities or prejudices about his character. You have chosen an expression close to the so-called "gore" (splatter) film to impress the audience with one of the best representations of war horror that we have seen in recent years (playing in excess with the theatrics and hubris, everything is said), which reaffirms the idea of brutality that characterizes the myth, and from there eliminates any type of apologetics soflama. A succinct script - many unwary confound simple with simple, what going you to do - focusing on the essence of the character and the violence surrounding it. Patria, rights, justice, revenge, loyalty.Virtually non-existent words in the script, and appearing in the mind of the Viewer as well as concepts (prejudice) from suggested in the images that speak of the Warrior essentially. But why the Warrior has no answer. The Warrior simply acts according to his nature - which cannot escape-, and violence is a fait accompli before which just react or die.Because of this, in principle, the Sylvester Stallone film is a cheater product because not even dares to raise a debate on the need - or not - to use violence. Situations set out leave no other alternative than the make use of violence or die, there is no possible choice and consequently the violence of Rambo is justified per are. In its apparent simplicity, we find the absence of apologetics. And this environment of violence inevitable is the ideal to put the warrior who never kills a country or on behalf of an ideology, but - as verbatim remains that in the movie--and motivated in a moral imperative that pushes it to give free rein to their savagery in defence of the oppressed. In this case, a group of missionaries (pacifists well-meaning but ignorant of the reality of the war), and in particular the female protagonist that represents the idealism of the action against oppression, and his hopeful address ends up causing the disguised empathy in John Rambo, whose introversion and taciturn character make that we continue looking deadpan, even though it has always defined by their silence. Realizing, in some action sequences filmed camera in hand have nothing to envy to the moments efectistas and most impressive of Saving Private Ryan (heh, if it is work of Spielberg is hiper-realista film, if it is work of Stallone.hasta say it's a bad film), although occasionally also remembers the bad Paul Greengrass. In any case, here the documentary style results in a continuum of space and time which fulfils two functions: recreation (with a few ups and downs) of an avorágine of electrifying through violence, very powerful charged sequences of dramatic intensity in which the viewer recognizes the victim and executioner, which can be identified with the victim without that there is need to develop more developed characters (and again emphasise the virtues of a dash centered in) Essentials. (It is important that the viewer understands the situation in a relentless deployment of violence intended to culminate in ninety minutes). And on the other hand, the integration of the personaje-icono in the reality of the events. The prologue documentary that shows images of the conflict in Burma Announces and introduces the Viewer to the hell of which John Rambo is a crucial piece in its resolution. With regard to the alleged Manichaeism in the characterization of characters, we return to the above. Taking into account the type of situations that are exposed in the film (situations designed on the basis of an intention or narrative purpose) - the essential Division into victims and executioners - talk of Manichaeism is out of place. Manichaeism is the simplification of the human dimension faced with achieving some political purpose, moral or aesthetic, supporting or rejecting an end or another by the dichotomy between "good" and "bad". But John Rambo is a completely visceral story; on varmints to dismember their victims in a pure and simple action film. Live for nothing, or die for something. Continuing with the essence of the icon, the ancient mysticism of the hero, and its best expression, blows on the incandescent iron, while the Warrior reaffirms its nature than any country or individual. Before the slackness of the life of a loser, the struggle for those who still believe in something. After the final massacre, a few planes idling underscore the connection between Rambo and the female protagonist, this bleak crossing of glances which confirms the vision of the warrior to hell as a true home. The end evokes the beginning of First Blood, closing the circle. He has fulfilled his destiny, the hero goes in search of his origins. They sound like the first chords of the original score of Jerry Goldsmith, and the viewer who has understood the beauty that hides this underrated personaje(desde_estas_páginas_hemos_intentado_arrojar_algo_de_luz_en_los_últimos_días,_esperamos_que_todo_no_sea_en_vano) feel the knot in throat saw Solitaire, for the first time, walking towards a predetermined place. Film, ultimately, far more atonal than it seems. Is like saying: to survive will have to commit these savagery when estes in war zone, or if the war comes to the door of your House. It exposes brutality without nuances or euphemistic valuations, what makes it a harrowing film both in its subject matter and the Mise en scène, especially due to the magnificent photography that collects all the infernal impulse of the Burmese jungle.</body>
</review>
