<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Juno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very estimable comedy with a tinge of drama, but without that never reaches the blood River.</summary>
	<body>A veritable filigree guionística of Diablo Cody, and the wise conduct of Jason Reitman, that does not elucubra with the script adocenando you absurd shots to try and give a patina of qualité, make that "Juno" it is little bit but without possibility of escape, with the heart of the Viewer.At the beginning, the first fifteen minutes, appears will be a "yanquilandada", a story only possible in the United States of North America, far from other countries. However, and as a result the confession of Juno parents, on its current state, the story takes some byways impresivislbes, continuously changing direction, of gender, of situations, from humor to drama, romantic comedy, to the socio-cultural notes and very sensitive scenes such as Jennifer Garner playing the bulging belly of Juno while this look you at but satisfied. A scene which will be vital in the final decision of perfectly tack Juno.Todo, with great dialogues, excellent performances, with special mention to two actresses: Ellen Page, simply superb in his role as talkative teenager, which serves as a catalyst for some personjaes, somewhat lost / s in their wrong lives, and Allison Janney, wonderful in her role as Juno's stepmother (simple and vibrant escema ultrasound)an actress already with proven experience but that, I'm afraid, so far it had passed fairly unnoticed for the public (myself included, although her he remembered other jobs).Entertaining anytime the interest increases with every minute, offering us a life lesson in the most entertaining way, without absurd morals, moments riídiculos or children's condescencias.It is nominated for several Oscars, being the cheapest film that has crept into the list of nominees. It is difficult, but in the section on the best screenplay I think have real</body>
</review>
