<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Juno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A real character of a realistic comic, played by a successful Ellen Page in this funny and incontestable tale of initiation, consisting of remnants of an elegant, even if with mood highlight suit.</summary>
	<body>Lucid and entertaining, Juno is the 'another teen comedy', which leaves no bad place to young people, is more real - despite the overwhelming burden of snooty dialogues-, convinces with its mix of sweet and sour and spicy tone and, above all, is surprising. That nobody put the product 'indie' label, on the path of little Miss Sunshine, because that can only burden the becoming of this atypical tape. The atypical comes to delicious and rightly irreverent - something more than Ghost World, by putting it on some point - in an era in which only occasionally be grasping an oasis in the middle of a desert full of bland sand.The character of Juno and its problems - and their ability, or not, to resolve them - articulates a story seasoned with a just hint of bitterness and in the savoring some drops of brilliance. The dish, a substantial and original, incoming presents dotted by samples of a gallery of beings somewhat stereotyped although suitable to sustain the viaduct between the two worlds that transits Juno on the road ranging from immaturity logical and seized, to the land, or you are an adult. or you are an adult!Our travel companion has this attractive aura of sabionda girl, a repellent point - very seductive, by the way – to believe a much superior, although he presumed not let us believe. For that and many other reasons, Ellen Page is exultant in a credible character, much more than the of the 'lolita-caperucita' of Hard Candy, that was something forced - demands of script, of course--. We must point out that these laudable work are not comparable: Juno, the character of Page - with a sense of irony much more worked - recalls the girl it was Natalie Portman in Beautiful girls and matured to become the protagonist of Garden State (something in common).Jasón Reitman, director of the curious thank you for smoking, and Brook Busey-Hunt (alias Diablo Cody), former stripper and erotic line stuck writer, voice have been successful with this glimpse into the adventure of grow. Nobody consider Juno a work to use, but a crushing fable of intensities and roads which, although longer, are more striking and enriching than the common shortcuts. In short, is a proposal that take salt to that that life you play tricks, something which is not that we take suddenly. Now that the grace of life is live with intensity, being a little well, insolent if you leave, know you, even though few dare to put it into practice.</body>
</review>
