<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="United 93" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do made with nerve and tone? cinema verité?, with a nervous camera on his shoulder, which in this case is fully justified. Quality, honesty and rigour.</summary>
	<body>We are in the days in which commemorates the fifth anniversary of the tragic events of September 11, 2001, when several Islamic fundamentalists hijacked planes destroyed the two twin towers in New York, and part of the Pentagon in Washington. For these purposes, the collapse of the Workd Trade Center can compare with the assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand in Sarajevo, causing the spark that would lead to the first world war. Of course, the New York drama was infinitely more seriously, not only because of the thousands of human lives lost, but because instantly transmitted "urbi et orbi", produced a huge trauma at the global level, not to mention within American society itself. As often happens in these cases of very strong emotional upheaval, has taken some time so the USA film dares to put in images that national catastrophe, whose consequences later (call the disastrous invasion of Iraq and the polarization of the world in Islamic East and the Christian West faced each other, although they do not want to admit it, a new covert war whose outcome is unpredictable) have had occasion to see during these years. "United 93" (also "World Trade Center", Oliver Stone, without brand new in Spain when writing these lines) is the first approximation in cinema to that ill-fated day, and tells a plausible reconstruction of what might have happened on the fourth plane hijacked by Muslim fundamentalists, United Airlines 93, which is only known that you crashed in Pennsylvaniaclose to achieve its goal, the Capitol or the White House. As there were no survivors, Paul Greengrass, screenwriter and director, has made a reconstruction based on interviews with loved ones of the deceased, crew and passengers, and in your recent calls to their families, friends and loves. Made with nerve and tone "cinema verité", with a nervous camera on his shoulder which in this case is fully justified, and using little-known actors that there no rift in the spectator, Greengrass makes a stimulating work, hour and a half which reproduces those long hours in the morning of 9-11, when the world lost the innocence and New York went from being happy and confident city to a sullen city thatat least in the early days, he distrusted everything and everyone. It is true that perhaps in the Greengrass film abused the scenes set in the control of American airspace flight, and not say sequences shot in the military stays trying to understand and tackle those unusual events, with a jargon often only to initiates. But is also true that, when it comes to the truth, and the crew and passengers realize that going to the slaughterhouse, the film momentum grows (I better not say "raises the flight" do, as it will weld metaforizar in these cases?) and becomes a thrilling race against time, much more shocking that we know what happened in that plane was authentic and that the end is none other than the death of all that the they occupied. That documentary tone especially suits this last stretch, with passengers killed of fear but willing to fight for their lives. By the way that this is a success of Greengrass as a writer: when the tragedy occurred, was speculated that the crew and passengers, to realize that would be scrambled against some emblematic building, as had happened with the other aircraft, decided qualms that not happen; Greengrass opts for another possibility, perhaps less heroic but more likely: according to the same passengers rioted because they wanted to regain command of the aircraft, counting among them with a small plane pilot. It is certainly less bombastic, but it is a very plausible view: rather than thinking about crashing without killing others, thought that they could save their lives if they take the controls before they crashed them. Well is that the American film begins to exorcise the ghosts of the 11-S; already did, and with a result of whatever stripe, with the Viet Nam Guerra. Hopefully whatever is done about that unlucky day have, at least, the same level of quality, honesty and rigor to this dramatic, tense, stinging film.</body>
</review>
