<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Soy leyenda" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In short, an unfortunate adaptation of a classic, irregular, simple and with a 100% palomitero use because of all the employed pyrotechnics. Only saves the decent performance from a credible Will Smith; except that, embarrassing.</summary>
	<body>Third film adaptation of the novel by Richard Matheson. Simple and hackneyed version with a pace of more irregular in terms of narrative and action, use the totally failed flashback that seeks only to the involvement of the Viewer without get it. This time, we change to Charlton Heston by Will Smith, place you a dog that penalty when he dies - so we win to the public easy tear - some quite poor and very bad vampires achieved, and the rest to do so with phrases marketing team: the last living man on Earth, or with the more expensive sequencing of the story. Best remake of infectious virus (28 days later, Resident Evil, dawn of the dead.) where no doubt passes when it Will Smith is only found in a deserted New York City. Impressive levels and recreation of an apocalyptic ravaged Manhattan, where the protagonist has fun day hunting deer (excellent scene) or going shopping, and hiding at night. Acceptable - not by its originality - so far they appear vampires, where the director happens to opt for the show 100% American in the form of budget, and forgets all the above so far. Finally, a whiff semicatólico caught with clamps that abounds everywhere in the final 15 minutes, which compels us to believe in order to be saved. Attention to the 30 seconds from the end, the phrase, the sound of the bells, the Church, the doors of the salvation by opening pair in pair and the entire community of blessed to receive us. In short, an unfortunate adaptation of a classic, irregular, simple and with a 100% palomitero use because of all the employed pyrotechnics. Only saves the decent performance from a credible Will Smith; except that, embarrassing.</body>
</review>
