<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Caramel" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The most delicious recipe that gives as a result a delicious dish with the curious ability to leave an aftertaste of bitter and sweet at the same time can produce with warmth and serenity.</summary>
	<body>To go at least trivial topic only must learn to give way to the right ingredients and let them stand in memory so that the good taste we repeated from time to time. All these similes culinary give an idea of the interest aroused by this daring and modest tape should not see.You can not establish a strong parallel between them, but if not seen in his day the French film Venus, beauty salon can compensate now entering the hairdresser mounts Nadine Labaki, a Centre for social gathering in which five women, different from one another, leave emerge their feelings and secrets, in short, a curious shape, subtle, with a touch of sensualityto give brush strokes on the status of women in Lebanon. between these four walls is possible to openly address the five major themes revolves around which their world, close and intimate: freedom, friendship, men, sex and maternity. Taking advantage of the aesthetic impact that proposes the Director and establishing a metaphor with the color of the candy, which does not become brown or yellow, Caramel is halfway between the sweet and melancholic touch and the bitter slap.The young leader to do the outline of this piece of life painted with a palette of Mediterranean tones proves that, besides being good make-up artist - known cover defects with a layer of details-, know give stitch the fabric of patchwork, or short stories that make up the costume of Caramel. More than one exalted filmmaker should apprehend the philosophy of walk House proposes Nadine Labaki in footage that is taking us, way paused by the domains of a group of females with their problems and virtues, without neglecting certain political commitment. And more interestingly, that a reality of more quiet in one of the countries most scrambled, shows although, on the other hand, this is the greatness of this film which gets into the arena the dilemmas that crosses the woman without the minimum explicit reference to the civil war that plunged the country for 25 years or to more recent conflicts. Because, without neglecting the problems, another film is possible.</body>
</review>
