<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="This is England" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Excellent suggestive and honest portrait of England in the 1980s. We see the progressive personal and cultural maturation of a boy of 12 years that will lead to a change of innocence to experience.</summary>
	<body>Excellent suggestive and honest portrait of England in the 1980s. Under the context of the depressed English political situation, where the war of the Maldives has ended a few months ago and Margaret Thatcher continued to rule with an iron, a 12-year-old boy hand feels welcome in a peculiar group of youth of the movement skinhead who then began to spread in the districts of England. British, very committed to the story, director has managed to reflect perfectly the life of a child rejected at school and accepted by a skinhead group. Pure social English film far removed from which we are accustomed always controversial Ken Loach. Divided into two parts, the first comic and made to perfection after a brilliant presentation of the characters, and a second which nests too in the drama and social realism to affect the sensitive vein of the Viewer; It keeps the interest thanks to the simplicity with which the director will little by little humming all the elements of the film and at the same time we see the progressive personal and cultural maturation of a boy of 12 years that will lead to a change of innocence to experience. Are you missing face the absence of some major characters in the face at the end of the film where its history disappears and does not return to know nothing more than them; as well as the mother figure, passing on tiptoe to the physical and psychological transformation of his son. Special mention deserves the small actor Thomas Turgoose (winner of the best actor award novel of 2006 British Independent Awards) that makes the film at all times and a - too - sobreactuado Stephen Graham as a racist skinhead. Social and human x-ray full of drama, with a strong and crude picture of England in the 1980s. Excellent atmosphere, music and interpretation for a tape that will like to stakeholders by social issues and its human background. With some of the best initial credit titles I've seen this last year (as well as the music that runs through all the footage), This is England, well-deserved winner of the award for best film at the British Independent Awards, becomes a pleasure for the senses and one of the 15 best films of 2007.</body>
</review>
