<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Hacia rutas salvajes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Confirmed as accurate director, with their own style to tell things, Sean Penn proposed a story simple although of epic proportions, more so it has that false claims of greatness.</summary>
	<body>They say that to delve into the big issues facing human beings only we must look within oneself. The search for the truth and one's identity is already almost a genre in every rule in the literature, in the film &hellip; now this title combines both formats - could include here the musical, thanks to the superb soundtrack-, although the best-selling book becomes a semi-autor film.The actor got to filmmaker leaves the urban drama to which we had become accustomed and opts for a story calling beautiful panoramic, risky levels and shots in which time seems to stop. Too idyllic to the story so hard that presents us with? It may be, now well, it doesn't matter that a such raw story, the way of overcoming that undertakes a lost young man, has a suggestive wrapper, the problem is that sometimes you forget the tragedy suffered by the character with the inclusion of Visual effects such as the writing on the screen. One of the bets of this production was the young actor Emile Hirsch, tanning in TV series and short appearances on the big screen. Get impregnated really a character that could have been lost between so much literary ínfula that can Sin a soliloquy, but Penn resolves the ballot with a montage which are not at all agile, relieves at times - while this story requests shouts two hours of our time, at least 120 minutes of concentration and avoidance of reality.Speaking of footage, the film only has a few drawbacks: extend in certain stages of the voyage; the protagonist Leonardo DiCaprio - this remember not to blame the poor-; the action is descompense because the visual is imposed on narrative; and that, in general terms, the tape see diminished its qualities for a lot of critics to denote it as a committed, philosophical or initiatory work &hellip; none of that! Towards wild routes is not more than a choice of life, a lesson in cinema.</body>
</review>
