<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Mulholland drive" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Dreamlike, hypnotic, mixed, poetic and wonderful work perfectly hilvanada and studied by Lynch. Best of Mulholland Drive is the feeling of satisfaction and fullness that gives you when you have understood her.</summary>
	<body>I do not know very well how to start this comment on the unclassifiable work of David Lynch, so I simply say that it is great visual spectacle. Magic eye. Dreamlike, hypnotic, mixed, poetic and wonderful. Disturbing to infinity. Chaotic in every sense. It is one of those works that does not leave indifferent anyone, or you hate the love; and I just am that loves her. Don't try to look for logic or any consistency during viewing (or after the), only let yourself go by what it conveys. Opens the mind and get ready for a trip without return to the universe Lynch. And is that gentlemen, is Mulholland Drive. Film after film, David Lynch does amaze me and passionate me in equal parts. The strength and power of his images is overwhelming. This ability to mix the situations and context is a genius. The treatment that gives the music in all of his films is mysterious, shocking and excellent. Lynch has this innate ability in some directors leave in shock the Viewer after their films. Let be the same viewer who interpret and you way to what you have just seen. Lynch gives you the canvas and paints, and it's you who should paint the picture. Lynch you hints and you interpret. Lynch does not display and you are looking for desperately "something" in the level. Lynch gives us a puzzle, and we who must mount it. Genius of the suggestion has the seventh art. And it lasts for many years more. Exciting atmosphere delusional, austere and disturbing you catch a few minutes and the best you can do is to let yourself go. I have come to the conclusion that the Lynch film to abandon all hope of logic and coherence, leave to seek the why of things and plunging fully into what vomits us Lynch. As for the cast of Mulholland Drive, overhangs a stupendous Naomi Watts all. With its dual role (track) tries to deceive (rather Lynch) the spectator to confuse us and do not understand anything. We are in their dreams, and their dreams anything can be possible. Then we have a very sensual Helena Laura Harring also embroidering his amnesiac role where the ambiguity and confusion seize him. Dark and gloomy photo, play with colors to suit (especially blue and red, track), to move the camera in a very subjective way, it seems that her wear yourself at times (the Tramp and the apartment scene). Attention to the order which gives Lynch to the end titles (that pillo are, David); in order of appearance. (TRACK). With memorable scenes, such as the scathing criticism to the world of Hollywood and his pawns; scenes difficult to forget and charged of feeling as in the theatre or in the hearing; and moments of extreme beauty as the lesbian scene, Mulholland Drive has become everything a film concerning the current; filled with symbolism and full of metaphors. Ultimately, a story that breaks down completely all chronological and narrative conventions to which we are accustomed. Lynch takes the canons and clichés of the film normally accepted by the great public and given a 180 degree turn. Hypnotic and dreamlike is a tape for the enjoyment of the senses. Intelligent more not to and perfectly hilvanada and studied by Lynch, it is more stimulating. Best thing about Mulholland is the feeling of satisfaction and fullness that gives you when you have understood her.</body>
</review>
