<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Across The universe" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cutting of the All you need is love in 133 minutes or how to tell a story of love, friendship and desire for freedom with the help of 33 songs from the boys that Liverpool became them too small.</summary>
	<body>That nobody is misleading: this soft musical not narrates the adventures of the Beatles but it tells a story that serves as an excuse to honor them and a last time, through their songs. Incidentally, in addition to launching anything subtle criticism, the musical genre charged again force with this tragicomedy that sometimes clears the parody and other stays on mere submission of remnants of life set in the 1960s. Why when something is out of normal we call experiment? Julie Taymor does not experience, but that is it safe: takes well-known songs, seeks an account capable of connecting with the youth and those who yearn - or simply remember - past and framed it in one of the most convulsive decades and lavish turn in claims of all kinds. The result is a simple and fun feature where the content is at the service of the form. Even so it will delight the avid of curiosities, details and cameos Viewer.With a visual network care Fund, almost unknown performers give the do and are displayed at the convincing time: make credible a plot which is conditional, and much to the lyrics of selected songs, do not but highlight the environment of persecuted counterculture, delicious debauchery and Orgasmic explosion. And reiterate here the possibilities of sensory and efectistas resources exploited by filmmaker, very close to the effects of psychotropic substances and hallucinogenic. The Director of Titus and Frida sought to foster the widespread good vibes still sinning of simplistic. Perhaps this comes despite too with regard to film strictly, burdening a footage which seems a hilvanado of tissues and several remnants and which in turn just lengthening is too for the detractors of the genre, although those who connect with his philosophy always you will be insufficient. This goes for others: Across the Universe entroncará with these films of which sales with the uploaded mood. Just have to wait for that purists do not see against the visual film, and for empty moments, Taymor and that fans of the Beatles not put the cry in the sky with certain adaptations made, that Yes, respect.</body>
</review>
