<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Cache Escondido" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A terror suggestive, since that obvious invisibly fear. Haneke is still obsessed with passing a hard time to the viewer and certainly succeeds.</summary>
	<body>I have to admit that I love Michael Haneke since I saw the grinding and the brilliant couple film entitled Funny Games, and that he himself has remakeado 10 years after its premiere. But after the viewing of cache, I must say that only created me indifference. At the technical level is impeccable, faithful to its fixed flat continuous so characteristic are his works, and the bright flat sequence which both abound in cache. Haneke maintains his style on his latest tape, a psychological portrait of a family well-off and bourgeois (e.g. not in a film from Haneke), he begins to receive mysterious recordings. With an overwhelming staging (100% Haneke), and disturbing, disturbing atmosphere, mix equal parts classic suspense with a suggestive horror. A terror suggestive, since that obvious invisibly fear. Haneke is still obsessed with passing a hard time to the viewer and certainly succeeds. Succeeds to suggest and not show, as well as longer base towards with Funny Games; and it seems that not given entirely bad. With a tremendously open and ambiguous ending, it forces you to draw your own conclusions. So those people who like it will all masticadito so they can accept it and understand it all before bedtime not come to this work, since it will think long and resting on the various points of view that offers to them. To my personally made me thinking some things and setting me on the last fixed plane that closes the film, I can get an idea that I will not share to not spoil the film to anyone. Some will say that it is extremely pretentious and Haneke plays and laughs at us (I'm not saying that not), but that already knew it to be to see a tape of his. One of the key figures of the modern cinema, both his technique and the pertubadora atomósfera that surrounds his works is undoubtedly Michael Haneke.</body>
</review>
