<review author="Iñigo" title="Saraband" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Dancing to the sound of Bergman</summary>
	<body>To the skeptics that we believed that the film was losing all degree of humanity and was sinking into utter vulgarity, still Ingmar Bergman. We still have his work confessions, of fleeting light between so much darkness, heavenly music that requires a (forced) reflection prior to viewing. Our pleasure, in any case, be brief. Bergman, in his own words, here signed his film Testament. The testament of a genius. As if it were a preparation for his films, the acolytes found in his film more than sense and sensibility can not stop launch prayers so that this does not happen. It is the only thing we have left to satisfy our spiritual concerns. But, to his 87 years, as much as it could extend his legacy, we must kneel with the reality. Many do not want to participate in the signing of the testament of Bergman, but it is true that increasingly are is depleted, after disappearing from the celluloid with "Fanny and Alexander" in 1982. In fact, "Saraband" in the beginning was only a proposed television in Sweden. But, on its own initiative, is has been premiering gradually throughout the world. With almost all of his life devoted to the film, Bergman is still the Bergman always. And it is a pleasure to be able to confirm this. But "Saraband" stays there. It goes beyond, if that is possible. Here is the spirit of the master, culminating its zenith, reaching a rank of unspeakable maturity. It is a great example of how to end a career, how to reach the top without changing or force an iota of his personality. What other "dying" directors decline, in Bergman is maturity. And they may not observe his work rather than envy and cleanliness. This is what distinguishes the art of purely aesthetic. "Saraband", whose production dates back to 2003, but its premiere us fails so far to our country, is, above all, cinema of confessions. Here, the visual power of films such as "Wild strawberries" goes into potential of dialogues and people. Bergman immerses your analytical camera to hidden most of us, until you reach a closeness that goes beyond the impossible in the purely material. The camera is approaching our faces, to decipher them, to scrutinize them and continue getting to penetrate the eyes. His emotional, serene and leisurely, analysis is so human that, occasionally, it goes beyond the unbearable. Its density, its simplicity at the same time, does not lead to breathing. On many occasions we are so participants of the torment of their characters that we cannot maintain the type. For this reason, "Saraband" is not a film that we pull the couch kicking. It is not a film that really us. "Saraband", as entire Filmography of the director, generates a feeling of helplessness so strange that it causes that, at times, our eyes flee from the screen and seeking refuge. It is more violent, in this regard, that any film that is meant to be using other methods. The theologian born in Upsala, gets full (no possible return) in the turbulence of a family is any grubbing-up sense of our more full of humanity nature Genesis. From the cruel and deranged hatred (that seems to have no sense at times) until the love of more rampant, going through the agony, the anguish and sacrifice. A sacrifice that detailed the unexplained family ties which unite and generate all kinds of reactions, but that gives us the pleasure of knowing that we are the same person, a same blood. same pain. It is always the desconhort understanding our past, know our roots, and feel that we are, inexorably, part of them. Our life will seek new paths, away or not our family, but that invisible Union we grab and doesn't let us escape is inevitable. Bergman, "Saraband" retrieves the characters of "Secrets of a marriage", but in a different environment. While the second focuses on a topic in particular, in his last film, Bergman, speaks to us of everything and nothing in particular. It portrays the obsessions of his lifetime of film, as the ravings about the death, strained family relations which arouse more profound and irrational hatred and heartfelt love (among which there paradox, however much it may seem), convictions, deep belief and the elitist musicality surrounded by the person of Freud or Strindberg. And here we have everything. And it scares much the follower of the Bergman film, it has an air of vital and intimate testimony that makes arise many (and obvious) things. As if it were a theatre or a piece of camera work, Bergman builds, thus a story which is structured into 10 pieces, as well as a prologue and an epilogue. This story follows the beat of a music that hides the sins in the most intimate of us and manages to corrupt us until the selfishness and intolerance, without addressing to confessions and emanating from wounds not healed from the past. The sublime music of Bach and Brahms, at certain times and intentionally reaches rumbling until the pain in our bodies. It is not more than a metaphor plotted by the genius to reinforce the sense that aims to acquire the narration. Therefore, without going any further, the title ("saraband") is related to times of the Bach suites, composed for cello and normally done as a couple. As the intense talks of the protagonists, who engaged in them two by two acquiring a musicality that establishes the resemblance between the musical metaphor and the emotional situation. As a metaphorical point of Union and family destruction (and music, is to continue with the structure of the work), have to Anna, the mother, the wife, the "daughter". She (this actress is, neither more nor less, of a wife of the own Bergman, who died of cancer) is the point of family coherence, which if it collapses and disappears, will cause the loss of stability in this core. Occurs the amputation of a member of the family, and the consequences dot so far as to the own Marianne, as we got to see in this beautiful and poetic epilogue. So, we have a range of subjects ranging from the religiosity of the music and some of their images (despite focusing mostly on dialogues and people, there is a scene that shows a nearly utopian and Heavenly beauty) to the successful treatment of the aging or sordid torment that accompanies the characters and goes further than the personal sufferinguntil spiritual torment and, in essence, metaphysical. Like them, we will feel anguish, but because of the sacrifice we will achieve the beauty of the company, the rubbing of skin that prevents that the pain is something unbearable, and the conviertirá in a raw, but pleasant emotions obtaining. Because this is how we are human beings. Paradoxical? Incomprehensible? Maybe too easy and primary. As those families that, after the loss, dot the surroundings with hatred, claiming thirst for revenge and demonstrating an intolerance and selfishness unexplained. But, at the same time, loving. For this reason, nothing makes us think that, as some cited, Bergman was present something more negative than usual. Is he himself. It is maturity. With this consistency overwhelming and full of sincerity in the totality of his work, and with it, his hand, as it could not be otherwise, farewell also. It is Bergman. We ourselves. With our concerns and our vital dalliances. And that surprises every day in its form of film-making (art): possesses a domain to bring the catharsis of the moments of the talks beyond doubt, without giving an opinion or making judgment about it, simply by pointing and introducing, as do the great artisans with existential concerns (see Kieslowski). And it shows pain that exists inside the storm of emotions, the stream of unexplained sensations, confusion and desire, the inherent power of pride. and beauty, although us escape and hide in the most recondite areas of our being. It need to know find her, that it sometimes seems not to want to be found. Thus bids farewell to Ingmar Bergman. As always. At the top, and well over his "opponents" film. He says goodbye with a sublime mixture between the power of theatre and cinema, focusing on dialogues and actors (sovereign work by Liv Ullmann and Erland Josephson) to deal with all the weight of the work. If "Saraband" isn't a masterpiece (adding what it represents and is at the same time) or rights not the unmitigated 10, it is not easy to say what other movie could deserve it. His finest plans, their anthology confessions. the film is simple development, but it is so complex and deep, contains both vital sense inside that, at times, will escape to the understanding of many. It requires an "extra" effort and preparation and knowledge of the filmmaker. Perhaps, therefore, the Viewer is not ready feel how weigh you the dialogues, you will notice uncomfortable, dazed and anxious before its density. But these are the effects of knowing to Bergman. Although for them it is already too late. Or not. So are things. "Saraband": the testament of Bergman, not to hear or read between lovers who have been persecuted during his career the figure of the genius. But a testament has pages. And these pages can be read over and over again throughout life. And with them learn and, increasingly, discover new things. As much as Bergman disappears, as reflected at the beginning of the critique, its footprint it will never. There is his timeless work for souls in search of course. A course that, despite everything, are unaware. We lost to Kieslowski, we lost to Dreyer. Now. He is about to lose the other with the disappearance of Bergman. Despite the greatest of everything, those pages are indelible. They are pages of a genius. And do never forget. Forever, Ingmar Bergman. </body>
</review>
