<review author="Hartigan" title="Clerks 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story that do not recover the magic of the original, but that does not stop being a tolerable continuation.</summary>
	<body>Twelve years later, the laborers return. Dante Hicks (Brian or?)(Halloran) and Randal Graves (Jeff Anderson) again put behind a counter to do what they like, without its trabajos-basura, laze and have witty conversations (or at least intended) on inconsequential and preferably offensive subjects. Does the original campus (replacing the original shop with a burger bar) joined Elias (Trevor Fehrman)? a fan of the transformers ultracatólico freak? and the two girls in the life of Dante: his girlfriend Emma (Jennifer Schwalbach, the director's wife) that is about to marry and whose parents seek to fix them life in Florida, and Becky (Rosario Dawson), the Manager of the premises with which he maintained an adventure. And how it can not be otherwise this being a product Kevin Smith, there teem Jay and the silent Bob (Jason Mewes and Smith himself), icons of the generation X or very worn jokes as fall you to everyone.Curious decision of Smith returned to where everything began. Clerks was an unprecedented independent cinema triumph and Smith catapulted to fame, but the director of New Jersey has failed since then connect with the public that exalted him. With the exception of the products only to fans of Jay and Bob, his last films (Chasing Amy and Jersey Girl) were sonados batacazos. We don't know if what the success or the age has lost to Kevin Smith, but the key to Clerks was in its irony, bad milk and bittersweet look on his generation. Since then, Smith seems to have been only saved the bad baba to his critics and demonstrates the need for sentimental plots which do not square and that leave one perplexed.Smith knows that it is his hooligan side that makes it special to his film. In Clerks 2 has tried to overcome the original but as it has not succeeded in creating more funny situations, these are simply more beasts. Frankly, one understands that a spectator to the tone of the dialogues is tempted to get up and go (without justifying the critic who starred in the famous scene). In Clerks, a person inadvertently had sexual intercourse with a corpse. In Clerks 2, a person has willingly considerably explicit with a donkey sex, while another masturbates at the time that apologizes to Jesus. Of the prank we have gone to the coarse brush, which will not dish taste for all.That is why the sentimental plot of the movie even more incongruous. Not only is conventional: is even ñoña. It is the triumph of love, family and friendship, the need to believe in yourself without being conditioned by the conventions. A final truly Disney, replacing the fairy godmothers by Jay and Bob in an acrid plot twist. Because that is what intuíamos with Mallrats and here are proven definitively: Smith is Disney with swearing. We dare to say that Clerks 2 is a family film with images as Dante's drooling before a toothless little girl that yours (again, the daughter of Smith), but see hard to keep the ears of children covered during the other half of the film, in which discusses the virtues of a sexual practice of alternate consecutively sodomy with oral sex.Smith is the Shyamalan of comedy. A director not merely has his own style, but is identified in aberrant levels with their own films and those locks himself in his personal universe, which seems able to secede. Smith grabs its players and its themes as fetishes, and thence out the successes and failures of the films. As successes highlight that, when it does not exceed, the humor of Smith reaches quotas of genius, well within its genre meta-freak. The generational clash between fans of the star wars and the Lord of the rings is hilarious, but one has the feeling that instead would be outside the cinema, not on screen. The main failure is however the inability to carry the film beyond the anecdote. The love triangle is particularly disastrous. I think wonderful Smith considered his wife as "the girl that everyone wanted in the Institute", but the reality is one and does not forgive. His role as blossom not simply strain. Dawson, for its part, seems to have only two records: sex bomb or girl freak, according to camera privilege their succulent Anatomy or his little graceful jaw (another trick is usually set if get you glasses or not). His romance with Dante seems completely forced, by many miraditas of lamb put you (does not help you create to hear the music of shark everytime Dawson smiles) and its conversion of cynical nihilist believer in love has the credibility of a euro of San Marino. The rest of the actors make the unique role that have ever made (I am not exaggerating, lean your chips: most or only working for Smith or Smiths) in a story that do not recover the magic of the original, but that does not stop being a tolerable continuation.</body>
</review>
