<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Savage Grace" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This recreation of the tragedy of the family ' bakelite' is nothing more than a folletín ill-conceived, closer to weak than a solid story. That Yes, Julianne Moore, as always, salvageable.</summary>
	<body>I do not know you, but I'm bored of the claim of some to not leave anyone indifferent. The unbalanced characters based this novel story had a mental cocoa can be, to some extent, something logical and interesting to show. Since then, the nuances and folds are enriching when making a movie, but the director of the concoction - certainly nothing cheap - is not clear how to tell it, is something that weighs as a slab.Tom Kalin friend jumped to the fore with a key title in the New Queer Cinema, something that I had to explain - is the split more gay of the independent movement that emerged in the ninety-. This understanding it costs least find out the reason for the change of direction of the passionate filmmaker by unearthing the secrets of the criminal mind and the stories out of the ordinary though curious as all real. It is also true that no vira too the filmmaker of Swoon, because you will that carry taboos to the screen.This challenge is noteworthy although claims are not live: no matter that explicit sexual scenes that violate our modesty are, is somewhat interesting to see how the performers try to deal with cumbersome lands, but fails the frame, the outline of the characters and the relationships between them. It is a pity, especially for those who have left their mark in this movie and those who expected something more about this episode on the decay of the upper class in freefall, that always like to see on the big screen.If something this proposal is to demonstrate that Spain can come from outside to make cinema: Barcelona disparate locations are recreated each other as Paris, London, New York and Mallorca - in Cadaqués Yes that rolled of truth. They are places for those who pass the heirs of the creator of bakelite, the family Baekeland, deranged, Yes, but with adventurous spirit, or rather, escapist. By the way, are just illusory effluents, that lost in the garden of casa, by very large, emotion has no. Like this movie.</body>
</review>
