<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Inland empire" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Abstain-loving people of classicism and the basic narrative approach, knot and outcome; There's nothing of that, the classical is obvious and is destroyed, giving way to the new concepts of modern cinema.</summary>
	<body>First of all, may I begin my particular vision of Inland Empire with a few words of its director, David Lynch, when searching for funding to finish filming his last work: I told them two things, I'm shooting on digital video and I do not know what I'm doing.With two balls Lynch; more impossible sincerity. And not content with that, ended his argument by saying: never saw a whole. I only saw holes. A lot of them. But that I was not concerned. It happened me an idea for a scene and then filming her. I occurred another, and her filming. He didn't even know how could relate each other. Is true that after Mulholland Drive, expect much again from the Sr.Lynch; and as always happens in these cases, expected just disappointing. Inland Empire has a undeniable visual, harrowing, dark and sinister power. It is a visual spectacle unmitigated, seasoned with a touch of mystery and despair so your mind retuerza and try to get a more or less logical explanation of what is happening. But on the contrary happened with Mulholland Drive, this explanation fails never, or at least I didn't the see. But I've already discussed above in Mulholland Drive, i.e. the universe Lynch and Lynch is not Michael Bay, so they abandon all hope of matching in the work. If with Mulholland Drive, Lynch laid the foundations of the new era of postmodern cinema, breaking all the canons of narrative structure up date you, with Inland Empire has taken one further step, it has spawned a new cinema, has elevated his original idea to the maximum power. It has done what they wanted and as wanted. And he has wanted to do some extensive three-hour, spread over an hour of more or less logic and two hours of disjointed scenes (in) communicated through doors that open us step to parallel realities, to changes in temporary space where mixed us the yesterday, today and tomorrow. Film inside the film, that is what has been proposed but altering the concept of reality and mixing it to infinity. Laura Dern, the basic pillar and character envelope behind the film is supernatural, adapting to every scene perfectly, and closing an interpretation of how complex and credible. Just great. It is technically perfect. With an excellent digital image, with the virtues and shortcomings that this entails, gives us a dirty and dark, grainy texture and artificial image photography, but as well is in the film. Thanks to the digital Lynch allows to play with the camera to suit, deform and adapt the image of thousand forms. The most striking in Lynch is the visual power of its images, capable of loading of concern, mystery and even fear oppressive and distressing spaces. During the viewing, we have hundreds of first, finest levels where we will see pores, stains and any type of damage on the skin of the actors. A montage of lights, where they emphasize the blue and Red (is Lynch) generating a sense of disquieting proximity with the protagonist. In short, exceptional postmodern film from Lynch that breaks with all and like more unconditional fans. Abstain-loving people of classicism and the basic narrative approach, knot and outcome; There's nothing of that, the classical is obvious and is destroyed, giving way to the new concepts of modern cinema. Rest you two points from Mulholland Drive by its excessive length and have not understood the message I wanted to convey Lynch; 100 % Although I have very clear that he himself knows, and not be laughing right now me and all his fans. Still, bravo David.</body>
</review>
