<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Donnie Darko" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sobrevaloradísima excentridad wrapped in the form of mystery and psychological drama. All the enigma that appears at the beginning goes to deaf ears, losing all the suggestive and stimulating that was.</summary>
	<body>Sobrevaloradísima excentridad wrapped in the form of mystery and psychological drama. Is true that starts well, start very well, but little by little and measure that go is diluted so inscrutable to wanting to cover more topics which in truth can withstand the Richard Kelly film. To begin with, we have a mysterious and disturbed Jake Gyllenhaal (not hit anything) as the protagonist of the story; becoming pass through teenager Institute with twenty or so years. But that is not the best of all, it is best that attention! Drew Barrymore (Drew, you are almost on the same level as Sandra Bullock on my black list; have been the charming girl from ET?) makes her teacher! By God, if it may have him older than her in real life. At the moment a 0 for responsible for casting. Returning to the film, seems that you want to boot, hook the Viewer, hypnotize by the mystery that surrounds it, but everything remains in an I want to and I can not. Really want it to work, but fails. All the enigma that appears at the beginning goes to deaf ears, losing all the suggestive and stimulating that was. He wants to be independent cinema and at the same time attract the youth audience with the story of the problematic teenager in the typical American people. This is all very touched, so strain you of travel time, and go; We have movie. Not me so I swallow. Apart from all this, the pace is tedious and slow in equal parts, with scenes without sense (Smurfs) and amount of resources that lead to nowhere (scenes and Assembly with rate 100% videoclipero) and that fill in only minutes of footage. Let's go now to the good stuff. The interpretation of Gyllenhaal is elite and interesting. Empatizas quite well with his character, but do not know that it is what is happening. The music is great, fits perfectly in the "roll" that brings the movie. The initial idea is good, but as I said, is diluted as it progresses. He wants to play many existential and philosophical issues, and at the end just to not complete in depth none of them. The "evil rabbit" is impressive. For me, the best of the film by far. Manages to reflect the anguish and confusion he feels the protagonist. Everytime it appears the film manages to be real scary. Bravo for the people of design. Anyway, which part of a good premise but stays in a simple intent. The end is coming from far away, a little more than originality Sr.Kelly. The conversation of the Smurfs, smurfette and the sexuality that was intended to? Please, leave the job of absurd talks to the genius of Tarantino, and focus on his film; the public will thank you. Anyway, I do not know, found it me too pretentious in some moments, and especially in the last few minutes. Of subject matter similar to the great trapped in time, and the suggestive the butterfly effect. Certainly for me, it is the third of the three. Ultimately, sobrevaloradísima place at the tail.</body>
</review>
