<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="En el valle de Elah" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A patriotic father in search of the truth that finally reflects on the mental and political state of the Goliath in which it lives. In the Valley of Elah is the proof that this 2008 can be a real year of cinema.</summary>
	<body>In the biblical story of David and Goliath, a strong Monster - Goliat - challenged to a village on the other side of the Valley that fought with him, and several of its inhabitants dared, but however none managed to defeat him. One day appeared David, with his ingenious strategy managed to defeat Goliath, not approaching, but a simple honda with a stone. It is known by all that the United States have always been symbolized, politically speaking, such as Goliath, a strong and powerful type that only attacks with his useless physical powers and not his head. The Viet Nam war was already symbolized as this confrontation, where Vietnamese people represented David and the aforementioned States Goliath. And this, as, unfortunately, time has not changed, continues with the ongoing war of Irak.Brian of Palma showed us a hard realism with the life of the soldiers in this latest war in the magnificent mockumentary Redacted. Now, after this and several attempts to revive the consciousness USA, as Redford with his lions and lambs, comes the wonderful and award-winning Crash, Paul Haggis, director to show us how to return these soldiers of Iraq and what and why have become virtually inhuman beings. With a breathtaking and superb performance of Tommy Lee Jones, the film moves at a prodigious pace slower than fast; It is a discourse on evil and useless war, on a patriotic father in search of the truth that finally reflects on the mental and political state of the Goliath that lives (magisterial and memorable the last plane of the film). Charlize Theron gives us another of his great performances, putting at the height of the main protagonist and perfectly equipped with pure humanism, as well as the always sensational Susan Sarandon, which in brief appearances we shrink the heart to all. And it is behind a police plot and a terrible family tragedy, a fierce and already mentioned criticism of the policy of one of the most powerful countries in the world, with brilliantly carried out and cinematically wonderful sequences that reach the heart and conscience. Perhaps the only thing we can condemn this magnificent film is the amount of characters that appear in a seen and unseen and that, however, could have given much more than itself (as a result, there are some scenes of which I, personally, convert), but not in this intimate drama. Full of realism, with a virtually perfect script and some interpretations of Oscar, in the Valley of Elah is proof that this 2008 may be a real year of movies, therefore it is undoubtedly an exceptional start.</body>
</review>
