<review author="Jesus David" title="Juno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Juno is a good film, different (but not both), entertaining, fun, but neither is the eighth wonder of the world, which is what suggest many critics and nominations to the Oscars.</summary>
	<body>A few days ago I said that he would go to see John Rambo, but I had to choose between this and Juno, that the economy does not provide for both. The case is that I thought that see the new Stallone would make me a lobotomy by what went to see the movie before us. Juno is a good film, different (but not both), entertaining, fun, but neither is the eighth wonder of the world, which is what suggest many critics and nominations to the Oscars. Even so, ceo that I was right to choose movie, if you follow reading I tell you. If not, not.The story focuses on Juno (Ellen Page) a 16 year girl who becomes pregnant of Bleeker (Michael Cera) a classmate. Juno is believed to be the most convenient giving child/Amoeba/bug nail some adoptive parents to not be ready for such a commitment. A simple and at the same time complex story with good intentions and a more than credible interpretations. Even Jennifer Garner is more than acceptable.When I speak of the actors I would highlight to Ellen Page for one more than credible role, it is possible that his nomination as best actress is not so far-fetched idea at first may seem, especially after watching the competition. On the other hand is Michael Cera, a guy who falls well just to see his face, here it seems that he repeated the role of Superbad but the truth is that it comes to or painted, see much future in the two. Also note to Jason Bateman and j. k. Simmons, although it could have given them a little more than role.If we adhere to the nominations, for best foreign film comes a little big, at least when comparing loser. And the nomination for best director. for more of the same. More understandable are the nominations for best actress, as I have already said, and best original screenplay, which is fairly currado. The film leaves a good taste, due, in large part, to the excellent soundtrack that accompanies and, for me, the end find it me beautiful and very successful.Are not dealing with a comedy of splitting the chest as it can be Mortadelo y Filemón and Donkey Xote (Note irony). It has good comic moments, intelligent but sometimes dialogues are "too smart", and a touch of drama that comes pretty well. A good movie totally recommended to view throughout the week. For the next must be open hole for the new Coen (is No country for old men) and Tim Burton (Sweeney Todd).</body>
</review>
