<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="The Jane Austen Book Club" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If someone has the higadillo endure nearly two hours attacked women discussing life and love with the background of the novels of Jane Austen (basically complaining about it) then later.</summary>
	<body>A group of five women: a divorcee expert, a lesbian, a frustrated married, one in separation process and another with serious problems to the commitment decide to meet once a month to make one of these clubs of books that both like the Americans. The object of reading will be the work of so of fashion Jane Austen what need a sixth member as each chooses one of the novels and host one of the meetings. Six books, six months and six appointments. Each of them will have a curious parallel with the characters of the novels who choose. That is the common thread. The unsuspecting sixth will be a handsome young man who rides on bike and is assiduous reader of science fiction invited by one of them to help her friend on full separation to forget her husband and that will obviously lead to the romantic entanglement of this as linear plot.I am not a faithful reader of Jane Austen. Not so much at least as the protagonists of this film are able to devour the chivalrous novels by English author over and over again. I recognize that of his six books I have read (some more than once) more than half but I do not consider header books why in the middle of talks was so lost cone character Grigg, which, in fact, found me the only thing decent and entertaining the tape.Otherwise if someone has the higadillo endure nearly two hours of targeted women discussing the life and love (basically complaining about it) then later. For the rest of mortals who have not decided to do a master's degree on the female philosophy since the 19th century to the present day, well will ignore this tape and cease to be seduced by the young Jane Austen, sense and sensibility, pride and prejudice, Emma, Masfield Park and persuasion (the sixth, that with "a title with some Abbey" as my friend shiny new Dancy is my weak point and not even know that it will) in their large or small screen versions; Another option is to devour the books in order to keep some of the illustrative club meetings of readers of the tape before us (which is a great effort that honestly does not deserve) and the final option is to directly go to the website of the film before and study well the synopsis and characters in books that explain divinely (and also link with little shame with wikipedia)(, indisputable source of universal knowledge).</body>
</review>
