<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Casino" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Scorsese directs and runs well. After a lengthy introduction of characters, he hoped a rhythm and frantic Assembly, where the greatest achievement consist not bore to the public despite his extensive footage.</summary>
	<body>While watching Casino, he could not find Parallels and commonalities with a work by the late Ted Demme. I am referring to the unjustly undervalued, Blow. Someday will analyse Blow, that shocked me a lot your viewing, and still regard her as one of my favorite movies. But let's go back to what we are discussing and replace the game in casinos worldwide by drug trafficking, and have two extremely similar works. Yes, I know that Blow (2001) is the later Casino (1995), but I have not been able to stop find similarities between the two. From the escalation of posts in an illegal organization, until the betrayal of your best friend, through the pu ** of your wife that only cares your money and the situation with the small daughter. Up a musical theme is repeated in both films. Two tapes have found me very similar, with De Niro as Depp, Sharon Stone as Pe Cruz and Joe Pesci as Jordi Mollà. It seems that Casino Scorsese wanted to film he both likes and better given in directing. After two works which away a bit of the context that it was Martin, I am referring to the Cape fear, and especially the age of innocence, Scorsese takes the film to better do. Casino can be understood as a sequel to Goodfellas, but ends up being a rehash excessively long (almost 3 hours duration) full of clichés of the genre where adds nothing new. What good? That Scorsese directs and runs well. And does it so with dignity and as one of the greats. After a lengthy introduction of characters, he hoped a rhythm and frantic Assembly, where the greatest achievement consist not bore to the public (Although everything I have seen over and over again) despite its extensive footage. De Niro is sublime as always, and with such contrapicados that makes you is Martin patent who carries the weight of the film. Sharon Stone is simply amazing as she the truth. And who say Joe Pesci, exceeding (was already difficult) outweigh its role in one of our reintrerpretándose if same as bully without a brain. Just brutal. Bright and luminous photography, get truly convey the lifestyle of Las Vegas, and these enhanced levels of the casino are simply great. Finally, what I liked most has been the final scene where we see to the rhythm of The house of the rising sun by The Animals, the slaughter of some members. It reminded me also a lot at the end of the godfather I, when Al Pacino indirectly running his revenge while he remains at the baptism of his nephew. Too many coincidences right? Despite everything, a work complete and very well directed by Scorsese albeit at medium bellows if compared to Goodfellas, the basic pillar of the next Scorsese filmography to Taxi driver and raging bull. For my taste of course.</body>
</review>
