<review author="Cecil B. Demente" title="Mad monster party?" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Musical comedy with puppets animated by stop motion and a delicious dish for all good lover of the genre.</summary>
	<body>Baron Frankenstein, head of the world Organization of monsters and scientist crazy, just invent a formula capable of destroying matter, so it decided to mount a party so that all their relatives know the good news. Quickly sends his messengers bats to Dracula, the Wolf Man, the Mummy, the Hunchback of Notre Dame, Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, the creature from the Black Lagoon, the Invisible Man and Felix Flanken, his young nephew pharmaceutical (the thing not invited because it has a reputation for spoilers it).During the event, the doctor makes a demonstration of the destructive capabilities of its new potion and informed his guests that he has decided to retire now that he's at the peak of his career. His successor will inherit the position and all its secrets, so there is no one who does not want the post. Tejerán conspiracies, planearán murders, create alliances and betrayals as if it were a Shakespearean play, and is soon rolling of Saint-Quentin. But, what are King Kong on all this?Musical comedy with puppets animated by stop motion and a delicious dish for all good lover of the genre: Jules Bass made of head chef, Harvey Kurtzman (Publisher of EC Comics and Mad magazine creator) is responsible for the script and Jack Davis from character design, while Peter Lorre and Boris Karloff, Phyllis Diller provided voices and features the characters. Have they begun to babear already?If they now give us the coñazo with the great magical epics, the 1960s was fashionable in the monstrous. A monstrous child and quite low in calories, that Yes, that in the previous decade had imposed the fucking Comics Code, and everyone was with the fly after the ear for stopping censorship (do won't be the Mr Fotolog relative of Fredic Wertham, evil bug author of the book The Seduction of the Innocent?). The own Kurtzman was one of the hardest to clad his line of horror comics ("Stories from the crypt" and company), and those had happened straws really if it weren't for him remained in the limelight magazine Mad. Humor in this film not far from the television era productions as "The Addams Family" and "The Munsters", genuinely white humor composed mostly of easy jokes, obvious double entendres and much slapstick (remember that this is a basically child movie and not a sophisticated comedy). Animation also may seem rudimentary, but is that when it comes to taking stock one is forgotten these details. Rarely has parodied the monsters of the Universal with both respect as here, the presentation of the characters is just great, excellent design of the monsters, the hell soundtrack, and there are unforgettable momentazo to stop a car. We have for instance Dracula dancing tap dance to King Kong battling an army of zombies bird men, and a fight for female puppet in underwear, starring the bride of Frankenstein and a femme fatale of reddish hair that has stolen my heart (is that me bad I can!). The such Francesca her ask for reyes.It is logical to think that where the rest of Americans save a Bible, Tim Burton has this film. In the table, along with your pills for insomnia and the comics of Edward Gorey.</body>
</review>
