<review author="Ramón Besonias" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With such that talk of a product, what does that roses to tomatoes throw you! The essence of what cool is not the beauty, but advertising. Congratulations, Abrams, and fun while it lasts.</summary>
	<body>Cloverfield (his title in Spanish is so monstrous that better ignore) is born more of the reins of an effective and and intelligent marketing of production - at the hands of the geniecillo of the world television (yours are the lost series or Alias) called the j. j. Abrams - that of the artistic idea of its almost inexperienced director, Matt Reeves, Director of that other television success of name Felicity.Y Abrams is that the letters notice you to Cloverfield, which shows the Viewer without modesty but not without moving with carefully orchestrated steps. Little was known of this production, and that leaking out made with willingness to rouse the curiosity and passion of thousands of souls geeks that populate the universe of our network in search of fresh meat to feed his cinephiles before even still in Turkey have been slaughtered.Cloverfield is a precast product to win, though not without certain risks that come in its vast majority of aesthetics still Virgin in the large format (although make the delicacies of the youtubeadictos), that easily misleads even to the palomitero public that is delivered without any more words to nothing prophylactic love of the cine-espectáculo. It uses two attractive premises from outside indirectly to the seventh art media. One, the cathartic need the American people anesthetized or purge the ghosts of 11-S, and two, take advantage of the pull that provides fashion of new audiovisual formats born without c-section in the digital world.On the first point, Abrams plays with the spectator, marking a script austere, more like soap opera than a blockbuster (without appearance of being), focused on the need of the young protagonist through the barriers that are precise in order to tell his beloved i love you. Of course this rescue romantic plan medieval folletín with Dragon somewhat orientalizado through, although without much sword that mediate conflicts (that are already the marines), garnished with the pageantry Hollywood special effects that are intended to cover the Schematic of the proposal. But let us not deceive ourselves, the result convinces, fun, even in some another scene up restless. That Yes, provided support Parkinson's hyperactive camera that follows the Odyssey without Ítacas of its protagonists. In its favour joins a fair (sixty-five more or less) minutaje makes perdonables these excesses.The metaphorical iconicidad of the head of the statue of liberty on the asphalt of the streets of Manhattan; These lacquered bodies of dust, walking as zombies, disoriented in a whitish penumbra; skyscrapers set ablaze overnight; the collective paranoia of hundreds of citizens fleeing from a threat whose identity unknown. Cloverfield too reminiscent of the feeling of a population who still tries to put the pieces of the chaotic emotional puzzle of that fateful day. Only that Cloverfield not it will provide them more medicine that one hour of audiovisual catharsis, touring with the protagonist the horror and the nonsense of a phantom menace that is still there, enthroned in the psyche of New York.This therapeutic end, without redeeming will plays into Cloverfield, repositioned within the virtues of the genre, beyond the usual ideologizantes Caprices to which we are accustomed. (Even I am legend falls without remission in this weakness made in Hollywood).On the other hand we have the aesthetic issue of mad and subjective camera, vaunted as maligned by critics. Opportunism? Course, and will die (envy, of course) the Puritans that exorcizan (the bishops as sex without love) the film dedicated to the pleasure of the banal. Right opportunism? Well if look at the box office, certainly very successful. If on the contrary we circunscribimos to the flat aesthetic and their suitability with the Mise en scene and the script, the views may vary according to taste. About (and not only will the talluditos) it mareará them both to Penina, and they may expect that the monster comes out more between plane and plane of people screaming and Fireworks. Others interpreted this as a virtue that ennobles the whole, either because it predicts a film if not new (already there past examples), less foreboding of the absorption of this art by other hitherto debtor audiovisual industries endorsed, either to raise the altars of the geek sanctuary a product that refuses to be taxonomizado.There are even in a hermeneutic effort (it must be said, very conventional) deconstruirán Cloverfield as a clear symptom of the virtual nature of the conception of the world in Western culture. Everything is seen through the eyes of a lens that replaces the emerging physical reality in everyday acts shamelessly. This lens moves, breathes, simulating reality; why you need movement, these frames and cut dialogues. The very fact of the attack of 11-S is drawn under the perplexed gaze of a spectator watching TV without believing that beyond the screen nothing may be real. But it is.Finally, in order to speak of a product, what does that roses to tomatoes throw you! The essence of what cool is not the beauty, but advertising. Congratulations, Abrams, and fun while it lasts.</body>
</review>
