<review author="Yul B." title="Monster house" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When you contrapones the child aspect of the House with such a serious air, adult and real scenes completely breaks the climax of the film.</summary>
	<body>I read recently in a blog in which they usually visit the more critical a film by bad, more is the public to see. It seems that we are a few moviegoers masochists. In my case nothing happens at all. By deformation blogger I'm aware of the criticisms of the greater impact of the film scene movies to contrasting views; and that makes me quite the choice to see one or the other in the film.However, there are tapes so overwhelming that they are criticisms against do me not desist in my decision to watch her. And one of them was this. The fact that Robert Zemeckis and Steven Spielberg are his godparents are part of blame. The trailer for the film got with me the effect I wanted (the desire to see it), and the story also: D.J. Walters, a twelve-year-old boy, has too much free time and he has gotten in his head that there is something strange in the House of the elder Nebbercracker on the other side of the street.Just a day before Halloween, D.J. and his friend Croquette have a meeting with Mr Nebbercracker after releasing the ball from basketball to your garden and mysteriously arrives at the interior of the House. When the House comes swallow to his new friend Jenny and no one believes what he says the three children, who claim that the House has something evil, they rush to the task of investigating what's happening.The visual invoice of the film is impressive. Animation of motion capture, which is used with an incredible master, here manages to insurmountable levels of perfection to date. Do the magnificent rendering of each character and its surroundings and the amazing handling of the camera, getting this absolutely amazing flat, do us believe that we are witnessing a film? real? of real actors. My friends, everything around?Monster House? has personality and life of its own; here a 10 as a House.With regard to the development of the plot, another success. Who has not had any time in his childhood ghostly fantasies with abandoned houses?; and, who has resisted to enter these houses, with more fear than value, to discover his secret?. In the latter perhaps not so many have dared, but this film plays with this approach and shows you a charm, with a frenetic pace, what is what might happen in that situation.Do we have a product created with a clear mix of horror and adventure, and with clear references to movies of these two genera belonging to the 1980s, with?The Goonies? and?Night of fear? at the head. At this point it shows the League the hand of her godparents, Zemeckis and Spielberg; and, in this regard, I enjoyed as a child.Then, in what it fails the film?, why her qualify as mediocre?. Because, in my opinion, it fails the main thing: the House.Let me explain. ?Monster House? is not a child tape; do not we are before a movie? disneyniana?, type?Looking for Nemo? or?The Little Mermaid?, with white and sensibleros moments. We speak of a product aimed at teenagers and adults who retain something that teens. Because from the very beginning of the film, and during the rest of its duration, we will witness harrowing scenes, those that transmit some trepidation. It's a light fear, but sufficient to create an atmosphere of uneasiness, sure would provoke more than one nightmare to more than one child.Bearing in mind this premise, not block too that what causes that fear, the House, represents form humanized and caricatured, or infantilizada llamemoslé (SPOILER: yea, yea, Windows are the eyes, the door is the mouth, the tongue is a carpet and timber with which it is built are twisted to make gestures and expressions).It is clear that there is a reason for why it is, that I do not desvelaré, but when you contrapones this child aspect of the House with the air so serious, adult and real scenes completely breaks the climax of the film. Do do i.e., at that time ceases to be credible, and not perfect? motion capture animation technique? She is saved. In any case, knowing this fact and opening your mind to the fantasy, you'll spend with her a fun time.</body>
</review>
