<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Bajo las estrellas" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Movie Viscarret, offers us a return trip to the roots for a second chance, found in oneself. One of the great Spanish bets of last year and a movie that invites you to dream.</summary>
	<body>It was released as brand new winner in the latest edition of the Festival de Málaga awards for best film, director, actor (Alberto San Juan) and novel screenplay under the arm. Under the tutelage in the production of one of the great conductors and Spanish producers, Fernando Trueba, director beginner Felix Viscarret, signing one of the best Spanish films seen in the rooms in many years, and one of the great surprises (at least for my) 2007. Watching "under the stars", you realize that to the better is still a glimmer of hope to save the current Spanish film. The magic that transmits the character of Alberto San Juan (in his best role to date), the freshness of the Assembly, this mesmerizing soundtrack that transports you to the selfsame navarro people where the film takes place, and of course this unusual niño-adulto relationship develops throughout the film and which evolves to unsuspected for the Viewer.The tragicomedy that gives us Viscarret, smells that good Spanish movies before, but with the media now. And we have no because being hotly contested classicism and today if sign works like this. Viscarret knows how to insert humor in some dialogues that still making you smile you don't confuse and not fall into the easy laugh.The magic that has succeeded in creating the director in his first long work, and that magic wrap all the footage from the film without rest or a single frame is fascinating. This mix of everyday simplicity and at the same time film poetry that has the work makes this film a cinematic wonder. One bold and brave movie which I hope will become a key part of the future of the Spanish film.Alberto San Juan is simply sublime. Get transmit everything what proposed without just act. It has that innate ability to act in a natural way. Throughout the viewing seems a mere Theatre improvisation. With a perfectly defined character, San Juan sella which is for me, the best performance of his career. After a somewhat hesitant in "Days of the cinema", San Juan gives us a stellar performance, a momentous evolution of his character Benito through some superb dialogues (great also Viscarret writing the screenplay of the novel by Fernando Aramburu) where to find the perfect tone always between comedy and drama.Emma Suárez for his part is simply correct. The truth is that her expected much more from in this role, but fails to fill her scene wherever it appears.The girl, Violeta Rodriguez, is really good. It represents an introverted creature, by the lack of affection and care of an abandoned mother. It shows that it has fitted perfectly with San Juan, and in every scene they have together is overflowing with the chemistry between them on all sides. Encounters between Benito and 'Puerquita' are the best in the following between the two feature a subtle to complete in a mutual love friendship. The evolution of his character, and the complicity that this acquired with Benito is more natural, highlighting the scene in which both characters that are known. They do not need to speak to understand the game of the two eyes says it all in certain sequences. 'Puerquita', which is how St. John refers to the way girl loving, located in the figure of Benito the father that has both sought in his childhood and finally found.Finally, Julián Villagrán, which makes St. John's brother is claimed as an actor giving us a very poignant role mainly by his bonda and innocence, complement to perfection with his other half, his brother Benito.La truth is that unwittingly, Alberto San Juan obscures somehow interpretations of his companions, falling on him all the weight of the film and leaving not only graceful, but adopted with note.As regards the section of sound, Mikel rooms sealed a phenomenal job worthy of the selfsame Alberto Iglesias in any movie by Julio Medem (except for the failed "Caótica Ana"). A perfectly chosen soundtrack, and fits in the movie which gear on a clock. To emphasize, the beginning and end of the film, and the scene that gives title to the film, in which San Juan runs the way back to the people under a blanket of stars. Excellent music and photography in this scene work.Movie Viscarret, offers us a return trip to the roots for a second chance, found in oneself. In short, one of the great Spanish bets of this year, a film that invites to dream; because at the end and life after they are dreams</body>
</review>
