<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="John Rambo" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that despite a flat script, a few mediocre performances and topical development, manages to reach the virtue of fun through a beautiful scenes of action, full of stark and non-political violence.</summary>
	<body>During those warlike 80 years (could well be the title of a compilation of film action cinema bombings), arose a number of actors who fired his popularity playing crude heroes action, in many case touching patriotism reactionary, or in the best of cases, without even being patriotic. Names such as Steven Seagal, Van Damme, Charles Bronson and Arnold Schwarzenegger were commissioned to show us that subtlety is not part of its portfolio of skills. Nevertheless, earned the approval of the public with products where the only trump card played in his favor was a departure violence cool appealing more primary instincts of the human being, and thus of the Viewer. Among them was a character named John Rambo portrayed by Sylvester Stallone, whose first film, back in the year 1982, showed us the complicated return home of Veterans of the war of the Viet Nam, and its extreme difficulty to adapt to daily life, being also little considered by their own Government. In the first film, name "Rambo", attempted to draw an effective portrait of these ex-combatants, and although the film was a solvent product, interesting even, stayed pretty on the surface, using their plot excuse as a pretext to develop what ultimately interested the participants of that project, pure and hard action. Its two sequels, "Rambo: Rambo II" and "Rambo III", as its argument a cluster of reactionary situations mostly would come shortly after to describe in a dangerous manner the intervention of the former soldier in conflict away from its own competence. Especially bloody was the third party, where, in an ironic wink of the destination, the argument placed as comrades of fight to the American Government and the sector extremist who has now posed a threat to its thriving imperialism. All this accompanied by a story full of topics and several chascarillos.Twenty years later comes close to this series, again performed by Sylvester Stallone needed immediate success, and in the hope of finding ourselves with a product the less respectable after the correct "Rocky Balboa" (his previous film, a respectable and entertaining film in development, quite satisfactory but is attends him with too many expectations). "On this occasion, Furthermore, undertakes to direct this"John Rambo"(of"Rambo"name to dry on the American market), a film that retrieves a way of making action films lost in oblivion, and involving the closure of the saga.""John Rambo" shows us the contemplative life that enjoy well-known character in his advanced age, devoted to fishing, catch snakes for a typical show of such demonstrations and wandering aimlessly fixed on some corner lost near the Burmese jungle rivers. When a group of Americans with the intention to trace the River to give humanitarian and medical aid to a Burmese Village, the first reaction of Rambo is tell that it is not a good idea, and refuse to do so in resounding. Finally, by the intervention of a woman (who but) that accompanied the humanitarian aid group, Rambo agrees to carry them up the river and keep them there, intending to return inland themselves. When the plan is twisted and they are captured by the more radical section of the oppressive army Burmese, a group of mercenaries, in collaboration with Rambo (although in principle his opposition to this was obvious), is preparing to rescue them from the barbarity that is lived every day in the Burmese jungles.Stallone is responsible, in his work as director of breathe a visual style recharged, oppressive, so in the taste of the most extreme war genre, in a mise en scene in which demonstrates (as did in "Rocky Balboa") a solvency to take into account when it comes to filming action scenes. Scenes like that opens the film with this macabre game from the Burmese army, they show that the less you know how credible and close a terrible fact, without artifice, form dry and direct. There is never a creative game between image and more director than to advance the narrative, but not why it is less effective. It is also true that the script of the film is extremely flat, devoid of double readings rather than obvious references to the horror of the war, and phrases that are quite ridiculous as that our dear Rambo lectured us with pearls as "live for nothing, or die for something, that really cause more sarcastic laughter that the dramatic effect that it intended to. And although it is true that this script, so it is sensed, leaves a lot to be desired, at least the story unfolds in a fairly direct way, without resorting to script twists that make even clearer the shortcomings of this mindless action product.And it is that the acting section also a truism that scare, removing small nuances of the actress in the role, Julie Benz (known primarily for being the object of desire of Dexter, in the series of the same name), you know give some interest moral dilemma and the suffering the horrors of the war cause it. Of the rest, curiously highlight the degree of absolute nihilism, beyond good and evil, which has acquired Rambo as a character, while this time correct for what was his "absent" performance. The other characterizations of characters are all prototypes of characters already seen thousand times in the war film, with a group of mercenaries which resembles any similar production of gender (some character reminds of irretrievable way certain characters in that wonderful "predator"), and that in addition, do not seem to much endeavour to do better.With all these elements, one might think that the final product is a negligible by-product for consumers of live video, or lovers of the less demanding action. But it is not precisely the case of "John Rambo". And if not so, it is precisely by the previously annotated ability of Stallone to create truly effective action scenes, violent until the end, in a display of incorreción inevitably reminiscent of eighties movies, one that obviated any visual consideration to show us scenes which more violent.Stallone is responsible for offering us a feast of desmembramientos, amputations, GLUGs blood, several explosions and even children's violations, causing a surprise the bystander effect by atypical of the proposal in the current film genre. With regard to this issue, to clarify a couple of important points about glorification of violence as the host of the story. Demonstrates a tremendous ability to overcome setbacks in the form of non-existent through choreography precisely this orgy of blood posed the ably distributed scenes of action throughout the footage, camouflaged with ability to his advanced age and poor ability to choreograph scenes, moments of savagery paroxista, in a plot trick does work, and that leaves a sense of privileged action scenes film (when an in-depth analysis)(, or even a second viewing will stop these alleged scenes, which are simpler than they appear in evidence). It is appreciated anyway, reactionary ideology shine by their absence resulting Rambo even less attached to any kind of ideology in this regard, because it helps those action scenes to justify more empathy for a woman than by anything else (if neglected their ballpark thoughts about his inability to get rid of the war as something inherent)(that they are extremely stupid to all lights).The other point that dominates such effective action scenes, is mounting. It is clear that American cinema it is advancing the action scenes with the level of ability by the editor in these scenes. In this case, it allows not only bolster the trick that used by Stallone to effectively distribute action scenes that seem to be more physical than they are, but also enriches and gives wings to the meaning of these scenes, making them integrated into the story very effectively. No doubt very successful mounting and it helps create the illusion of deep draught action scenes. No opta, for example, by the ability to impeccable place action that normally has the Asian cinema, but by advancing the physical action through a great visual montage. Extremely skilled and solvent, no doubt.Say that the influences of which the film baby are multiple and very mixed, attending even own self-referential sentiment for much of the history, as well as recall in its extreme violence to films such as the hongkonesa saga of "Men behind the Sun", with their various atrocities committed by sickly Asian General.As a result, a film that despite a flat script, a few mediocre performances and topical development, manages to reach the virtue of fun through a beautiful scenes of action, full of descarnada and non-political violence. For fans of the less demanding action.</body>
</review>
