<review author="Christian Sandoval" title="Tras el cristal" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"A disturbing film, showing the unhealthy relationship between victim and perpetrator, that it will be quite difficult to forget once it is seen"</summary>
	<body>"Behind the glass" (1987) is the first feature film of the Spanish director Agustí Villalonga, which was facing a series of problems that delayed its release date. I first present serious problems due to the lack of money to make the film. They were only $300,000 for its realization, which is relatively little if we are talking about a quality production. Once released the film, I am presenting a series of problems of censorship. The truth is that this film is a blow to the senses, it presents a raw and disturbing, plot by what refers to the stir this production reached in his time.Klaus (Gunter Meisner) is a nazi officer who worked in horrible experiments for children. After torturing and killing a child, he attempts suicide, falling prostrate and depending on an iron lung.When Griselda (Marisa Paredes), the wife of Klaus decides to find someone to look after her husband, introduces a young man name Angelo (David Sust) who claims to be a nurse, which offers to take care of Klaus. Despite the mistrust that he produces the younger to Griselda, this it ends up hiring. From this point, began to develop an unhealthy relationship between these two characters, to the point where the young woman offers to be he who run new experiments.The director was inspired by various themes that ended up coming together in this heartbreaking film. First he thought how serious live life through a person, due to the impossibility of moving from one place, which also implies a great degree of confinement. This added to a story he saw about a man dressed as a clown, which divided them sweets to a large number of children, killing them. Finally listening to the story of Gilles de Rais, a Marshal of Joan of arc, a man who allegedly fought for faith in God and finally term committed a series of atrocities, among them who are murdering hundreds of children.These three ideas were that joined to get the central idea of the film. To achieve a greater closeness with the times, her it linked to Nazism and its record of children's experiments during the war.This is how they will make up the two main characters. Klaus, because you are connected to the iron lung, is confined to the machine and the room in which it is found. At the same time, this situation ends cutting off both his wife and his daughter Rena (Gisèla Echevarría). This type is a pedophile and a sadist, which committed a series of atrocities and whose apparent remorse came too late. The other sidewalk is Angelo, a notoriously disturbed young man, which lost the purity and innocence that there may be a child, the same time that he was sexually violated by Klaus. Now the young man has become an extension of Klaus, willing to continue with the atrocities of the nazi ex-oficial began years ago. The difference is that now the roles have changed. Klaus is now who is helpless and scared with the presence of the Angelo who is now where abused and tortured physically and psychologically from him.The plot is rugged and the truth is that the performances, the colours of the film, scenarios and the soundtrack help quite achieve an oppressive atmosphere and quite disturbing. The film occurs mostly in shades of grey or bluish, breaking this pattern only in the few scenes of foreign, which are otherwise quite grey and with the irruption of the color red in three scenes quite specific. This same concern for the visual is complemented with gloomy House in which the film takes place and used costumes, notably that of David Sust which ends up looking like a participant of the Hitler youth. Actions are generally pretty good, protruding from the young Sust, who builds a character quite scary and as sadistic as his "mentor".The soundtrack was conducted by Javier Navarrete ("El laberinto del fauno" 2006), which fits perfectly in the scenes where it is used, helping to increase the tension of these.The film is not exempt from some anecdotes of esoteric and the supernatural, character who align themselves with the problems that existed for lack of money. For example the actor David Sust presented a transient blindness during the making of the film. One of the leading galleries of the House collapsed, dropping a piece of enormous glass very close to the producer of the film. They also had that there was a part of the House where never is could shoot, because there were always strange problems. The director also mentioned that some hallucinogenic mushrooms are known as dealt with in the covens were found in the garden of the House. The truth is that this movie has scenes that are difficult to see, and even more difficult to digest, especially scenes involving children of itself are quite strong. It is a good film, considered to be within the genre of horror, in which translates the evil present in humans in the more obscure manner possible, without necessarily resorting to a large number of scares. The film meets fully the Mission of disrupting the viewer at the same time that the end gives us a reflection on the effects of a circle of abuse, which apparently you cannot escape.Recommended film, but not for everyone. It is definitely a work that can hardly go to oblivion. At least meet with warned.</body>
</review>
