<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="John Rambo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fourth film in the saga of Rambo, where this has to liberate a few doctors from the Burmese clutches. Extremely violent, with special recreation in the viscera and amputated limbs, it is entertaining to see and hard thinking about it.</summary>
	<body>Director: Sylvester StalloneDuración: If die X bad Burmese each and second (where and tends to 0), the duration will be an hour and a half bloody.Release date: 1 February 2008Tengo a couple of teenage girls who I train that the other day they confessed me that they were loving (and do not think that simply Platonic way) of Sylvester Stallone. It may well be his grandpa this gentleman, but it sure that if he learns of this anecdote, takes a plane to meet so young and Idol enthusiasts. By the way, this man you not already worth or use Botox, liquid for embalming mummies? That left the question.The film is about Rambo which is dedicated to the collection of cobras in the asia of the charlies. One day reach his humble abode a mixture of preachers and doctors seeking to enter Burma rio arriba to bring relief to people suffering from a bloody civil war. That they were a moza blonde, if they didn't have to go by metro. Total van, they pick up doctors, and you have Rambo with some mercenaries to release them. Classic pattern.What most impresses the film isn't seeing a man of 60 years dale you hit to the bow and fine cutlery. It impresses the harshness with which conveys a horrible situation that makes us doubt much of the human being. It is clearly the most violent film of the saga, with moments in raw excesses, but that can be taken more as a vehicle to convey a story that as a curiosity by the thick guts. The plot is very simple, letting the developing flow in a very logical way (to be a Rambo, clear). I liked enough, despite a slow start, but it is a tremendously harsh film. I will not return it to see.In short, film fourth in the series of Rambo, where this has to liberate a few doctors from the Burmese clutches. Extremely violent, with special recreation in the viscera and amputated limbs, it is entertaining to see and hard thinking about it. I consider her a plea against violence and wars. I liked it.Besitos.P.D: The joke of embalming is not mine, I heard it on TV. My mother says that this man used growth hormone to keep young. That I estimate that when you have 100 years measured 7 meters, more or less.Pd2: And what looks like this gentleman to my ex-vecino Ricardo.</body>
</review>
