<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Alien vs Predator 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bad film as a testicular kick on a few alien coming from picnic to the Earth and a predator makes guardian of mankind. Or what is I. Bad, very bad. Only viable for those viewers who like this type of movies.</summary>
	<body>Director: Colin StrauseDuración: Infernal hour and a half.Release date: January 11, 2008. how great was Hugo Sánchez, the more male between males. It was to go to the field, accommodating güeval, and feminists go crazy (maybe I have stopped carrying). I remember a time before going out to a party, a companion pointed Coif a Keyring of this Lord and knelt to entrust to him. And that we played handball. That what's this? That one of the actors is the great Hugo Sánchez, or his cousin of the people, for that matter.The film is a predator that has a tremendous constipation. Given that the natural route goes, because created you a milestone by the belly, like sang Albert Plá, so that it looked like both his mother and his father. As you know, these alien are affectionate taco, so they roll to morreos in the mouth everything what are caught, including all humans to fuck when the ship crashes into the Earth. Before his death the estreñido, makes a loss which recommended him to eat plums to pass it, and this is going back to kill the Alien. That I said that could have gone with one couple more, right? why not you think that the movie is that I've counted? It is true, but it is what this milestone, I think that my readers deserve better than the vile reality. While the first part had an argument, bad or good, this is simply that the Alien want to colonize the Earth (reproduce more than the Gremlins in the bathtub) and a Predator are encouraged to go for them. Brave masters! The characters rub pathos, the plot is absurd, the action is such that the Director told him "do that don't have eggs?" And what if you had them. My madrecita that milestone.In short, bad film as a testicular kick on a few alien coming from picnic to the Earth and a predator makes guardian of mankind. Or what is I. Bad, very bad. Only viable for those viewers who like this type of movies but which are enthusiastic. At times, it has really pathetic scenes. Tremendous truño.Besitos.P.D: never have I told my theory about the aliens? Which I must say why have that power breathing our air, why not kills them water (as in signs of bowel), why are corporeos may be a mere gas, etc. Other day I tell you my theory that you are going to laugh.Pd2: "the Government never lie us" is the climax of the film. It is placed so that you get to endure what remains of petrified that you stay. Repeat with me "the Government never lie us" without laugh, that if.</body>
</review>
