<review author="Heitor Pan" title="Juno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The screenwriter, Diablo Cody, get a perfect blend of laughter and more tragic moments in one delicious story, perfectly located on the shoulders of a small genius of the interpretation, the amazing Ellen Page.</summary>
	<body>Normally, I choose the movies that I'll see the film after reading about all the possible options. 6 euros (average) is not feat to go wrong many times, and although there are genres which I am launching head and without float (the horror and science fiction are evidence), I normally know what go the movies before you choose them. So, afterwards, I have the opportunity to compare say what them criticism of professional (and amateur) why not with what I just believe.It is clear that there is always and will have differing points. The discussion of whether the film can be assessed objectively was presented in a discussion I had recently in a forum, or whether, on the contrary, vision, tastes and experiences of each viewer make it impossible. I chose the second option more and therefore understand and appreciate that each movie has its audience and that a film that to me I love to another to loathe.In the case of "Juno", read a series of overlapping opinions on a few occasions, these itself given by the "professional" critique, which fail to understand. Some scholars of the cinema, pointed too listillos dialogues of the protagonist, with the ingenious answer always to point, pro-life air of the tape and try to exploit your independent invoice to the slipstream of hits as "Little Miss Sunshine", in a negative way. But before joining these points, we would point out what is the movie.For reasons not clarified, the sarcastic, acid and independent Juno, for 16 years, she becomes pregnant after her first sexual relationship. After coolly assess the options available to them, decides to go ahead and hand over to his son in adoption to a couple who is looking for a descendant unsuccessfully. In tone of acid comedy, the film explores the relationships of Juno with the different characters that surround: the sympathetic father, stepmother advocate wishful thinking, the "inseminador" shy and good-natured, the rich couple who opt to receive the son in adoption or the intimate friend that supports everything, accompanying her physical and mental over the 9 months of gestation and something else instead.The screenwriter, Diablo Cody (Nom de guerre of Brook Busey), gets a perfect blend of laughter and more tragic moments, but is the sense of humor which are just imposed in one delicious story, perfectly based on the shoulders of a small genius of interpretation, the amazing Ellen Page. discover this fine actress, this month celebrates 21 years, in the uneasy "Hard Candy" where he impressed me, admired as he stole the few scenes in which came in "X-Men 3: the final decision" and "Juno" is over of fall in love. Page is one of those rare actresses that appear to have been born to acting, possessing a crushing naturalness and a magnetism out of the ordinary. If that join you a modest and calm personality (as they have those who know) and a huge ability to choose good roles, we are faced with one more than promising start.Let's now review the points that had been listed at the beginning of the text on the defects pointed to some critics of the film. Firstly, intelligent dialogues and witty responses that have always the protagonist. Strikes me that critics threatening to give birth this feature of the film probably praise fast dialogues of films of Cary Grant or Katherine Hepburn and Spencer Tracy, and are those who cry because already there are no scripts worked as in days gone by. Probably compare this film of the time gold with 'Juno' is a nerve on my part, but do not believe to be so far removed from reality. It is true that quick responses of a teenager of 16 years not usually so scathing and smart, but I do not think that it is realism that was intended, but, precisely, a script agile and scathing, capable of showing a thorny issue as the pregnancy unwanted with sense of humor and without falling into the sentimentality.With regard to air pro-life, I have not seen the pamphlet anywhere. Only a scene refers to this issue and is the time in which Juno is decided by the option of adoption instead of the abortion, faced to a companion of the Institute by making a lonely campaign to the gates of the clinic. Let's see if we are going to be now so modern, with being in favour of abortion we not arrived and we will criticize the rest of options available, falling into the same trap of who opposes legalization.Finally the snobbery now load against the independent tapes. The gafapastismo is now criticizing the movies of huge budgets, which carry many special effects, which are few and cardboard decorated stone, in budget and independent air &hellip; to take this look to a point that never ceases to enjoy any movie the public hosting mostly. These critics, who only fall of the Iranian film slow and forgotten are which end up tire me, with his elitist air and, despite the redundancy, TVGuide.com.For my part, I enjoyed the film like no other, with a script and so elaborate and attractive characters that I am not able to find him not a single but. I am so easy.</body>
</review>
