<review author="Ethan" title="Ha nacido una estrella" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Does the director chains a wonderful travelling of round-trip with the impressive number?The Man That Got Away?, where Judy Garland sings with a torrent of voice and gets to the highest point of his career.</summary>
	<body>"Never second parts were good." That at least they say for films that are sequels or remakes. Let's talk about an exception that proves the rule; Let's talk about "A star is born" George Cukor. It's a based tape in which he made - and wrote, William a. Wellman in 1937. He narrated the story of Norman Maine, an actor in decline and alcoholic who discovered Vicki Lester, a young promise that later married (Fredric March and Janet Gaynor in the original movie, James Mason and Judy Garland in which concerns us); everything is twisted when Norman's career was coming to an end and had no choice but to get used to be the shadow of Vicki. That film seemed difficult to overcome, given the success and the numerous awards garnered, however, seventeen years later, producer Sydney Luft tried a new project designed to relaunch the career of his wife; the career of Judy Garland. Although this objective failed - due to other factors - the end result was excellent and we can now say that it is one of the best films in the history. And all thanks to its director. George Cukor was facing his first musical and also had to perform in the new Cinemascope. Both challenges them resolved with note not only because of its known ability to the direction of actors and actresses-, but also for the perfect handling of the camera and the excellent inclusion in the plot of the musical numbers. Sequences as the second encounter between Norman and Vicki are an example of the personal form was Cukor understand the film. The director chains a scene in a night club - a wonderful travelling of round-trip with James Mason searching for actress and smoking as a locomotive, with the impressive number "The Man That Got Away", where Judy Garland sings with a torrent of voice and manages to get - in the opinion of many, to the highest point of his career. Wherever I see "Has born a star" term thinking same thing: "It is curious what it resembles Cukor Minnelli". It is that there are many elements in this film resemble the best Vincente Minnelli, and I don't mean only the use of the color red or the brilliance of the choreography and the decorations, but the use of the script speculate; the method of "narrating dancing"; and psychological treatment of the characters. In the number "Born in a Trunk", Vicki sees herself in a film as the protagonist of a film where he sings and dances to tell the story of his life. It is the film within the film, but it is also a new form of narration. The sequence follows very closely the modern style that began with the final ballet of "An American in Paris" ("An American in Paris" of Vincente Minnelli, 1951). However, in the number "Someone at Last", Cukor reaches further than Minnelli. Here Judy Garland uses lamps, plants, tables and other objects of the Hall of his house to represent an imaginary journey where moves from Paris to Brazil passing through China. The denunciation of the environment that gives them eat also is another point in common between the two directors. For Vicki day in large studies can not be more frustrating: nobody seems to care her face - in fact, in his first role insist that do not see you the face-; It is lost between sets and screens where all kinds of films are planned or are trapped--literally--by the system when it is entangled in a kind of revolving door. The symbolism of this type is continuous in the footage, but it is also the similarity or cross-checking with real-life. Thus, the personal situation at the Judy Garland - consumed by drugs - time seemed too close to Norman Maine in fiction or, if see him otherwise, that Judy embodies a young woman who began her career crashes too with the fact that this film was the last of the actress as a protagonist, with success among critics and public. The last one, Yes, but also the best.</body>
</review>
