<review author="Iñigo" title="C.R.A.Z.Y." rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do witty drama with strong load symbolic and large doses of? magic?, with a special aura and the feeling that, despite seeing something entirely new, is innovative and fresh.</summary>
	<body>How develops the film and are successively exhausted ideas, plots or stories, in times that concern us is merely being repeated the constant that the important thing is not what are counting, but how are counting. "C.R.A.Z.Y.", despite being aware of that was too dangerously close to the repetition of previously established formulas, leaves very airy what you see as an example of the previously mentioned.Jean-Marc Vallée is not cut when it comes to telling us the stages of growth of a young man very in the style of what did this deceased teammate Lauzon in "Léolo". The director Canadian (for more INRIA), the truth is that you achieved a result certainly interesting, influenced by a notable psychedelic, almost extravagant and markedly hippie Halo.Here, the repression and the denial of the reality of one's own, evolves as does it fashion and music more purely sesentera/setentera: double pants, hardly etiquetable clothes to the sexuality of who the porta, religious ceremonies to the rhythm of the Rolling Stones, snuffed and "highs" anthological presided over by Pink Floyd and his psychedelic, family discussions and, above all, undoubtedly personal, intimate and non-transferable.Our Narrator particular family is Zac, a typically problematic young man, with your questions and needs. Everyone is aware that the rest of the "kooky" descent (already know in due course as to why that enclose the word) also has its problems. But our nearest support is logically Zac, which tells us what is happening throughout his life in their family environment.In a fatherly circle so purely conservative and religious, our peculiar stem, is emerging as the classic misunderstood bug. From a very early doubts regarding their sexual orientation do more than bring him down the street from the bitterness, and still not sure of nothing, refuses his condition himself, decides to suppress to retrieve his father.Thus, Zac grows, at different times, to different rhythms (beautiful time "Space Oddity") and with different horses on the heels: drug addiction of his brother, knowledge of his body, the search of unknown sexuality (both male and female), strong family religiosity that leads him to the selfsame Jerusalem (crucial moment in which the director enters as mystical as marshy land), and despair by a stability that never comes.It is neither more nor less than the history of growth, an adventure in constant evolution and constant potholes. Speaks to us of the classic family discussions that do that we find ourselves, our frustrations and our mistakes. It is life, the family, music with which we have evolved, the doubts with which we have lived? and the moments that we will never leave behind. Do the new paths occur over and over again? and these paths, create or not, are inscrutable. It is true that the basics and, occasionally, the foreseeable or the extremely laughable/absurd, dot to work doing that it becomes somewhat excessive in footage, and manages to wake us up some another yawn. In that regard, it is a film that suffers excessively changes of pace, you will end up giving has that sins of irregular and that, sometimes, it gets a bit of context. The mixture of child with wit (see dreams that carry our character to an onírico world that, inevitably, reminds us "Léolo") and evolution by stages in the style of "Almost famous" (basically by the environment in which we dipped), make that, a priori, it was something original, is not really so much. But with all this, no one can deny is an interesting film, treated with much success, with a musicality and a Halo which are not you going of the retina in a long time, with plausible scenes, more fine humour and a sincerity that invites reflection and the nostalgia in many respects. All detailed and dosed by an unknown cast, but that line to a perfect level of credibility.And most importantly: despite seemingly weak points such as the troubled narrative limp family in a particular environment, time and with a particular belief/culture (disadvantage that, without doubt, the director is knowledgeable) or an irregular rhythm that ascends as easily as it descends in the respective to the attention of the Viewer, "C.R.A.Z.Y." is a film that captures the viewer's attention.Simply take advantage of their mistakes to make little original in original and interesting, in a witty drama with strong symbolic and large doses of "magic", with a special aura and the feeling that, despite watching something not entirely new, it is fresh and innovative. As much as you try, "C.R.A.Z.Y." not will erase your memory at a time, because, ultimately, it belongs to our own history. As Léolo trying to escape their inevitable "degeneration". Clear that, not compare one with the other, because as pray out there: comparisons are odious.</body>
</review>
