<review author="Ethan" title="Cartas desde Iwo Jima" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Eastwood is able to move from the emotive close-ups of the general to the almost ghostly presence of the enemy. Each and every one of them represent the same: death.</summary>
	<body>"Letters from Iwo Jima" is part of a project of immense proportions - and high quality - which began with "Flags of our fathers" ("Flags of our fathers", 2006) to finish up with this jewel of the seventh art. Clint Eastwood and Steven Spielberg have created a reference future of cinema with two feature films that not only have in common the battle which gives its name to the title, also share the same "tone": a very hard picture, with a low color saturation, touching the black and white; and a continued use of flash-back to project to the present - and the past - what happened on Iwo Jima. Eastwood, Spielberg and &hellip; Paul Haggis. Each one contributing what better do to achieve a harmonious whole, a masterpiece. Thus, the coral structure, with successive jumps from the point of view; various efectistas resources of acute writer, as the in the "Strip protective" - which reminds the "invisible" costume used in "Crash" (2005)-, are some of the excellent contributions of the writer - and November director - Paul Haggis. Exciting task the discover the elements of each of the two remaining filmmakers. Let's do this: of Spielberg, realism - the whistles of the shot, as in "Saving private Ryan" ("Saving Private Ryan", 1998) and the metallic sound of the guns are very close to the true - and the mix of effects to introduce the Viewer to this hell. But in addition, the "Wizard", insurance that has influenced with his wand to give form to two of the main characters history. One of them is the soldier "in force" (Saigo), alien to this world of horror and anguish false honor. So lost as E.T. on our planet or Tom Hanks in the terminal of an airport. The other character is Colonel of cavalry Nishi. A sensible official, a Schlinder on Iwo Jima that respects their subordinates and also to the enemy, which attends, practically, as a priest - religious staging that both likes the Director-; always in white in the battle (symbol of goodness, but also of death) contrast perfect with the prevailing darkness of the tunnels where resisting the Japanese. Saigo and Nishi have a lot of Spielberg, I have no doubt that the character given to general Kuribayashi is the work of Clint Eastwood. He is the protagonist and comes outside to save an endangered community governed by a bunch of useless. Their harangues, the intimism of the character, the letters, his attitude towards life, everything that fits the personal address of the filmmaker present in some of his best films. That Yes, Eastwood is able to move from the emotive close-ups of the general to the almost ghostly presence of the enemy.To achieve this effect the great director doesn't let us see the faces of any American soldier (with the exception of the injured who engaged in contact with Nishi). The marines are almost unreal - as the protagonists of "Pale rider" ("Pale Rider", 1985) or "Hell of cowards" ("High Plain Drifters", 1973) - are from abroad, almost extraterrestrial beings for the Japanese; their faces are just macabre shadows. Each and every one of them represent the same: death. No doubt the conjunction of the above elements is what gives "Letters from Iwo Jima" important work. Synergy which is reflected in the shiny flat end; which justifies all done previously; which leaves us with such good taste.</body>
</review>
