<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To sum up?Monstrous? includes the stories always but told otherwise, and time, this makes it a novelty.</summary>
	<body>J.J. Abrams returns to give us shows his talent and great business vision is, which is that "Cloverfield", here translated as "Monstruoso", tells the story of always but in a "different" way, or at least not so common.The shadow of "The Blair Witch project" continues to bite, and recently what we have seen in "Rec", and I guess that we will see "Quarentine" (the remake of it). Well, taking such a scheme, "Monstrous" presents us with a group of friends and how they live a creature attack to New York City, specifically in Manhattan. All told from the subjective point of them, a video camera will be who let us them see what is happening.The first moments of the film, after the first tremor, have a great realism, which relies on the idea that are having a new terrorist attack, and clear, that we can stay away, but the protagonists live very close to ground zero of the 11-S, so they have that feeling very present.In addition to the aforementioned film, we can find references to "28 weeks later", "Godzilla" and "The Host". In the acting section, Matt Reeves (Felicity) leads to unknown faces, which help to give more credibility to the story.Good sound, and special effects support and sustain this story, in which there is also time for the courage and love. The antagonist of the story, the Monster does not appear clearly, something that helps create more suspense and provokes the curiosity of the Viewer. Also the style and the chosen point of view make that we can stay eager to further explanation, but what is this proposal, which is not counted in the traditional way, and if you have seen "The Blair Witch Project", you can get an idea of what you're going to find you. In short, "Monstrous" encompasses the stories always but told otherwise, and time, this makes it a novelty.</body>
</review>
