<review author="Renegado" title="Hitman" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sporadic action scenes, a character that conveys little and too irregular pace at times, make this a film purporting to most of what ends up offering.</summary>
	<body>With honorable exceptions as they could be, in my modestísima opinion, the saga of "Resident Evil" and "Tomb Rider" (and this only because it is Angelina and that justifies anything), until today attempts to film movies based on famous video games have not been very successful to say.Although probably had the best of intentions when it comes to production, the final results achieved never managed to transport the necessary to conquer fans mystique of the original games to the big screen, or managed to round out a product that capture the interest of the public in general as to make these tapes a genuine success.Thus, years ago were attempts with classic games like "Mortal Kombat" or "Street Figther" failed miserably leading to films that actually better not to remember. Much more recently in the time, landed in theaters two productions based on the popular "Doom" and "Silent Hill" games which, although quite improved the level, have gone through billboards without penalty or glory.In the case of this film, "Hitman", I think that unfortunately qualify to swell the list of the latter.The story focuses on the activities of a relentless, almost infallible, killer created through genetic manipulation of DNA from criminals and murderers more dangerous in the world (as, not is &hellip; Charles Manson, Al Capone, Casaca (jojojo that spark), Blas Giunta, Professor Neurus, José Luis Chilavert, and many others), and coached by an independent international secret organization known as "The Organization" (is that the silver had been spent training assassins and were not left) (anything to hire a creative that invent them a cornered name), which does not respond to any Government, or movement, or political party, and which offers its services (consisting of killing people, walk dogs and prosecute unfaithful wives) to the highest bidder, whoever.The Association of that salad of genes of evil with this unscrupulous company comes from this man become an almost perfect machine kill, strictly professional, elegant, meticulous, cold and lethal. A man without feelings, without remorse, without hair, and extremely attached and obsessive with his work (i.e. killing people).A man without a name, known only as Agent 47 (although there in the company colleagues called him Cacho).His life was normally as any relentless killer: a murder here, a trip, another murder there, another journey, a degollado, a poisoned beyond. Nothing out of the ordinary.However, (and luckily because but the film would have been even more boring), a day is assigned a seemingly very routine like any other mission, consisting of flying the sabiola to a so-and-so and quite important.The peeled, goes, hit the shot, save everything and turns away making pasito murga.When returns to his hotel (because always stops at hotels to be more cool) report you that in carrying out its mission something that seems to have failed, with the aggravating circumstance that, in addition, there was a risk to be identified by an occasional witness (which coincidentally is more good to miss a Monday to school). In other words, the message was "Che gilastrún, note that it seems that flower crap you sent to you." Now not going to collect a sope. "To mourn the Church".The 47 (Cacho) says "Cannot." "If I do not you erro never to anything" and there just to check, with your eyes closed spits a seed of an orange which was eating, and her take on an ashtray was on the other side of the room.At that time, and thanks to its extraordinary deductive powers developed during the comprehensive years of hard mental training to which it was subjected, but more than anything because passed you a piece of paper under the door that said "Sos ballot forros head." "Signed: the Organization", realizes that that last assignment had been a trap mounted in order to eliminate it.Hence the peeled gets like crazy, not only because they had been told "head of forros" knowing that you don't like, but because also realizes that killing him was a form of fire him without paying him compensation nor the unused vacation and that, after many years of service, is intolerable.From then on, and then choose to disaffiliate from the SACG (Union of assassins created genetically) do not feel represented, will undertake the Mission of discovering who and why he wants to do on their own ballot, why you do not want to recognize the antiquity, why is peeled and why demons has no name if not it cost them a hell put him one.Of course to achieve this must evade police forces who seek him for the little that that killed a lot of types, in addition to having to deal with those who until recently were their "brothers", or assassins so effective, cold, lethal, peeled and expressionless as he.The film itself, ends up being difficult to define.Obviously it is action, but he succeeds only at times. In other passages becomes slow, and others is that it seems that you are booting with everything and stays in the threat.There are many shots, fighting, blood, explosions and everything that one would expect to see a tape of this genus, but developed in a way that does not seem to reach to round out a film in accordance.Admittedly, they strove to include shots that seem really taken directly of the game, especially those in which sees the protagonist walking by corridors of hotels and other (and speaking of which, the type walks very rare.) Not is if trying to mimic the game or why, but it seems that he walk holding a carrot with the ass, so everything straight and medium shirring), but otherwise, no longer a tape of ordinary shots with little support.As for the cast, we find Timothy Olyphant in the leading role as Agent 47, in a work that never ends convince. His performance lacked almost completely of expressivity, depth and above all charisma, making the viewer will be quite difficult to excite with the protagonist. Accompany it with the beautiful Olga Kurylenko as Nika, Dougray Scott as Mike Whittier, Robert Knepper as Yuri Marklov, Urlich Thomsen as Belicof, Michael Offei as Jenkins and Henry Ian Cusik as Udre Belikof.La film was directed by Xavier Gens which should perhaps play a little more with the Playstation before get to adapt the game to the film format.Rating: 2 forsaken and a half (does not become bad, but good either.) A bit more than regular it would be good. (Sporadic action scenes, a character that conveys little and too irregular pace at times, make this a film purporting to most of what ends up offering).Recommendations: If you is a fan of the game and just want to see his character coming to life in a movie, go. Sure he likes.If you expect a dizzying and violent action film, go by the violence, but not ilusione with the Vertigo.If you are depressing because he believes little expressive, go; see the protagonist and will find consolation.If you are of those laburo, and one, and one to win the romantic favors of a lady and still most of the time fails; go, and retuérsace of indignation seeing such wasted every opportunity with a mine as I would say the Bambino "Esss a mannnnteca!". "!!"</body>
</review>
