<review author="Moebius" title="El hombre que pudo reinar" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The man who would be King, is a film as immortal as the cinema itself, one of the jewels in the Crown of the adventure genre.</summary>
	<body>Shoot this film meant for John Huston fulfill his long desire to bring to the big screen the work of Rudyard Kipling's The Man Who Would Be King. He led several scripts and nearly two decades achieving a definitive version of the story, and find the ideal actors for the project. Initially Huston had wanted to take Humphrey Bogart and Clark Gable (sounds really good!), but time passed and his great friend Bogart and the most famous orejudo Hollywood died. He also thought Burt Lancaster and Kirk Douglas. The project continued postponing, until that in the 1970s Huston contacted the most famous pair of actors of his time, Paul Newman and Robert Redford. Newman rightly advised Huston hired British actors. It was just as he reached two actors whose chemistry on the big screen was such that left the Hindukush to the height of a small pebble. The faltering figure of a beggar breaks the silence that surrounds the young journalist Rudyard Kipling. Between the shadows a figure supported by a cane is heavily moving towards the amazed Editor. The beggar calls sacir water for their thirst. "No I know?", she asked. Kipling answers negatively, and then gives you drink. "Here decided here was, in this room, do you remember?" Danny and I signed the contract and you witnessed. You were here, I there, and Danny here. "Do you remember?" The journalist finally recognizes him. "Carnehan!". The beggar that day was a proud British continues: "Peachy Taliaferro Carnehan." Follow mirándonme, so it will not escape my soul. "" Carnehan!", repeats an amazed Kipling." "The same", answers Peachy, "and not the same one who was at his side in a wagon train of Marwar first three summers and a thousand years ago". And a flashback to a railway station three years ago he began one of the definitive adventure films. The man who would be King tells the story of a friendship and a time where much of the world was still a mystery and romanticism of the danger and what remained to be discovered were still possible. It was a time that the white man was confident in itself and in its technology to open passage between forests and mountains and lower towns that were destined to be dominated by the great Christian power. And between the man white power to fear was Great Britain. In a India recently subjugated by Victorian England a Rascal former military and Mason, Peachy Carnehan, survives emptying their pockets to English and rich confused. A young man dressed in white, thin, being glasses and a thin moustache, he steals a gold watch while buying a train ticket. When it considers the symbol that crowns the clock chain he curses his fate. Just steal a fellow Mason. When you try to return it so the traveller already is in his wagon. Peachy he seeks and gets to it. You know there has been stolen from a writer and journalist, Rudyard Kipling. Peachy will try to return the watch while it knows, but when an Indian ricachón rises to the carriage accompanied by a watermelon their plans will be ruined. Neither short nor lazy it will use to blame the Hindu of theft and throw it on the train. Kipling will tell you it threw under the clock at the station. But between masons, it forgives everything. Later Kipling were are with Danny, a burly ex-suboficial of large sideburns that journalist should deliver a message. Danny and Peachy, both former army of his Majesty, after almost stepping on the prison to blackmail a Sultan, will meet in the Office of Kipling that exercise of witness in the signing of one of the most unique contracts ever written. Peachy and Danny have risked their lives for Britain, like so many others like them, and have helped to make the country of Queen Victoria the first world power. However, his reward has been poverty and oblivion. Proud, brazen and without a penny ("I have good taste for whisky, for women, jackets and for many other things, but I can not exercise," says Peachy), both have decided that next time they will play the neck for their own benefit. His plan is to cross the Afghanistan, crossing the Hindukush and become Kings of Kafiristán, a region of warrior tribes. "Apparently have 32 Kings," says Danny. "We will be the 33 and 34". "No white man has gone there with life since Alexander", says Kipling. "What Alexander?", asked Peachy. "Alexander the great, King of Greece", answers the journalist. "Because if did it a Greek do us", ends Peachy. As I have already said, the English blood was then valued in carat. It is then when Peachy and Danny sign his contract before Kipling, in which commit themselves to not prove neither alcohol nor women until they have achieved their objectives, and promise to share all the profits fairly. While Kipling creates are two crazy, everything seems to be well planned. The next time that the journalist be found with them you'll be fascinated by the ingenuity of two adventurers, because you will not find two Englishmen but a crazy magician and his assistant. Disguised as that way they will cross the border with a caravan and see in Afghanistan. If in the first half hour of the film have seen especially the portrait of an era and the colonial life concept, while we begin to glimpse closely United that are Danny and Peachy, is from Afghanistan where really strong and peculiar friendship that joins the British descastados look in all its dimensions. Peachy is the wit and the wisdom, while Danny is the charisma and the heart. After surviving the Afghan guerrillas, the two friends they delve in the Hindukush. "The mountains were high and white as wild Rams." They were always fighting. "At night prevent us sleep the thick of his fighting". Danny is temporarily blind by snow and follows the path taken to the tail of a mule. In a surreal moment, the English initiators with two giants. When they discover the secret of the silent guardians, the Earth, both had mistreated them but that in a chance of fate had left them expedited the way, collapses behind them. There is no turning back. On their way through the mountains when in a crucial moment we can understand the idiosyncrasies of the two characters and as their friendship goes beyond the usual. Trapped in the snow and believing already dead, the two friends are reminiscent of old deeds of the army, sing and laugh. For a long time they have lived day by day, and together they have drawn many dangers and dodged many arrows and bullets. You know accept what fate onwards them. At any time there is no reproach, and both expect the end with joy. But the avalanche that cause their laughs will open the road to Kafiristán. Fate plays in his favor through her particular vision of life and death. Arrivals Kafiristán Peachy and Danny will launch his plan: submit to the King of the first village to find and offer you their services and their rifles to create a modern army and overthrow the rest of Kings. To do so they will have with the unexpected help of Billy Fish, a gurka who has served in the British ranks and will be for the two English translator. Fish will be the closest thing to a third friend who can find Danny and Peachy. As they checked very soon, the King has many enemies, which urinate upriver when they bathe (custom deeply rooted among those tribes as they will soon see). Peachy and Danny will soon get rid of the pathetic monarch and occupy the throne of the Kingdom are building. At the village, Danny and Peachy they ask if they are gods. "We are not gods, we are English, which is almost the same." A colonial claim to charged a new dimension later. The plan will continue its course with success, but everything will change when Danny resulting unharmed after receiving a crush, is taken by the son of Alexander the great. King, Danny would be considered a God on Earth. By Peachy Council the English are continuing with the deception. Before departing with the Alexandrian Treasury to the monks of the place custiodado have for centuries, the British must wait to pass the monsoon season. Meanwhile, Peachy builds a bridge over a huge gap and Danny plays his role of divine King. The patilludo soldier turns out to be an excellent legislator and delivers justice "as if he had invented laws", in the words of the own Peachy. Once again, the friendship of the two British shows unwavering. Its objectives, and the role that each plays in this particular Association have clear. At no time Peachy complains or shows discomfort by suddenly be a simple helper. Danny asks him he reverencie also to not arouse suspicion. Being a logical request, Peachy accepted without further discussion. When the formidable plan is about to be fulfilled, a woman crosses on its way. Roxana as the mythical wife of the Macedonian King, is called and Danny will be love with its formidable exotic beauty. Peachy will succeed in removing the idea of approaching her momentarily, but the low passions of Danny will begin to bite in the iron discipline of the man-God. The man who would be King is an ode to a lost era, and as I have said, an exaltation of male friendship. During the film, the role of women is secondary, anecdotal. Out of the friendship between Danny and Peachy feminists are practically a sexual object. When Danny begins to believe his role, the importance of the terms of the contract (in the background, almost the terms of the friendship of the two thugs) will be floated. When in your room the two companions discussed for the first time, rather than a curtain seems to separate them a chasm, as large and deep as that on which have built the bridge. The Pact has been broken. The wrath of God Imra hangs over them. To betray his friendship and violate the contract, indirectly Danny has signed the fate of him and Peachy. Although it aims to start with his share of the treasure, you can not deny a last favor to Danny, and attend his royal wedding to Godfather. It could not be otherwise: as the formidable friends that are the destination of Danny will be linked to the Peachy. Both Michael Caine playing the cunning Peachy as Sean Connery as Danny are formidable in his performances, making a chemistry on screen much more intimate and close to that of Newman and Redford. Two Britons should have shot many more films together, but I guess that the lack of success of the tape did not possible. Although it is difficult to stand out from two giants like these in what were some of his best roles, Christopher Plummer manages to get his small piece of cake as Kipling, fitting in the role with the softness and perfection of a silk glove. Of the actor who plays fish and of which little has become to know say that he endures the harshness of the two adventurers, and who are already is to much. No doubt an endearing character. The beautiful Roxana is played by Caine women back then (and I think that they are currently still together), Shakira Caine. A guy with luck, this Michael. When Huston was almost desperate to find his Roxana, he and other guests saw Shakira at a party and could not but affirm that fate her had put there for them. One of the constants in the career of John Huston has been his intuition to surround himself with good writers and a particular smell and know do almost magical to adapt literary works. His film adaptation of the monstrous Moby Dick is proof of that. In this film Huston helped of a collaborator, Gladys Hill, to write the screenplay. The construction of the story is perfect: we have action, adventure, humor and drama in equal parts. The imprint of a male in the American sense as Huston leave note in the construction of this friendship typically male and brava keeping Danny and Peachy. The work after Huston cameras is equally impeccable, maintaining a pace balanced at all times, letting everything flow naturally, developing the characters at the time that the story follows its course. A work of craftsmanship that has not had the popularity of tapes of subsequent adventures as the archifamosa of Indiana Jones. I will not go to say which is better, for me are all great films of the genre, but yes I think that the man who would be King is a mature romanticism which the archaeologist with whip films lack completely. In a fleeting and strange racing film, the vejete who plays the high priest debuted in cinema at the age of 103 years. Huston discovered you while the grandfather worked as a night watchman in an olive grove. The director offered the role and accepted the good man. In the early days, everything seemed to go well (a Shaman could be interpreted more realistically, it seemed that the priest would have been contemporary of Alexander mismísmo) but the team soon noticed that the Moroccan slept in the shooting. The reason was that the poor man had followed with his vigilante work. Huston made him see that so going to pay him could forget of los olivos forever. Furthermore, let's see some filmed scenes, the elderly considered that thereafter it would be immortal. The man might be a vigilant illiterate of olivares, but certainly failed to comprehend the first that this film. The man who would be King is a film as immortal as the cinema itself, one of the jewels in the Crown of the adventure genre. </body>
</review>
