<review author="Monica Jordán" title="Hacia rutas salvajes" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Towards wild routes is an honest and direct proposal at the same little complacent. Enters a dangerous game that goes airy: there are no bisexual, cheap tears, nor imposed dogmatic speeches, only broad suggestions.</summary>
	<body>It is not accidental nor free to wild routes have as prelude a quotation from Lord Byron, one of the banners of English romantic literature that exemplifies the spirit of which baby the new film as director of Sean Penn in his ideals and poems. And it is towards wild routes history who lives in the 20th century completely anachronistic way, with ideals and ways of thinking own clandestine meetings of Byron and Shelley than of the Vortex industrial and surface of the contemporary age. Chris/Alex (a more committed than ever Emile Hirsch) is a young family man rather than following a set of vital disappointments decides to unleash your adventurous spirit and embark on a journey of extreme survival towards Alaska. Obviously the travel is the excuse to show the personal growth of Chris, who is also formally separated creating blocks in the film with the different stages of learning of the human being (birth, adolescence, age adult.) thus proposing a clear structure to the viewer and making a gesture honest to show the purpose of the trip: more that a shift is learning in search of happiness and/or the flight of a past not just to accept.All the romantic draught (important here the uppercase) the film is hypervideo with landscape plans where nature is formed as another character in the story. The camera captures humans (small and insignificant) before the immensity of the wild mother nature in an exercise of trip to aesthetic romanticism in search of painters as Friedrich with Walker on the sea of clouds or monk at the edge of the sea. It is clear that Penn has been surrounded by large cultural references to bring to the screen the novel of Kracauer on which this film is based, but more certain is that the story of Chris McCandless was already written with letters from their mere existence. The history is overwhelming in itself but Penn knows not to fall into the easy and manages to find the distance needed to reach out to the intimacy of Chris without turning a hero nor an anti-hero. Chris is, as good romantic, purely and simply a human being and so as shows it us Sean Penn, without praise and without admirations; with their strengths and their weaknesses; with the wisdom of who knows what he wants and selfishness of who does not measure the consequences of their actions. The eyes of Penn is anthropocentric virtually throughout the film to give the power to the enlightened that through the experience learns and understands the chaos which conforms the real world but also opens the door to metaphysics and spirituality without cerrár is none and giving a whole to set that few films get the protagonist.The great evil of the romantic is the society which imprisons it, and Chris has been devoured by a way of life that can not sustain: Chase you the lies of the past which has failed to deal with the problems with his parents (Marcia Gay Harden and William Hurt), and therefore decides to flee from them at a stadium in absentia. It breaks with everything and everyone to look for himself, to find happiness in small things and the apparently empty images from scratch. It will be his sister (Jena Malone) who tells us through a voice in off the prior to the departure of Chris as well as the consequences that this has in it and in your home. The multitude of points of view narrative that has wild routes surprised by its complexity and the well that Penn solves this problem. In the film we get a plurality of narrators diegetic makes it surprise unanimous result. There is no good nor bad, neither victims nor executioners. Each explains his story from his point of view but all contribute to understand the total, even when they talk about their personal stories the link found with the plot of Chris is important.Towards wild routes is an honest and direct proposal at the same little complacent. Enters a dangerous game that goes airy: there are no bisexual, cheap tears, nor imposed dogmatic speeches, only wide in which suggestions fit all ideologies, all forms of interpreting take place and where the truth is made up of the plurality that is life. Something that is welcome and that it was difficult to be a film with all the weight in a surrounded by secondary main character exercise of satellites (highlights Catherine Keener as delicious as always or Vince Vaugh in one of the most entertaining of recent times detective "fighters"). The film accompanies giving the viewer the ability to pose look before on celluloid than of centrár, with the exception of those intimate scenes in which small workplaces are oppressors for Chris and the spectator, closing to the observation of the specific levels.The story of a vagabond solo and idealistic could lead many to hastiar only of thinking in which two hours and media is a long time sitting in an armchair, but towards wild routes get know little by well built of his gear. He is not already of that add all the pieces of the puzzle, but that Penn has formed a patchwork with remnants of different origins. Therein lies the great magic of this film which, sometimes sweet and sometimes bitter, get to do a portrait of melancholy of a way of life that has little to do with the times. Something that would have loved to Byron or Friedrich and which is now part of a common imaginary. Rest in peace.</body>
</review>
