<review author="Jefe Dreyfus" title="Fast food nation" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hard coral movie that tries to cover more than what can be, but that is recommended to the end and all.</summary>
	<body>Good morning, I am the Chief Dreyfus and again with another release on dvd, that will help to lose weight to anyone who has taken a few quiilitos during these past festivals (damn family dinners), because I assure you that not come it very in taste return to stop by a fast food restaurant for a while, because today: Fast food nation &hellip; started! One of the bosses of a fast food chain calls one of its executives to travel to the deep America to investigate the plant which produces the raw material because, apparently, outside the company analyses have detected a high volume of shit in their burgers. Yes, Yes, shit, pure and simple, exactly cow excrement. At the same time, some Mexicans be played life trying to cross the border and enter illegally in the United States in search of the American dream. Both, initiators face to face with a harsh reality. This would be the starting point of a choral film, directed by Richard Linklaker, a director whose filmography looks like a fucking roller coaster with both slowed (personally I'll stick with its peak in "before sunset") and full of faces known with more or less role as: Greg Kinnear (little Miss Sunshine), Ethan Hawke, Kris Kristofferson, Patricia ArquetteCatalina Sandino Moreno (full Maria are one of grace), Bruce Willis, Avril Lavigne (if, if, singer, what is &hellip;), and many others &hellip; seems as if Linklaker, also in the script, along with the author of the book on which the film is based had wanted to put much of the things you dislike their country and split to taste in less than two hours. The film talks about fast food, true, but is also criticizing the animal abuse, illegal immigration, labor exploitation, the despotic multinational (globalization), sexual harassment at work, the discouragement of American youth, etc, etc, etc &hellip; even to the new hippies tontosdelculo! So, the film, which well might be called "Blow to the American dream 2", is somewhat weakened by that of wanting to fight on too many fronts, and fails to tie everything well tied, leaving half some of the open plots or medium gas leaving the others. And I warn, for sensitive stomachs and/or friends of cows in general, that the last five minutes of film are, to put it mildly, something durillos. Summing up: Recommended (despite everything) and hard coral film that attempts to cover more than what it can, but, at the end and after, behind good manners and intentions.</body>
</review>
