<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Los amantes del círculo polar" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The history reads similarly of the right than vice versa, as well as the name of its protagonists. You catch in his visual and dreamlike poetry full of strength and mystery, enigmas and coincidences, love and hatred.</summary>
	<body>"Lovers of the Arctic Circle" is the Summit of Julio Medem, and one of the shocking and EMA film in the last 15 years of the modern Spanish film. Imposing and majestic in all its levels and moments.A hypnotic and dazzling love story that revolves around the coincidences that encounter the protagonists; that is the best way to define this film.The film, told in the form of chapters, where you enter at the beginning of each of these, the name of the character that refers the chapter (point to favor already for mounting).A from there, we will see from their particular point of view as the action (thus observe two different one same fact views). And the magic begins soon. It begins at the time the first name appears on the screen - Otto-. When another name reappears on the screen - Ana - continues. The story of Otto and Ana, the story of two boys, the story of two children with names capicúas, matching the name of the Basque filmmaker - Medem - also capicúa do we have here the first chance of the film?The history reads similarly of the right than vice versa, as well as the name of its protagonists. The circle begins to draw in the first minutes of footage, to end up closing it perfectly in the face at the end of the film. Storytelling fulfils a circle, ending where it begins.Divided into three distinct parts (child, adolescent, adult), Medem get you involucres in history since the beginning (if not do these lost, odiarás). He wants you to feel what they feel the characters. Plays with you and random, you wrapped in a magic halo which do not want to flee, nor never escape. You catch in his visual and dreamlike poetry full of strength and mystery, enigmas and coincidences, love and hatred.Otto, Anna and a coincidence of fate (a bad ball released), do they know. The same accident (a newspaper) will be that you separate them.Separated for years, after living one of the most beautiful experiences that can live in the life (find the love of your life and live every moment with that person), meet again. They meet again but in a place completely unknown, a hidden and very pure place in the world, away from everything and everyone.Personally, if had to choose between one of the three main parts of the history, I would be with the child. That innocence, those Virgin feelings yet undiscovered, that magic inherent in the environment.The chances that occur them in children are truly amazing, the dream by everyone at some point in our lives. A shot to a ball with poor marksmanship that sneaks through the wall of the school, a paper plane that will stop at the foot of Ana, the love story that arises between the parents following the note of the paper plane (excellent not reveal that you put each one to imagine their perfect love phrase).Although if I had to highlight a key scene in the chances of players, it would be that of the stage in the plaza mayor of Madrid. Truly, you put the willies thinking that they are side by side, even only with rotated were; simply stunning (only you are want to shout them to the two, who are just behind). But its fate does not want that, the circle which began to draw has end up where he started, and was not.In the role of Otto, we have a somewhat tense Martínez Fele - perhaps the least notable of the film-. With a face that does not vary in practically all the footage, I think that it is the only character that isn't at the height of which requires the film. The figure of Otto requires more than what Fele Martínez may bring. A deeper than the "thesis" character is, and seems that not end it to understand.Child and adolescent making his same role a few years further back are much more natural. Also comment that the child of Otto (Peru Medem) is son in life real director July Medem.Por other side, in the role of Anne, is an unbeatable Nawja Nimri - as always. His voice provides the perfect tone which requires the film. Harmonious and poetic, rounded (as the circle) to perfection his performance with his tone of voice, leisurely and relaxing.Nancho Novo, which repeats with Medem after "Red squirrel" and "Earth", is more than correct in his role as father of Otto. The truth is that it is a multi-purpose, fitting perfectly both comedy and drama actor. Unfortunately, not given the importance it deserves, and seems that it finishes does not fit into the national film scene.And Maru Valdivielso is also very believable in her role as mother of Ana. With Nancho Novo, are a wonderful couple that complements perfectly, giving more realism even if possible to the film.Perfectly built and structured the characters, and superbly directed by Medem, the set of players rounded up the movie to the level of genius.As regards the technical section of the film, highlight the work of photography and editing. While it is true that mounting is not entirely novel, because the reference use the voiceover and various flashbacks to narrate past actions, possess a concentric structure that is taking shape to pass the minutes, as well as the choice of telling history under the subjective views of the protagonists make the work of the director of mountinga sample of elegance and virtuosity rarely seen before - especially in Spain-.tanto the choice of landscapes, of the filters used in camera and post-production, playing with bluish and cold tones (especially at the end of film in Finland) are exquisite and as opposed to the ardent love that exudes the protagonist couple.In the sound section, highlight (again) the collaboration of the fantastic Alberto Iglesias with Medem. Working together since "Cows", comes an exquisite music to our senses in "Lovers of the Arctic Circle" which fits perfectly with the action that takes place in every moment, marking the tone and the pace during the viewing.In short, we have a great love story told from the particular point of view by Julio Medem, magical and melancholy touches at the same time, developed in an environment where the life of the two characters with capicúas names are intertwined. An atmosphere full of chance and coincidences, where the destination is the true protagonist and not always gives us happy situations. The destination has a double face, joy and sadness, smiles and tears, life and death.An excellent work of the Basque filmmaker, which adds to the already-known as "Medem universe". A work that reflects perfectly innate human feelings and transforms them into pure visual poetry. Only Medem knows how to do that; He is a master to do so. If you don't like Medem, if you don't understand his films, if you get bored in the room, better forget about this. For the rest, prepare yourselves to enjoy like never before. Not do a preconceived idea. Watch it with the Mint opened and cleared more than ever, knowing that you're seeing a world recounted and built by July Medem.Con all summarized in his favour, majestic in all senses, is a film that transforms into everything a forced reference in the Spanish film of the 1990s. A real masterpiece that could give only us Medem. Thanks July.</body>
</review>
