<review author="Christian Sandoval" title="Pero.... ¿Quien mató a Harry?" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"A dark comedy, courtesy of the master of suspense, showing perfectly ironic humor that this was owner"</summary>
	<body>But...Who killed Harry? (1955), is one of the films that tends to escape to the parameters by which one knows the Filmography of Alfred Hitchcock. This is a black comedy, which is based on the novel by Jack Trevor Story. This film was not a very good public acceptance, because it was not what one would expect from a work of this director. However, as it is often the case with many things, over time, is recognized the virtues to a realization that this far be one more than the pile.The story takes place in a small village in Vermont, where one day appears a corpse of a man named Harry. Several characters in the town encounter with the body of Harry. Although no one seems to care what this dead, some believe to have been responsible for the death of this man, including his wife Jennifer (Shirley MacLaine) and retired captain Albert Wiles (Edmund Gwenn). With the desire to avoid problems, Harry will be buried and dug up several times, giving place to a to a comedy of errors and some other affair.The fantastic cast that has this film this constituted by newcomer Shirley MacLaine, who was called after seeing his participation in the play "The pajama game". John Forsythe, who personifies Sam Marlowe, an eccentric artist of good heart, which seems to have fun helping your friends to hide the corpse. This actor would later star in another film by Hitchcock called "Topaz" (1969). In addition to these 2 great actors, the film boasts Mildred Natwick, Mildred Dunnock and Edmund Gwenn. They all do a fantastic job, representing a number of people that react in unusual way, in a way very hitchconiana one could say, find a corpse in the middle of the forest.This is the first film in which Hitchcock worked with the composer Bernard Herrmann, society which lasted for several years (the first post that I speak of this).Hitch would recognize later that this soundtrack was his favorite of the composed by Herrmann, even above those of "Vertigo" (1958) and "Psycho" (1960).The film works wonderfully well, in large part because the work carried out both by Herrmann as the by screenwriter John Michael Hayes, who write a fairly intelligent and fluid, script with dialogues quite well achieved and direct, even a little advanced for his time. An example of this is when Sam Marlowe tells Jennifer that she wants to paint nude, so without further ADO.The use of New England landscapes gives a rather special colorful film. Hitchcock chose these foreign because I wanted to show the different shades of nature in autumn, and go that he got.Although this film could be considered as the only comedy made by the master of suspense, in the final stretch, as if it were part of his nature, Hitchcock introduces a quota of suspense, to join the plot to the deputy sheriff Calvin Wiggs (Royal Dano), who can leave evidence involved, attributing them to the crime. However, this is also taken in a tone rather comical, involving a series of situations that opting in a happy ending.Another important fact in the film, is that the director through the shots done, is responsible for give the impression that the characters are dealing more with an object which with a body. Much of the shots that you performed the dead are shots of his feet. In fact his face only go in the drawing created by Marlowe.A despite being a work of undervalued by the director, is a cornerstone of his filmography, which accomplishment out of the genus mastered to perfection, to enter spoiling to the realization of a comedy, that despite that not brings laughter, is an example of ingenious ironic humor that was owner and director.</body>
</review>
