<review author="Cecil B. Demente" title="La llamada de Cthulhu" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film made by the historical society of h. p. Lovecraft based the famous eponymous tale of this man and designed in the style of the silent movies of the 1920s.</summary>
	<body>The death of a prominent professor of the University of Miskatonik will lead to his grandson to investigate mysterious events that seem to be associated with the Satanic Cult to a millennial alien entity: Cthulhu, a bug huge Octopus-headed and more ugly than Picio, who came from the stars millions of years before the appearance of man and thatAlthough it now rests in a deep sleep under the Pacific Ocean, one of these days will wake up and armará a fat looking for a cup of coffee.Film made by the historical society of h. p. Lovecraft based the famous eponymous tale of this man and that, in part by staying with you and in part by lack of guita, is designed in the style of the silent movies of the 1920s (as you know, in black and white and with little signs), as if had been released just after writing the story.The influences of Lovecraft in the film are many and varied, both abound direct adaptations of his stories (Terror Dunwitch and Re-animator, for example) as the movies that only take their peculiar universe (the thing, Infernal possession, or any of Lucio Fulci) provided. Curious is that something so similar on paper gives disparate on-screen results, that can be summarized the work of the Lord in a single sentence: "people which becomes majareta after having tripped up with some foul being unpronounceable name". Not hesitate even for a second that the movie here we will follow this premise to foot juntillas.See call of Cthulhu have had a feeling similar to when you go to a karaoke and upload someone to sing to the scenario that puts eager and believes mogollon, either because the item arrives much or by an excess of alcohol in vein. It may be the film full of economic, artistic shortcomings and techniques (such as the drunk friend of karaoke), but surely not missing attitude and tenacity. Things like this film are what happens when the stoked worldwide come together with a common goal.The make-up of white complexion and eyes and lips painted is quite successful, but the characters are not as well characterized than should. I do not know if it is because I this type of film have seen mainly comedies (I refer in particular to the factory Chaplin and Keaton,) but I think that the actors should be more theatrical and more overact. Besides these movies were pure visual ingenuity, and here lack a little magic and expertise.Be the most faithful adaptation made to date of a Lovecraft tale plays in his favor, clear. Like the little footage (only three quarters of an hour) and the fact that is filmed in Mythoscope (technique to get the look 20 years). The quality of the image on the other hand, is far from what might be and the thing stays in an I want to and I can not only recommended for the most versed in the works of h. p. Lovecraft, the stalwarts of the cinematographic rarities, geeks, Goth, and other evil people live.The phrase: "'nglui mglw' Ph nafh Cthulhu 'r'lyeh wgah' R nagl fhtagn."</body>
</review>
