<review author="Yojimbo" title="United 93" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film is a lesson of many things: how to make a brave but respectful, film how to be based on actual facts without overshadow the film with ideologies, of how adapt film rules and further exciting.</summary>
	<body>Adapting facts to the cinema is conflicting. Much more when they are recent and have changed the story. 9/11 Is a date that we all in our memory. In the information society, we see how we were attacked in the most unexpected way. And how the agony and anger at the time made us react. However making a starring film which already are not present is something that requires, as well explains Paul Greengrass in a small making of, sensitivity, approval of families and based on the facts that are known. With this delicate work of the director, and knowing that I had to make a movie, the result does justice to both tasks: faithfully portray the time and get a great movie.Why this film which portrays what happened in flight United 93, the fourth plane of 9/11 that crashed without achieving its objective, is a large container of so many lessons to be learned. The documentary treatment of this film gives us a role of spectators with "special pass". Their reality ficcionada, starring many of those (which not actors) of that day we gets fully into uncertainty, doubt and fear that the worst can happen. The only problem is that viewers know that it will happen the worst.The structure of the film is a function of the chronology of events. Abandon altogether the standards in which the presentation, situation being and Division of history into acts have a certain number of pages of script. That is why many people feel baffled or bored during the first hour and ten minutes. It seems that nothing happens. However the hidden tension in the tranquility is something that becomes clear in the talks of drivers and military personnel. And then gives way to a brutal half-hour, taquicárdica and emotional that it destroys our false hopes of "happy end". Climax and end at the same time.This film is a lesson of many things: how to make a brave but respectful, film how to be based on actual facts without overshadow the film with ideologies, of how adapt film rules and follow exciting and, above all, how to fight until the end for our lives and our freedom should be a natural attitude in us. Quiet, this phrase is not accompanied by the American flag. It is the greatness of the film. Simply. Greengrass has succeeded with this film change the film similar to the attacks in which relies changed our history.</body>
</review>
