<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Curious blend of romantic film, in the style of "boy finds girl, loses and tries to find to make peace and live happily", and genuine science fiction film / fantasy, banked fully towards the genre of disasters.</summary>
	<body>Curious blend of romantic film, in the style of "boy finds girl, loses and tries to find to make peace and live happily", and genuine science fiction film / fantasy, banked fully towards the genre of disasters.As idea is not bad. The famous and frankly nice television producer J.J. Abrahams, out of the manga, not without much risk by dubious company, a tape that has something of the original and is not regularly in this type of product, although for a time this part really starts to spread (see the Spanish "REC", much better)(incidentally).However happens, well, not true broadly, but what in my regard, the company is turning with the passage of the minutes, somewhat repetitive and charisma.Not much, lasts less than 90 minutes, but it becomes something long, although it never bored or miss the interest, at least as to know how Earth will end the shebang.And that, that of seeing everything through a camera in hand, with continuous movements of camera, with the passage of the minutes become something sea, it is a double-edged weapon. On the one hand gives a greater patina of credibility, of realism, and, sometimes, a documentary halo which gives strength. This happens, for example, at the beginning, with the scene of the head of the statue of liberty falling suddenly on the streets of Manhattan and the huge polvaredas that will cause and leave the streets you miss a few foxes where poorly populate the atónicas people of the place. Achieved scenes, that put the willies and make good hope.However, I think honestly that will gradually losing strength as the film progresses. Fail to maintain interest in the same way that the beginning and the originality becomes conventionalism.The final, against what perhaps could be expected, it is different from what one might expect in a movie of this kind. Not just trite way, so in this case I do not know if it is a good thing or not. The truth is that I get equal. No, I spent the time of agreement, but has not convinced me.The best, without doubt, the extraordinary music of the opening credits end, with a powerful, superb orchestration. By the way, who stayed to listen to?.</body>
</review>
