<review author="Cecil B. Demente" title="La terza Madre" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The expected end of the saga of the three mothers is not the return of the giallo as they wanted us to believe, if not another handful of Earth in his tomb. Sad what they have done, hear.</summary>
	<body>The work of reconstruction of a street next to the cemetery of Viterbo allow the discovery of an enigmatic URN. The URN refers to the Museum of art ancient Rome where works the archaeologist Sarah Mandy (Asia Argento captivating) under the command of Giselle, viceconservadora of this institution. Drawn by curiosity opened the URN, finding the same inside a series of mysterious objects. What they don't know is that they just released from his confinement to Mater Lachrymarum, the return of this beautiful but terrible sorceress brings chaos to the world and leads the Italian capital to the apocalyptic point where the psychic powers of the young American student are the only hope for defeating the last of the witches which starred in the two previous films.If I were Homer Simpson abofetearía with a glove to Dario Argento and tell what "demand satisfaction" (that or it would take me a couple of Duff's and would try to forget about the whole), but as I am not, I complain style grandfather Simpson.Hay many directors who lose their direction, to corroborate there are Tim BurtonRidley Scott and Brian De Palma. The history of Dario Argento is no different, years ago he lives of renda of his early works, which has lost the favor of critics and the public, and has accommodated as old glory. That is why we want to sell this movie as a return to the origins, something he also did Kevin Smith in his time with the second part of Clerks and that went pretty well.SUSPIRIA (1977) and Inferno (1980) are the first deliveries of the hitherto unfinished trilogy of the three mothers and two undisputed masterpieces. The expected end of the saga, however, is not the return of the giallo as they wanted us to believe, if not another handful of Earth in his tomb. Unfortunate what has done, hear. The movie is bad if alone, although I suppose that if its predecessors were not sorted as if they were not so full of strength and beauty, would give less tirri the thing. But it is Mr Argento that they are there, and would be much to see them because it seems that it is the only one that has forgotten.In this third installment has put more characters, more foreign, more screenplay and more light of those two previous boards, thus breaking any kind of link with them (less is more, Mr Argento, and you should know it). If they are breathing an atmosphere of nightmare where the murderer was a supernatural and unknown figure who moved outside the laws of physics, this evil is very visible and very physical, especially because it has some tits you shit and gets balls environment throughout the film. The movie in general has a shabby appearance and videoclubero, the plot is more banal and vision that transmits the tape on the apocalypse is pretty pimp (with many points in common with what come to be the Ramblas of Barcelona a Saturday night). But the worst, what makes that I go up the colors and you want to go out to the balcony to smoke without pressing before the pause, are the ghostly moments with Daria Nicolodi. Very strong Mr Argento (you've seen Ghost, right?). Is the disaster that only comes to head such an analogy of the same caliber; that gruesome sequel of the 2001 Kubrick.La phrase: "Mother!" "Mother, you've come!"</body>
</review>
