<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="La noche de los diablos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Inspired, more harm than good in a play, nothing less, Leo Tolstoy, where were these mysterious and terrifying creatures: the Wurdalak.Sin however, the film is rather boring, quite slow and with few moments of dramatic intensity.</summary>
	<body>"At a place away from the Russian steppe, comes a businessman in the city, which bears a timber business." He wants to meet with another man to reach an agreement and carry your company great amount of wood.Bundled before two paths, he extends his car by the worst of them, when it is night. At any given time you think to see a woman wandering the roads and almost hit him. Suddenly not viewed, but the crankcase of the car has been seriously damaged.Wandering through the forest, it is a strange family composed of the grandfather, three children, a beautiful daughter and the fascinating widow of another son who just bury."You must spend the night with them, learning that the woman believed to see in reality is one witch, a not dead, a Wurdalak, which seeks someone alive to become one like her".Criticism always said of her that, although mediocre, was superior to many of hair that were made back then in the early 1970s. And it may be true, but it is still rather poor. Inspired, more harm than good in a play, nothing less, Leo Tolstoy, where were these mysterious and terrifying creatures: the Wurdalak.Sin however, the film is rather boring, quite slow and with few moments of dramatic intensity. At all times it seems that something truly good visual impact of terror, there is even content, but the truth is that they go through the minutes and the sense of loss of time is increasing.Only the first twenty minutes, until that a flash-back us back to the Russian steppe, are fine. We still don't know what awaits us and the presentation of the protagonist is eye-catching and very mysterious. But, except scenes such as the confrontation between the grandfather and the Wurdalak or the end of the film, which is not bad but it is not bad, the rest is sometimes mediocre and others simply silly.The special effects seen today are ridiculous, although in those days they were fine, but since we saw "A man lobo-americano in London" above seems rather sloppy.Very beautiful Teresa Gimpera and Agostina Belli and convincing Gianni Garko, an Italian actor who his famous character "Sartana" gave immense popularity, but him typecast, think, seriously, because it had a higher than average quality. Ah! And this comment should be subject to the copy that I saw, that is, which issued by a Spanish payment channel. Most likely it was, apart from a copy in a pretty bad state, with streaks and all, I guess it was the version that premiered in Spain. It is well known that some co-productions between Spain and some foreign country had the particularity that, in other countries aired complete. In Spain, however, is mutiliaba when there were increases tone, i.e., erotic. or very violent scenes. The full version of this film and that some will be lucky enough to see, perhaps, but I speak of that I saw that Yes, seemed quite cut.</body>
</review>
