<review author="Plissken" title="Rocky Balboa" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A brief history of back to the neighborhood, an invitation to look back and see how it has changed everything except the will of iron from a guy recently and limited.</summary>
	<body>Two of my first film memories are the cruel sea: one is the death of Bambi's mother, and another Rocky Balboa rolling to hosts with Apollo Creed. The first tragic event still I am not able to speak in public, but the second I'm more than obliged after seeing 'Rocky Balboa', the sixth and final part of this series that accompanied us during much of our childhood and adolescence.The fact is that each new installment of the exploits of this expert loser who was in 'Rocky' Balboa seemed to me I lost more and more bellows. As if it were a match for one of those killers that it relies everything to the stuck because they know that they may not endure twelve rounds on foot. What initially was a beloved and limited character was becoming a born winner, in a superhero who fought against horrible people who violated against their most loved, even against his country. After a second notable part, a third entertaining (and with 'The Eye of the Tiger'!) and a fourth in operetta, became a fifth that I took off all the desire to return to see the Italian Colt again.Then came the last time. And I did if people told me "it is not so bad," because my last memory of Rocky was Rocky giving a beating to a brat got Boxer (Tommy Morrison, which was by the wayside due to AIDS). But almost a year after its release, I find what should have been 'Rocky V': a brief history of back to the neighborhood, an invitation to look back and see how it has changed everything except the will of iron from a guy recently and limited.So Stallone surprises with a beautiful and tinged nostalgia boot (first thing that sounds is the great ' Take it Back' to his brother Frank played in 'Rocky'), half an hour that you reconciled again with the character (played by Sly way endearing and ducks). The story then enters a loop of redundancies and warm scenes (a training who know little, and not much more), which are nothing more than an excuse to give us the last fight of Rocky Balboa: a little gem of the sports film filmed in high definition video and it returns us the epic saga. Total: thirty minutes bright, last fifteen minutes bright, and "in the Middle", light.In the technical section, highlights photographic treatment (at times almost documentary) j. Clark Mathis, and the spectacular environment that exists in the last match (took a real match to shoot between 11,000 euphoric fans, including Tyson). Of course, makeup and boxísticas choreographies of the expert Stallone give a far cry from the unreal fight air with Ivan Drago, in one of the best filmed fighting in the saga. The music of the emblematic Bill Conti also brings its grain of sand.And on the negative side, a choice of actors something flojita (the two kids are indeed mediocre, and Antonio Tarver is a boxer, not Marlon Brando) and this second act that takes turns to an unlikely relationship.The feeling that remains is more sweet to sour, however. You know that already never again to hear Rocko terrible jokes, or the rough voice of Paulie, or the eternal 'Gonna Fly Now' with his triumphant fanfare. But you miss a lagrimita, think that that "nothing ends until it ends" is a truth as a fist of heavyweight champion, and you stay glued to watching the end credits to people imitating the most famous race in the history of the cinema. "Gettin' stronger!". A 7.</body>
</review>
