<review author="elprimerhombre" title="Los amantes del Pont-Neuf" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film with a special charm that, despite its footage, a bit extensive for the story told, hooked by its visual strength and mise en scène</summary>
	<body>Elprimerhombre has seen a movie with a special charm that, despite its footage, a bit extensive for the story told, hooked by its visual strength and its staging. A director did not know and that has only directed five films, am talking about lovers of the Pont-Neuf, of Leos Carax, the last of which was Polar X, in 1999, with Guilleme Depardieu. It is an intimate film featuring the work of a director inspired as Leos Carax and the role of the two main actors, Denis Lavant and Juliette Binoche. Lavant it did not know him, but his character is quite credible and emotional, and the truth is that the role was intended for him. Shortly before the shooting start, Lavant had an accident: cut the tendon in the thumb of one hand. Following this event, the film had to be postponed a month and insurers wanted to change of actor, but Carax refused outright; He had written the script thinking of Lavant and wanted to do it with him. In the end it was. And it is that actor and director already had rolled together the two previous films. "The Binoche" (as they call in France) is an actress who since that I saw her in blue has me in love (although it has lost much; the years not passed in vain). And it seems that the characters difficult to interpret, as in blue or wound, with Jeremy Irons, suffering likes (other than such), and is that not given bad doing this kind of characters. In this film it is a sober role that shows you know laugh and cry brilliantly. And not all the actresses do, because you will not tell me that the great Greta Garbo laughs in Ninotchka credibly. Carax manages to supply some ups and downs of the script with beautiful drawings. And there are things that happen that they are little credible, as see the character of Binoche in drunk State doing water skiing, although this can be considered as a joke, as a magical moment. The scene at the pont-neuf with fireworks in the background seems to me the best of the film. And now that I am speaking of the Pont-Neuf, the oldest bridge in Paris, I will tell what happened during the filming of this movie. In 1988, the producers got authorization to shoot during the day on the Pont-Neuf, from July to August, while to shoot at night, a decoration of the bridge, real but simplified, in a village called Lansargues was built. Leos Carax wanted that the cost of the decorated not passed 5 million francs, but was growing increasingly affecting the production of the film. Stopped repeatedly shooting because nobody wanted to put so much money taking rile the entire team, making the start of the film increasingly problematic. From October 1989 to June 1990, no one appeared the sets. They were only two security guards to ensure that no one will take anything or trashed nothing, although storms spoiled much of the buildings erected with scaffolding. At the end, thanks to producer Christian Fechner, at a cost of more than 70 billion francs in August 1990, two hundred workers eventually finished on an area of 10 acres (10,000 m2), one of the largest French cinema sets, as a major Hollywood Studio, creating the illusion of reality with ingenuity. Ultimately it is not belittle the efforts that took place to finish the film. Leos Carax is a director with great talent, with very interesting details when planning a plane. Top with a few homeless people scene is shot in a realistic and cruel and an emotional moment is when Lavant throws a stone to the river and every pot in water he is whispering the name of it: "Michele, Michele, Michele.". The funny thing is that, in my opinion, this film has some points in common with blue, Kieslowski, especially at the beginning, with a vibrant music of a cello, with the camera focusing on from a car with planes from the hands of those who are in the same car caressing tenderness, or the character of Juliette Binoche who escapes from a relationship with a musician, and who in one scene in the Paris metro, hears a melody produced by a cello (the same music we hear at the beginning) that he reminds his expareja and runs through the corridors in their quest. This is not to say that Mr Kieslowski had this film as a reference, but I think something to highlight. A greeting!</body>
</review>
