<review author="Yojimbo" title="Rescue Dawn" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The director pretends its players to a Port Aventura in Laos. A genuine physical and psychological torture that impresses the spectator.</summary>
	<body>A friend and I have dubbed a war cry after seeing this film: "Werneeeeeeeeeeeer". And it is that we imagine that it would be the cry insistently repeated the actors during the filming. Director Werner Herzog pretends to Christian Bale, Steve Zahn and Jeremy Davies to a Port Aventura in Laos. A genuine physical and psychological torture that impresses the spectator. This modest film comes with a simple argument but a treatment and a realism in your images so impressive as daunting.Bale is a fighter pilot that falls in the jungles of Laos during the Viet Nam Guerra. The vietcong him aprensan but it will end up in a prison camp where you find other soldiers being there awhile. The pilot, with great decision, decides to escape and invests his ingenuity and commitment to get out of there, even with the other captives.Although the film appears to be a telefilm, the quality of the implementation and interpretation, as well as the realism of the setting, manage to get into a movie more than the Viet Nam with few elements, without too many helicopters or napalm explosions. It does lack. It is a small story in a great war, and the small stories are many differences which mark. A delicate, paused and emotional music by Klaus Badelt accompanies terrible images of file of a forest devastated by bombs. This contrast will be the note to mark the entire film: the story of how to keep calm or inventár is when things go disastrously wrong but also how to solve an untenable situation. And no one better than Christian Bale to play the pilot. One of the finest actors of the current scene.One of the great virtues of the film is the commitment of the director and the cast for putting in situation to the spectator through risky scripts and dangerous characterizations staying in the bones, literally. And for Bale are two, counting of the driver. An effort worthy of mention.Although the argument is something repeated in many war films, this is achieved suffer with prisoners and participate in their plans and celebrations in silence. A beautiful lesson of survival and struggle to not fall into madness.</body>
</review>
