<review author="Cp" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There is no denying that you as Monster film, style kaiju eiga manages to innovate the way of telling us it. It is a fantasy film with a filter of reality.</summary>
	<body>When sales of the film, and not stop to talk about the film with friends with whom you've gone to see it, it is usually that you liked. This is more about what you have just innovate J.J.Abrams. Now you can talk for hours about a movie, but in fact you do not speak of what you've seen on the tape, but all the information that surround. Like in lost, this shot well, is agile, interesting and really you it is counting a culebron &hellip;... Sorry!, a human history of relations between the characters, I wanted to say. There is no denying that you as Monster film, style kaiju eiga manages to innovate the way of telling us it. It is a fantasy film with a filter of reality. Everything seems credible, as it would really be the reaction to the attack of an unknown, including the go listening theories of all kinds of mouths of the characters to be. As with the Bourne saga, or the Ultimates comics, verisimilitude and realism is the master rule of director, screenwriter and productor.¿Pero that we have left if we remove all of that, and above all, not we have been following advertising campaign on the Internet that gives us a lot of information, which then does not appear in the film? Since fleeing a movie Monster and colleagues, shot camera in hand, where that is carrying the camera is actually somewhat useless, and sometimes teaches us cleavage, or has the monster to one side, from the 59 floor of a building and not think filming it. In that sense I like me, it's not like other movie camera in hand, where the camera does not lose or a detail, here is an amateur who does not know to use it. For the rest, I liked also that the first twenty minutes are to present the characters, giving us a sense of tranquility, until it reaches the time of action. A from there, scares, races, quite spectacular images, especially for this very measure the appearance of any horrible thing, and the feeling that you are not anyone. The military ignored you, you're one more in the mass of refugees, do not know that it happens, and every decision leads you to a new danger.The theory that we had yesterday, is that it may be a good trick to make a low budget movie, get a million dollar box office, and then make a second part, with a huge budget. So, Cloverfield would be the vista version from victims, and Cloverfield 2, a more classic film, with its scientists, military and political. Although Abrams that this involved, namely that history can get us. A crossover between Lost and Cloverfield? Rarest theory could be true, because the end is open and they you never really get anything.</body>
</review>
