<review author="Ethan" title="Él" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>On startup, Buñuel already presents his two major obsessions, which more upset human being: religion and sex.</summary>
	<body>The Mexican stage of the director from Calanda, stresses the trilogy which took place "in their own way", on the bourgeois customs of the time. It is "He", excellent melodrama that accompanies the important "El Ángel Exterminador" and "Trial of a crime". Before enter in history and, above all, in the form of tell by the brilliant director, it is worth a brief reference to its usual partners in this important period: Oscar Dacingers producer, responsible for several masterpieces of Buñuel; cinematographer Gabriel Figueroa, very skillful in the handling of the lights and the shadows, indebted to the expressionist movement and author of tapes that, occasionally, darkening the work of important directors to erect as true creator - see "The fugitive" ("The fugitive", 1947) of the selfsame John Ford-; and, finally, his inseparable Luis Alcoriza, a sharp writer and, later, excellent director, also exiled from war and preferred target of jokes by Buñuel. They say that a day of hunting, when Alcoriza was going to charge a piece (a bird that had shot shot), found it already filling up with the price on a label tied to one of its legs. Spanish filmmaker works are very personal and features as if "He" we would have lost the credits, just seeing the close-up, we realise straight away dealing with a tape of his own. And is that at boot already he presents his two major obsessions, which more upset human being: religion and sex. -"Sex without religion is like cooking an egg without salt," he assured Buñuel in an interview-. This scene of the washing of feet in the Church happens to be one of their sequences more provocative and best shot. In the hands of Buñuel, recreation by a priest of what was written in the Gospels has a lecherous meaning. Also the presentation of the protagonist (Arturo de Córdova), a perfect summary of his personality when he observes the feet of his future wife with passion and barely be able to disguise their desire. Throughout footage Buñuel repeats with plans detail the same situation, scene, on the other hand, can be seen in several of his later films ("Diary of a Chambermaid" or "Belle de Jour", are two examples). Although the production of "He" is very modest, however the decoration of the House where the events take place is worthy of study in detail. In a first viewing of the tape can we pass unnoticed, but if you look in the doors, the arches separating the rooms, stairs and Windows we will observe a very daliniana and modernist architecture at the same time, with touches of Gaudí, all in accordance with the tortuous personality of the tenant. The entire film is a prodigy of mise en scene, but apart from the boot, already commented, I would like to highlight two sequences: one confirms that still very personal film Buñuel isn't free from influences. It takes place at the top of a Bell Tower, there the couple protagonist observes people as if they were ants and produces a situation reminiscent of "The third man" ("The Third Man" by Carol Reed, 1949); in fact the dialogue about insignificant people is almost the same as pronounced by Orson Welles in the famous sequence of the Ferris wheel. The other scene is the final conclusion. Sums up the film perfectly, leaves the viewer with a, say, attractive anxiety and it contains many more clues about the Buñuel film than what I can tell these lines in a single plane.</body>
</review>
