<review author="Red Stovall" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie full of ups and downs, with excellent rations of great action movie, but that does not stop being a small disappointment for those who do know what Mr Mann is capable.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Michael Mann. That simple phrase is more than reason enough for any good amateur film passing through box office to see 'Miami Vice'. The American director was responsible for the famous television series and has now commissioned to film, in a fairly free, more than expected adaptation. In fact, if get you another title and the players characters other names, this would have worked equally and no one would have noticed the similarity to the television series. Seems to me that the series was going or I came, Mann succeeds by doing this, but just as many see it as a disappointing commercial play. Either way, important thing is the movie and not what is based on. And the film is not as good as that one would expect of a filmmaker he has filmed two absolute masterpieces such as 'Heat' and 'The dilemma' (his best film). It is a notable action film mixed with silly romantic scenes. Fortunately, the successes of the film are much more powerful than the skidding. 'Miami Vice' focuses on the detectives James 'Sonny' Crockett and Ricardo Tubbs 'rico'. After the call of an infiltrator to Sonny, the stylish protagonists learn that a band of criminals has uncovered throughout a covert police operation, ending the life of several agents. Convinced that there is a very big fish behind affair, Sonny and Rico will prepare a major operation to catch him, whose first step is the infiltration in the business of drug traffickers. What they did not expect is that the 'gangster girl' go to cross on the path of Sonny and endanger the mission. The film begins almost without warning, putting us squarely in a nightclub in luxury to the beat of Jay Z &amp; Linkin Park (a great song, by the way, is much better without the participation of the rapper). Soon we will see the two protagonists and we will feel immersed in the best film by Michael Mann: great technical virtuosity, beautiful images perfectly accompanied by great music and striking lightning of extraordinary action. The best from the beginning is that you leave you little room for manoeuvre. You enter or enter. What does Mann, as Billy Wilder, would say grab the Viewer by the lapels and (this already so I say) throw it without alternative to the dance hall. With some few strokes we learn what is happening and who are the protagonists. Everything is underway. The boot is the best of the film, but it will soon give way to a disturbing change of pace, following the call to Sonny, who will be the tone of the rest of the excessive footage. Moments of extreme action with others of extreme boredom. Because Mann not only boasts of his grandiose style that makes it taking it to the highest level, with their advantages and disadvantages. The advantages I have already commented, and, really, is what survives to the end: the beauty of the images and the thundering action scenes. Special attention, talking about the action to the realism that emerge, not only by the visual format that chooses Mann but, above all, by the brilliant planning and staging. As I have said, these successes of the film are the ones who left after its viewing, but. There are also obvious weaknesses. A poor argument, usually empty dialogues and exaggerated duration, to what counts. Course, it's an action film and matters such as character development and the argument must not be regarded with magnifying glass or affect the enjoyment of the session. Since then, here one that he aims at that. But the own Mann takes a bit of reason to the raised and becomes his major opponent. And I say this because there is a peliculón of the same director entitled 'Heat', which we must take into account when assessing 'Miami Vice'. We can even put on the table the recent and notable 'Collateral', where Mann demonstrated that the characters are as important as a good scene of spectacular action. In 'Miami Vice' not given the most minimal importance to the characters and handles them as if they were regular puppets of a topical tape action of B series starring Van Damme or the shift Seagal. Okay the excuse of the series behind to save this aspect? Neither of coña. The Viewer does not have why have been soaked in the television series to enjoy fully with the film adaptation. In addition, even so, the excuse powerless when the treatment of the characters throughout the film, without any depth is. To this must be added a few dialogues that leave a lot to be desired. The encounters between the 'good' and 'bad' are a good example of the great void of the talks. In fact, there are scenes in which the characters are talking and when you respond to one, stays silent and a few seconds later, change of scene. It seems that Mann has tried to give a spontaneous touch to the dialogues and the tyre, by this time, has left by the stock. Not to mention 'comic' scenes as the fake 'gatillazo' rich, more like another type of film (and everyone who thinks that wants to). As I say, for more than two hours there are moments for everything. For both the startle and more involuntary yawn. Not understood the excessive length of the movie and when the story lacks any kind of complexity. They could have longer times of cheap SOAP in the editing room. Because if I mentioned before that of the dialogues, we must make reference to the fool and forced romance between the characters of Collin Farrell and Gong Li. Are they look, they return to find they look, become to find, they look. Finally, he asks the 'favor' to invite a cup and she, without think about it much, takes him to Cuba in a boat. The most normal of the world since then. What is happening there is also normal. They drink, dance and fuck. She cries. He is like a champ. They showered and returned to the attack. Shortly after, they are talking about parents and teaching pics. But they decide that they cannot be together. and back to bed. In reality, the romantic moments starring Jamie Foxx and Naomie Harris is not be best narrated, but as they have less time on screen it shows less. Interestingly, both parejan have a 'meeting' scene in the shower; already could have sought Mann otherwise make palpable passion in the two couples and not to repeat the scene. Certainly no less curious is that Foxx disappears from the film for quite a few minutes to make Farrell as the absolute protagonist. I had read somewhere (as you would say Alatriste, my memory is harmful). (for some things) that Foxx was not nothing happy with what Mann did with his character and his role in the film. Now (without knowing if this is true or not, eye) I see it more understandable. Which one of the two stars, in particular to the two best actor (for something has an Oscar and the other is not), so out of the film, without any reasonable reason, must be less than mosqueante. Leaving that aside, and returning to what is important, the real problem of 'Miami Vice', the film would have won a lot and could have been that great movie expected Mann if the romantic scenes seem not filmed by the 'director' of any soap opera that tend to emit after lunchtime, but by the same who did 'Heat' or 'The dilemma' or 'Ali'where there were moments for the couple of question time and, unlike on this occasion, they were very accomplished and excited. Quite possibly, the reason for this can be found in the coldness that follows the film at all times, a coldness which is well connected with the protagonists of the story and the fact that at night where more comfortable feels the director. The best example to sum up the coldness of the film is the great villain of the film, a guy named Arcangel de Jesus Montoya, role who plays (i.e. a) Luis Tosar, recovering the 'touch Spanish' from 'Collateral'. Tosar represents a very cold and deadpan kind that sometimes it seems that the actor is a statue of wax. I do not know what will be said Mann to make the Spanish as hieratic, perhaps photos of Seagal taught him and told him: 'imitate him'. What is clear is that Tosar is a great actor and has presence, charisma, whereupon his frozen character, with the help of the Mann House, becomes a figure of power, some threat. Not in vain, the most terrible character is transmitting its power without reaching exercise it. No charge, Jose Yero, the other 'bad' of the film, subordinate of Montoya, boss is much more active, nervous, direct. The 'unknown' John Ortiz has good scenes in which shines and shows where your choice has been very successful. Notably, leaving us with the set and leaving aside the useless verbiage, the first encounter with Farrell and Foxx, where the three put their cards on the table. Duo protagonist, as I have already indicated, Jamie Foxx, with less minutes on screen and slightly less prominence, beats him Marist (not surprisingly) for Collin Farrell, who, on the other hand, does anything wrong. Farrell still has much to offer to justify his fame (apart from events of gossip or rumors about its Anatomy) but no one should forget, assessing him as an actor, some their own interpretations of excellent level, as in 'The last call' or 'Alexander the great' (essential, obviously view it in original version). Gong Li, an actress beautiful why seems that do not pass the years deserves special mention. If in 'Memoirs of a Geisha' was totally irresistible, here it is not less. A pity that his character is so cardboard and have to rely on both his great physique to highlight on the screen. As for the rest of the cast, almost all side with little time on screen, I can only say that they comply with far and you wish that they had given them some minutes to develop a somewhat decorative character. I speak of Naomie Harris (promising actress that we saw, very lumpy in the sequel of 'Pirates of the Caribbean'), Justin Threoux (who just does nothing), Barry Shabaka Henry or the own Luis Tosar, to quote the best-known. Therefore, a good movie full of ups and downs, with excellent rations of great action movie, but that does not stop being a small disappointment for those who do know what Mr Mann is capable. With a more elaborate script, would be his third masterpiece. No wonder that you had a very warm welcome in the United States. UU. and to be repeated around the world. The first week gets a good sum for the issue of advertising and the protagonists, and then down, without remedy. The public is not for a quiet film, is considered a waste of time. If you do not get the kids that fill the Chambers are glued to the screen, there is nothing to do. An sms and to give cane to the emule. The truth is that you have to be a little mad (who it is not?) to pretend that this 'Miami Vice' is a success. It seems that your site is another, here at a time, when it comes out on dvd and you to situate next to his older sisters, 'Heat' or 'Collateral', on the shelves of many of us and others who now prefer products of rapid consumption (television, especially) and leave the cinema for a session more comfortable Casita. Nothing to object to, by the way, don't get me wrong. And speaking of dvds, we hope that Mann has decided to make a touch to the film and give us the ability to contemplate an alternative mounting. It would not be bad. </body>
</review>
