<review author="Emilio Martín Luna" title="3:10 to Yuma" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Highlight the part final film, very exciting and frenetic and the chemistry between the two main characters played by Russell Crowe and Christian Bale is great absolumente. Great movie.</summary>
	<body>In 1957, Delmer Daves believe the train of the three and ten, film starring Glenn Ford and that became a film of cult, by having a different treatment, a western psychological, closer only to danger and roots deep, a tension which produce, to the prevailing westerns at the time. It was an imperfect film, something improbable, but really fun. Fifty years later and in full fashion do remakes of all existing film, James Mangold is proposing a new version of this classic, and the film is surprisingly very good. Nothing changes from the original, perhaps delves more into the characters and the plot becomes more contemporary although calcada to the original pero.¿Es better than the original?Really if the chemistry between the two main characters played by Russell Crowe and Christian Bale is great absolumente, it is undoubtedly the best of the film, their conversations and their relationship. Russell Crowe gives Ben Wade, this nuance of bad buenote, intelligent and eager to leave his life of Bushranger, which makes you fall it well. Christian Bale gives many strength and credibility to his Dan Evans, a man in search of reconseguir respect both their own as his family, very honest man and interpretation of the Welsh actor you do that also you identiques with him. Colossal this duo. But these two actors not just the thing, the side are also sensational, Ben Foster making bad malísimo with great charisma and Logan Lorman making son of Bale with much poise. Apart from the performances, highlights much both photography and the setting that makes you're the dangerous and old West, as well as a great soundtrack for Marco Beltrami. The address is sober, direct and with a frenetic pulse.James Mangold an artisan than a director, demonstrates his talent in this film, and redo of earlier works giving an own label, with personality and taking the best of a good script and great cast.I want to highlight the part final film, very exciting and frenetic, perhaps the last final twist is not liked by everyone, and during the film can cross out of some inverosimiles of the actions of the protagonists, but is a film adventures in the West as a whole life, and so have to see it. I really enjoyed and I was thrilled it history. I recommend it to everyone.</body>
</review>
