<review author="Emilio Martín Luna" title="No es Pais para viejos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not round, but, for me, is a great movie, displays that good cinema with little can be done, and that the important thing is a good idea and people with quality about to translate it.</summary>
	<body>Making a memory exercise, I come all films of the Coen brothers, different to the norm, of varied genres, films based on atypical places and diverse characters. A film different therefore with seal itself, for good or bad, the Coens are faithful to his origins and his films always have the classic aúrea that distinguish them from the average of independent American cinema (if you can call movies indie which make the Coens, perhaps less budget). Ultimately a film, whose films are most cult, El Gran Lebowski, Barton Fink, death among the flowers and the great Fargo, are a good sample of the talent in the direction of these brothers (although in most is his brother Joel which directs and Ethan is responsible for the screenplay). Now this month of February we will be his latest creation, the multi No Country for Old Men, praised by the critical American and very serious contender to win the Oscar for best foreign film (although who cares awards.)also in its cast have to Javier Bardem in a great role and it will report no less recognition of both praise and awards.After seeing the close-up, the prologue with the voice of Tommy Lee Jones, comes to mind the three burials of Melquiades Estrada, southern USA, border with Mexico Earth, desiertos.para start the photography is fantastic, you permeates the heat in the area, creates an uncomfortable land and so makes it you feel your address, long flat, many silences and (varied) characters as real as you take a stroll through Texas. The plot is simple well linked, perhaps somewhat slow for the public of a foot used to action even if you have a meaningless, and perhaps it could show somehow light and fluid, but then wouldn't the Coen.El distribution of first order, special mention for Josh Brolin, reborn as a serious actor, Tommy Lee Jones sensational, credible, thoughtful. A Bardem eats the camera as a ruthless killer, a man with principles (though go principles that spends) it gets you very afraid and produces a tension without equal, he and his "weapon" clear. I would also like to mention the actress Kelly Mc Donald, which get little on screen, but seems very successful as the wife of Llewelyn Moss (Brolin). The story is fragmented into three parts: flight Llewelyn, the search for the murderer and the investigation of our police (Tommy Lee) and van alternating during the duration of the film, and as said before perhaps not with a 1920x1080p my I like so in some time slows down the pace.It is not round, but, for me, is a great movie, shows that good cinema with little can be done, and that the really important thing is a good idea and people with quality around them to translate it, and the Coens, will get their way, because they have done another classic which will mark the beginning of year and will have their reward in the advertising campaign of awards.</body>
</review>
