<review author="Emilio Martín Luna" title="Expiación: Más Alla de la Pasión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The truth is that it has many positive elements this film, but with the feeling of being a very touched history in film, with many aspects already repeated, a film whose purpose is to excite the Viewer, with difficult love, adversity and good background music.</summary>
	<body>One might ask in the first place without Joe Wright and the Minguella brothers were at the same Academy of cinema, or if they have any kinship or if Wright for being youngest admires the eldest of the Minguella, Anthony. I ask myself these questions by the resemblance of the works, in the formal aspect and its method of narration of his major films, Wright: pride and prejudice and the film I took in these moments, and, Minguella: the English patient, the talent of Mr Ripley (this only at the time), and Cold Mountain. All different movies, but with a cut film 1960s drama of times, lavish production, and very academic (translation: go to the Oscars). These are all great films, shot with a space of considerable time, aimed at an adult audience, British style, great deals and much pretension.My words do not want to extract that the film is bad, quite the contrary, simply that lets you "dejavú", ya I've seen, in another way, in another country, with other characters, even of different style, but I've already seen. Atonement, is a drama of time between wars, with the second world war in the background, Inglaterra-Francia. Two people who want and a terrible mistake. Production of primerisimo level, changing rooms, photography and an excellent soundtrack of Dario Marinelli, clear candidate for an Academy Award. Very good actors, being weak by James McAvoy since what I saw in the last King of Scotland, actor very believable, which follows in the footsteps of Jude Law, Keira Knightley, evoking the classic Hollywood actresses, physically and with his slow and steady work. And good side, as the young Saoirse Ronan (that will be the next Peter Jackson "from my sky") Vanessa Redgrave and Romola Garai. A script good and great direction of Joe Wright, I love these weather changes, with regard to what sees Briony (Ronan) and his subsequent explanation, can be messy, but as a final product gives a touch of distinction to the direction of this young director.The truth is that it has many positive elements this film, but with the feeling of being a very touched history in film, with many aspects already repeated, a film whose purpose is to excite the Viewer, with difficult love, adversity and good background music. It's interesting, entertaining and beautiful, like many others.</body>
</review>
