<review author="Emilio Martín Luna" title="Adiós pequeña, adiós" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It has a good pace, though he suffered ups and downs in the middle of the footage, perhaps the final moralina, do doubt some, to my it made me think, and I liked the end.Very well written and directed this directorial debut of Don Ben, who has earned my respect.</summary>
	<body>BEN AFFLECK.decir Ben Affleck i.e. lousy actor, bad movies, Golden Lion in Venice by Hollywoodland.donde portraying a failed actor. There are many cases of actors that are passed to the other side of the camera with greater or lesser success. By fortune, and incredibly, Ben Affleck as director in his first film, meets and meets considerably. You have good taste good Affeck when it comes to telling a story, I am very sure who has drunk of the great directors of recent times, and Mystic River liked and muchó, because it has some coincidences and winks to the work of Clint Eastwood. Affleck seeks the classicism in the narration of a controversial and topical, good plans and taking advantage of a quick script and investigating in the main characters.He has a large cast, headed by his brother Casey, at first, his character is cold and little credible, as it progresses the footage work is convincing and we feel empathy towards him. It has been a great year for Casey Affleck, rewarded with a nomination for best secondary in the Oscars. Accompany the classics Ed Harris and Morgan Freeman, that fill the screen and give strength to the film. In the women's section are Amy Ryan, also nominated for her role as mother, even when mother. And Michelle Monaghan as girlfriend of the protagonist, which meets in screen.The film has a good rhythm, although he suffered ups and downs in the middle of the footage, perhaps the final moralina, do doubt some, to my it made me think, and I really liked this ending. Solid performances, very well directed and written this directorial debut of Don Ben, who has earned my respect.</body>
</review>
