<review author="Oscar Martínez" title="Sweeney Todd" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A work of worship although somewhat slow in their execution, which lies directly along The Rocky Horror Picture Show' and 'The Phantom of the paradise' on bizarre musical refers.</summary>
	<body>Directed by Tim Burton and starring Johnny Depp, Helena Bonham Carter, Alan Rickman and Sacha Baron Cohen, Timothy Spall, among others, Sweeney Todd: the evil Barber of Fleet Street has won two Golden Globes, opting instead to three statuettes, a musical based on the work of Stephen Sondheim and Hugh Wheeler.Sweeney Todd tells the story of Benjamin BarkerHe is imprisoned because of a false accusation of Judge Turpin, only proposed staying with his wife and daughter. The return of unfair captivity, Barker returns looking for his family, but discovers that his wife committed suicide after that Turpin would like to take advantage of it and maintained captive his daughter. Then, Benjamin Barker changed his name to Sweeney Todd, returns to his old barbershop and begins plotting his revenge. To do so, it complotará with Mrs. Lovett, the lonely owner of the premises located below the barbershop. In the bloody revenge, she will find a way to revive his meat pastries business.That Tim Burton is a single director and which, therefore, drag a number of unconditional supporters, is nothing new. Through titles as mythical as Eduardo Manostijeras, Bitelchus, nightmare before Christmas (despite not being the director) or Sleepy Hollow, the Californian filmmaker has created a unique universe that combines the Gothic, the bizarre, the romantic and gloomy. In fact, when has avoided such aesthetics (read Mars attacks!, planet of the apes or the wonderful Ed Wood and Big fish), Burton has not gone as well as I would like to by what the return to this neo-Gothic aesthetic with Johnny Depp in the lead heralded an acknowledgement a resounding success.In general terms, we could say that Sweeney Todd is a good movie, although neither by far the best Tim Burton: despite all their awards and nominations, the excellent reviews it has received from the American press, and despite the fact that the sixth collaboration between Depp and Burton contains all the ingredients to become a new classicThere is something that ends not materialize and that something is its duration.With a length of nearly two hours, this dark Broadway musical adaptation may exasperate anyone who is not familiar with the universe Burton, because its starting slow in excess in a succession of very successful although somewhat cansinas musical permutations, especially because of the almost total lack of prose over the tape. Sweeney Todd is therefore a beautiful film with a fun although perhaps plot too predictable and whose main handycap lies, ironically, with its musical base, despite contain certainly brilliant moments.Already the fact that Sweeney Todd is nominated to the best costume design, Best Actor and best art direction, and it is not the best soundtrack, says a lot of which have been priorities of Tim Burton at the time of making the film. And it is that the only thing that differentiates Sweeney Todd of, for example, genius as the bride corpse or nightmare before Christmas, not animation, neither the plot nor the setting, but forty minutes of footage.On the other hand, if something worth mentioning of Sweeney Todd, is undoubtedly its production design and artistic, as always address, beautifully executed and carefully designed, moving to a Downtown grim and spellbinding London presented with a flat sequence simply master, while a server you mentioned somehow that Coppola use in Dracula during the phase licántropa of Oldman. And it is that if something is a master Tim Burton, in bizarre and oniric worlds at the same time extremely beautiful and romantic.In short, I will say that Sweeney Todd is a good movie in general terms, a sort of Sleepy hollow merged with The Rocky Horror Picture Show which contains great achievements and a plastic, on the other hand, regular beauty already in the Tim Burton film, but placed perhaps an excess of duration or, rather, a slowdown because of an abuse of their musical numbersas you look.Nevertheless, viewing essential.</body>
</review>
