<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Saw 4" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Zarrapastrosa narration, with a multitude of negrísimos holes and inconsistencies of script her try us strain distorting reality and mixing us continually flashbacks with today.</summary>
	<body>Definitely Saw saga has come to an end. Not to an end as a franchise, since Lions Gate seems the goose that lays the golden egg by with Jigsaw, and as long as they build the pull you have to Saw V and Saw VI. I say that it is over for his screenplay, Bill, history and quality. Not be can stretch more a saga when he doesn't more than if. If already with the third level fell considerably, now this fourth there where take it. Firstly, this incoherent storytelling through flashbacks, mixing past and present. Sr.Lynn Bousman, with all due respect you is not (nor will be at this rate) Iñarritu in 21 grams, Amores Perros and or much less Nolan on Memento or Tarantino in Pulp Fiction; then not try please, leave that to the professionals of truth. Zarrapastrosa narration, with a multitude of negrísimos holes and inconsistencies of script her try us strain distorting reality and mixing us continually flashbacks with today. To all this we add the (im) predictable plot twist at the end - typical in the saga - and have a trash in every rule. Is that not realize that turn script was more than exhausted in the first part and if I hurry in the second? It seems that they do not understand. And to make matters worse, the 83 - endless-minutes that lasts by removing end credits, 10 minutes correspond to scenes past previous deliveries, which reflected the lack of ideas coming from the team and the need to fill with unnecessary flashbacks that all footage that make is rolling to the Viewer. For the fans of the guts and gore, among which certainly I find, highlight only the scene of the autopsy to Jigsaw with all kinds of detail and a unique "test". The only thing the to really interesting (testing) has lost its originality and grace. A shame, certainly the worst in the series, every hand along with the 3. Finally, the phrase alive or dead, your decide to just getting tired when you hear her 20 times. Renew or die, never better said.</body>
</review>
