<review author="Ana Belén Pacheco" title="Good luck Chuck" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a masterpiece of the genre but it can help to an audience accustomed to a hybrid between crazy most of the current comedy and a bit of restraint.</summary>
	<body>Chuck is a type simpaticote, good mozalbete and guaperas. But it is not very lucky in love. That will change when she discovers the world that is delighted (or cursed,) as you look at, it seems that any woman who will lie with him will marry the next person that Kiss desdee that small after a traumatic the bottle game girl lem cursed at a wedding of a friend. On the same day he met a beautiful girl that appears followed by the disaster, a carer for the penguins with a special ability to destroy everything that touches that obviously is going to fall in love with. With all the women of the city wishing their sexual favors to get to the altar as soon as possible and the woman of his life waiting for you Chuck will have to take some "painful decisions".I am confused with this film. A superb beginning of absurd comedy (with a man hugging his penis almost) the thing drift in a little strange directions. As soon as they try to put online a Farreliana as it jumps to the juvenile comedy more topical. Despite this junction of sensations felt me of the most refreshing I've seen in quite some time. While the presence of Dane Cook, hitherto a real unknown for me (because I try to desperately forget his role in Mr. Brooks as well as the rest of the film and because it has nothing to do his performance on this with the other) has been rewarding. Long ago that there were no new faces in the American comedy. On the other hand also helps correct Jessica Alba as a perfect couple (not has depleted much this girl?) have helped round out a little more.It is not a masterpiece of the genre but it can help to an audience accustomed to a hybrid between crazy most of the current comedy and a bit of restraint.</body>
</review>
