<review author="Moebius" title="El bueno, el feo y el malo" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Critical vapuleó the film, but the public responded in an enthusiastic manner. Thereafter the American western never again be the same. As it was not the career of Clint, an actor who had yet gain recognition in his country.</summary>
	<body>After finishing the filming of death had priced Clint Eastwood remained a while in Rome to participate in the witches, an Italian film divided into chapters which would in turn directed by different directors. Eastwood worked under the orders of Vittorio De Sica portraying a normal and somewhat boring husband who neglects his wife after many years of marriage. After finishing the job, he returned to the United States, where you would find that it was now the main protagonist of the television series Rawhide. His partner had been dismissed. Eastwood was now the protagonist. Meanwhile his two films with director Sergio Leone were still not released. In his country, Eastwood was just a familiar face that appeared on television once a week.Meanwhile, in Italy, several North American producers had stalked Leone to lead a new western. Offering a great budget, bigger than I could ever imagine, the director and Italian producers soon accept the offer. Interested in demystifying the difference between good and evil and the topics linked to the western, the director wanted to shoot a story about three Grifters, three gunmen who are not what they seem, and that depending on the circumstances can be generous or cruel. The director wanted a mixture between the picaresque tradition and the drama of a bloody civil war. That would be the starting point for developing the new script. The story would be titled "The magnificent two harapientos", title which was changed before you start shooting.The film deemed the futility and cruelty of wars ("never saw that so many lives malgastaran so vain", says more or less one of the characters) with the picaresque and the low morale of the protagonists of the film. The gunmen, capable of murdering, cheating and stealing, are still well, more human and worthy than wars and those causing them. In the tradition of Hollywood the American civil war, when he had adapted for the big screen, had always to do with moral values and the construction of a new nation. Heroism and sacrifice. However, Leone was ready to do anything heroic portrait, where the war of Fund that takes place in the film is reduced to the dead and dust. Orson Welles told Sergio that making a film about the civil war was "crazy". Except for what the wind, no film dealing with the subject had triumphed at the North American box office.As regards the distribution, the role of the "good" was reserved for Clint Eastwood. However, this time, Eastwood was not so eager to accept. While the previous films had been premiered in North America and having become the protagonist of the series, Rawhide, the actor feared that the that you get to associate with B-movies Italian could damage the future of his career. On the other hand, he also expressed his doubts about its role, that it seemed that the real hero was Tuco, "the ugly". The own Leone had to travel to United States and convince Eastwood that he accepted the role. But both ended up discussing what the wife of Leone described as "a clash of male egos". Eastwood agreed to sign, but it assured of bagging a high sum for his involvement in the film.For the role of "the bad", Leone had hesitated to work with Lee Van Cleef again. He tried to sign Charles Bronson once more, and this time it had accepted, but contractual incompatibilities made it impossible to make it available. Leone, entrusted the role of judgment to the good of Lee.Por last, for portraying Tuco Benedicto Pacific Juan Maria Ramirez, I had thought originally in Gian Maria Volontè, but Leone wanted an actor with more comic vis. The chosen was Eli Wallach, prestigious Actor's Studio from actor and which had already been a bandit in the magnificent seven. Anyway, Leone chose him for his role in "The railways", episode in the conquest of the West, and where Wallach left Leone impressed by his capacity for mimicry. Wallach, who then felt pigeonholed as the eternal Latin Bandit, at the same time was difficult to mold his theatrical style to the technicality of Hollywood. Eli wanted to return to the film, but again came a director, this time Italian with an Italian paper. Leone begged to before agreeing to see any of his films. That was all what was enough to Eli Wallach to accept work in the good, the bad and ugly evil.Wallach and Leone congeniaron quickly, and during his stay in Rome the script underwent important changes. Director and actor it is spent in great playing and contrasting ideas for the character of Tuco. The bandit would be an atheist but at the same time superstitious who not to extensive, rather than a belt has shoulder straps and belt and takes the pistol hanging from a rope.As it had feared Eastwood, Tuco became the central character of the film. The best quotes and scenes had to do with the mischievous Bandit. The enormous talent of Wallach managed to move from the Centre of attention to eternal "the man without a name" Eastwood. So the tensions between it and Leone continued during filming, although Clint not only did not show any antipathy to Wallach, but helped him advising him and giving him ideas for his character. Anyway, the long filming of the good, the ugly and the marked the swan song for the collaboration between Eastwood and Leone. The progressive diminution of the role of the Californian ("if I continue this in the next film will be accompanied by all the American Cavalry") and the friction between the actor and director marked the end of a wonderful symbiosis that gave the big three film western, to each of which better. Eastwood and Leone grew to see up, shortly before the death of the Italian left to eat at a restaurant in Rome. Despite that sour final Eastwood always had good words for Leone, with never denied what they had learned during the European shooting: the economy of means, a different way of working, freer than in the old Hollywood, and a way of portraying the raw violence and openly. He was also with Leone developed the archetype of his hard and silent characters, and it was also shooting those western where he met the interesting thing might be the dual characters. As he had done practically since the beginning of his career, Eastwood did study work and ways of working of Leone. The bug of the address would reconcomiendo the actor a few years more.The good, the bad and ugly evil premiered on Italy in late 1966 and constituted a new success, although it grossed less that the death had a price. Meanwhile, solved the legal problems with Akira Kurosawa, producer Alberto Grimaldi, who had finally made with the rights of the three films of Leone, sold to United Artists. In this way the three films were marketed in the United States as a trilogy, and for advertising purposes was when coined the phrase that would give immortality to the Eastwood character: "the man with no name". Critique vapuleó to the movies, but the public responded in an enthusiastic manner. Thereafter the American western never again be the same. As it was not the career of Clint Eastwood, an actor of by then 36 years who still had failed to obtain recognition in his country for his work on the big screen.</body>
</review>
