<review author="Moebius" title="Por un puñado de dólares" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After a resounding success in Italy the film succeeded throughout Europe. A lawsuit by Kurosawa stalled its release in North America. Clint Eastwood returned to the sets of Rawhide without knowing it for much of the world was already a star of Westerns.</summary>
	<body>In 1964 Clint Eastwood co-starred with Eric Fleming series Rawhide, which chronicled the adventures of two cowboys and their transport of cattle from one place to another. For years had tried good luck in the film, looking for that great role given to know. He had worked on films of the talking Mule Francis, in serie B as Tarantula films or inexpensive westerns as Ambush at Cimarron Pass, classified by the actor himself as "the worst of his career". Although Rawhide gave him enough money to keep together with his wife, artistically the inexperienced and impulsive Rowdy Yates role not him yielded nothing. Eastwood took notice how to do different managers who were going through it, although obviously the moment that it became after the camera still was far in the shooting of the series. By the time I had to search for the way out of the vicious circle of television. Surely he would have never imagined that that opportunity was waiting on the other side of the Atlantic, in old Europe, where a renewed Westerns and orondo Italian director were about to change life.The birth of the subgenre known as spaghetti western occurred before that director Sergio Leone was even raised to shoot a film of this genre. For when the Italian decided to shoot a story set in the old American West, around 25 western films had been shot in Italy by directors and Italian teams (including the father of the own Leone, Vincenzo). But the work of Leone marked a turning point: even with few resources, the director managed to compose a magnificent piece that site of the majority of films above, not only by having higher quality, but by an enjoy a treatment different, very personal, close to the "westerns" mature as Solo at the danger.Since the 1950s the co-productions between Italy, Spain and Germany were very frequent. The main reason for such collaboration was to reduce costs and ease to take economic risks of any film that was carried out. One method was renewed when Samuel Bronston landed in Spain to a series of diverse gender megaproducciones. Bronston brought money and American equipment, built studios, sets, and, even more important, the Hollywood method carried Spain. A whole series of technicians and filmmakers were formed under the tutelage of Bronston. And this was a hugely important breeding ground for the step that would give Leone in his career. Spain was the perfect place to shoot a western: had the landscapes, the media and technicians. And entire villages dedicated to the film industry. At the beginning of the 1960s the scenery was prepared. Only needed a story.The western, as myth, had been abandoned by Americans themselves. The genre remained, but in 1963 it represented 9 per cent of the total number of productions in Hollywood. Each time was less profitable, and the big studios producers preferred other types of stories. The creators of the invention had left him to his fate. The witness should be picked up by others. Artists and filmmakers from other countries, who had grown up watching westerns in film, and who had drunk of the sources of John Ford and the rest of major Hollywood directors. And the history that should serve as inspiration for the start of the trilogy of the dollar came from the most unexpected place: the far East.Director of Yojimbo (mercenary), Akira Kurosawa Japanese, acknowledged the influence that the western had in shooting the film. Among other factors and reasons, Kurosawa appropriated the imagery of the far west of the Hollywood of the cowboys and the lone heroes myth, and sifted it to adapt it to the conscious and the history of the Japan. He adapted a detective novel (Red Harvest by Dashiell Hammett), her moved to the medieval Japan and her shot in the western manner, as if it words– deep roots with Samurai instead of with gunmen.Sergio Leone found in the mercenary history that you were looking for. While he saw in the film he decided to adapt the story and turn it into a western. Thus closed the circle: a history of gangsters becomes a story of Samurai to end up being a story of gunmen in the far West. The myth was revisionado over and over again. Leone said always to be "translated" into Italian, rather than simply copy the Kurosawa film. However, after the premiere, Kurosawa (quite rightly) sued Leone by have copied his film without acquiring any right or have mediated some conversation. The courts gave him the reason, and Kurosawa and his partners saw a 15% of the total of the collection of the film and the exclusive rights of the film in Taiwan, Japan and Corea.El main character of the film, the stranger, the man with no name, it should be played by an American. Leone had in mind Henry Fonda as his outsider: expected a surprise effect that would cause sensation. However, the agent of Fonda is not even deigned teach the script that Leone had sent him. Leone sought then to James Coburn, but was too expensive. Later, Charles Bronson turned down the role, stating that the script was "simply the worst thing I have ever read". However, later said: "what then I did not understand is that the script was that mattered." "It was the way in which he was set to direct what would be the difference". Leone finally found their man in one a young promise "empty eyes" appeared that it could fit into the role. His name was Clint Eastwood. Apparently, Leone seemed not very convinced, but the possibility of the cache of the actor to rise in the coming months convinced the producers that Eastwood should be the man. Tonino Valerii, Assistant director of Leone, said: "Not remember Leone said never really 'yes' to Clint Eastwood". Instead, Eastwood, interested in the script, if accepted the offer of Leone. It also contributed the desire for his wife to spend a holiday in Spain and Italia.Eastwood is not only devoted to portraying the stranger, also helped to design it. He bought the black pants in a shop of Hollywood Boulevard. The hat did in Santa Monica, and apparently his famous poncho acquired it in Spain. Also his idea was the constantly having a cigar in his mouth. Also said its characteristic look and those entornados eyes were product of the Sun and the lights of high voltage is used for lighting.Leone, who had already worked on Spain earlier at the beginning of his career, made his Westerns Almeria (and also the mountains of Madrid and Burgos). Many of the sites for his scenes already knew of his previous visits. Others arose by chance while traveling, and others emerged after the search for locations. But the truth is that the dollar trilogy and Spain were inextricably linked.The last characteristic element of the trilogy in discord was the music. Ennio Morricone, who had been a classmate of Leone, was not the first choice of director. Sergio Leone was not impressed by the earlier work of Morricone and met the composer after being pressured by the producers. However, he decided to give it a try.Under the direction of Italian Eastwood began developing thus interpret that it has become their particular label: scantiness of words, hissing voice, tone off, a glacial look which over the years has become really expressive and a sly smile became a rogue that although he killed in the back we fell sympathetic to his ruthless gunslinger. With Leone he also learned that a low budget may be enough to make a great movie, and there was another film out of Hollywood where you could kill someone on the same plane and where a director could really make his movie.Once the Eastwood filming he returned to North America believing that he had rolled an Italian western third of which he would not hear talk and who had reported an amount of acceptable money and holidays in Europe for his wife. Meanwhile, in Italy, changed the name of Il Magnifico Straniero to the final for a fistful of dollars, while the actor was warned of this (so that when the first reviews were published in the United States believed that this was another film). After a resounding success in Italy the film succeeded throughout Europe. A lawsuit by Kurosawa stalled its release in North America. Clint Eastwood returned to the sets of Rawhide without knowing it for much of the world was already a star of Westerns.</body>
</review>
