<review author="Moebius" title="La muerte tenía un precio" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film premiered in large rooms, was expected as a new event, and was a resounding success. It tripled in Italy the most box office film figures.</summary>
	<body>After the resounding success of for a fistful of dollars, everyone expected a sequel. Pressures on Leone to shoot a new western were becoming greater, although he tried to carry out a different project. As he himself said, they seemed to challenge him, and nobody seemed confident that he could shoot something other than a western. However, others who knew him claim that their refusal to shoot a sequel due to its eternal fear of failure, and that, although in reality yes willing to shoot another film of the same genre, he feared greatly that this time the film does not work. Finally, which apparently led to the sequel was the contract that Leone had signed to be able to move forward with a fistful of dollars. According to this contract, Leone was still filming another film for the same company. However, Leone found a lawyer, Alberto Grimaldi, which offered better conditions for shooting his film. Although it had no history, the director already had a title, Per a few piú dollars, apparently a kind of joke relating to producers who worked on by a fistful of dollars.Meanwhile, Clint Eastwood was still working on the TV series Rawhide, and a fistful of dollars still had not reached the North American cinemas. While Sergio Leone started again several contacts to tell with some of their favorite actors (Henry Fonda, Lee Marvin) to Eastwood was offered $50,000 to that is enfudara of new guns and he wore his old poncho and interpreted to the main Bounty Hunter, known in some versions as Manco. Eastwood agreed. The villain would be played by Gian Maria Volontè, who already had participated in the previous film. After much searching the actor for the second Bounty Hunter, Colonel Mortimer, Leone found in an old photo of a film magazine to its Mortimer. According to Leone, the man in the picture seemed "a Barber of South Italy", but also had "Hawk nose and the eyes of Van Gogh". The name of the actor was Lee Van Cleef.La movie, I had more budget, was also more complex in its approach, with small flashbacks and various nuances, but still had all the ingredients for a fistful of dollars, although in more quantity: the irony of Eastwood, the close-up of eyes, characteristic music of Ennio Morricone, and a rather unusual principle: a plane of a Valley, and off-screen hear different sounds: someone whistling, a cigar that glows, a rifle loaded and shot that knocks down a rider that passes. The death had a price began in impressive form, and featured her first character, the Manco, without even appear on screen: just a whistle and smoking a cigarette so that we know who it is. In the next scene, a Bible will give way to the second Bounty Hunter, Colonel Mortimer.La chemical between Eastwood and Van Cleef it proved effective, and they were memorable both endured their revolvers giving kicking and fighting as two children on the street. Eastwood repeated in its role as the gunman with a little talkative and quick hand three-day beard, although on this occasion was perhaps less cynical, but keep its irony and his primary motivation remains money. The smile of Eastwood rogue had in death had priced its big debut. Also said that the leisurely manner of speaking of Eastwood began to appear in this film, during the sessions of dubbing in Rome. It has pointed out that it was inspired by his Italian dubber, Enrico Maria Salerno. Other sources, such as the former actor, Sondra Locke, claim that it is based on the way of talking about Marilyn Monroe.El film premiered in large rooms, was expected as a new event, and was a resounding success. It tripled in Italy figures of the most box office film, and while the film was sold to abroad, some North American producers who had come to meet with screenwriter Luciano Vincenzone in situ checked the enthusiastic reaction of the public to the film. There and then began to take shape the film that completed the "dollar trilogy". Meanwhile, taking advantage of his stay in Rome, Eastwood took to participate in a film coral before returning to the United States and return to the shooting of Rawhide.</body>
</review>
