<review author="Moebius" title="Laura" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"Laura" meant stardom for several names now immortal on celluloid, and is a title to highlight in this splendid film noir genre.</summary>
	<body>Rouben Mamoulian had been removed from the project. Any director enough Prestige was available. He was the producer, a Viennese of nearly forty years, who took over the direction of the film. His experience was not too abundant: a few minor films had alternated with works on Broadway since he emigrated from Austria, fleeing the nazi madness. His name was Otto Preminger, and Laura was intended to be the movie that launched him to stardom, as it did with the two protagonists of the film, Gene Tierney and Dana Andrews.Un ironic and hard detective of police, McPherson, was responsible for investigating the murder of a famed publicist, Laura Hunt. In his wheel of interrogation of suspects attends the House of Waldo Lydecker, a brilliant and hedonistic radio columnist who is has characterized by a great interest in the black Chronicle. Through his statement we UNGASS in the time to learn about the history of Laura and the events leading up to his death.Long ago a young Laura tries to Lydecker to be advertising for a pen. Bothered during their lunch by the impetuous young writer her dispatches in a bad way. However, he was impressed by the personality of the beautiful girl. Later he will attend her work to apologize and accept the offer of the publicist. It will be the beginning of a long friendship that Lydecker (much older than her) will become a protective and fatherly figure, the feelings of Lydecker to Laura will be increasingly confused.At a party Laura meets Shelby Carpenter, a ruined and vividor landowner is supported under the protection of the Mrs Ann Treadwell, a woman of good position which is in love with Carpenter. However, after meeting Laura, Carpenter attempts to seduce without much success at first, until that past time will be instructing to make wedding plans. Lydecker, who despises Carpenter, try by all means prevent the wedding, coming to reveal Laura a relationship that keeps the Gigolo with a young model who works in the same agency of Miss Hunt. Doubting whether or not to break the commitment, Laura retreats to his home. Shortly thereafter, a Friday, Laura calls Lydecker cancelling an appointment for dinner that had that same night. Some hours later discovered his body.After all this detective plot hides a great secret, a hidden fact that will turn the plot in the most unexpected moment. Detective McPherson will be discovering a complicated tangle of romantic relationships, feelings, jealousy and emotional games in which is will be complicating is a total way, to the point that will be obsessed with the portrait of the deceased Laura, discovering that the magnetism of this woman is so powerful that persists even after his death. With such convoluted tangle of interests and half-truths as plot printed in a quick script and brilliant lines of dialogue, and a flawless direction, Laura is its own right one of the great titles of the film noir, containing traditions of the genre (starting with the work of Agatha Christie) and elements of previous tapes such as the Maltese Falcon and is linked to later as the intricate Hitchcock.El Vertigo films script (although seen today maybe not what) (so much) stands out by its vibrant fabric in the regular line of the whodunnit and that kind of phrases ("do not use stylus, I use a goose feather dipped in poison") that turn the classic film noir into a really delicious genus. On the other hand, Otto Preminger builds the facts in a clear and concise way, without beating about the Bush, a style that however kept being usual at the time. Aided by a splendid picture, Preminger surrounds the tape of an oneiric halo, especially in certain shots of Gene Tierney, whose beauty, on the other hand, is portrayed in sublime form Laura.As I have already said, the film elevated Tierney and Andrews to the category of big stars. Laura Hunt is one of the definitive roles of the Tierney, (I never tire of saying it) wonderful creature that makes me think that God exists. Laura his stage charisma and its port are captured on the screen as rarely managed to do so; In addition, the interpretation of the actress reaches Captivate as captive to the scathing Lydecker. For its part, Dana Andrews (for many years thought that it would be a woman!) also stands out as the typical gambling and foul-mouthed detective of the genre; Although it cannot be compared with Detective portraits of the great Bogart, the good of Andrews knew to live up to the occasion and give his character a hook good enough to collect role in certain key scenes. Vincent Price, who plays the womanizer Carpenter, comes out unscathed with his usual charisma; While his character is too ungrateful to shine with their own light, its mere presence is enough to remind us of the great actor who was this man. Mrs Treadwell, the admirer of Carpenter, has the face of Judith Anderson, the unforgettable Lady Rebecca keys. Impossible overcome or further match a role as well, but his unflappable face perfectly adapts to his role in the film.A separate chapter deserves Clifton Webb, an actor imposed by Preminger for greater tantrum of the all-powerful Darryl f. Zanuck, who the homosexuality of the aristocratic Webb should remove you the dream. Luckily for the film, Zanuck and the own Webb, returning to the cinema after an exile that dated back to the beginning of talkies, Preminger rescued you that he interpreted the bifid dandy Lydecker. Clifton Webb is simply immeasurable, and fits into the role as elegantly as they do fit suits. Theirs are the best quotes of the film, as well as most of the scenes in which it participates. A ten for him.Another element of the film that has remained in memory is the main theme of the same, also titled "Laura" and composed by David Raksin. Although personally to me tells me much, can not deny is a beautiful composition, and many insurance moviegoers who have among their favorite.Laura meant stardom for several names now immortal on celluloid, and is a title to highlight in this splendid film noir genre.</body>
</review>
