<review author="Alex Baldoví" title="Monstruoso" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not disappointed in anything: is what you expect, neither more nor less. The expected forward the film going to pass a very good hour and a half in the armchair of the film. That Yes, he does not seek the "why" of things. Look at her and enjoy.</summary>
	<body>I come from the press pass and I must say that the movie I loved it. I was eager to see her, with high expectations and I was not disappointed in anything: is what you expect, neither more nor less. What is recorded in hand camera looks good, and is the elemental of the movie to see the event from the point of view they want us to give. It is a mixture of "The project of the Witch of Blair" and "REC" but surpassing them in far. The theme of the video tape is generally very well treated, is date, recorded under "film", and details that give credibility to the subject (as these seconds of video that shows what is recorded under the current when you stop recording, rebobinas and see what you have grabado.no know if I can explain xD). The film keeps you tension all the time (not counting the first 20 minutes in which you presented the characters), with the point of view of the camera, not seeing exactly what is happening and to listen to those sounds that leave you ice cream, and ice cream that leave the protagonists. Players that make it very well, the truth. Come see the dubbed Spanish copy and I must say that dubbing is not as bad as they make us believe in the trailers. Vale there is a couple of characters and scenes in which dubbing is not right, but ultimately is what have worked hard. And recognise one thing: would see this kind of movies in g.w. us cost much recognize the characters, that on many occasions they are not on screen. And if you have the voice in Spanish and put them a face, already you recognize them when you hear them. So to the final grateful to see it dubbed, and check that the dubbing is not as bad as we thought it was. Or at least I thank you. Another thing of sound: soundtrack. There. And what makes me more strange is that not is missing, for nothing. Mira music is a very important factor to create tension in a movie, but in this we can see how it creates the same tension but without music, using other techniques. The monster? The truth is that it is OK, after so many rumors and so many guesses, the monster suits, and already we can say, is clear. And same thing happens with the small bugs. Come on, that the film is very well. There are only a couple of details that I liked, and that at least my I have dislocated. And I already notice: care, SPOILERS! Do not expect to find "by Fishbone", that the film is only the point of view of the characters, nothing more. And with that the film, for my taste, earn a lot. I say that not tells us the origin of the monster, who not tells us that it happens to the monster at the end, than anything else, not tells us almost nothing. And why? Because, again, it is the point of view of a group of people that have been found in the middle of everything, and I, as a geek of video cameras, and be always recording birthdays, meetings, and others, have to say that I love. I love it. I love that this is the case and left as is. END SPOILERS! If you expect her so much like me, the movie will not disappoint and you pasaréis a good hour and a half in the armchair.</body>
</review>
