<review author="Caruco" title="Hula Girls" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Topical to say enough is enough.</summary>
	<body>Based on a true story is a subgenre itself, and what happens in this tells Japanese production, between the sympathetic drama and comedy that wants to play the chord of the spectator, the initiative in a mining town, Iwaki, than in 1965, and the crisis of the coal by the substitution of the oil, he decided to recycle much of their jobs by creating a Hawaiian theme park as a tourist attraction.An unusual idea for the time needed, as a first step, the collaboration of the girls of the place to learn to dance the traditional and tourist, dance Hawaiian hula. A few young people who begin their particular Full monty clad these exotic and daring costumes even showing the navel!.The work also will become a personal struggle for trying to leave the mediocre fate that awaits them, and logically a way to overcome if same as people. Among other battles, they must deal with conservative and traditional attitudes especially between fathers and daughters, that ocasionarán not few discussions, even physical attacks. But against all adversity, and the logical initial setbacks of the emerging dancers, nothing will stop the progress.Young Japanese director, of Korean origin, Lee Sang-il, has in its hands a material with abundant ingredients to please easily to the public; and in fact, Japan has been an overwhelming success. Hula girls has in addition a clear will to try to conquer the international market. Seems both in its treatment and staging more a Western film that not Asian. If cambiarámos their interpreters for other Europeans or Americans, we left without any distinctive trait of their nationality.And isn't that one wait to find the spirit of Ozu in its history or images, but not expect check copy the manula topical situations for the occasion or as falls repeatedly into the more helpings, sweetened and predictable. A collection of topics, both in the characters and situations, or unnecessarily lengthening the scenes supposedly more melodramatic and important. The only thing remarkable perhaps dance sticks the Professor Hirayama (Yasuko Matsuyuki, almost a kind of Professor Keating, in exit of the club of dead poets, female version), before its first pupils who contemplate it, through a window, with admiration.</body>
</review>
