<review author="Alex Baldoví" title="Sweeney Todd" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tim Burton has done again it. Create a musical based on his style, dark, dismal and bizarre was a difíficl task, but the director has done in a masterful way. One of the best Tim Burton film.</summary>
	<body>I was delighted! Mira that my duo Tim Burton and Johnny Depp not makes me laugh but I have to say that the movie is very well! The director manages to mix of masterly his dismal, dark and Gothic style in a great musical. And say great music because the film are almost 2 hours, hours to do not become long. Is possible that by the middle of the movie the pace down a little, but then quickly recovers. What he said. A music pure and hard, come on, think that 90-95% of the film is sung. After a magnificent sequence of the principle, to 3 or 4 minutes can already see people to sing. A magnificent sequence of the principle accompanied by a great soundtrack. In general the entire film has good pieces of music, and the leitmotiv of Sweeney Todd mola! The actors are great. Who would say that Johnny Depp sing well, eh? Jejej. But the role he goes like ring finger, and is perfect in the world Tim Burton. Helena Bonham Carter also makes it very well, they are a good Duo. Songs I have to say that it hooks, or at the very least, yesterday I went out of the room singing a par.xD but well, that if something stands out the film is by its (as is likely) design of production and its art direction, as always, are very well taken and perfectly knowing what you want to show. The film with muted tones already seeks the grim and gloomy looks. Only stresses in this context of darkness (quite gores) splashes blood there for more than half of the film. Brutal, too much blood even for Tim Burton! Lol is that the history hooks. The truth is that it is ingenious, and as he could not miss has a couple of touches of humor are welcome. Come on, I was delighted. It would not with high expectations and at the end sales of the film with a good flavor of mouth and watching one of the best films of Tim Burton, his style is 100%. By the way, almost so I left. What end. Okay there are perhaps a few predictable things that can be guessed, but the flat end. The flat end is the very best I've seen in a long time. And I'm not saying more. All to see it because you like it. Unless odiéis musicals...</body>
</review>
