<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="Odio en las aulas" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pretty mediocre film, is supposed social complaint, also supposed, was created to contribute to peace in the institutes where there was mixture of races and existián problems for such reason.</summary>
	<body>"A Professor of black literature must return to the village where he grew up to take charge of the classrooms of a conflictive Institute where always there has been only student/ACE of their same race." However, now, for reasons of transfers and records, a group of alumo of white must study there. This, of course, thought will create various conflicts, requiring, for not to be more than someone with experience and has worked with all kinds of students."Despite his efforts, every day will be muddling atmosphere, with eventually physical and verbal disputes".Pretty mediocre film, is supposed social complaint, also supposed, was created to contribute to peace in the institutes where there was mixture of races and existián problems for such reason.Therefore, after seeing her, firmly believe that failed its purposes, it is a soft movie, something infuriating in his inanity, almost nothing deep and that, even if it is full (I think) of good feelings, the truth is only seeking economic success, I do not know if it failed.Everything is full of clichés, silly supposedly intelligent dialogues, with irregular performances (well Jeff Bridges in one of her first major roles) and a use of music, which is the best of the tape.The rest is something bobalicón how such products be tomárselso seriously and not stay in Midlands which only impoverish the final set, as it is the case. A final outcome poor, moderately entertaining, rather tedious and with good photography, that Yes.But da creeps see the "deep" pedagogical value of the film, especially in the episode of the boy "of color" who, despite the fact that it is already in the last year of the Institute, just read. The teacher, knowing that the guy likes the magazines "green" gift you with reading a good novel with accent sexual and erotic. The boy, to what it reads (rather squeal) takes interest and do not know me, but almost one or two days at most, read faster and understand everything. We must implement this subtle method in all schools in the whole world.And it is also nice that tells them at one point to his friends the black head of the AUL: "-I, as a black child had white friends." "Now that I'm"of color", already I have none".Finally, intelligence in the script.</body>
</review>
