<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Adiós pequeña, adiós" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Much of the footage remains integer. Acceptable Opera prima for Ben Affleck, but no point of comparison with the play master Mystic River genius Eastwood. The worst, a simpleton Casey Affleck.</summary>
	<body>Well know all the aforementioned Director Ben Affleck, but rather (and unfortunately) in his facet as actor. Anyone surprised by the non-existent acting ability of Ben Affleck (is also true that the quality of the scripts which decided to accept dismal, except "The unforgettable Hill Hunting", which occupied the role of co-writer along with his tireless friend Matt Damon). But the truth is that me I brought a pleasant surprise in terms of the work as director Affleck. Without an exceptional work of technical invoice, the film stays more or less throughout much of its duration.Affleck, also exercises here as co-writer along with Aaron Stockard adapting a novel by Dennis Lehane. Although the raw material from which leave is undeniably fantastic (let us not forget that it is the same author of the novel in which this based "Mystic River"), the final result is tottering. Will not go into comparisons (forbid Sr.Affleck), but I think the narrative pulse print Clint Eastwood has nothing to do with the Affleck.En first, we occupy about 45 minutes of leisurely pace at which adormecen the Viewer to coma. At times you think if not you've teleported of cinema to the armchair of your House and you can see Antena3 or Telecinco at 16: 00, as the first part of the film is more reminiscent a telefilm that chains to a (presumed) film in conditions. Suddenly, the pace of the film changed completely, the story gives a turn of 180 degrees and you say: but that is happening now? Where do we want to bring Mr Affleck? Then to the garden, to the very same orchard.In the final stretch, the film starts to get a bit of pace (but without exaggeration), to give us a resolution too explicit. Affleck should think that the spectator is half stupid or that he had written the script of "Memento" because but I do not understand his decision to put past images while describes the final explanation.As regards the protagonists, I do not have more than positive notes for Ed Harris (impeccable as always) and did cameo? Morgan Freeman (3 few scenes). When they appear on screen does not need anything else, they alone fill content the scene.Casey Affleck (the hermanísimo of the director and protagonist) is limited to go top to bottom, to make grimaces of pimp and bacillary tall blacks while they point a gun to the head. I can hardly believe me the role of his character. A detectivillo private three to the fourth going 'smug' and with that face of pamphilus, without no gesture without any emotion. It has the same interpretative ability a melon (or Sandra Bullock), just that the melon is the brother of the director. Michelle Monaghan is just right. You don't have the papelón of his life, but nor it it tries too hard in their scenes. Anyway, it just being a little wasteful.Technically speaking, acceptable although most normalito mounting. Decent to be Ben Affleck, and his first feature film. That put a final means to half of this movie picked up with tweezers. The picture if that is more accomplished. Dirty environments in Boston, street ghettos with a lower-middle class society are perfectly portrayed through the camera. The band sound, simply correct. It starts great at the start of the film with the voice-over of the protagonist, but gradually he loses bellows as it progresses the film. Finally, in the latter part of the screening there is the central axis of the film. The backbone of the film joins in the morality of the character and the decisions of their acts. Good and evil, yin and yang, right and wrong. Affleck, invites us to empathize completely with the protagonist, to ask that would do us in their situation, to choose between the rational and the emotional. Moral values become the protagonists in the final minutes of the film, loading of tension thanks to its approach. And it is here when the film gets what he proposes. It explores between the borders of good and evil and manages to succeed in the attempt (luckily).</body>
</review>
