<review author="Bruji" title="Juno" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A new Cinderella called dance of the Oscars. Their weapons to conquer: the performance of Ellen Page and revision of the dramatic comedies of good intentions.</summary>
	<body>The fall of the Flashbacks and the voices in Off seems be that the director and screenwriter of "Thank you for smoking" does not want to miss the newest techniques of contemporary cinema. It sometimes feels that many of the filmmakers of new batch, even those who have raised between cameras like him, they forget (if you ever knew) what emerged and how to use the aforementioned inventions. In the case before us, the first-, fortunately, relampagueantes falshbacks - are extremely repetitive, with a dangerous approach to the graphic description of characters that Todd Field tried to in games secrets and which, according to the criterion of who says the film, only worked under the direction of Vincent Minelli in an American in Paris. The latter, voice-overs, are employed by way of notes on blog TV series, as it could not be otherwise knowing the curriculum of the novelist. And is that it is enough with a brief reading of the career of Mrs. Devil (screenwriter of fashion in the USA, discovered by a film producer while his literary hand Internet) to seriously rethink door give the 190 and take seriously that write. Only that, for now, I know not how dealt with a history of social court saying nothing. The winter of the good intentions in Juno, Goddess of motherhood in mythology Roman and, unfortunately, a far cry from the powerful Aphrodite of Woody Allen-, not only no space or place to pay tribute to the above-mentioned not to focus on the problems for teenage pregnancies, either to establish approximations or connections with the situation of infertile marriages, or even to make prevail the fundamental rights of the child, target priority of any civilized society; entering failing in an unreal universe of good intentions that never were so little disputed. A fact clearly reprehensible to modern American criticism, which in other times of similar lack of criterion not him trembled pulse to tar naive to Frank Capra, lawyer of the goodness inherent in the human being at a time in which all the well-intentioned thoughts knew little to alleviate the effects of the great depression. In 2007, date of the present production, the only pending overcome depression comes from the amazement that causes the obsession of American cinema to include independent films of low budget nominations, eliminating unfairly red carpet Kodak Theatre to large scripts as American Gangster, or directors such as Tim Burton or Ridley Scott.La spring of the classic American comedies the new Cinderella called dance of the Oscar will compete with a purported review of the classic comedies in American, losing in an unobtrusive approach that pursues and fails social satire, emulating the fast and sharp dialogues of the screwball comedy, and even with the intention to ridicule the male characters as the Howard Hawks film. The difference is that the creation of special situations aimed at this end, whereas in Juno, the boys are already ridiculous series was necessary in this. Against the independent status of females which move to music coup "indie", able to take responsible decisions even with sixteen, are immature future father adoptive, confined in a box of memories, and the young sportsman who asked if a pregnancy is that which happens to moms and women teachers. Go to...often exemplary. If in a gesture of good will (and considerable effort) the viewer decides to join the optimistic message that motivates the actions of the plot and left drag by the positive spirit of a romantic comedy without more pretensions, it will soon discover that the script, typically American, alternates various comments of undeniable wit, aimed to draw a slight smile, with a multitude of jokes from the worst galas of Billy Crystal. Those and those in which a lively audience (American) applauds enthusiastically, while this albaceteña stays as it was; to put the icing with the malicious tendency of Americans to taunt other cultures. Difficult is that a society which is announced in the newspapers to be parents will understand that China will not give children as if they were ipot. If, on the other hand, someone tries to repair in the central axis of the plot, will fall into the account that what there called "private adoptions", without government regulation?, and possible financial compensation, looks suspiciously like a sale of puppies, unthinkable in the Asian country the mocked. Summer a great interpretation despite listed everything, it is undeniable that the tape get transmit tenderness and warmth from the striking opening credits, enhancing parental relations filiares inherent to Jason Reitman film, and with a priceless lesson (i.e. American films) who is a mother. Remember, the role of Allison Janney and the relationship that is established between the protagonists. But, above all, be sure that Juno attends the birth of a new Star: the witch Ellen Page. Do not lack reason critics already her comparing with Meryl Streep, both are able to save a mediocre film, making credible a bad script.</body>
</review>
