<review author="Carlos Giacomelli Puig" title="Across The universe" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A disappointment that despite having a nearly infallible chips, sinks due to a Director committed to Excel above his film. The orgasm that could have meant stays in a coitus interruptus.</summary>
	<body>Julie Taymor is known for its numerous clashes in directing, either with actors (Anthony Hopkins was getting ready to leave in full shooting), or producers. Considered (by itself) as "the Spielberg Theatre", the truth is that so far his only real success in the stage adaptation of "The Lion King", because his three films, "Titus", "Frida", and which concerns us, have not managed to never count the total satisfaction of critical and/or public.The problem is that the Director seems committed to wanting to navigate upstream, creating Visual experiments that may be more or less achieved (to a server seem enough infumables) but setting completely aside fundamental aspects such as the rhythm and the script of his films. Thus, while end see "Titus" awake became a feat for the Viewer, "Frida" rewrote the life of the legendary artist transforming it into a kind of soap opera of three to the fourth.As well, in "Across the Universe", history repeats itself. On the basis of a romantic comedy as predictable as, why not guarantee (and it is a musical love stories always work), towards the half an hour of footage the thing distorts becoming a revolutionary pamphlet that ignores almost altogether by the relationship of the characters and is immersed in an authentic journey nowhere nearly a hour that is pretentious in its form as simple as vacuum in its Fund.Thus, what had to be a fabulous journey to another time to the beat of mythical songs happens to be a film old-fashioned, predictable and identical to many other (if not for the soundtrack), only returning to resume the flight in its final stretch, where away finally from subversive extravagances to resume what really matters to the publicIt remains the initial love affair.If outside little, at all times gives the impression that "Across the Unievrse" is no more than a succession of video clips, placed one after the other rather abruptly at times, surely fruit of numerous cuts and montages that suffered the original film (which lasted more than two and a half hours!). In this way, the jump from England to America seems brusque, and merges with a presentation of characters made without too much sense, without destroying too much nor understand who they are or where they are. Worth as an example the first appearance of Prudence (sung a wonderful version of "I Wanna Hold Your Hand"), which no one knows anything either before or since (and is the character returns to make Act of presence many minutes later).The visual section runs the same fate as the plot. Starting with a handful decoreografías simplistic but effective, even exciting (versions of "A Little Help from My Friends" and "Come Together" are impressive), everything collapses as soon as the protagonists know Dr. Robert (played by Bono), who embark on a journey amazing and amazed that not is if not the kick-off for the part more jamaipanese, complacent and, unfortunately, longer. It matters little that the version which composed "I am the Walrus" bonus is one of the best of the film, when its Director strives to overload each frame with rocambolescos effects of celluloid, in the purest style Aronofsky. And as the film progresses, the thing gets worse, saving only one other image of merit (soldiers carrying the statue of liberty by the battlefields, bleeding strawberries, or naked bodies singing Darin. until they deform casposos Visual effects giant).Equal to that with the script, the film takes the right path again for the last part, when (finally) terminating the pamphlet and resolves the part sentimental with the best songs of the Beatles (or at least, the most important and tarareables) and a few choreographies again simple, elegant, and emotive.Thus, "Across the Universe" it is a disappointment that despite having a nearly infallible chips (good actors, best actors, romantic history), sinks due to a Director committed to Excel above his film. Orgasm that could have meant a "Moulin Rouge" with songs of the Beatles, becomes a coitus interruptus that pleased only to his half-hour initial and final. Correct, nothing more. (3 stars that would be 2.5 justitas.)</body>
</review>
