<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Desayuno en Plutón" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>These two hours and little film know, let's see, what going you to do, little. I have no doubt that some festival with pretensions of self-promotion quickly given a stardom which does not deserve.</summary>
	<body>Neil Jordan is a competent director left convinced by the cinema of Hollywood (interview with the vampire), but that looks askance (with heart) to a film of roots, which some call copyright, although it would have such great fabric baste I marchamo.In this installment, he rummages in the Ireland that was born and, without shying away from political reflection, explores in the melodrama direct and unambiguous. As Jordan is not Douglas Sirk, the film stays halfway because he abused the clichés and hence in excess to the commonplace, to the dramatic space that the viewer has visited too many times.What we see is a Ireland of catalogue, who ruminates the provincial NAP of tranquillity. What threatens this brittle stillness is the character of Cillian Murphy, born man, but vocationally female, who prefers to be called kitten and it devotes his turbada life to find the mother she knew not. Time will be in this sentimental journey of lost identities for political Ireland (ANGER, found neighbors, street riots) also take his particular universe of topics.Everything is very fast and shines above the narrative set, a precise soundtrack and a sober acting composition which, although sobreactuado, Cillian Murphy, who remember Batman begins or in this monstrosity of abductions in the already outdated aircraft Wes Craven, give packaging a difficult character.Breakfast on Pluto is a melodrama with touches of comedy that we cannot call tragicomedy entirely as humour that presents is dark, sordid, sometimes. It has in music (I insist) an invaluable ally. Punk rock to Haëndel of the local folklore to disco music. Until Bryan Ferry has his perverse slip by more signs.It seems, to the way in which Tarantino modeled his scripts, Jordan would like to the turns of history to drink of the soundtrack of the movie. In fact, Patricia "Kitten" Braden, the character of Murphy, lives for those songs and guide its growth as a person throughout the footage.Came me to the memory the game of tears, better movie than this, signed also by Jordan. Both deal with cross-dressing. Both portray the terrorist violence. Here everything has been in a tone lower, effeminate to the sweet, but tender at times.Liam Neeson as selfless and courageous priest and Stephen Rea (a fixed Jordan) as the little traditional magician embroider, in my opinion, their characters. In short, the gentle reader has a mottled Behaviorism practical ration on the Bulletin Board and also, behold the absolute magic of cinema, a fun bit of film European, burdened by the traces of the American neighbour, so thief, so loved, so our.I have no doubt that some festival with pretensions of self-promotion quickly given a stardom which does not deserve, but nor criticaríamos in excess. There is so much trash and sold with so much complacency that these two hours and little film know, let's see, what going you to do, little. Tonight I will see with skirts and crazy. It has nothing to do with the writing, but I miss Jack Lemmon and Tony Curtis.</body>
</review>
