<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="El Orfanato" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Exceptional, that is the adjective that should give this piece of jewellery, which works perfectly from the beginning of austere and manners, style to a poetical without why not be bleak ending.</summary>
	<body>Very appropriate choice of this film from the debutante at the long Juan Antonio Bayona (of Barcelona's origin) to inaugurate the new edition of the Sitges Festival, a clear statement of principles concerning the quality that promises a pageant, a priori occurs for the best, but the best, in terms of film proposals referred to. And once again, and not get tired of repeating myself, a new hit full in the diana of the tasteful film, again the debut of a Spanish director in the fantasy genre, and again one exceptional film. After attending the screening of a gem like this, one finds answers about the expectation that had created this new film of terror Spanish, so well received in Cannes and with distribution on a large scale in Usa for upcoming dates.History us situated in the skin of Laura (Belén Rueda), a woman of 37 years returns to inhabit the orphanage where he grew up, in this case to convert it, as well as your home, a home for disabled children. After a start where we see that it was adopted by some family sienda girl, Bayonne takes us without further ADO when Laura is living in the old orphanage alongside her husband and their son Simón, which we will shortly discover later that it was also adopted, and that he is ill, which forces him to take his medication every day. Advances the film and quite subtly, we are discovering as Simon speaks to parents of imaginary friends, something which does not pose the slightest concern to parents, considering it more a typical attitude of a lonely child than anything else. But everything changes from the moment in which Laura and Simón visit an ancient cave close to the beach, where the child tells his mother that has met a new invisible friend. This causes various confrontations between mother and child, thing that is twisted completely in the moment in which Simon disappears for months, without knowing their parents which remedy to that situation, but feeling that it isn't as far as may seem.Exceptional, that is the adjective that should give this piece of jewellery, which works perfectly from the beginning of austere and manners, style to a poetical without why not be bleak ending. The story is developed with an impeccable narrative pace, this narrated with a voltage increase, including a couple of scares that cause one adjournment of the armchair as a spring, and a capacity for the description simply impeccable.Bayonne creates a visual style that makes the economy of means a virtue, because always round a sense of hopelessness in the characters on the screen and that is due to put them in those gray and austere, environments where the contrast with large spaces, as this brilliant scene of the beach and la cueva, creates a sensation of constant oppression.It is not intended in this film a visual appearance very ornate or even with a beauty of the images that stands out above the history (which is partially in some other directorial debut of patriotic filmmakers). I.e., the virtue of Bayonne, if we are guided by his first film (already we will see how it evolves in the future), is to penetrate inside of their characters drama and terror, not so much a mise en scene especially bright, but rather a large counter of stories.Many layers has the film, as the special connection established by nature between a mother and her children, although in this case it is taken, and that is so hard seeing on screen display as effectively as in this film, or references to children's stories from the perspective of an adult, as his constant allusions to Peter Panwhere the final is particularly significant. The constant threat of madness pervades the images of the film, where even the end of the film could be much talk about whether we're seeing something real experienced by the characters or is an insane vision, with a suggestive ending that could not rule out in my opinion the second option.About actors, to say that all are especially prominent, with special consideration for Belén Rueda, her role as mother traumatized by the loss of the son, or of own Simon, which gives his child character certain nuances which are not usually watchword of the genus precisely that outboard. They both operate at a strictly physical level acting as in scenes of internal torment, impeccable.Some of the scenes of the film are a capacity of synthesis in if same of the horror genre insultingly bright and frightening, as the scene where a mysterious hooded child, then we will know who it is, is coming slowly to Laura emitting animal sounds that are frightening, shown with a voltage and an ability to shoot scenes of this amazing type in a newcomer. Or one of the best of the film, where almost at the end recalls the game which enjoyed as a child in the orphanage, and what appears on his back puts hairs tip anyone. Simply brilliant.Perhaps the only but that is you could put as bright debut, consists in the own plot of the film, reminiscent of films already treated many times previously and that subtract the virtue of originality (we could remember as recent "The boarding school", although with many worst results of final finish), since known as argument of a threat from the past which manifests itself in the present in a cursed placewhich it always tends to be an isolated House, an orphanage and a hospital, it is present the film consistently (I will not appoint some film based on the novel by Henry James to be already very repetitive).In short, a brilliant film, a demonstration that we are faced with a director with a bright future in the breeding ground to fantasy films, with a special ability in storytelling and a very direct style with no concessions in the form of topics, where despite the "but" mentioned in the previous paragraph looks to offer us one of the best films of terror in a long time.</body>
</review>
