<review author="Jaime Martínez" title="Un funeral de muerte" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Descacharrante tape full of brightness and nothing pretentious. Intelligent and absurd in equal parts, a tape that despite the few characters and places, keep you a smile in the face during his viewing.</summary>
	<body>From the ingenious initial titles that give way to the film, until the last frame, await us 85 minutes (is grateful for the short duration) a kid humor in charge of director Frank Oz, responsible for not too many good things but include In &amp; out and the remake of perfect women thanks to the presence of Nicole Kidman. Intelligent humor and typically English is what follows the tape of Frank Oz. Death at a funeral is a hilarious proposal where his comic base goes increscendo as it progresses the footage. The work is simple: a House, a couple of hours of temporary space, a good handful of actors and a dead. How wonderful of all this, is the extreme ability of the director to obtain resources with so few ingredients and squeeze them to the limit. With these basic premises, Frank Oz gives shape to a tronchante very English comedy where the humour is ever-present. With a virtually non-existent script, the greatness of this film lies in laughter (or laugh) caused in the public. It appears a bit hesitant and not these very safe to where this movie will take you, but within minutes you realize that front have a nice movie, mocking and Disney over not being able, with a few gags and situations of more irreverent and Surrealists. The humor of death at A funeral, as I have already said, increases as we move forward in the plot, and what appeared to be fixed in the next scene just getting worse to unsuspected heights. It is brilliant see how a seemingly easy situation can degenerate so much and even get to touching moment of total gap; excellent pace imposed by the director in carrying out the gags. If I have to throw something on face, is the presence of some escatological jokes as seen in the genre of teen comedy, and so little they give this type of intelligent comedies. I think that it is not necessary to resort to this kind of uncouth humor and helpings, that harms the covers total that remove from the film. In addition, some gags are kilometers and when they are executed lose all sense of grace that they are more predictable. Another negative point would be the creation of some characters lack. It is missing be better drawn and defined, although that is probably more irrelevant in a tape of 85 minutes where the real charm lies in its british humor. The cast of actors who appear in death at A funeral are virtually unknown in Spain. Matthew Macfadyen is the only one that stands out a bit from among others, for his appearance in the film pride &amp; prejudice. Actor Alan Tudyk gives us a hilarious performance with his character, a lawyer drugged with acids by mistake hours before the funeral. Without doubt, the best of all the tape occurs around this character. Simply hilarious. In short, a descojonante and descacharrante film full of brightness and nothing pretentious. Intelligent and absurd in equal parts, a tape that despite the few characters and places, keep you a smile in the face during his viewing. A well done comedy that makes you laugh up her spinal cord. Highly recommended to have a good time and a good bag of popcorn.</body>
</review>
