<review author="elprimerhombre" title="Taxi driver" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Each sequence, stage or level deserves a punto y aparte. The camera uses slow travelling and camera moves that only an author as Scorsese could make.</summary>
	<body>Elprimerhombre and Columbia Pictures presented to Robert de Niro in Taxi Driver, directed by Martin Scorsese. Of the penumbra, as emerged from the darkness, appears between smoke which dissipates the taxi of Travis Bickle (De Niro). If you want to carry them to the Bronx, Brooklyn or Harlem, they only have to climb your taxi. Let yourself be carried away by such as beautiful drawings of New York shot from the same car and relax with great soundtrack of Bernard Herrmann. "All the animals out at night." Whores, macarro, thugs, ladybugs, lesbians, drogatas, junkies. Sick, corrupt. "One day rain of truth and will clean this scum off the streets." (Actual words of the voiceover of Travis Bickle). In principle, to run a film must be knot, development and outcome, i.e., that every time something that impacts the Viewer, to invite him to stay in his seat, always without losing the thread of the story happens. And this movie not only manages this, but goes far beyond. Paul Schrader, the author of the plot, gives us a script subtly structured, with findings to the 10 minutes to half an hour, about the 50 minute and before reaching the final. Each sequence, stage or level deserves a punto y aparte. The camera uses slow travelling and camera moves that only an author as Scorsese could make. He himself appears in the film twice: the first time watching seated to Cybill Shepherd, who is Betsy, the girl that invites Bickle to leave at the beginning of the film, and the second time being a client of Binckle. This role should have done another actor but in the end it was not possible and decided to do it himself. "Solitude I has followed all my life, everywhere." In bars, in cars, on the sidewalks, stores, everywhere. There is no escape. I am the lonely man of God "("God's_Lonely_Man",_es_una_obra_de_Thomas_Wolfe)." During the film, the character of Binckle is going crazy, is changing into something that is scary. Days after having bought a 44 Magnum, a 38 short, a Colt 25 automatic and a Walther 380, she faces in the mirror, as if he retara to someone telling him: "are You talking to me?." You talking to me? "(" do I say to me?...")"("Do I say to me?"). From that scene, people often imitate De Niro gesticulating and saying that, as Javier Bardem in the mouth movie. Paul Schrader made the script in a rather critical moment of his life. He had separated from his wife and had no where to live. He slept in his car or once at home of his ex-girlfriend. I didn't know what to do with his life. Then came up the character of the taxi driver as a metaphor for the loneliness of man. He chose the name of Travis Bickle because it has a point poetic and hard at the same time. "Travis" comes from the English term "travel", as a wandering. And "Bickle" comes from "bicker", which means "discuss". In short, this movie is huge and a unique experience. You're sad or happy, looking at these images you transported to another world, another kind of life. If for me, I could see this film today again, but I will leave to spend time. Sure that I like even more the next time. And, do a favor, see in subtitled original version. Bernard Herrmann, composer, known especially for the music for films by Hitchcock as Vertigo or psychosis, died at the end of the recording of this soundtrack. This film just recalling his figure. A greeting!</body>
</review>
