<review author="elprimerhombre" title="Una noche en la ópera" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although I paint the eyebrows and moustache, although I encorvara dragging the ground floor of a chaqué or jump into the arms of a woman, I could never be like him. I would lack talent and sympathy to be a tender nerve.</summary>
	<body>Elprimerhombre reminded the brothers Marx (Groucho, Chico and Harpo) in A night at the Opera, Sam Wood. Unlike the previous films, this are three brothers, no longer appears Zeppo, the youngest of the Quartet and he had also previously left the Group Gummo, who years later was associated with the same Zeppo agency representatives. After shooting goose soup, Paramount closed the contract to the Marx and MGM, in the hands of Irving Thalberg, considered the producer more ready and in the history of the cinema, opened them the door with the intention that his arguments were more credible for the Viewer. It was thanks to a game of bridge, where one of the opponents of Mr Thalberg was boy, whose gambling served so propose them making some movies, giving them a fixed salary and 15% of the profits. In the script for this movie collaborated several writers, until himself Buster Keaton, who drafted the best moments of Harpo and did the same in A day at the races and the Marx Brothers in the West. At the beginning of the film is priceless presentation of Groucho. Lavishing with intentional praise, Groucho reveals to Margaret Dumont his love towards her: "Do you know why he was with that woman?" Precisely because it reminds me to you. That is why I am now dinner with you. Because you reminds me of you. His eyes. His throat. His lips. Everything in you reminds me of you. Except you. I think that it is abundantly clear. I ahorquen that if I understand! "." The actress Margaret Dumont repeats the same role of millionaire women of goose soup, getting the funny jokes of Groucho. This woman had already spoken with the Marx Brothers in the theatrical versions of four coconuts and the conflict of the Marx. Then came one afternoon in the circus and big store in Goose soup, A night at the Opera, A day at the races. Groucho had much affection, even considered the fourth Marx Brother. The joke of "the Contracting Party of the first part shall be regarded as the Contracting Party of the first part" represents the paradigm of absurd and surreal humor. With barely a role that represents a contract, Groucho and Chico get a memorable, where at the end scene, after cutting clean clauses that are not interested in, only there is a strip of tiny, accepting both the contract without signing it. And what I say about the scene of the cabin, where a small carrier reach match 15 people. Perhaps the best joke of the Marx Brothers. Although the film was the most economically successful of the Marx Brothers, for my taste, what have left you to this film is the story of love so pompous of the protagonist couple, as well as the song "Alone" that sing two lovers before sailing, which also wanted to discard the Marx Brothers themselves. By the way, the subject that interprets boy at the piano, All I do (is dream of you), appeared later in the soundtrack from singin' in the rain. Definitely, I want to highlight the great Groucho, who died on August 19, 1977, three days after the death of Elvis. Although I paint the eyebrows and moustache, although I encorvara dragging the ground floor of a chaqué or jump into the arms of a woman, I could never be like him. I would lack talent and sympathy to be a tender nerve. A greeting! And two boiled eggs!</body>
</review>
