<review author="elprimerhombre" title="4 meses, 3 semanas y 2 días" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is picking up interest while it is advancing the plot, mainly thanks to a few very well achieved ellipsis that make it seem that the story is told in real time.</summary>
	<body>Elprimerhombre went to see 4 months, 3 weeks, 2 days, of Cristian Mungiu, a tough and intelligent film, which addresses the issue of clandestine abortion in Romania in late 1980s. It represents the first installment of the series stories of the golden age, a project of the director, whose objective is to speak of that time without making direct references to communism of Nicolae Ceauşescu, politician, Communist and Romanian dictator who was executed in December 1989, accused of genocide. A shocking fact are objective data that have inspired the film: between 1966 and 1989, i.e., until the end of the Ceausescu dictatorship, more than half a million women died in Romania because of illegal abortions. This film's story focuses on two girls students share room in a residence of a city in Romania. One of them is pregnant and wants to abort. They have everything prepared to perform their duties in a room of a hotel, but things will not go as he had planned. The character of the amiga is essential because the strength of the film lies in it. The director had the luck to find Anamaria Marinca, whose performance is exceptional. After doing theater in Romania, this actress screen debut took place on British television, with "Sex Traffic" production, which provided him a BAFTA Award. Back in Romania, participated in this film which was nominated for the European Film Academy Awards. The director, Cristian Mungiu, before devoting himself to the cinema had been master of English, conducted in 2002, "The West", which won the international award of the filmmakers fortnight in Cannes that same year. But it will be known internationally for this modest production rumano-belga, which won the Golden Palm at the Cannes Festival last year. And perhaps get more movies of their country of origin, that for the first time in 60 years of the festival, a Romanian film wins the famous award. In 1965, a short produced there had already won the Palm. And in a country which only occur in some 15 films per year, it is appreciated to reach our screens films of great caliber as the Mungiu. At the San Sebastian Film Festival it won Grand Prize Fipresci. In the wake of the first fifteen minutes of the start, perhaps a little slow, in which the director fails to catch the Viewer, the greatest achievement of this film is to achieve that interest go picking up while it is advancing the plot, mainly thanks to a few very well achieved ellipsis that make it seem that the story is told in real time. Filmed as a documentary, unaltered, without music (except in the final letters of credit), with the intention of capturing a reality as it is, we find scenes that last about ten minutes where there is a plane fixed, in which the work of the actors is only thing that counts. And, without a doubt, the best are the last twenty minutes, with a forceful level that leaves a mark and an end that invites the Viewer to comment on what happened in the celluloid. A greeting!</body>
</review>
