<review author="Jefe Dreyfus" title="Ratatouille" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Highly recommended, great film animation and direction, but could perhaps ask something else in the plot.</summary>
	<body>Good morning, I am the Chief Dreyfus, today is Friday and return with one of those movies that has been in many lists of the best of the past year: Ratatouille &hellip; started! Symptomatic form of Americans to face the best chef of France: a rat! (rookie) The story focuses on a rat's field who dreams to cook delicious dishes and away from the garbage that eat his family and teammates, but that, by a twist of fate, it will end one wandering through the sewers of Paris until it ends up doing a friend a kitchen Assistant responsible for washing dishes in a restaurant come to lesswith which you decide to join forces to achieve his dream. For a few years now, I have the feeling that films aimed primarily towards children (while bearing hanging the sign of "film for the whole family" makes me something nervous) are too overvalued. This film, in the wake of what I had read before see it, also. Ratatouille is a film that is good, and if you press me even I would say that it is very well, but here to rip vestments and put it nothing more release of the label's film of the year, I think we, as little, out of the line. Pixar continues to do a brutal work in animation, surpassing the Ribbon film to film and this is not an exception, getting great results (especially in the animal field, in the human perhaps I would be still with the Incredibles), but which above all highlights the movie is in the section of the direction which I think is the best that I've seen in animationbecoming the real strength of the tape. On the contrary, the history, not just me conquer, because the somewhat child (if they sell "film for all ages" I can say that the plot is child) and because in the end we are telling the same thing have been telling us during all the movies premiered with the Pixar label (and the vast majority of the Disney): that if there is not to settle if conquering spirit, that if there is to pursue your dreams, that if the importance of the family, that if the triumph of friendship, that if whistles, that if flutes &hellip; and stating that in the end history is very well resolved and you can find very funny gags, but it is that basicallyone, always want more and tells us the movie because we know. In short, Highly recommended, great film animation and direction, but perhaps we could ask something else in the plot (and something else of bad milk) posts to ask and to vary.</body>
</review>
