<review author="Sandra Ríos" title="Ahora o nunca" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If it hadn't been for the presence and genius Morgan Freeman and Jack Nicholson this tape would be easily forgotten.</summary>
	<body>Jack Nicholson was said about this film: "are the things you do in life, which you most sorry, not that you do" and might say then that this is the phrase that contains the deepest sense who can it be now or never as it resulted in Spain or before starting as it did in my country. This American comedy has already made its premiere in the majority of countries and was quite chart in the United States even came to occupy the first place at the box office, something which seems exaggerated to me after seeing a tape. Today to managed to collect a little more $ 80 million with his low-budget of around 45 million.There is an undeniable magic tape despite the simplicity of its history and great modesty of its production. Obviously the main cause of this magic are the two "mega" actors Jack Nicholson and Morgan Freeman and the fact of seeing them reunited for the first time. The second thing is the intention, to some extent successful, generate comedy at the expense of one of the diseases most fatal today and that makes them vulnerable from the youngest of beings to the more old, from the weakest to the more strong, thus turning it into a universal, intimate, story that touches the fibers and that more than one could be identified.The interesting thing about the film is the dialogue underpinning these two monsters of the performance, because the rest details and elements can completely ignore. Dialogues are entertaining, funny and put us to think and reflect on the decisions we take or which fail to take in our lives. The Bucket List, name is original, of those tapes which we comfort the soul, make us dream and manage us to make out the skin to the point almost make us cry. Another of the interesting things about the film is seeing as it maintains throughout its length, between the thin line that separates this plot of the tragic and the comic without really reach exceed some of them, allowing in this way, that of a real and painful topic as it is cancerRemove us some accounts shy and respectful laughs.But there are things that are not also operated in this film as e.g. mounting much of his scenes that are enforced and quite unrealistic, subtracting the importance enough to be considered a good tape with uppercase B. Nor is there a waste of intelligent dialogues, which should not be confused with a waste, that Yes, but genius hand Nicholson to know "how to say" a few dialogues simple so that they sound as such. In fact, this feature is easily palpable because right in the moments that were proposed, they manage to make you laugh, cry or unfortunate viewers.There is not much to really say about this film that we could call as a typical American film which tries to earn some money that is saved by the fact of bringing together the two oscarizados actors, but sins by his exaggerated modesty and lack of caution to take care of many details in their scenes.I wonder: what will have been of this film but had benefited from the participation of these two actors? They noticed the amount of times I mentioned at Freeman and Nicholson in this post? That is not more than the evidence that they are the only really important engine that makes taking forward this film. I confess that the enjoyment in my innermost subjectivity and that his 1: 37 min passed relatively quickly.Before leaving, it is simply pleasant, relaxed tape that can be seen.</body>
</review>
