<review author="Cecil B. Demente" title="Matar o no matar: éste es el problema" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Only to see Vincent Price that elegantly degolla and beheading critics while quote Shakespeare, already worth.</summary>
	<body>Vincent Price reaches unusual interpretation quotas giving life to an actor of third that a complex revenge plot. This delicious drama combines horror, comedy and Shakespearean Theatre in equal parts in a cocktail capable of satisfying everyone, including critics! Tired of receiving critical killer for years, the Shakespearean actor Edward Lionheart (Price) Decides that the time give them with the iron curtain in the faces his critics has come. The plan is simple, kill them using methods inspired by the works of the great master: a chopping style Cimbelina, a stabbing in the manner of Julius Caesar, and the untimely removal of a pound of meat, inspired in the merchant of Venice. That proves, once and for all, that the world really is a stage. The scene of the crime!Talk about this film is to speak of Vincent Price, and Vincent Price is fucking master. Myth and icon of film culture, few players have so much charisma to justify with his mere presence not the existence of a film, but dozens of them, as it is the case. "This man was one of the causes of that serie B lived beyond a glittering era in the 1960s and 1970s and has left behind a unique legacy:"The collapse of the House of Usher"(1960),"The Raven"(1963),"The comedy of terrors"(1964) and"The abominable Dr. Phibes"(1971) to name a few.""Kill or not kill" drink precisely the formula of the latter, only that in "The abominable Dr. Phibes" direction and staging are superb and here, staying half gas. The director Douglas Hickox does justice to a script that had really great Crumb.Even so, the movie is a very recommendable divertimento, with much humour and high doses of bad baba. Price is great in their camaleónica interpretation of the actor been less with homicidal tendencies, giving that spoof tone you need the character. Just to see him, to elegantly degolla and beheading critics while quote Shakespeare, already worth. The phrase: "the critics usually have enemies, Inspector." We say that they are &hellip; part of the craft</body>
</review>
