<review author="Taliesin" title="Monstruoso" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This production of Abrams will not pick up awards at Cannes, but offers a different experience to what we are accustomed and becomes the first "Monster" film in which the monster is not protagonist.</summary>
	<body>Imagine that Godzilla comes to town. After a running gag with a fisherman and destroy some buildings, they enter in scene Matthew Broderick and Jean Reno. Both one and the other know where comes the giant lizard, know what it is and how they can face him. A few blocks from there, while that campa Godzilla by rampant by downtown, there is a group of friends celebrating a party and suddenly they see as the city becomes a chaos. They don't know that there is an animal of fifty-storey walking through Central Park, just do not know what has happened and all have clear is that we must leave the city cagando milks. Cloverfield is about this group of strangers. It is clear that Abrams with Cloverfield bet (I refuse to call it Monstruoso) is risky: a "Monster" film in which the monster isn't important, apparently recorded with camera in hand and total absence of music. I do not think that Lars Von Trier gave the label dogma, but the proposal is innovative and avoids the conventional offer. Share with REC direct false and the immersion of the viewer in the first person action, although it is much more loaded with special effects. However, the effect is the desired and the film is oppressive, mystifying and thrilling moments. It is overwhelming because, as the protagonists, you suffer the continuous changes in the situation and the film becomes a roller coaster, which helps a lot the recording mareante camera in hand. The million-dollar question is: is the monster? Because Yes, although I think there is no an only flat fixed the see "of whole body" (in fact, there are few levels fixed in the film). Abrams makes good the maxim of the monster behind the door and only listen to it is sufficient to convey concern, so or let us see him a bit, although it is by far. Logically, when that is recording the action sees the monster approaching it stays standing to get a close-up, as that would be idiots and we saw in Godzilla. The guioncillo is unimportant, because Cloverfield offers an experience, rather than a story. The plot is only an excuse to not leave New York and to record the action everything how close as possible. Unknown actors are only puppets in the service of the film and are nothing more than bait with concerns, but with not too many. It is assumed that dialogue forward had distracted the viewer's main objective, which is none other that get him in the shoes of one victim. Ultimately, Cloverfield is not film. It is an experience that would perfectly fit into an amusement park and is irreproducible in the Hall of House, lot 5: 1 that you wear. Now that even the most computer illiterate can download a film in a couple of clicks, producers may have to consider extending the use that gives the film circuits and offer experiences that cannot be in the Hall of the consumer. Although I am afraid that the film industry inopia (on par with the music) did not enable assess the impact that movies as Cloverfield have in the market and will return to the formula that never fails: copy, tweak, sell, copy, tweak, sell, &hellip; or if that fails?</body>
</review>
