<review author="Jefe Dreyfus" title="Los 4 Fantásticos y Silver Surfer" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film for children than anything else, that holds for barely an hour to conclude with a very bad ending.</summary>
	<body>Good morning, I am Chief Dreyfus, with one of these releases on dvd are leaving pending or lack of desire, until that one day you're going and you decide. Big mistake. Now: The fantastic four and Silver Surfer (a test of fire) &hellip; started! Because that second part of the fantastic four, which are a few superheroes coming out of the pages of an older comic shit, where a guy is stretched everything you want to another becomes invisible, other lights up flames and fly and the fourth is a Turkey of stone. In this second foray into the big screen (jojojojo typical sounds like this, I'm going to potar) will appear a few weather irregularities on the planet (nothing to do with the tight dress of Jessica Alba at first) and it is that they are caused by Silver Surfer, a silver guy, who flies on a surf board and turns out to be the dog lazarillo de a sort of cosmic entity that comes to lunch is our planet. To all this, the doctor death (guess I appearing for what that the actor should already have signed for several films because in this not paints nothing) also points to the party for a bit more messing. Can our heroes save the planet? There will be third party? And, most importantly, do have possibilities to link to Jessica Alba? Good, good. I am aware that when one begins to see this kind of films already know what faces and must be consistent. And in fact, when I saw the first part, the total and absolute lack of pretensions of the tape got that, in part, the movie even I came to fall sympathetic at times. But now I notice that this was not the case of this second part. And is that here the history gave to much more, with the entry into the galactus fucking scene (damn, that are not talking about just a sister of charity, that here are theme!), but the truth is that they are more than one hour of film fucking the SOW (no, now I was not referring to Jessica Alba) with nonsense and in the end when he had to come really interesting and the pyrotechnicsthe thing is solved in the most simplistic, ridiculous and easy (and incomprehensible) we are posts. Already notice that I am not exaggerating, the final twenty minutes is not that they are bad, is that they are terrible, with a staging of school primary school in village of twenty inhabitants play (these scenarios of Tokyo not slip anywhere) and with a bad is a bluff. And tell me dance by Reed Richards in the nightclub scene? Was someone else tempted in cutting veins? And I think that the writers should think: If this is taken from a comic book, is that it must be for children!, or something of the sort because if it is not not be understand why they insist on getting the plots of the comics, to ignore them or fucking when it comes to the truth (or much less respect them) and do their own adaptation to all kinds of public (for all kinds of audiences of 3 to) (7 years, of course). Oh, and take the time to shout from the rooftops: am up to the eggs of the fucking cameo turn of Stan Lee's balls, which already is being done more than heavy with so much nonsense, hosts! In short: Film for children than anything else, that holds over an hour to harsh penalties to conclude with a very bad ending.</body>
</review>
