<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Dragon Wars" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film about two serpientazas that Chase through history a woman to become Dragon, which the mate. Special effects of Cape tail, explosions, bugs everywhere, impossible battles, etc. do argument? What else does?</summary>
	<body>Director: Hyung-rae ShimDuración: short, and becomes short. Na more than an hour and a half.Release date: March 1, 2008 do you remember a game table for many years ago that was called "The Empire Cobra"? They were three heroes that had to come to the island of cobra, going through each desert, or fire or ice. Then they came for the cobra, and if you looked at killed them. It was quite entertaining, unless you were the cobra silly character as none. That if the figure mantel horrors. What is this nostalgia treinteña attack? Therefore that it come out in this movie, the cobra and his cousin. I promise you.The film is about two large snakes such as the gas pipeline that comes from Algeria they have to sacrifice a girl of 20 years to become a dragon. One is bad and one good. Total, than the girl suffers an accident that nobody suspected in 1500 and item is postponed. But as we all have several lives, 500 years later resurrected the girl (converted into another, come on, who reincarnated) and again begins the dance of snakes. In an advertisement for pharmacies.Few movies lately are these with bug. It seems that it is a risky and brave gamble, given that daring you to remove the bug in frame 2 and that he bears much of the weight of the proceedings it is. The script is not wonderful, but we have two snakes, a deadly army, some flying bugs that Miss fire, some bugs that roam with missile launchers, helicopters, tanks, etc. is space to put all this and also give a profound script? No, and thank you. This is pure entertainment. For which you like, great.In short, film about two serpientazas that Chase through history a woman to become Dragon, which the mate. Special effects of Cape tail, explosions, bugs everywhere, impossible battles, etc. do argument? What else does? More bugs, this is war.Recommended to see one of bugs that don't stop fighting and destroy everything.Besitos.P.D: What wonderful surprise film.Pd2: It has their winks to the Lord of the rings and their battles, Transformers and bring Battlefield Earth, spirited away which equals the Dragon and King Kong for his scene of skyscrapers.</body>
</review>
