<review author="Christian Sandoval" title="La vida de Brian" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"The misadventures of an aspiring Messiah"</summary>
	<body>"The life of Brian" (1979) is the third film in the humorous group English Monty Python, consisting of John Cleese, Eric idle, Terry Gilliam, Terry Jones, Michael Palin and Graham Chapman, who altogether, were commissioned to write the screenplay for the film. The address went to Terry Jones, who together with Terry Gilliam, had directed the previous film of the Pythons "in search of the Grail" (1975). The film was not without controversy because of the combination of comedy with religious themes. Despite this, it is considered as one of the best comedies of all time.In Judea, Brian (Graham Chapman) was born the same day as Jesus in a manger next. From the moment in which the Magi so confuse with the Messiah and after realizing his mistake, take away gifts loaded with it, the life of Brian is a series of misunderstandings and misfortunes. The truth is that he is not more than a unhappy poor, unemployed and that in addition it is constantly abochornado by his mother. Brian lives in an era in which Queen poverty and chaos, with men everywhere who claim to be the true Messiah, willing to follow parishioners to whom be and a myriad of small clandestine groups of Jews who conspire to catch the Romans. Brian will be completed involving in one of these groups and very reluctantly will be proclaimed Messiah then for "in search of the Grail" (1975), Eric idle suggested that the title of his next film should be "Jesus Christ, lust for glory". However, this was one of the many ideas that they arose in its creative meetings and was completed to discarding because the idea of making a mockery of Jesus simply would not work, because it was not a particularly funny character and the truth is that they felt that his speech was not something should taunt. Then it was thought several ideas again, as for example to make a film about Judas Iscariot, a type that was always late. Another idea was to film the life of Brian San, the disciple number thirteen. Finally and after documented reading the Bibla, this led to the idea of making a film about a contemporary type of Jesus, whose history loosely resemble to the life of the real Messiah. However shoot a plot with religious overtones them would not be easy. Once certain people linked to EMI producer responsible for financing the film, read the script, believing that the subject was blasphemous, they persuaded Lord Delfont, head of the EMI who was better to cancel the project. To see the situation in which the Pythons were left to rescue his friend Beatle George Harrison, who along with his friend Denis O´Brien banker, formed the production company Handmade Films, which finally funded the film. In gratitude, Harrison has a small cameo in the film.As it was expected, after premiering the film quickly was treated blasphemous by various groups of Catholics in the United States, while in England an organization called "Festival of light", persuaded several countries so they qualify the film for over 18 years. According to these groups, there was an excess of religious satire in the film and at the same time was the believers as hypocrites and fans. Also thought that during the course of the film, it is understood in a subtle way as many of the miracles performed by Jesus were nothing more than bizarre accidents that people interpreted as something else.Far the scene that more controversy caused was the final scene, showing the crucifixion of Brian. Christians criticized the fact that the film mofara of this landmark where supposed that Christ suffered and forgive the sinners as opposed to what happens in the film that instead, all those condemned to crucifixion are singing the song "Always look on the bright side of life" that had humorous dyes. Director Terry Jones said in an interview in which he asked him about this scene: "any religion that makes a form of torture an icon to that then they worship makes me feel honestly quite disgusted of any religion".Which best explains the error who commit all those who criticize the film however is John Cleese. For all it is an error of perspective. According to his own words truly funny is that someone has preached so passionate about love and peace so that then his followers spend two thousand years killing and torturing each other because they are unable to agree on the manner in which said it. The absurd has nothing to do with the teachings of the founder of the religion, but with what they did of them which came later. The irony of all this is that Jesus comes out only twice in the film, failing him, the center of the sketches, but people to your around, so it is difficult to understand how the film has could be interpreted as a mockery to Jesus. as in all the Python films, all members interpreted numerous roles either as Roman Centurions, parishioners in search of a Messiah who followed or as part of the "front of the people of Judea" which is a kind of terrorist organization that seeks to overthrow the Romans. The role of Brian the was given to Graham Chapman who came out of a series of problems caused by his alcoholism, which took him even to enter into a Scottish clinic because he suffered daily bouts of "tremens delirius".For the filming took advantage used in Monastir, Tunisia sets formerly used by director Franco Zeffirelli in his miniseries "Jesus of Nazareth" (1977).Director Terry Jones is responsible for that the film has a fluid rhythm and not get bored. Perhaps the only scene that could be considered as excess is the one that leave the aliens. The explanation of this particular scene was the influence of the recent success of the film George Lucas "The war of the galaxies" (1977). Actions are simply fantastic and there are some really hilarious scenes. As always, the opening credits, animated by Terry Gilliam are very good invoice and the songs of the film are equally good.The Python regard this film as the best of his filmography, and I think that I agree with them. While the British humor isn't everyone's taste, this is a film that definitely will make you laugh, something in the majority of polls it is situated as one of the best comedies in the history.</body>
</review>
