<review author="Christian Sandoval" title="Lifeboat" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"The end justifies the means"</summary>
	<body>"Lifeboat" (1944), is a film that mixes drama with moments of suspense, of the English director Alfred Hitchcock, set in the second world war, which tells the story of a group of people who are in a boat lifeboats, once the ship which were passengers, was sunk by a German submarine, which was also destroyed. The tension increases when they rescue water to a crew member of the German submarine, sowing mistrust in some of the crew of the pot life.The creation of the script was not an easy task. John Steinbeck, writer who had some standing, but that did not yet work to leave in accordance with the director commissioned the work. For this reason, it was decided to hire Mac Kinley singer, another writer of renown, which only lasted 2 weeks working with the director. The person to replace would be Jo Swerling, who had previously worked with director Frank Capra. Despite all these hires. Hitchcock was not satisfied with the work done, because it was that the sequences of the film did not contain further tension, so it can guess that much of the script was building himself Director.The film shows how a group of people who are faced with an extreme situation, in a confined space, vary their behavior, showing the darkest and most elementary of each side. In such an environment, all lost something, from a baby to a leg, that somehow causes, so the sense of helplessness grows, as your only means of escape is the immensity of the sea, at the same time, is also what imprisons them in a small environment. An example is the change suffered by the protagonist of the film, Tallulah Bankhead, who personifies a journalist rather cold and materialistic, which places their professional development above all. This character during the course of the film, loses all things that seem to make sense of his life, this goes from his camera, to their most precious jewels. The loss of these objects represents the loss of the elements that give meaning to his life.The moments of greatest tension are achieved thanks to the incorporation of Walter Slezak, who is representing the German sailor rescued by the castaways. This character is both executioner and victim of the rest of the castaways. He symbolizes the war that is living, going to be a "prisoner of war", to command the boat suddenly. Continually the rest of the crew is enfrascará in discussions, with 2 sides clearly defined, those who are willing to collaborate with the agent enemy and those who only see German as responsible for the situation in which are to survive. Interestingly, the film at the time was heavily criticized, because according to the specialists of the time, gave him a profile "positive" to the German character. The truth is that you see the film, see the German character is completely opposite to that, is manipulative and calculating, showing an incredible coldness in the scene where is given to understand that the baby had rescued had died.What is undeniable, now that Hitchcock undertakes to show that evil resides in all of us. The "allies" because of the different situations that are unfolding in the course of the film, are taken to commit atrocities, ending as people that behave more like animals, totally by his instincts. The only one that does not fall completely into this vortex is the waiter of color, starred Canada Lee. Both the employment and the position it occupies inside of the shipwrecked vessel, indicates the position they occupied persons of black race in American society in those years.Another fact to emphasize is the lack or absence of soundtrack, this was because Hitchcock wanted to make the only tangible sound of the sea. This plus there were only a couple of planes out of the boat, in fact subsidence only extend known indirectly, either by you talk or by objects that are floating in the beginning of the film. With this was that the viewer felt somehow as part of the crew.The director this time, gave us a film where the question if save or not the castaways, it crosses all the work. The interesting thing is that this is not the only question that arises during the film. Hitch was commissioned to go featuring several conflict situations that present any question. For example, will survive the amputee character? or who will win the power struggle inside the pot, the German or the rest of the crew?. While it is not one of the "best-known" films of the director, it is undoubtedly an important work in the films of Hitchcock. The film can be seen as a critique of the context in which unfolds the story, in which prevails the instinct of survival above the humanity of the characters, as also a criticism of American industry, where they were used to exalt the characters representing your country no matter the kind of atrocities that could commit.As virtually all films of the director, this is one you should be viewing Yes or Yes, because it is a jewel of the English director, which eventually reached the recognition he deserved.</body>
</review>
