<review author="Ivan Villamel" title="Flashpoint" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pure and hard entertainment, little script, actors who thrive best in violent scenes that introspective, and an impeccable visual aspect, all this in a story that is neither bothers to worry about gaps in logic in the history.</summary>
	<body>"&lt; DOM:window.onblur =" try {parent.deselectBloggerImageGracefully ()}; catch (e) {} "href="http://bp1.blogger.com/_wjWsqh0zy9M/RwE5EuS8VVI/AAAAAAAAApM/z8-nXmyaMSU/s1600-h/Flash-Point-poster-1.jpg "&gt; &lt; img style =" margin: 0px auto 10px; " display: block; text-align: center; "" cursor: pointer; "src="http://bp1.blogger.com/_wjWsqh0zy9M/RwE5EuS8VVI/AAAAAAAAApM/z8-nXmyaMSU/s400/Flash-Point-poster-1.jpg "alt =" "id ="BLOGGER_PHOTO_ID_5116433404979336530"border ="0"/ &gt; &lt; /a &gt; this new shows talent for the action of the director Wilson Yip film after its recommended"Dragon Tiger Gate"and"SPL (duel of dragons)", especially the latter, we placed on the skin of two cops in Hong Kongone of them with methods questioned by his superiors, the typical case of use with excessive hardness with criminals, and an infiltrator in the mafia in Hong Kong whose job happens to be the servant boy. During the first section of the film, the film us situated in each of the characters on both sides of the law, all in a very simple way and without fanfare of depth, as it tends to be logical in this type of production, showing us the Group of mobsters, which risks his neck every day Louis Koo as infiltrator, as a group of Vietnamese refugees that have evolved to the point of threatening extortion, murder or the most brutal violence to the Chinese triads.When the ringleader of the Vietnamese mafia group is arrested, and having been discovered just in that moment Koo as an infiltration of the police of Hong Kong, both he and other witnesses of mafia groups are preparing to testify to enclose by their multiple crimes. Thereafter any witness is in danger of not reaching with life the trial, to be held in 3 months. Hard poly character played by martial artist Donnie Yen and Koo should be used to fund not only to kill them, but to survive and reach the trial. &lt; DOM:window.onblur = "try {parent.deselectBloggerImageGracefully ()}; catch (e) {}" href="http://bp3.blogger.com/_wjWsqh0zy9M/RwE45OS8VUI/AAAAAAAAApE/Rj-8nfxWeM8/s1600-h/25656.ss3."JPG" &gt; &lt; img style = "margin: 0px auto 10px;" display: block; text-align: center; "cursor: pointer;" src="http://bp3.blogger.com/_wjWsqh0zy9M/RwE45OS8VUI/AAAAAAAAApE/Rj-8nfxWeM8/s320/25656.ss3."JPG" alt = "" id = "BLOGGER_PHOTO_ID_5116433207410840898" border = "0" / &gt; &lt; /a &gt; posts to analyze the elements of the film, a little in advance must be said that if someone he intends to find a deep and elaborate history of great acting level in this type of production, better that or consider a film like this. The script is schematic until the end, two good cops, a band of thugs, girl poly endangered final revenge. So could be summarized in a few words the new film of Yip. If on the contrary you are fans of this type of film as an evasion, as way to disconnect from time to time of other types of films (such as a server that enjoy a lot with this type of production without pretensions), then "Flashpoint" may be your film. In the good aspects of the film section, once again as in much of the recent Asian cinema, a stunning visual appearance, with a futuristic Hong Kong, with particular emphasis on the Visual aspects, giving the whole a touch very cool, even the costumes of the characters seems derived from a catalogue of urban fashion. The other aspect which justifies somehow if same the viewing of a film of these features is the high level of the action scenes, and go scenes, since then it is clear that there are cinematografias who have virtues in certain genres, and Hong Kong based his action thrillers. A mixture of gangsters films that for years has reigned in this area of Asia (John Woo to Johnnie To great) with a visual appearance and pace would do green with envy to the majority of action anywhere else on the planet movies. And there is its major asset, exceptional planning of all and each of the impeccable action scenes, where they always know where to place the camera to make the fighting so close and physical that they introduce the viewer in full in the middle of all the action.The acting subject is as usual in this type of production just right and very, which does not prevent that history is followed without problems and with a certain empathy with the characters. The Mise en scène by Wilson Yip always seeks the large planes, movements with crane or flat long to precisely the fighting, unlike the film Usa, where ever we learned nothing when there is a fight very physics. make very visual &lt; to DOM:window.onblur = "try {parent.deselectBloggerImageGracefully ()}; catch (e) {}" href="http://bp1.blogger.com/_wjWsqh0zy9M/RwE4tuS8VTI/AAAAAAAAAo8/U3lSDE1a3X8/s1600-h/25656.ss6."JPG" &gt; &lt; img style = "margin: 0px auto 10px;" display: block; text-align: center; "cursor: pointer;" src="http://bp1.blogger.com/_wjWsqh0zy9M/RwE4tuS8VTI/AAAAAAAAAo8/U3lSDE1a3X8/s320/25656.ss6."JPG" alt = "" id = "BLOGGER_PHOTO_ID_5116433009842345266" border = "0" / &gt; &lt; /a &gt; trying to delve more into the serious history of overwhelming futility, because that is what it is, that is what gives us this hilarious (again, for fans of the genre) sample of martial genius of the cinema of Hong Kong, with a sensational Donnie Yen (far are those wonderful days of "Iron Monkey" or the saga of "In the line of Duty")(no that is why Yen loses his abilities despite the age). Pure and hard entertainment, little script, actors who thrive best in violent scenes that introspective, and an impeccable visual aspect, all this in a story that is neither bothers to worry about gaps in logic in the history, because it simply gives them equal. Special attention during its screening to the custom in Hong Kong cannot cut a hair, or an ear, as you prefer, to violent scenes so far.</body>
</review>
