<review author="Iñaki Bilbao" title="EL BARCO DE LOS LOCOS (Ship of the Fools, the) 1965" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Interesting film of Stanley Kramer, almost always motivated to tell human stories, with dyes socio-political.</summary>
	<body>"Few dates of start of World War II, a large ship, with people of all countries, especially natural Germany, begin a journey linking between them."There are all colors, single divorced Mrs in life you are looking for a partner for the rest of his days, the pair of lovers of different social class, a pro-nazi German Jewish &hellip; among them there will be their dimes and bickering."" This is add some 600 Spanish workers who worked in Cuba, bind to them, suffering an excess of passengers the ship"."-You is the more German I've met in my life. But don't realize the danger posed by the new party?-No, of course, that does not. We are in Germany and a half million of German Jews. What will you do with us, kill us all? "." Interesting film of Stanley Kramer, almost always motivated to tell human stories, with dyes socio-political.Here does the same, using the method of the successful "intrigue in the grand hotel", only that on a ship as a place where human feelings more found and bitter can give CITES causing a host of emotional ups and downs.The film is irregular in its development, being a very interesting times and slightly less. It depends on who are the characters, because these vary widely from each other, according to his personality.Thus, characters of the physician aboard, incarnated by Óskar Werner, or the lady who sees how away his youth, embodied by the great Vivien Leigh, are very interesting, as well as the of José Ferrer, magnificent in its role of pro-nazi German, who feels contempt for Jews and other people "of evil living".If, however, other characters, as the sixteen year-old girl that nobody out to dance and even of the young who must take care of at all times of his greedy Uncle are dispensable.There are intimate moments of great emotion, as when the doctor caresses you hair to Simone Signoret or great dialogues and situations, such as those that take place between Michael Dunn and Jewish German seller.Broadly, okay, but has somewhat excessive duration and some elements, like the external sets are not credible, noticing in excess cardboard stone, though after writing this last I get into imdb and I read that "won an Academy Award in the best art direction section!)." Well, I have not had good eye on this. Although I am still saying the same thing. I imagine that it refers to the decorations in interiors, Amen that it is not the same see a movie in the cinema than on TV.Also has a little too schematic drawing and something devious, of as / Spanish bailadores ACE, resulting in the end be a cool whores and their prostitutes.It is not bad and there are good interpretations, but is below many of its good author, among other things, and is my personal opinion, by influence on the dangers of the time nazismo.una past many years.It is very easy to talk about what already happened twenty years earlier, but good thing would have been to do something at the time. As my father says: "After seeing the balls to the cricket all we know is male". Then that.</body>
</review>
