<review author="Cecil B. Demente" title="Los monstruos del terror" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the worst pastiches of monsters that have been ever filmed. The only thing that saves him from the burning is that camp tone and naive that is and that drops sympathetic.</summary>
	<body>The planet Ummo has counted, so his countrymen sent to earth the doctor Odo Varnoff evil with a mission to kill humanity and leave via free to move. As human beings are a superstitious and cowardly race, these squatters space plan is to relive the classic monsters of the films of the Universal and with your help, to dominate the world. So they cast hand of "Anthologie of the Monsters", an entertaining guide tombs and secret Crypts indicating the whereabouts of Dracula, the Wolf Man, the Mummy, the Golem and Frankenstein's monster. Mad doctor full time can be tiring, so the such Varnoff will take advantage of the night to do some sightseeing and purple watching the WTF are the land, something that will make you decide to form an army of massive slave at your service. This is a Spanish, German and Italian co-production, and asked me I; do for what the hell come together so many countries if this has less budget than the video for my communion? The film was shot in six days by three different directors, the Dracula name never appears in the film for not having to pay copyright, and the same goes for Frankenstein, which makeup the name and call it the monster of Faransan, but the worst part is the Golem, which at the end or leaves. The Wolf Man, as it could not be otherwise, is portrayed by Paul Naschy in one of his many incarnations of Waldemar Daninsky. As curiosity, say that the character of Waldemar has appeared in more than ten movies with different origins and motivations, and in different times and situations, but always keeping the face of Naschy and the curse of Lycanthropy. Returning to the film, the hyphen is awkward and full of artifice and pompous dialogues which actors recited as who reads the letter at a restaurant, the make-up and effects are crappy and ridiculous, which is greatly noted that Frankenstein faltering step and entrecerrados eyes that seems a drunk people, and that Mummy with aspect of Chinese that have chopped the bees. This may be, in short, one of the worst pastiches of monsters that have been ever filmed, and the only thing that saves him from the burning is that camp tone and naive that is and that drops sympathetic. The phrase: "we'll call her Ilanka, it will be the first of a group of beautiful women who blindly obey my orders."</body>
</review>
