<review author="José A. Peig" title="Monstruoso" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cloverfield has overtones of future masterpiece of exemplary reformulation of language film, incentive to reflect on our relationship with reality. No, the film is not dead.</summary>
	<body>Modern audiovisual recording media transmitted the reality from the guidelines of any observer. Typically, we call this way of displaying the low film story the epitome of "subjective camera", as if it were an application for exception to the traditional staging. Entire House is subjective, a personal look at the universe of phenomena represented. Even when a filmmaker sets the picture from the perspective of a character, not doing something else which concretize their point of view standing at an angle from which to accommodate the whole. The star of Cloverfield is not the / characters who maintain and directed the recording, it is not its exclusive point of view, but that includes the rest of the cast and the same Viewer, which you can - that filming breaks the canons and the traditional technique and this allows improvise and understand the dynamics of the narration without previous knowledge - feel that it is he who controls the image and the movement in the process of adrenaline and exploration of the bends of the reality. On the other hand, it should not be forgotten that in cases such as REC and the now before us, the impulse that drives the image is not exactly one of the character's eye, now that this subject to patterns implicitly marking technology in use. The character precedes the registration, similarly the spectator creates their own image in his mind. The issues raised by this debate: is this metacine, or rather the deconstruction of the cinematographic language in order to understand the link between spectator and a half in a new technocratic framework?. Today, everyone can be creators of images. Improvisation, moreover, is somehow a "metarealidad" that sneaks into our future everyday with a simple act of consciousness: look at the fabric of the phenomenal world from a second registration who will be at the same time contemplated by other minds, with the consequent modification which it cannot produce in our relationship with the world. Reality within reality, multiplicity of views registered in a single image, multiplicity of consciences which ultimately are a same experience at all. (Inland Empire, David Lynch, is the latest parable about the synergy between metacine and metarealidad).In the film of Balagueró and Plaza, the registration of the "reality" is limited to a univocal and linear route which, from simple plain of its conception, stagnates in the dramatic reality that transcends not the obviousness of the used resource, without exploring the possibilities of this language. Cloverfield appears to be a nut back over to the monster movie, but the truth is that the monster is only the variable that puts in motion the emotional flow that takes us to the resolution of the drama. Matt Reeves film is a love story truncated by the brutal eruption of the present in the past, although the tense remains in the registry. In the first images, at the dawn of Manhattan of an April 27, we see the protagonists - Beth and Rob - representing the budding romantic relationship. Weeks later - 22 May - the same camera - and the same tape recorder - confronts us with the prospect of another character to take step to the representation of a banal feast and people who don't have anything interesting to say. But soon the story comes to a bitter tone through the description of a latent problem between Beth and Rob (stress the magnificent use of the ellipsis between the segment which opens the story and which now pickpocketing, by synthetic expression). As so many times we have written on these pages, it is essential that the elements that shape the narrative are duly vertebrates in all relationships and meanings. Rob, accompanied by his brother (the first victim of the circle of friends) and his best friend (which holds the camera that will allow us to be witnesses of everything), get outside and sitting in the fire escalerilla, express their bitterness and their inability to resolve the emotional conflict with Beth, to express their feelings. As well, at that precise moment it sounds the first outbreak, from the right corner of the image (we see how turn off the lights of skyscrapers).Given the insecure and turbulent internal situation of the character, the extraordinary bursts in with fury from the outside. This is a fundamental feature in all major mythological tales: the uncertainty of the hero is a (necessary) correlative phenomenon in the external world. Thus, registration is not confined to a statement of events that break the rules of the known world (the monster, in this case), but it expresses the events from the psychological layer of the central character. On the other hand, the sequence of events follows this same pattern; set the reader that in the course of the journey through the streets of Manhattan until the building of Beth, everytime Rob expresses doubts about what to do before the dangers and the desire to save his beloved, the monster appears from any corner to motivate the solution and the progress towards the objective. Ongoing correspondence between the internal state of the character and Monster creates a rhythm not only in the visual layer, but in the same internal dramatic flow, which demonstrates the devilish dynamism that characterizes a single film in the eyes of viewers less smart. In the penultimate sequence, the last outbreak caused by the presence of the monster motivates the Declaration of love between Rob and Beth, definitive and realization - somehow - atonement of the latent conflict. That scene, the desperate proclamation of mutual love while they are buried by the avalanche of Earth and cement between the fire of explosions, has a potential huge dramatic. The final sequence represents the State of original happiness before the decline of the world surrounding Rob and Beth. Bloating in the face of both and the idyllic image of the sea, the normality of the world before the catastrophe, is the reverse of the two faces of reality recorded in a same tape. The juxtaposition of two worlds, two States of existence and of being and a continuum in which the past invades the present, and the present reevalúa to the past. This cinematographic language is made of the same stuff that memories are made. And the Viewer from the armchair contemplates the future of space and time and carried out their own assessment from its present thanks to a visual language that makes them part of the represented. In what representation of reality this placed the Viewer?. Metacine and metarealidad.Let us also look at this excerpt from the text written by Nacho Vigalondo, from his blog on CNN. com: the best time, and perhaps the level sequence bolder all: driven by blind chaos, guys assail an appliances store. Rob follows that if you want to get in contact with the missing girl, you must steal a mobile phone in the same establishment. The camera follows him. Inside the premises, a plasma television emits an informative: an air Chamber and the voice of a speaker tell us the destruction of the Brooklyn Bridge, that minutes earlier had referred, in a confused and volatile manner from the very center of the tragedy. Our camera moves to another TV, it broadcast live images, in which we see the monster loitering among buildings, cleverly hidden to our eye (to our lens?) between skyscrapers. A thunderous noise draws the attention of our camera, which goes on the outside. It focuses on the horizon, with what we receive, again the perspective, even more fragmented, but immediate, Monster. The House, espeluznado, again entering the store, to notify Rob of the proximity of the creature. Inside, the confused attackers with objects stolen in hand, are looking at TVs, without leaving a tab. Our camera also looks at. This time, the screen shows the attack of the criaturas-araña soldiers. The cries of shock that accompany the horrifying onslaught do not come from our room cinema, but own fictitious viewers inside the tent. That you download the movie in one of those shoddy screeners may not notice the difference (which multiplies the metalinguistic attraction, admit it). Sequence not only recasts the situation, recapitulates what has happened, and anticipates further disasters based on overlapping views with enloquecedora skill, but that condenses the essence of the movie in seconds: the collective disaster is reduced to the individual event (at the end of the world, why not steal a Wii), which in turn is crushed by the collective disaster (even with a Wii in the hands)(the end of the world is the end of the world). New foray into the collective crisis 11-s, but on this post can soon say it won't say until exhaustion. It is the least interesting aspect of the film and - especially taking into account that still has not made the definitive film about this state of affairs - does not exceed the value of previous reviews. Be destroyed in our freedom by a projectile which takes the form of the head of the iconic monument, is a potentially painful, terrifying vision. Although certainly not beat the "decapitation" seen in the last seconds of Planet of the apes.Without reaching the State of perfection, Cloverfield has overtones of future masterpiece of exemplary reformulation of language film, incentive to reflect on our relationship with reality. No, the film is not dead.</body>
</review>
