<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Munich" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are some sequences nailing in the hearts of those who shared the movie theater</summary>
	<body>To write about a movie like "Munich" it is recommended to send to sleep at least eight hours first to neurons, but I can not tell you everything. Tell you that the film has left me a bad too evident body. Is that eight hours will not be enough. Is that eight weeks will not be. There are some sequences, some images, some pieces broken nailing in the hearts of those who, by my side, shared the cinema today.There is a particular message before, and almost three hours of a consistent and fiercely tenacious spirit behind. The violence only trigger more violence. Violence is not spectacular. Violence is simply something terrifying. A nightmare that is hidden under the mattress for our bed, inside the TV or our phones. A dream become a terrifying reality, disguised as a religion, homeland, of courage, of heroism. A piece of rotten becoming ill the human heart. Spreading tirelessly. Destroying everything. There are no winners, there is no innocent, there is no hope in a conflict in which the different political and economic interests, they descarrían and they catapulted the answers, do jump through the air solutions to lethargic and prolong human suffering eternally. A grim, cold, cruel, bitter and brutal message emerged from the darkest part of a masterful director, which remains in its untiring search of the master, the genius that has inside.Narrated murders are not spectacular, the shootings are crude, chaotic, realistic. Terrorist acts saturate the footage. They saturate the mind of the Viewer. The narrative structure of the settling of accounts is reiterated. These are repetitive, pervasive, in a monstrous routine and desasogante. All this in a stretched and dense footage. Without concessions. No room or space for romanticism, or the epic, not even for the respite from the Viewer. In the tape no good. There is bad. There are only victims. The home is expensive. Peace has no price in a world in which life if you don't have it.Spielberg, of known Jewish origin, is the Israeli-Palestinian conflict, but it doesn't stop there, because you know that the war of which speaks is fronts opened in many other places. Wound is a sea of clone sores, open sores, and while it heals a new ones arise, and much worse at his side. The message is therefore a universal message. And in this way focuses on telling the Interior of one of the terrorist conflicts. Conflicts that all direct we understand, humanizing a drama that makes us all participate.Not all the technical aspects in the film are my taste, that damn difuminador filter that tarnished images of almost all their latest productions. Aesthetic taste that seems to share with his faithful director of photography Janusz Kaminski. Neither find nor necessary already commented excess footage. But we are, without a doubt, in front of one of the most important and brave of this outrageous director sentenced for merits to be remembered along with the masters of the seventh arte.¿Pero that fuck is the movie?Friends, go to see her. Suffer with the "beautiful" discovery of the terror of such violence as, unfortunately, the order of the day on the other side of our newscasts. Acongojar you with the true face of State terrorism. Discover the poignant sense of feel, for a few minutes, closely akin to those who really suffer from the reality of violence from all different aspects with your own eyes. Go to the cinema to also witness an eternal tragically topical.</body>
</review>
