<review author="Kiko de España" title="Manderlay" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Harder than Dogville, Von Trier shows, as it did in this, that the people we are some real shit, only that this time comes further, because they are not saved or cotton pickers.</summary>
	<body>People are fucking shit. This could be the title of the series in the head of this great son of the great whore that is Lars Von Trier. Manderlay, 2005, is the second of a trilogy which began Dogville (2003) and close von. Grace is now with pueblucho where slavery is still present and decides to intervene. Sometimes things, although we do them with good intentions, not should be fixed, the great plot twists of the film are responsible to prove it.Harder than Dogville, Von Trier shows, as it did in this, that the people we are some real shit, only that this time comes further, because they are not saved or cotton pickers. Almost all of the "present" elements remain invisible, but what dazzles at all times is a wonderful script and a few excellent interpretations on all a Bryce Dallas Howard, which I've love definitely and it is certainly the best work of Ron Howard. (Is it yours?) Well, redhead if) John Hurt is narrating the story, divided into nine parts or chapters.Strange is my relationship with the director, Dogville, Manderlay this or dancing in the darkness seem wonderful, what happens is that idiots seems to me one of the greatest offenses I have seen ever, which made me deny him until I saw "the musical" with Bjork. I greatly disgusts the intelectualoide movement who invented the smart people like him or Vinterberg and that, see you where, at the moment there is no trace. (Or in Dear Wendy is present somewhere fucking fucking oath?)I guess that when they discovered the pop music, the very asshole renounced its principles. And everyone wins. Great end credits. 9. PS: Go streak of outstanding, hopefully be kept, although I very much doubt. PD2: Despite rumors, not seen any animal killed in the movie, but if there was, there is the news.</body>
</review>
