<review author="Vsancha" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>At the end you stay with a film that is a good film adaptation of what was technically impeccable, television series, but that doesn't have anything, or at least anything new, and that is extremely irregular in his narration getting boot more than one yawn to the staff.</summary>
	<body>Recently I read a story in which an American web had developed a ranking with the best movies based on TV series, among the top we could see the untouchables of Eliot Ness, the fugitive or Blues Brother, these days comes to our screens the adaptation of the legendary ochentena series Miami Vice in the hands of one of its producers Michael Mannthat already we had delighted in the past with great action such as Heat or the latest Collateral thrillers. If you are film could be on that list, I suppose that if to see that there are also films such as South Park, or hold it as you can, but the feeling that one is after seeing this Miami Vice, it is somewhat bittersweet. I.e., the film is not bad, but at times becomes heavy and boring, especially for a screenplay that leaves much to be desired. The film is technically impeccable, Mann address almost touching the perfection, large flat General resembling postcards and where the Viewer may not depart the gaze of a boat across the sea or a car at full speed at night through the streets of Miami. In the interpretive section we have everything, a great Colin Farrell is benefited by a script that focuses on her character and the love story that has the worst, with the character of Gong Li, that anyone would say that she is 40 years old, just the opposite happens with blurred character portrayed by a correct Jamie Foxx, and at the risk of being accused of alleged phobias to Spanish actorsis the do performance? of Luis Tosar, although if I have to be honest not is if it was Luis Tosar or a wax of the same figure, because his inexpressiveness reached unsuspected heights, is supposed to speak but we do not see his mouth due to its abundant beard and his eyes seem not blinking while it appears on the screen. And in general all the film is very well done, the soundtrack is also luxury, I would say that even the best of the film, photography, and as we have said, the direction and performances, saving any exception they are notable, but it is nothing more, the movie has nothing, crap very well wrapped gift, the action scenes are very fewfew, a couple of them or three, that if very well shot and very spectacular, but is not enough. The film comes to bored of greatly to the Viewer. At the end you stay with a film that is a good film adaptation of what was technically impeccable, television series, but that doesn't have anything, or at least anything new, and that is extremely irregular in his narration getting boot more than one yawn to the staff.</body>
</review>
