<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spanish cinema has lost an historic opportunity to create a jewel easily exportable to much of the planet. Had material to do so and we have failed. Again will be.</summary>
	<body>Big advertised as the most expensive film in the history of the Spanish cinema (cost 24 million euros), came to the end to our screens "Alatriste" of Agustín Díaz Yanes.Como everybody knows, is the adaptation of the five novels by Arturo Pérez-Reverte on the adventures of Captain Alatriste (Viggo Mortensen) and his friends in which the battles they in Flanders and palatial intrigue of the count-Duke of Olivares (Javier Cámara)Fray Emilio Bocanegra (Blanca Portillo) or King Philip IV are dotted with references to Velazquez or Quevedo (Juan Echanove) forming the whole a good portrait of the Spain of the 17TH century.This historical fresco is one of the strengths of the film Diaz Yanes, due among other factors to their beautiful soundtrack of Roque Baños and its wonderful art direction (Benjamín Fernández) and costumes (Francesca Sartori). Because if something get the film is moving to Madrid from the 17TH century with great effectiveness, dirty and dark streets, their social differences, their morality? The option of realism is evident in scenes of battles in which Díaz Yanes decides to renounce the showmanship and great typical mass movements of the blockbusters and offer us General plans in which we can clearly see that the soldiers in contention are a few tens.Photography (Paco Femenia) is also an authentic delicacy, imitating the style of some paintings of that time and helping to create that pessimistic atmosphere that envelops the entire film. Fully justified being, pessimism in a way, of the portrait of a society and an empire began to crumble.With regard to the actors I can not complain me because they are all fine. To those already mentioned, it should be added to Elena Anaya, Antonio Dechent, Eduard Fernández, Ariadna Gil, Pilar López de Ayala, Eduardo Noriega and Unax Ugalde. For me all are equal but that aspen me if I know why Fray Emilio Bocanegra is portrayed by a woman (the great Blanca Portillo).But, above all, the soul of the film is Viggo Mortensen, who composed a perfect, fatalistic, Alatriste disenchanted, ruthless with enemies but loyal with friends. An actor with a magnificent presence which, although it is true that has a strange accent is so stuck in the paper that there comes a time in which convinces me that no one else could have been Alatrsite and that rare voice is the perfect for the character.So far it seems that everything works in the movie, right? Well not. Everything actually works in the film, except for the film. I do not know if it is a failure of script because of wanting to do too much (remember that he fits five different novels about the character) or Assembly by having excessively cut footage to give a more commercial period. What is clear is that the rhythm is never right, to the point of becoming imperdonablemente boring in some passages. Also lacks strength and narrative pulse that does not help to make attractive the least boring moments.The sensation is in the Viewer is watching a lavish television series which you have cut half of the scenes for its passage by the cinemas. So we skip a few scenes to others without solution of continuity, without giving time to create the right atmosphere and with ellipsis that they cry out to heaven. A trailer for two hours and a half which could have been a great movie for four or five hours.Final "Alatriste" demonstrates, once more, a blockbuster that nothing we can do with money on the table have envy to the Americans in the final product. The trouble is that we have failed to know better than they do them and one is left with the impression that Spanish cinema has lost an historic opportunity to create a jewel easily exportable to much of the planet. Had material to do so and we have failed. Again will be.</body>
</review>
