<review author="Caty" title="Buenas noches y buena suerte" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lesson civic, worthy of being shown in schools</summary>
	<body>It is incredible (and depressing) that a story that happened 50 years ago can be as current as the narrated in "good night and good luck". The climate conspiracy that exists today in part of American society is not very different from the one led by Joseph McCarthy during the Decade of the cincuenta-la difference is that an invented history, is not if at that time those who questioned the Senator feared they were branded "Communists", today the critics of Bush and his cohort are questioned as regards "patriotism" that can feel or, in extreme cases, classified as supporters of terrorism.What remains today, therefore, is that someone take the place of Edward r. Murrow, legendary CBS flagship, and in its programme "See it now" was essential, with its criticisms and reports, for the sinking of McCarthy. Instead, the newspaper Guild (including Spanish) comes to be dominated by cowardly figures and without ethics, whose search for truth was diluted in time for corporate and political interests: therefore, the figure of Murrow, with his courage, his ethics and his career, is a real class of journalism (good night, and good luck should be exhibited in schools only by the splendid speech made by the "character" in the beginning) (and the conclusion of the film).Set in a period of time relatively short, from October 1953 to may of the 54 (with the exception of the aforementioned speech, occurring in the 58) the screenplay written by George Clooney and Grant Heslow shows Murrow and his team at the peak of the McCarthyism, when the climate of paranoia fostered by the Senator carried Aviation forces us to expel a Lieutenant based on anonymous reports related to the father of the military (something which gives rise to an episode of "See it Now", dedicated to the case). From here, Murrow and his producer Fred Friendly, begin a search that would result in a program in which used the words of McCarthy against the. Returning to the Chair of director after his excellent "confessions of a dangerous mind", Clooney shows rather content this time, avoiding strange camera movements and concentrate more in the dialogues and the tense atmosphere inspired by the clash between two large forces: the media and politics. In an effort to maximize to rescue visual taste and mentality of the era, the director uses advertising pieces produced in the fifties and includes small interludes throughout the narrative in which Diane Reeves arises singing Classic Jazz give the film a nostalgic tone. Reeves holdings represent the only musical tape interventions, as Clooney-following one trend growing contemporary filmmakers - discards the use of soundtrack. Photography, black and white work of Robert Elswit, usa the shadows in a superb way, by adopting a realistic tone, and stressing that, throughout the film, there are only a plane outdoors, highlighting that dark tone that reflects a battle within the buildings is underway.Clooney as an actor, also does a good job to orchestrate actions: in the middle of a very competent cast Frank Langella deserves a special mention for giving life to William S. Palley, President of CBS, and he is portrayed as a man divided by corporate obligations and its commitment to journalistic ethics. We also are Ray Wise, who embodies the tragic Don Hollembeck with sympathy and suffered dignity, while Robert Downey Jr. and Patricia Clarkson teach us the problems of a couple that should hide his union bosses, prohibiting marriage between workers. Finally, the Clooney himself, with his usual charisma, established an air of important complicity between the Fred Friendly and Edward Murrow, played by David Strathairn. The latter, as it could not be otherwise, represents the absolute centre of the film: famous and prestigious, journalist never settles in the status that is, looking for, rather than maintaining this status, new battles to make just the influence who can exert on the public. With an always formal air in front of the cameras, the journalist tries to present a facade firm and safe, although the film would win more dimension if we had access to other facets of the journalist, as his family life, or their well-known attraction to the danger, often showing in risky reports during the second war Mundial.Consciente of the importance of this projectGeorge Clooney used to Murrow as a symbol of the journalistic virtues: after the program in which they unmask McCarthy, we feel as these men will sleep with pride at night. At present, what we have today is ever overturned programming with the vacuum and surface. Television has become, as predicted by Murrow into something banal, wasting his potential newsletter for entertainment, most of the time, empty and disposable, becoming a weapon for the rulers who want to keep people distracted in a constant vacuum of information.Good night, and good luck is more than a film interesting and efficient: is a civic lesson as those that own Murrow was in charge of teaching in its programme.</body>
</review>
