<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Clerks 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What twelve years ago struck mightily for his brazenness, its freshness, its desparpajo, already not surprised now, especially when that language of unusual sexual openness today handles up on television.</summary>
	<body>It seems that the career of Kevin Smith, who drew attention to powerfully twelve years ago with "Clerks" (see criticism in CRITICALIA), not ends of find their way. After this years dozen, neoyersino filmmaker returns where began, the small, certainly pleasant universe of a couple of grey guys who were waiting in the astroso supermarket in the first part. After a title of interest ("Chasing Amy"), Smith made some incursions into stories by throwing into delirious ("Dogma"; see criticism in CRITICALIA), which did not work too well, so returned to his old characters ("Jay and silent Bob Bob"), and now, definitely, to the same previous landscape, although for the occasion has defenestraded it through a fire and the protagonists spend working in a burger bar district.But the truth is that, that twelve years ago struck mightily for his brazenness, its freshness, its desparpajo, already not surprised now, especially when that language of unusual sexual openness today handles up on television. So, time has not only passed by then somethings clerks of the supermarket, now already thirtysomethings long and without much idea of what to do with their lives, but also by the very concept of "Clerks": before was a joy to listen to these lenguaraces and see how Smith, no idea where they put a camera and shoot decently a filmHe was capable of making us laugh to mode. Now Kevin knows since roll with ease, but the theme catches us something talluditos and the characters sound too well-known: the reasonable Dante; Randal, so bocazas as usual; Jay, as a goat; The silent Bob, who does not speak for do not disturb? Is also true that some scenes are funny and even recordables: see the diatribe on the sagas of "The Lord of the rings" and "Star Wars", or the deslenguado Randal and its "normalization" of an allegedly racist insult; It is also true that sometimes are passed three villages, as in the scene of the zoófilo gimmick of the bachelor party, a donkey too (do literally?) scene. But often the verbiage of the characters bored staff: is difficult to be talking for an hour and a half and did not tiring, and the dialogues are not precisely written by Shakespeare. Anyway, hope that Smith will not fall to a "Clerks III" (although you would not surprise me, because in the USA its fund-raising has multiplied by five budget?), because it is then clear that his work is going to turn on a single topic, and it is already sufficiently squeezed.</body>
</review>
