<review author="Kiko de España" title="Supersonic man" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Supersonic Man needs no phone booths, just has to push a button of your reloj-calculadora to one euro and say: that the strength of the galaxies is with me. CCU!</summary>
	<body>This Spanish film supposed homeland response to the "Superman" Donner. Where do I start? Kronos is a masked alien who carries a black fardahuevos and is sent to Earth by a distant relative of Jor - the. Flies with a song of Abba (or almost) and the credits are as phosphorescent that shit is not read.When it reaches the Earth calls Paul and has moustache. A very bad man named Dr.Gulik (clavadito to Captain Kirk of Star Trek, he dresses like, combs is equal and has the same fucking complexion) kidnaps a scientist from the elderly to steal a formula. This uses a robot that is a mixture of the robot bad Robocop and Inigo of great Hermano.Supersonic Man should avoid it.Our hero, so that I could see, is invincible. unless you legolpeen in the neck by surprise, that lets you KO (!), like fly in circles and made overwhelming demonstration of power. opening doors. CCU!Supersonic Man needs no phone booths, just has to push a button of your reloj-calculadora to one euro and say: that the strength of the galaxies is with me. CCU! Oh, I forgot. If you are at the bottom of the sea, enclosed in a SAC and surrounded by sharks file, can also speak!!The first (and trapidantes) five minutes, in which occurs the attack and kidnapping, seem to be one of those infomercials Pascual who gave for years on TV. The bad launch rays leiser.As it is Spanish and takes place (i.e. a) in New York, all the bad guys are called Harrison, Peterson, Harrison, or any other name that ends in On.Sale Quique Camoiras. There is a drunk that comes everytime there to do a typical joke. Quique Camoiras is great in his cameo making jokes of stuttering, high comedy. There is a fight of the old, which are cool, just missing Terence Hill and Bud Spencer.El bad is so bad that quote Shakespeare or Julius Caesar (I mean that he cites the two phrases, not to stay with them in a pub) Supersonic Man lifts tractors of papier-mache being written Acme on the side. The battle against the robot, spectacular climax, resolves the Supersonic Man. giving a flying kick.Might I be so for days, three pages of notes for the movie. Worse even than "UV" but infinitely more fun. A 2. (But you spend a fucking).</body>
</review>
