<review author="Kiko de España" title="Misión imposible 3" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Agile, exciting, dramatic, fast-paced and entretenidísima, ideal for these evenings of heat African and far superior to the vast majority of blockbusters.</summary>
	<body>Olvidense of Scientology. Forget the placentas. Returns the best Cruise. After giving a month of term to all Brats comemierdas doceañeros that crowd the cinemas, I got, in a completely empty room, as he assumed from the outset (Tuesday, 16: 30) to see the "last superespectáculo Made in Cruise". and I liked it a lot.I think "Mission impossible" a masterpiece and one of the best films of my beloved Brian De Palma and after the drubbing of the delivery of the yesteryear large John Woo ("Face to face" is his best movie as well as an absolute masterpiece) was quite reluctant to see the third, finally signed by J.J. Abrams instead of the initially planned Fincher or Carnahan. Abrams, creator of "Alias" and "Lost", with note passes the test, I do not know if it will be a great director, his next movie is "Star Trek XI".SPOILERS (if you've seen the trailer can read quietly) but let's "MI3", the adventure "staff" of the agent Ethan Hunt, that deberescatar his beloved from the clutches of Owen Davian. Arranca masterfully in media res, achieving that my ass (and millions of assholes in the world) not moved one iota of your armchair with a sensational scene between the villanísimo, a son of perraPhilip Seymour Hoffman grandios and the heroisísimo resolved a few great close-up.END of SPOILERSEl case is that there is action during the two horazas that lasts and a lot of smart turns of script in which Abrams moves like a fish in water, in this aspect is a both television. (but television quality, i.e. If you like "24", "Lost", "alias". you'll love "MI3".)Cinematically, Abrams is not any prodigy, but we would appreciate that you do not use the "video clip system", arriving at times to the first filmimposible, especially the part of the Vatican desk, primahermana of the party who opened the original De Palma. Agile, exciting, dramatic, fast-paced and entretenidísima, ideal for these evenings of heat African and far superior to the vast majority of blockbusters. A 8´5.</body>
</review>
