<review author="Kiko de España" title="Calvaire" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hand crafted as few movies lately, tells the story without thunderous shock effect, without musical rises or free scares. Get spook me enough for having to shower after the film to remove mud and blood.</summary>
	<body>I am seeing "Calvaire", Fabrice Du Welz, because, without being 100% original (something extremely complicated today, hence that piece of 9 that I gave yesterday to "Kiss kiss bang bang"), manages to terrify me enough for having to shower after the film to remove mud and blood.Taking as models to Michael Haneke, "Straw dogs" to "Psycho", "Texas Chainsaw Massacre", to this great movie that was "The dam", Walter Hill, (another day I tell how big that was this man), "Deliverance" and with a European flair than by nearby achieves more terrifying to the Viewer, comoya succeeded in the above-mentioned director of "Time of the Wolf" or Alexandre Aja with "High voltage", hipertramposa movie, but that shows a director with ways and we will return all crazy with his remake of "the hills have eyes".Marc Stevens, a crappy singer, acts in a shabby nursing home. Before, we see how in silence, you makeup to function. We are warned, uncomfortable film and echoes Hanekianos, fasten the belts.When Marc embarks on the journey to his next performance, the van driving is damaged in the middle of nowhere. He began a nightmare of folly, fake reincarnations, torture and brutality. Hand crafted as few movies lately, tells the story without thunderous shock effect, without musical rises or free scares, keeping the viewer in constant tension.It has at least three anthologies sequences, namely: that camera through the window of the van to enter and then leave, the dance of the zumbados of the people (possibly more terrifying seen in a long time), and an overhead plane special, although confusing, vaguely reminiscent of the famous travelling of the overrated "Old boy". Incomprehensibly unprecedented in our country, thank people like Max Renn by recommend, and KesheR, for being a fantastic "subtitulador". A 7´5.</body>
</review>
