<review author="Berto" title="Clerks 2" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An excellent continuation of a comedy classic. Kevin Smith it was quite difficult to be able to live up to his great masterpiece, but say it exceeds, if dignity keeps the Ribbon just as higher than in the first part.</summary>
	<body>Back in 1994, Kevin Smith surprised everyone with a very unusual comedy at that time. Shot in black and white, with very few resources, it was simply a day in the life of a sales clerk in a store in the typical American neighborhood. Said it may sound quite common, but the screenplay Kevin Smith had prepared for this film, is one authentic masterpiece, with a few characters who steal, on more than one occasion, laughter and even get to identify with them. Do after this great masterpiece of our time they followed more stories from New Jersey, city where he was born and where he decided to locate their films?Mallrats would then followed of chasing Amy, that everything the world considered his best film with Clerks, some years more Bob late Dogma, and Jay &amp; Silent Bob strike back and for my worst of all his filmography A Jersey girl, attempt in vain to make a romantic comedy just being authentic basurilla.(Does in his own words Kevin Smith describes her as horror film?) Now, nearly 12 years later, again reunited with his two mythical characters, Dante and Randall, apart from Jay and Silent Bob, present in all of his films. In this continuation, and because of an accident, leave the store in which worked to enter Moodys, a species of McDonalds (the motto is i´m eating it). The years have not passed in vain, and while Randall remains the same that always, for Dante this is his last day of work before leaving his beloved New Jersey to marry and take the lead in a washing tunnel owned by his future father-in-law. It is this last day, this larghissimo day, which focuses in the film and which will bring all the surprises of the movie, and this is what serves as an excuse so again Kevin Smith build some more funny dialogues that I have enjoyed as comedy is concerned, something that should be taken into account imitators of American Pie and companyseeing as becomes truth, with its touch humor geek and rude sometimes, but I fixed just booting you a smile. The climax of the film comes with a discussion among fans of Star Wars and the Lord of the rings, and which is the best trilogy of the history, simply because that dialogue deserves the price of admission. For anyone who is already acquainted with Kevin Smith movie comment that it him no disappointment at all, I am big fan of yours and I have to admit that this film is his second best film, with Clerks in the first positions. For those who do not know, States from here that passes through the film and be prepared for an hour and half laugh non-stop, with a hyphen, again insisting, really fantastic that even feel sorry that the film will end.Actors because as in the first part, Brian O´Halloran great with his portrayal of Dante (think than an alter ego of the director) and Jeff Anderson remains the same that 12 years ago with his character of Randall Graves, mythical character that so many defects has just worshiping it. Jay and Bob (the director) are still there, seems no time passes by them, and the incorporation of Rosario Dawson gives a small commercial thrust to the film, and I have to admit that also this pretty well, with a character quite well built and that fits perfectly in any Clerks mythology, apart from the fact that it is an authentic Bonbonlol? Also deserves attention Trevor Fehrman, new incorporation as Rosario and a crack in her role as Elijah, Dante and Randall co-worker authentic and that double-dip almost all final Randall.En jokes, an excellent continuation of a comedy classic. Kevin Smith thing had quite difficult to be able to live up to his great masterpiece, but say it exceeds, if dignity keeps the Ribbon just as higher than in the first part and it is one more than exemplary continuation of the life of Dante and Randall. Let us hope that the Smith Let's now follow along this path and never more back into that big mistake which was A Jersey girl.</body>
</review>
