<review author="Marta" title="La joven del agua" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An extrañísima, too forced, story told as if such a thing. The result, as well as predictable and disappointing, it is boring.</summary>
	<body>I believe that there are few directors capable of having a career so short and at the same time as irregular as M. Night Shyamalan. It is difficult to believe the infumable "signals", with Mel Gibson taking advantage to give lessons in morality as he flees the alien's work of the same Director that "The sixth sense", one of the best films of suspense in recent years. Thus, the premiere of "The girl in the water" was a mystery. It would be great? Would it be acceptable? It would be very bad? To me I found disappointing. Very disappointing. I have read several reviews that praise. Normally, they claim a kind of right to create worlds full of fantasy film. All of that is great. Personally, I like the idea of raising what would happen if the magic entered the world of the everyday. Equal to make already in the "protected", where showed us the emergence of a typical superhero comic - included - in a family environment characteristic and supervillain uniform, Shyamalan not puts the actors in "The girl in the water" in an enchanted forest, but the pool of a few blocks of buildings. The characters in the story have their correspondence in ordinary people and the environment is familiar, as if what happens could happen, in fact, to anyone. The problem of the film is not this approach, but the way to solve it. Unlike "The sixth sense", where the viewer would discover the secrets little by little, the narrative pace of "The girl in the water" is excessively precipitate. Not allow to immerse themselves in the history to the rhythm of the protagonist, but soon since everything happened. She is already there, we all know who is and what is happening and nobody has had time nor surprising. Only have to wait the end, arriving after a couple of turns very simplistic and predictable - nothing to do with, for example, "the forest" (to cite one example that is not "The sixth sense"). The characters, on the other hand, are too flat. How can be a group of seemingly so different people react exactly like an incredible situation? Shyamalan knows this. Not me. Finally, the "explanation", appearing in the form of neighbouring tale, is too forced. An extrañísima story, told as if such a thing. And it is already. The result, as well as predictable and disappointing, it is boring. What could have been a beautiful film about the fantasy that could come at any time in our day to day is something to forget. Some say that Disney must be suffering for having let slip to M. Night Shyamalan. I rather think that it is breathing relieved.</body>
</review>
