<review author="Calaf" title="Alatriste" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is seen in the film? Then if. It has enough interesting items than to enjoy, despite its excessive footage, although it is quite far from being a round movie.</summary>
	<body>I start by tell me I have not read the books of Reverte, and that did not expect much from the movie after the comments that I had arrived. They say that when used to highlight the picture setting. It is because the film is bad. No I would say both, but it is true the artistic direction acquired notoriety by their own merits and says of other sections like the script, the worst of the film. Alatriste like pieces, is a missed opportunity but to praise.I will try to not roll me much. To do this, nothing better than to synthesize what I liked and what is not.The good news: the audacity of production Yes. Each and every one of those technical paragraphs called: setting, locations, costumes, photography. The music will have to listen to it separate, but even the departure of band of people not has been able to appear me more accurate in the final battle. More impossible Spanish. I liked Viggo Mortensen. It has personality and magnetism. Transmits bitterness. The characterizations of historical characters, magnificent. It is a joy to enjoy some images - pictures. Spanish film shows once more know shooting history.The bad: is made to pieces. There is no connection in the history. It gives the feeling that they could have eliminated many scenes and nothing would have happened. That is not good, is a script problem.Other sequences become longer unnecessarily (the theatre, some inconsequential link landscapes) when not enough directly (which commits suicide when they will stop, a duel) because none of the character has not been explained and therefore the viewer cares a damn.The movie lacks humor. You can shoot a grim story and not lose the touch of humor inherent even in the most jodidas situations. Some salpicones blood stand out without.The question. It is seen in the film? Then if. It has enough interesting items than to enjoy, despite its excessive length, even if it is quite far from being a round and consistent movie. Despite all applaud her only for the attempt, media, and because more than one politician "missions of peace" put you the colorada face (although not fall that breva) of what was the Spanish army.</body>
</review>
