<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Separados" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He could have aspired to imitate one of the comedies of Spencer Tracy and Katharine Hepburn, but lacks class.</summary>
	<body>The problem of "Separated" is who tells the story of separation. The has it, and gives the version of the American male unable to grow, which is something similar to the Spanish male, but with greater purchasing power. That is why I am not interested. Only interested me the version of the girl, Jennifer Aniston. His version on the billiard table, a boyfriend who only knows playing video games as a fifteen year old, which treads not the kitchen if it does not fall the way bath. I am interested in the version of the girl because the story is truth, one feels that what would have happened. The trouble is that you one also senses that are telling to her badly.The last time they told me so bad story was "The man of the time". There Nicolas Cage says that his wife left him because he forgot to buy tartar sauce. Vince Vaughn in a unbeatable prodigy of introspection and analysis comes to the conclusion that their relationship broke down because he bought three lemons instead of twelve. All it is known that the woman is unable to forgive such things by nature. However and though it may be difficult to understand, the character of Vaughn is proud of shrewd is. Forced to live on the same floor, she looks for other appointments, but he does not fall into the trap of jealousy and camela candidates, which should be worthy of applause. This man leads his life as one of their games, scoring points.The film could have aspired to imitate one of the comedies of Spencer Tracy and Katharine Hepburn, but lacks class. Comedy, is also lacking the exception of the first sequence in which are known and he plays everything to get an appointment. The end points a brochazo of good literature, it seems a final written by Quim Monzó. The trouble is all there is in the middle.</body>
</review>
