<review author="Darthz" title="En la cuerda floja" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sometimes the fragile line that unites us between the dream and the reality is broken</summary>
	<body>Sometimes the fragile line that unites us between the dream and the reality is broken. The dream we pursue, the woman we love the House we look forward one day have, the music that devour us when we are sad, everything is shattered in a second is countable. And so it was the story of Johnny Cash, the revolutionary singer, which began as anyone who yearns to achieve something big, with the basics by infimum, conservatively. He worked in the field, and also came to serve the air force, up to her voice to reveal a new icon of the music country and rock 'n' roll. James Mangold brings his story to the film, the story of Johnny Cash. A film very beautiful, romantic, comparable to Brokeback are, in some respects. There are places and beautiful songs that will recall us that another great movie. The image is good and the music, as I say, splendid. At the beginning the rhythm is accelerated, and makes us a flashback to his childhood, where we will find what will be after its most significant features. His family, where we all start. Johnny had one brother, more older than him, and said its parent much more skilled in the arts of the work, to get money to feed a family of humble and poor, as those of soon and the now and always. The boy was introverted, for that reason, perhaps as everyone always do when we leave the heart to act for us, will draw afloat throughout the rebellion that had never exploded. His brother died, and already we had only the poor and incapacitated Johnny. And it will grow with the scourge of a father who treated him badly, a family that seemed not wanting to. A loneliness that always accompanies the man beyond where it will. But everything changes, everything changes when he recorded a first album. He always love the music. And as any lover of a gift or something that yearns for have known, when one takes something so intrinsically, and loves him, and appreciated it beyond more above any other knowledge or circumstance, and even more then train in this art, ends up being an artist. And that is the summary of the story of Johnny Cash. Would inevitably tend to bring up the most unsuspected his music, and with it, his biggest dream and illusion. And there also known love, the love that perhaps never had his "official" wife. He fell madly in love June Carter. And the music would accompany him until his death, as well as love. An artist as not, and reflection on what it is, an artist who lived and died in what he loved and that really believed and was still alive. That spark that all us sometimes dries and a poet, a musician, an artist of truth never him disappears, because at the most unexpected moments enhances your view and find us. Music, his music, and love, that girl that cost him his own make, but know that we loved that the reins of love is very difficult to escape. And even more of the scourge that this us then paste. But not everything is nice, sweet, and romantic, and good. Lol There is always a bad thing. Something dark. A bad stage, a bad day, a bit of bad luck. And Johnny Cash experimented it with the drug, that demon extolled with his soul because of its reliable little popularity, cocky and misleading cusp reached thanks to his good voice and its good music, but which was then followed by serious consequences. He finished very badly, really wrong, as anyone who goes through this. On a tightrope. But as already said, what really we love and gives us forces is what we will always draw of that evil self-absorption which leads to pain. In his case, eternal love to a woman, and the love of music. These strings of a guitar that would accompany it until the day in which reconcile this dream that we never woke up. A fatherly voice that susurraría you until the most recondite moments an evil phrase, a few malignant words which would be imprisoned all his life. The love of a family that actually could never behave as I would have liked a brother who died, a mother who gave birth to some of the most revolutionary music of our last century to a death of a solitary and introverted soul that eventually overflowing of rebellion. The rebel of Jhonny Cash, the solitary of Johnny Cash, the always tormented and poet and musician Johnny Cash.</body>
</review>
