<review author="José Córdoba" title="Clerks 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is a small, nothing original, nothing ambitious film, but is welcomed and it is fun and entertaining while forgettable...</summary>
	<body>Twelve years ago, Kevin Smith made his first film Clerks, a small film that chronicled the life of two employees of a small supermarket, shot in black and white and very charismatic characters that not stopped talking. That was its main feature the verbiage of his characters and their brilliant dialogues and "geeks". Today it is a cult movie that I'd like to see to see how has aged. The later career of Smith has not been able to escape the long shadow of this film that marked the constants in his filmography: characters of uncontrollable verbiage close to thirty and very "geeks", understood in its meaning of fan of comedians, Star Wars, etc. Come on, a few characters that seem quite close to many of us and perhaps lie there, the success of his films. Following the disappointing results of their latest movies and the tremendous critical criticism a Jersey Girl, his latest work, Smith returned to his roots and presents the continuation of his first film, Clerks II, which was initially going to be entitled "The Passion of the Clerks". The result is a fun, small, nothing pretentious film sees with a constant smile and forget soon of seeing. It is a reunion of old friends, there are two subsidiaries of the original, Dante and Randal, Jay and silent Bob after passing through prison, and also appear faces known as Jason Lee and Ben Affleck. Twelve years have passed since the original, but strictly speaking it doesn't, the characters have not matured although Dante wants to lay your head and move away from New Jersey with his fiancée. Continue to have the same discussions and the same behaviour, as if nothing had happened in twelve years. Therefore the aim of Smith in this film is show us that, at long last, these characters will mature, will finally move from adolescence to enter the adult world. By the way, in the form of marriage, children, stable employment. Smith, despite the apparent irreverence of his films, is a fervent Catholic and devotes all of his films to God. The history is very typical and thousand views, Smith has never been a visual director and here again to prove it, his films based all his strength in the dialogues and characters in wild situations. And here the film works with a discussion environment to the Lord of the rings very funny, sporadic occurrences of Jay and Bob or the scene with the donkey. It is also narrated with an appropriate rate, so your footage goes really fast and includes any surprises as a musical number which is also very successful. Everything seasoned by a set of well chosen songs, which are perfectly coupled to the images.Ultimately, Clerks II is a film suitable for all those who follow the work of Kevin Smith and "geeks" in general. Is a small, nothing original, nothing ambitious film, but is welcomed and it is fun and entertaining while forgettable. A return to the origins.</body>
</review>
