<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Salvador" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A correct script and a good job of direction make, despite imperfection, 'Salvador Puig Antich' a story full of drama and film talent... good film.</summary>
	<body>It is not easy to make a film with political references: there is always the risk that much of the public (and critique) the rejected, either by having different or dislike ideology before it. And if it is also a time so close and so dark of our history, most likely the controversy. Therefore, best is abstract, work according to objective data but without forgetting the own criterion, i.e. 'make the movie that you want'. And it is this, for better or worse, what happens in 'Salvador'.Salvador Puig Antich was a young anarchist, Catalan, who lived (and 'fought') the end of the Franco dictatorship. Probably these four features on their person that mark the film: his youth, his fight against the power, the time, the Francoist repression and the fact of being Catalan.The complexity of history and of his person, is noticeable. But the script, despite their ups and downs, especially at the beginning of the film, finally get away: good reflection of the anti-catalanismo, as well as the harshness of the State security bodies. But the truth is that it is missing a greater depth in the childhood of the protagonist, in the why of his anarchism, therefore used, with greater or lesser effectiveness flashbacks (that rock music does not end curdling), are not enough.Despite knowing in advance the end of the story, the director Manuel Huerga, knows print interest, but above all, emotion. The death of Salvador is told of agonizing, cruel, real way: waiting becomes interminable, and inevitably feel some anxiety when it is about to be executed. The technical aspect, the soundtrack and the final Assembly, are, although without reaching clash, certainly improved: perhaps the director is looking for 'easy tear' in the latter part of the film and he notices too, its ideology and position before the historical period in which we find ourselves.However, is the performance of Daniel Brühl best film: while not exactly too chameleonic, German actor knows how to bring his characters, and this time would not be an exception. Tristán Ulloa and Leonardo Sbaraglia also made a good work, both well assisted by the family Puig Antich. so therefore a correct script and a good job of direction make, despite imperfection, 'Salvador Puig Antich' a story full of drama, talent and cine.buen film.</body>
</review>
