<review author="Javier Moreno" title="Salvador" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Huerga defines with splendor and dose of great film the attack on the freedom of a historical stage. A lesson of how Spanish quality filmmaking.</summary>
	<body>I am 26 years old, I was born in 1980 and my knowledge about the war Spanish civil and Franco's dictatorship are reduced to the fine strokes that my parents have been easing me in stages of historical concern, seasoned in a terrifying story that my deceased grandfather narrated me a summer in Malaga, their participation in the army against the "Reds" Franco as the called them during those three years. Told me everything that lived in Andalucia, front, even had access to a newspaper that wrote. 40 years were needed so that that individual squat, vileness in its purest form, no power, less time we needed to forget that many lived and that many are unaware. There is some phobia by patriotic cinema to recover memory historica of a dark age that belongs to us, that we should not forget, and I don't know the reasons, but it is when less disheartening that new generations born under the protection of freedom that promoted democracy, successively forget the events that led to a few to fight for their freedomagainst the oppression of a totalitarian and fascist state, which now all deny and which in turn almost all supported. Starting with those politicians that servian to the Franco regime and now hide after a political party and autoconsiderandose the most democratic State (we all know that Manuel Fraga was Franco's Minister). Outside that would be wonderful that those who defended 4 decades of terror, ask forgiveness, would be essential to our comatose Spanish film, be banana imitations of American by-products, and they devote to make cinema of quality, in which would accommodate recovery by the cinematographic language of those dark events that led the human condition until his most despicable shabbiness. Just for young people that we must build the future, must not forget what happened in Spain, nearby events in time, because at the end and all... 25 years, are not so many. And that is precisely what makes Manuel Huerga's Salvador, roll back to the last rales of the dictatorship, in which a young anarchist was sentenced to death by a State which wanted to demonstrate, following the murder of Carrero Blanco at the hands of ETA, that they still had power and after a trial full of shadows.We could argue about whether Puig Antich was a terrorist or a liberator, but this controversy was perfectly clarified in V for Vendetta, thesis that I support fully, because low specific circumstances in which the right of the inviduo of being, being ignored, the fight must be just to ensure that at no time were tread rights more universal of this society.Without the th effect of names like Almodovar or Perez Reverte, Huerga defines with splendor and dose of great film the attack on the freedom of a stage historical I repeat, never forget. Shot in a high definition format (something like what Michael Mann), surprisingly has a fast-paced rhythm and no lapses or in scenes apparently more inconsequential. Are the sequences supported by a really anthology soundtrack, with themes of Lluis Llach, Leonard Cohen or that sensational Knockin? do on heaven? s door de Bob Dylan. It rate accelerated, accurate and without blur the action at any time which we are witnessing, being perfectly placed on the screen anytime, without losing in impossible barullos that do not contribute anything to the implementation in scene. Surprisingly the film has two distinct parts, all that huge flashback detailing economically the beginnings of Puig Antich in the revolutionary movement, and the segment from which ETA kills Carrero Blanco and the young anarchist is aware of that executed it. And I say surprisingly because the fine line that separates both segments is so splendidly diluted at all times we have an amazing sense of continuity, with its consequent difficulty to elucidate on that point had just the first section of the film. Hit by the director, which supports with a dirty image and cold, the recreation of a completely different world that we know, and that brings not only proximity, but also a clear effect of realism rarely seen in these parts.The players are to feed, with the exception of Leonor Watling (that even this so more than correct) whose profile is not all defined, even the side such as Celso Bugallo and Ingrid Rubio they scratch at high altitude, but above them rise two names, Daniel Brühl and Leonardo Sbaraglia, which can already start preparing their speeches, because the Goya it not removed or God. In the case of the German actor, say that his interpretation is excelsa, is staying short, restrained throughout, repressed (and feels) the feelings that emerge in, with peak at the time of the execution, where its interpretative overwhelming lesson is get up and not stop applauding because he delights one of the moments more somber and emotional moments throughout the film (and can leave the audience in a sea of tears). In the case of the Argentine. I have no words, the few scenes shares with Brühl are anthology and brilliant, we perceive the evolution of the character, and every time the camera focusing on him at the moment more dramatic, causes a lump in the throat, of 10, especially when he attends the execution of Salvador (it not destripo nothing of the film, right?,) which rises in the 120 minutes of footage as one of the scenes most recent shocking Spanish filmloaded of a drama which forces to withdraw the look of the screen, and it is embarrassingly pathetic. Really, the last 30 minutes of the film would be by in its entirety, film quality and echo with the soul, even so, should not be denied that it is probably unnecessarily elongated.After both praise the film, would have to stress that I consider the black look of the film, the ambiguity that it is the authorities of the State (despite certain remnants of humanity in certain characters). In the movie the bad guys are bad, and except in specific cases, in any moment we perceive or a minimum of humanity, is to generalize too much IMHO. Admittedly, I do not know until that point the film is faithful to the facts, until that point is adulterated history, nor is it something that is very relevant when we are witnessing a lesson of how Spanish quality filmmaking.</body>
</review>
