<review author="Red Stovall" title="Skizo" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is so badly bad that one ends up taking her to joke, managing to have some fun at the expense of a bad film. Is this bad? Man, the laughter is never bad.</summary>
	<body>There are movies of bad which are ending sympathetic resulting because everything in them causes laughter. In this regard I will always remember a by-product entitled 'Dead Heat' starring Kiefer Sutherland and should enter into the annals of history as the funniest crappy one can see. His screenplay is so bad and is filled with so many inconsistencies and so utterly hilarious dialogue that one does not stop laughing throughout the film. And no, it's not a comedy. 'Skizo' could enter fully in this group of films that viewing is a really rewarding experience, but not because the movie is good, but on the contrary. The film is so badly bad that one ends up taking her to joke, managing to have some fun at the expense of a bad film. Is this bad? Man, the laughter is never bad.The film tells how Gorka, a young waiter of the bar of the Institute, wants to impress the girl he likes, a daughter of rich Dad would in principle not be established in a waiter (when this profession are those that bind more in this world). So happens the brilliant idea of hiring a type to her it scared a little, our protagonist appears at the right time to defend it, and so she is love of its hero. But the thing is twisted and the case ends up becoming a kidnapping with ransom demand included and stay in an old house in the middle of the forest in which is found a curious character.The film is intended to be a horror film with the figure of the typical psychokiller. Or at least what you intend to in its final part, that so far the film is absolutely nothing. The starting point is totally amazing and ridiculous, not to mention how it carried out a plan that is even more ridiculous. The characters hardly exist, that they are not drawn. We have a waiter with the face of lelo which does lack organizing everything organised to impress a girl that already from the beginning is clear that is interested in him. Okay, the script tries to show that he doesn't notice that key detail, but it is that you it's not credible at any time. Then there is a posh and stupid girl that wants to have it all. A pimp who can not speak. And finally a patient of peculiar schizophrenia, and hence comes the minitítulo of the movie, up in that have saved since there is an alarming shortage of means, although this past should not be hindrance to make a good movie. Unfortunately, it does not.One of the biggest poblemas film is the ridiculous character plays Oscar Jaenada, a badass cool which gives them ready. I don't know if the intention of the director was to be funny at times. I like to think that, but it is that almost all the phrases of this character are misplaced and ends up taunting. And if there was an intention of doing comedy with respect to this character, because we must not only not a gag that works. Everything about him is ridiculous and is passed to the embarrassed laughter. In addition Jaenada is completely exaggerated in its interpretation, and although the macarro talk about the way in which he speaks, is not credible and is like a pegote which is not consistent with the rest of the film but that accompanies us during a good time. And a film of these carcterísticas must first of all credibility.Regarding Eloy Azorín say that it is a dull very carefully, and Bea Segura is very cute but nothing more. In addition both Star some oniric moments, which are by far the worst of a film already on its horrible. The work of Jesus Ponce is limited to shoot four characters, and any more get out there and try to create a climate of terror or of anguish that does not exist. Schizophrenic character is simply a helper that does not fear nor gives nothing, and on which the film pofundiza not the least, and hence may have developed a good plot, not the case because the film does not know where to focus.A crappy fledged, and that making case of what I said at the beginning, can make you spend a good time if you take it to joke. If not, will be a real ordeal. In either of the two cases, the chance of a second viewing is something that anyone be will happen by the head.</body>
</review>
