<review author="Merce" title="Tan lejos, tan cerca" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To see the singer in a film or television screen, we dog a concert DVD? Of course, it is the logical possibility. But, and if I want to see the man behind the singer?</summary>
	<body>Lou Reed is? nuevayorkino, new New York, whatever the proper demonym, note that I've never been in New York, although Lou Reed Yes you listened. To see the singer in a film or television screen, we dog a concert DVD? Of course, it is the logical possibility. But, and if I want to see the man behind the singer?In this universe our fiction and reality, the appearance is confused with the costume, by mistake, because an actor is the person of truth, is liberated from the mask. But the talent to capture this brightness, not WINS of the night the day. I think that Wim Wenders dares to bare the actor, or singer in this particular case.Lou Reed, dressed in leather, as you walk any day or overnight any walking by a Berlin Street. Unlike reality, he walks led by a stage director. "It stops against a man lying on the ground, someone sunk, forgotten by everyone and by himself, Cassiel, the Angel fallen from the sky of Berlin.""Stand up", or "moods", says the singer to the Angel. Perhaps the firmament covering the German city, is the whole of the European sky. Do do covers the history, the French, the Spanish, the Italian? already seems increasingly absurd? differentiate the site? in any metro station one can find with fallen angels.The film is called so far so close. And every angle provides a different picture. It is waiting for an interpretation permanently. Why can't I be good I'd like to look in the mirror With a feeling of pride Instead of seeing to reflection Of failure a crime I don't want to turn away To make sure I can not see I don 't want to hold my ears When I think about meWhy can' t be good I. Once again, the talent of the German director power with the presence of large soundtracks, for example the "why not can't be good", "why can´t I be good".It's a walk up a video library and rent the film. It has already had its time in the film, everything has its time, as it reflects Daniella, the less human Angel, and everything has a beginning and end. Exclusive qualities of reality, intended.</body>
</review>
