<review author="JohnTrent" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A failed movie, a wrong attempt of wanting to give to Spanish Cinema? final overproduction? It falls short in its claims, empty as narration and did not finish the Viewer to reach.</summary>
	<body>Spanish film has been, generally speaking, a little (quite) useless to bring to the big screen stories who know how to lead the masses to the cinema. Come on, who can not do "blockbusters", i.e., those films made by Americans like hotcakes and premiere with a view to sweeping to victory at box office, giving to the public which, it is alleged, waiting and also releasing such films with advertising campaigns that carried the film to more people better. Removing (esperpénticos) cases like the two sequels to "Stream" or "Mortadelo y Filemon" in recent years, there has been what you might call a true "blockbuster" that has sufficed the doldrums Spanish market expectations. "Alatriste" was born as the film that was to change this, the first Spanish epic blockbuster that was able to cope (both at the box office and results) to American cinema (though not is has been able to ignore so that country star). Seen in the box office results we can say, more or less, that had been achieved. The rest is better to discuss it.I had too many expectations to this film, and the continuous negative criticism in reference to tedious of the proposal, did me presage that my doubts in this regard could be certain. I would have liked to say that "Alatriste" is a bad film, a truño of care, but is not. Certainly not are before a bad film? although it is not good. "Say"Alatriste"is a failed movie, a wrong attempt of wanting to give to Spanish film"the definitive over-production"which falls short on its claims, empty as narration and ending does not reach the Viewer, as much as its interpreters to work.""Alatriste" has two serious problems; the script and Assembly. From these two important elements for the development of a plot, the film starts to water as it progresses and newcomers at the end, one is left with the feeling of seeing a set of sequences chained one after another but which, on many occasions, they have no continuity and seem to be mounted, without much sense, in a random way. Clear that, by what I have read (and using logic) this may have to do with the fact of being based on several novels and, therefore, is intended to summarize all this in 145 minutes, which do not lead to both. From this, it is logical that the supposedly important characters appear and disappear from the plot without coming to story or don't know very well where we want to bring the narrative occasionally.A feeling that gave me to see "Alatriste" was something like this as the see a "Torrente" saga but in serious plan delivery. If I can now explain. Do not you you fijasteis of interpreters, more or less known of the Spanish landscape were left to see screen in supporting roles or anecdotal appearances? It is the same feeling of being attentive to say "Look, that's the kind of that series or looks, this is the actor that". It seems that everyone has embraced this project, even some have left out the final Assembly (case similar to what happened when Terrence Malick was to direct this wonder that is "The thin red line", with the difference of these what they wanted was to work with Malick and the "Alatriste" guess that wanted to join the bandwagon of the taquillazo).However, not everything is negative in "Alatriste", since then that not. Please I can say that, unless something time of boredom, I became more bearable of what was expected and that interpretations are all quite correct, without too much stress in any case, but are always credible, even the of Viggo Monterssen, which feared his American accent and, surprisingly, not noticeable to prison terms at any time. And, of course, the production design is wonderful, as well as the picture (sometimes truly worthy of prize, with these pictorial approaches), leaving to see the money they have been left in her.It shows that they have been able to sell this film, the figures are there, but still do not know how a large overproduction which is really round (or at least good) and you key in the armchair without being a failed attempt to give her reply to "so criticized" (the Academy of Spanish film, means) Americans.</body>
</review>
