<review author="Lara Croft" title="Transamerica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Road classic movie with characters well deep, geographically speaking, and grotesque in its description.</summary>
	<body>After the expectation caused by the excessive delay in its release, Transamerica is a stick in the wheel of good intentions. Anyone who is predisposed to recommend or mention it favourably and/or sugestionado will find the somewhat difficult task. It is true that the character who plays Felicity Huffman is a challenge of creation. Hence, I assume that the successful and award-winning star of Desperate housewives has chosen it. What is more, watching the credits one appreciates its increased commitment to read that her husband (William Macy) is the producer of the story. As well as many other times confessed that you let pass errors (or horrors) in pursuit of enjoy the story without much criticism, with Transamerica it was no easy task. My "good" vision is usually given to cases of a deep interest in history more than how it is told, or by his beloved characters. In this case no winks I could find anywhere. Concluding in a road movie classic with well deep, geographically speaking characters, and grotesque in its description. When Bree (Huffman) a transsexual to days of your desired change of sex her contact from jail a son who did not know, product of an adventure in the University, the visit to the operating room he gets. Her therapist must not you operate to resolve their conflicts with the paternity. A long way to Los Angeles, various byways in the route to visit his family included and logical friction with a teenager to know the status of Bree and their identity. I must admit that if this road movie would have been filmed anywhere else except United States my feeling to see her is had approached over the wishes of the debutant director Duncan Tucker than to exasperation that I finally felt. Perhaps either by seeing it too or for reasons personal but commonplaces and worn-out stereotypes of inland from United States managed to exasperate me.As a sign of study and characterization of character, Transamerica is a recommended product to view and surprise with the bigotry that Felicity Huffman plays Bree. Already a priori one presupposes it opposite. Now if you thought seeing her because her recommended Catherine Dlugi and that is more than enough then please do not: there is a nude male frontal! Without offending the intelligence of anyone, I am obliged to make this clarification given the amount of expressions of surprise and anger I heard in the room. Much unsuspecting Viewer in the end does nothing to disrespect us the rest.</body>
</review>
