<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="La joven del agua" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Regardless of whether the story can like it or not, and without ever noted, "The water boy" has more substance than many other tapes that are overblown</summary>
	<body>There are many directors who, after a success at the box office, are encasillados, both by critics and by the public. To M. Night Shyamalan has happened exactly that: after his second film, the famous 'The sixth sense', always it has waited him horror, suspense, twists inesperados.miedo. And this is probably the main cause of the ongoing attack since then, as many viewers and critics. 'The water young' is a Fable: a tale for adults. Anything terror, scares (do or maybe this Yes?).just a beautiful story, full of drama and details. A metaphor of life, human relationships, explained through a fiction that can still be somewhat absurd if analyzed coldly, does have a deep message. And this happens in all of his films: see beyond visual enjoyment that could give the film, consider how people, the deal between them have evolved. If 'The sixth sense' were overcome fears, and with 'The forest', una historia de amor, now 'The water boy' explores the part more personnel each, in their purposes.The interpretation of Paul Giamatti is excellent: this, previously eternal secondary, shows once more that he has talent to spare to star him only a film. His characterization is such, that becomes impossible to think of another actor for his character, and that requiring nor too difficult work, as not in Bryce Dallas Howard, compliant without too much clarity. The rest of the cast, everyone with its important role within the film, properly carry out their task, even Shyamalan, who was always reserved a small role in his films, acts more of what it is customary, and to tell the truth, not clashes.But if there is something that stands out in this movie is the beauty of certain passages that allows the soundtrack to the film. Priceless pair Shyamalan - j. Newton Howard: what there capacity to transmit, what waste of talent, allowing to be memorable cinematic moments, how I had already been in 'The forest'.Regardless of whether the story can like it or not, and without never highlight, 'La Joven del Agua' has more substance than many other tapes that are overblown: If you go to the cinema waiting for terror, forget about take you a good impression. Only see without prejudice, pending that you have a historia.y enjoy it. It is worth the trouble.</body>
</review>
