<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Stick it" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Prototypical sports film of overcoming and team that will vomit detractors and it encandilará to the fans.</summary>
	<body>One thing well, go ahead. This is the typical film that my medium Zucchini hates and that I finished with her nipples as darods of emotion. And I mean, I love sports movies of overcoming, in which a bunch of useless unmotivated arrive at something in life in the hands of a coach mamonazo who wears a tremendous heart under his rock shell. If this will we join that if there are two characters in a film and one shouts excited "Vaaaamos" and the other shouts him "Vaaaaaaamos" I have spasms in the marrow of ejaculation I have, why tell you that the movie I loved it but I am not impartial.The film is a girl of 17 years who likes urban risk sports, until that one day he shits and it is condemned to enter an Academy of gymnastics rítmíca. Here we learned that could be Olympic champion team, but he withdrew in the very final sinking to her companions. So he returned to find his ghosts of the past, with a trainer in decline which has become produce talents to produce lesions. Can you harness this girl and win something in your life again? My God, that emotion. Libeeeeeeeertaaaaaaad!What want tell you? The movie I loved, given that it is not at all typical of sports commented at the beginning. It has things that are fine, as the brutal criticism in competition systems, or voice-over comments that save us footage. The history is known and archiutilizada, but I like to see it. It shows a little hard which is the rhythm, although the largest is the end, Braveheart-style (but not blood). Great in which I was touched as a Magdalene. When it comes out on DVD I the crook to repeat even though you receive the mockery of my medium celery.In short, prototypical sports film of overcoming and team that will vomit detractors and it encandilará to the fans.</body>
</review>
