<review author="Natalia Eseverri" title="Separados" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good option to see a good story with great performances and not feel far removed from reality that represents.</summary>
	<body>While in Málaga and knowing that within an Anita more or less we will be living in our land, comes this beautiful task of finding floor and that you always have difficulties facing to seek funding, a floor in good condition and your taste and in the shortest possible time because you're noting that are certain these theories and the search will become worse than the Lost Ark adventure of Indiana Jones.Asi soaked magazines and multiple tips that always come in handy, we will get to the task and I will continue as the thing will. In principle, Málaga I like more than Fuengirola but must wait for what emerges, which of these things you never know, first to mourn the Bank to see that they give us and then investigate out there.On the other hand, the poster who heads this day is from the movie "Separated", a film that seems more a comedy by what you are trying to sell in the trailer but is actually a very accurate and realistic vision of what suffers a couple when after many years of coexistence are separated.Vince Vaughn as well as make a surprising interpretation, is one of the authors of a fantastic script in which minimum exaggerations that appear on a situation like that arises serve merely to raise a laugh in the spectator that comforting after many scenes of discussions and confessions that occur in many of the current couples can find us in reality. This mixture together with another fantastic interpretation of Jennifer Aniston (which I already dazzled in "The Good Girl" and again I am not disappointed) makes "Separated" a film with a long hook and that as the only downside would be the unnecessary use in times of a camera in hand that never ceases to continue the dialogue in the scene and the situation of the characters well.As curiosity, of high school you will see a Joey Laurie Adams, that is, lately, not lavished by the film after success with Kevin Smith in "Chasing a Amy" and Adam Sandler in "Big Daddy" and although it has a minimal role, it is appreciated that it has returned to the big screen. Jon Favreau is also amazing with some phrases rather than mythical.A good option to see a good story with great performances and not feel far removed from reality that represents. That Yes, laughter is guaranteed but in very small terms.</body>
</review>
