<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La noche de los girasoles" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the most interesting proposals Spanish film has given us this year.</summary>
	<body>It is curious how, quite often, the best of the year of the Spanish film we must find in little-publicized films or, even, of poor distribution. East has been the case of "The night of the sunflowers", the debut in the direction of feature films of Jorge Sánchez-Cabezudo.La official synopsis, which never should be much case, reads as follows: "Pedro and Esteban are two cavers arriving in a mountainous area of Avila to study the finding of a cave and determine if it has scientific interest." Gabi, the girlfriend of Esteban, which awaits accompanies them to the foot of the mountain. "But when the cavers come out of the cave, they find Gabi terrified?"Actually that is not the real starting point because the film consists of six chapters, each told from the point of view of one or several characters. The first two, precisely the most fragmented data, are those who will lead us to the point described by the synopsis. The problem is that this initial submission so fragmented is something trastabillada and not ends of being perfectly topped.But just now described by the synopsis, about half an hour from the beginning, the film catches the viewer and no longer him loose until the end. There the story, despite further composed of chapters, begins to move in a more linear fashion and offers us the most interesting moments of a plot that moves between film noir with enough thanks to a good script and sober Sánchez-Cabezudo address solvency and social portrait. In fact, at times reminded me to "Fargo", the great movie of the Coen.Ayuda brothers to the end result, and much, the cast of actors, among which I would highlight an always effective Carmelo Gómez (Esteban, a little grateful role), Vicente Romero as a peculiar civil guard and the couple formed by Cesareo Estebanez (Cecilio) and Walter Vidarte (Amos el loco) as part of one of the most beautiful and comic of the film stories: the feud between the only two inhabitants of an abandoned village.Celso Bugallo deserves special mention. His performance is a gift to the eye of the Viewer. BUGALLO is a big one; an actor who knows how to move before the camera and is able to express an incredible quantity of nuances with his eyes. I hope that Spanish Cinema will provide more opportunities to dazzle us with his talent because he amply deserves.Everything said above makes "The night of the sunflowers" one of the most interesting proposals Spanish film has given us this year.</body>
</review>
