<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Salvador" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>¡Que viva melodrama that manages to excite and transmit feelings to the Viewer, which take you a pinch and shakes it the bowels, that makes you feel, think, discuss, get angry, angry is and interested stakeholders in a period of our history.</summary>
	<body>A premonitory phrase concludes the latest film by Manuel Huerga. More or less he goes on to say that "the case of Salvador has been politicized to Spanish society, it is not just in this country".Too bad that now, newly released the film, while students have class and doing adequate time to drop by the film, the majority of viewers of "Salvador" already comb gray hair. Because it is a film that all this chavalería hedonistic and depoliticized should not see.Salvador Puig Antich was a young Catalan who, in the aftermath of the Franco regime, he moved on to direct action and took part in robbery armed to be convinced of that, as well as contribute to the precipitation of the Francoist regime, the intellectual vanguard of Spain should collaborate to bring a total and radical new State.But the dreams of Salvador were not met and after a chaotic detention, with dead of through, was locked in the model of Barcelona, tried by a military Tribunal and ratified the sentence by the Supreme, executed at dawn on March 2, 1974, through the sinister garrote vil.And all of that is what tells Manuel Huerga, through a flexible and dynamic style, but at the same time, discursive and inquisitive. Without judging them, the film tells us the reasons that led Salvador to go into hiding. Without fanfare, but with great effectiveness, it shows the robberies, arrests and those beatings that the greys gave the young demonstrators calling for democracy in the streets. Without squeaking, we are witnessing the stories of love and heartbreak of Salvador, with their girlfriends and their families.And, later, the prison. What is more criticizing of the film around the blogosphere is that Manuel Huerga has abused melodramatic elements to tell the final part of the story, including execution. I will say only that, coming last of Baeza Friday, Juanma told us to Sacai and to me that has stuck to March 2 of 74 as one of the most bitter days of his life, recalling the death of Salvador. SACAI had not heard, by no means the end of Puig Antich and while we passed box office, told me that I would have preferred not to know how the story ended before seeing the film, by that of intrigue, enigma and surprise.However, when the scaffold appears on screen, the eyes began to inundár him with tears and, while the executioner conformed the tack of death to the neck of Salvador before to turn the screw, I cried to mucus tendido.¿Melodrama? because living melodrama that manages to excite and transmit feelings to the Viewer, which take you a pinch and shakes it the bowels!that makes you feel, think, discuss, get angry, angry is and interested stakeholders in a period of our history that films like "Salvador", rescued from unfair oblivion in which have been mired!</body>
</review>
