<review author="Illaq" title="La noche de los girasoles" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>All development, as life itself, is based on chance: things come them the characters because, precisely at that time, they passed through there.</summary>
	<body>I have already said on other occasions that my "criticisms" are rather comments, although, of course, a commentary on a work necessarily implies a critique (therefore I assume the title). And it is that I find it difficult to criticize something that I do not know to do. On the other hand, I do not know for sure what the intention of the person in charge, which I have to bring me to work a little on tiptoe. Having said that, the first thing that occurred to me to go see the night of the sunflowers was ask me that I wanted to tell me Jorge Sánchez-Cabezudo in his first largomentraje. As well, something said: "the night of the sunflowers is a black film in a rural mountain setting but is also a film of characters." Half thriller, half drama, has the Peripeteia of eight main characters around a made dramatic will be complicating the history and which will be involving them successively to each of them. the film is structured in six chapters:?The man of motel?,?The cavers?,?The man in the road?,?The competent authority?,?The mad Amos? and?The Cayman? "." More than thriller, that something has, indeed, seems to me, rather, a drama, a drama which is inserted into the chances of everyday life, with a touch of black comedy, but comedy. Really, all development, as life itself, is based on chance: things come them the characters because, precisely at that time, they passed through there. Why is justified, in my view, fully, the choice of director for tables that have just engarzando. I do not see as a puzzle, but as a difference of perspective of the various actors, and the result I liked. The characters that inhabit 'The night of the sunflowers' are very different among themselves. The film begins with something that, apparently, "do not block": a commercial, in role of rapist (Manuel Morón), just his slaughter. and continues its path. By pure chance, just in the town in which the facts are developed. The Mayor of the town has called a speleologist, Esteban (Carmelo Gómez), that rule if a cave found in the village can be a good factor of tourist attraction. By chance, the another Caver who is going with this cannot do this and, by chance, is another individual, Peter (Mariano Alameda), and the girlfriend of the first, Gabi (Judith Diakhate), those who come. By chance, the commercial role of rapist will find Gabi in quite acceptable to play its role. She manages to escape in a bad way and find it her boyfriend and passenger in his vehicle, injured and in apparent shock. This is the beginning of the drama. Cecilio (Cesareo Estebanez), Amos (Walter Vidarte), the civil guard (Vicente Romero) and the Cape of Benmérita (Celso Bugallo) will be added to it. Everyone entering the drama by pure chance. Carmelo Gomez is simply masterful. No less masterful of Celso Bugallo, whose character grows as the film unfolds. Walter Vidarte dutifully plays a character that seems to me difficult: it is not easy to give verisimilitude to a person whose mental faculties are not very beyond without falling into the ridiculous. Cesáreo Estébanez gives the precise tone of hard man and law that is facing a monstrous absurdity. Personally, the performance of Judith Diakhte is discreet, but it seems to me that his character nor gives more. Not liked at all Mariano Alameda. It is true that the character is a both cantamañanas, but the Alameda version lacks even the credibility of such. Yes I liked, on the other hand, Vicente Romero, the guard that is corrupted to avoid having to provide explanations and, while looking for an airy exit. It seems excessive to me (but, obviously, so it seems to me) dedicated to the commercial rapist footage. I do not think an essential character, although Yes it is the trigger for the history. His performance is nothing to be discrete and not just see him in that role. As regards the aspects "negative", apart from those already specified in the interpretation, photography not has seemed too good. Perhaps more party places and people could have gotten. There is also, perhaps, an error in continuity (the vehicle which had to present the notable front coup, appears in a scene without a scratch). Also, the post-traumatic stress of Gabi is reduced to the immediate aftermath of the attempted rape. There is perhaps a somewhat "miraculous" improvement of the same. I think that most of the fans will enjoy this film.</body>
</review>
