<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Monster house" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Once all the characters have been presented and the adventure has begun, the Viewer is caught in a roller coaster of emotions and adventures which, if I forgive the cliché, will delight children and adults.</summary>
	<body>There was a time in my childhood in which came without fail to the movies everytime premiered a film produced by Steven Spielberg. At that time was very involved in the process of realization of the films he produced and was (and is) inevitable to see his "touch" in films and classics like "Poltergeist", "Gremlins", "The secret of the pyramid" or "The Goonies".I do not know the degree of implication that his most gifted disciple, Robert Zemeckis and Spielberg have in the production of "Monster House", the directorial debut of Gil Kenan, of which both are executive producers. What I have to thank you all for them is that, for an hour and half, he has returned to revive those happy days of my childhood.And I find no better way to describe the film that tell you that it has enough of the spirit of the Goonies, but with more touches of terror (at least more than I expected), with logical technical advances (the film was shot using motion capture) and adapted to the current time and the possibilities of animation cinema (amazing how move the camera throughout the film).Against it could be argued that the premise is somewhat simplistic (three boys who discover that one of the houses of the neighborhood is actually a monster ready to devour all those they come to him) and that it takes a tad more than necessary, for my taste, to enter fully in the field. But little else can be blamed.Because once all the characters have been presented and the adventure has begun, the Viewer is caught in a roller coaster of emotions and adventures which, if I forgive the cliché, they will do the delights of small and larger. It's nice to see some children's characters are not childish, that are funny without being graciosillos and inspiring tenderness while one laughs with them. Even the dubbing of the film is good (for a time).In summary, the tape is a joy for the senses, fun, entertaining, visually amazing and has a good script. If that is not good cinema, I like the hat.</body>
</review>
