<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="King Kong" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>And if this film is memorable for something, it's to make us believe the unbelievable, or at least come to understand the feelings are trying to convey</summary>
	<body>The morning after the night in which the return of the King won 11 Oscars, Peter Jackson was already preparing the pre-production of King Kong. The classical version of this film was seen by Jackson when he was 8 years old, and since then has been obsessed with the topic. Once achieved fame (and money) enough so the producer of turn him bend everything I like, he decided to make the film "in his way" (recall that years ago, before the Lord of the Rings trilogy, the project began but eventually cancelled for frustration of Jackson).The result was nothing more (and nothing less) than a real waste of digital technique, a considerably long (around 3 hours) movie in which action and feelings are mixed leaving a product, at least, memorable.The beginning of the film focuses on tell us how are the characters that appear in the film. We are in New York, at the time of the great depression, and we find Ann Darrow (Naomi Watts), an actress that is left without work, to which known by "chance" filmmaker Carl Denham (Jack Black), whom the producers intend to leave without continuing the filming of his movie. This offers you the role of the actress to Darrow once the initial abandoned the project, and both embark, with Jack Driscol (Adrien Brody), which is the screenwriter of the film of Denham, another actor and his team on a journey through the ocean to a hidden Island, uninhabited suspected. And all this, unbeknownst to him none of the passengers of the ship.Arriving at the island, Darrow is kidnapped by some natives, that offer as a sacrifice to a huge creature, our "Dear" gorilla Kong, no doubt, main protagonist of the film. All decide to go in search of Miss Darrow, especially Driscoll, who has started an affair. The problem is that our Kong is also in love with Miss Darrow. At first glance the argument is unlikely to us, however, Jackson manages to make us believe possible. The detail with which has done to Kong, a huge beast of more than 8 meters, is worthy of praise. The gestures, the looks. they manage to make us, as it progresses the film on the skin of the Gorilla: makes us (almost) believe that he is a person.The search for Miss Darrow occupies almost half of the film, and is full of action scenes, which really come to be heavy due to the continuous succession of bugs of all kinds (from centipede mutant dinosaurs, bats or huge slugs), and shortly after to the respite that leave. These are fights and more fights of all kinds between Kong struggling to save Darrow from the clutches of the dinosaurs, or the rest of characters against insects and other animals of enormous proportions. Without doubt, the movie could have been made shorter not including these scenes, than at a single point get tired.The interpretation of Naomi Watts is quite right, although it is not extraordinary. Jack Black, despite being known for comedy roles, manages to get into the role and fulfil its responsibilities as greedy and self-centered filmmaker who thinks only of money and the success of his film. Adrien Brody also get approved in its action, but neither is the role given to more showcasing of this great actor. The rest of characters not noted none above another, although the presence of Jamie Bell (Jimmy in the film), actor remembered for being the child of "Billy Elliot" deserves special mention. The rest of the cast is composed by Thomas Kretschmann (Captain Englehorn), Colin Hanks - son of Tom Hanks-(Preston), Kyle Chandler (Bruce Baxter) and Andy Serkis (who already played Gollum in the Lord of the rings) "interprets" again to Kong (in addition to the Cook of the ship).The recreation of the New York of the great depression is excellent, the scenes of action are very successful, although at times too much computer technique, as I have said before, tired. The picture is very good (could not be less having shot the film in New Zealand) and recall levels, and how to shoot that much to the Lord of the rings, because Peter Jackson has since put his signature on the screen with their magnificent "typical" displacements of camera. And if outside little, Jackson added a few touches of humor to the film, that far from being absurd, or extent, make more fun viewing.By the end I left Kong, who, as I mentioned earlier, is the true protagonist of the film. Not been few spectators at the end of the film have felt grief and sadness by the well-known unfortunate outcome for the gorilla. At the beginning it shows the beast, the animal, but over the course of the film, we get (and the work of Jackson has much to say in this) see their more human side, their sentimientos.y understand them, even put us in his place, and get to wanting to make him "who gets the girl". Such is the point to which arrives (again, within the implausible history), there are several scenes between the own Kong and Ann Darrow, great feeling.And if this film is memorable for something, it's to make us believe the unbelievable, or at least come to understand the feelings are trying to convey. And to achieve this on an animal that is nothing more than a huge Gorilla, was made by Peter Jackson.</body>
</review>
