<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Thai Dragon" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Much dislocation for so little East</summary>
	<body>Titus Chinchan will be turning into a critic of truth? With this film happened a very rare thing, given that instead of going for the flow of the aborregada mass that we are going to the movies in droves, I am against. Will this be the signal that need the frames for giving me the opportunity I hope? No, no, I see signs.The film is about a kid who lives in a community that is dedicated to pray and to live with elephants. They are part of a few warriors whose mission is to protect the legs of the elephant of the King (I think that was in antiquity), therefore raising elephants for the King. Total, in a contest of real elephants, steal them the elephant and a raised, what triggers in a bunch of hosts continued until that ends the film.World Society of physiotherapists warns that the vision of this film can cause contusions and dislocations to thousands. Therefore, the film itself is a little truño. The argument is not bad, a Thai chases from his native country to Sydney a couple of elephants, massacring everyone who is on its way. Does not seem bad idea is not original, but look good. But he has criminal things, like for example the photo collage. And is it intercalates photographic scenes that do not come to story in the middle of the fighting, which descentra much. The development is a little absurd as it is advancing the film to overflow on most Supreme stupidity in the climax. And fights have totally lost the freshness that showed in Ong Bak. Now there are only dislocations of all joints of the body. A couple of dislocations, whatever, but it is what happens throughout the film luxando Lords elbows, knees, ankles, etc. And the end, the apotheosis of the nonsense and the dislocations, especially the attack of the elephant, which is for stalks are.In short, dislocations to gogo for a film of medium hair he aimed high and it Star cochambrosamente on the floor.</body>
</review>
