<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Match point" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For any lover of cinema, it is imperative to see this film. And it is that, today, is missing real film, and this, undoubtedly, is</summary>
	<body>Do many times we've stopped thinking about how luck influencing things? How many situations of our lives have been marked by this random? How many times we wonder: what would have happened if..?? do and we realize how much the fate had (and has) to say in our lives?Woody Allen tells a story in which the fate and chance change the fate of the characters. Leave aside all kinds of prejudices, whether good or bad, because it is that the final result is what some have already branded, and quite rightly, masterpiece.Chris Wilton (Jonathan France-Meyers), an attractive former tennis player, decides to teach the sport at a London club, where he meets a young Englishman, Tom Hewett (Matthew Goode), which will begin a friendship that will lead to a relationship with the sister, Chloe Hewett (Emily Mortimer). But from the moment meets the girlfriend of his friend, Nola Rice, starring Scarlett Johansson, the life of Chris will be a storm of comings and goings, loving, jealousy, despair y.suerte.Woody reflects Allen, with a great talent, how the despair and anguish seize the protagonist, being immersed in two relationships: which has with Chloe (with which marriage), and that is with Nola. Two totally opposite relations: love on the one hand; and passion on the other.The protagonist, arrived a moment, debate between the stability that gives the relationship with his wife, and the obsession with her lover. In this sense, Allen makes us see how life is full of interests and how we move by them. The work of Allen is crucial in this regard, and only he is able to tell us magnificently how is the development of both relations with the circumstances, the coldness with which Wilton takes them, their lies and their tribulations. And above all, how it resolves eventually, when anxiety exceeds the protagonist and decides to put an end to one of its relations dramatically.Without doubt, the film will not leave indifferent anyone deserves special mention the grand finale, where luck returns to be decisive, and that Allen gets apuntillar to the Viewer. Although there are already several feature films in this style, the quality that gives the director is worthy of all praise. His way of filming allows us to comprehend the anguish that invades the protagonist, who is on the other hand, portrayed by a great Jonathan Rhys Meyers, who certainly makes his best role to date to perfectly reflect all situations that goes through the protagonist. A wise choice by Allen, who named him specifically, even coming to declare that: "since that I started to think about him for this role, already not could take me him head."Scarlett Johansson plays correctly Nola Rice, with that air of attractive and "Femme Fatale" with which seduces Wilton. The rest of the actors fulfils its task perfectly, "coming to exceed expectations" own Allen, such and as he himself recognizes; Although, however, are overwhelmed by the absolute role of Rhys-Meyers.Para any lover of cinema, it is imperative to see this film. And it is that, today, is missing real film, and this, undoubtedly, is.</body>
</review>
