<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Jarhead" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Although it is not probably his best film, yes it deserves a remarkable, especially for the quality of the picture and the perspective from which shows us the armed conflicts.</summary>
	<body>Each year, usually release an average of five war films. Soil dividarlas in those claiming to show us the cruel reality of the wars, and which focus on feelings and human reactions that give rise to those moments.Jarhead is a film about the war, but not of war. Those who love war films in his more typical concept, perhaps this is not your movie: there are no harsh and bloody battles or scenes and more loaded with action scenes. What us aims to show is actually what's Fund in all these soldiers, Lieutenant and one of the men (and women, although in this case there) that form part of any command or operation of war.The film is based on the story of Tony Swofford, a young American who, after his enlistment in the army and service in the Gulf war, arriving back home decided tell in their own words and from their own experiences, what the army inside: how is the life in the desert, how after months and months of isolation the human being changes to the point of going crazy.They are not the battles that take precedence, but every day: everything revolves around own loneliness and the coexistence with the rest of companions. Despite having an interesting startup, is missing more detail: us occurs the protagonist enters the barracks, without knowing any data about their past and seems insufficient representation of training which is submitted; something that may seem precipitate to the Viewer for the speed with which events happen. However, this also to be noted the total disconnection with the world and the radical change, and so helps in some moments of films such as "The metal jacket" and "Apocalypse Now", which makes certain references in order to demonstrate the vision of own soldiers of the war: lust for killing.With the arrival in the desert of Saudi Arabia to fight in the Gulf war, and especially with the passage of time, begins to see the real sense which has the film, that message that begins and ends the film:-this is my rifle, and although there are many, this is only mine. Many things you do in life, although he can love a woman, build a casa.siempre should have the rifle in my hands, and I will always be a "cabeza-bote".Sam Mendes us reflects from the eyes of Swofford (Jake Gyllenhaal) and his fellow snipers, all situations that daily living hundreds of men in the army: how different and at the same time equals the personas.las wars. How is assumed with the time that life is leaving behind, and once back home, no longer equal.It is another way of seeing the war. A real form, taking into account that it is based on real events. Lies, jealousy, thoughts, wishes, the temores.todo shows as realities that pass the soldiers. Despair, the paranoia, the locura.se become central in the life of each one of them, and we reflected, with doses of humor but also of cruelty, as when see the first burned corpses.The director takes advantage of one of the characters to add these critical touches (though certainly not delves into it) to the film: is how some raised the political reason why are there, the censorship to which are subjected, and as the senior commanders of battalions (commanders and generals) obviate them. It is not what matters: is the war and there is no objection nor possible criticism.But if there is something that stands out from the film is photography. Beautiful desert scenes. Striking of the rain of oil. Great work by Roger Deakins, with a few contrasts that may still seem confusing initially, we come to give one signal of the difference between the living and the dead. As for the soundtrack of the film, it is very good, with songs by Public Enemy, among others, and typically military compositions that manage to arouse in the viewer a "rush" in the previous battles scenes. or, at least, "alleged" battles.In the interpretations section, the prominence of Swofford makes we see the excellent work done by Jake Gyllenhaal (to who will soon see in Brokeback Mountain, and remembered by the general public for "The day of tomorrow"), to reflect how the character is winning in charisma and attitude with the stay in the desert and comes to show that this actor is one of the future starsIf not present, Hollywood. Also mention rather than positive for Jamie Foxx for his portrayal of Sergeant Sykes, and Peter Sarsgaard as partner of combat by Swofford.Sam Mendes, with his latest work, change log (American Beauty, road to perdition) to reflect the human side of the war. Although it is not probably his best film, yes it deserves a remarkable, especially for the quality of the picture and the perspective from which shows us the armed conflicts.</body>
</review>
