<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Hostel" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without doubt, the end result (and especially initial) is a pure garbage.</summary>
	<body>Everyone knows that in cinema abound bad films, especially in recent years. There is nothing worse than going to the cinema, with (or without) good expectations and find you a pure garbage. Because that exactly that, is Hostel.Producida by Tarantino, directed and written (why did?) by Eli Roth (Cabin Fever), Hostel is presented as a film gore, bloody, cruel. But in reality, we are dealing with a film with a screenplay unfortunate, really unfortunate, and a genuine engaña-bobos. Certainly what I happened to me how a film of no more than an hour and a half can have such home as slow, expendable, lacking in interest and empty? Two American students travelling on the European continent, an icelander they meet and go in search of sex, fast and easy. It is Europe as a world apart, chaotic, exemplified in Amsterdam, where there is no more life, from the point of view of the film or of those students, cannabis and the hookers.Rocambolescas chance, they end up in Slovakia, and after more nonsense and empty scenes, we reach what at first was believed to be the true story: a hostel where abducted tourists to kill pleasure.But no, not created those fans of gore, which here are good scenes of the genre. Just some things, which you can see perfectly in other films, much more successful (Saw and Saw II, say some). The end is perhaps less unfortunate of the film, and that it is totally predictable and lacking of sense (for those that have seen: there will be more terrible than the children scene?) (Really hilarious.).The cast, with absence of stars (which is appreciated), does not go beyond young people making young people. The address will pace that the movie, i.e. completely linear, does scares? typical. Leave the cinema with the feeling of scam is what happens when you see this film. A real hodgepodge, and perimitiéndome repeat myself, really awful script, found, insurance, away from any positive expectation created on the film.Sadly, I don't know what else to say about this movie. Only that, without a doubt, the end result (and especially initial) is a pure garbage.</body>
</review>
