<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="Munich" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Between confused and smothered by so much violence</summary>
	<body>Munich I liked very little throughout the film I spent her wanting to be at home watching American Idol auditions, imagine my boredom. I am fan of Steven Spielberg and I liked it until the war of the worlds (which many not forgave him), but it left me confused and smothered by so much violence where already not understood who he was Israeli, who Palestinian, where were the protagonists and end, a Grits of characters and stories.OK, the film was intended to be a complaint that barbarism only generates more barbaric and more barbaric and more to the infinitum. That, in the midst of so much confusion, comes to achieve. In this case the story from the murder of eleven israelíes-judíos athletes at the Munich Olympics in 1972, in charge of eleven árabes-palestinos, belonging to the Black September organization, intended to "mark a position" policy. The truth is that I myself do not know since when started this rivalry between ethnic different (?), but if I know that it has when finish. And in short, that was the main message of the film, which could well have saved a few deaths and minutes.The film raises various moral dilemmas for Israeli protagonist, Avner (Eric Bana, the Incredible Hulk, 2003): is due to his family or to their homeland? hero or killer? Justice or revenge? And the options that takes condemn it forever, because memories of so much violence will forever live in it despite the fact that at the beginning of the film, it was basically an average man: kind, devoted to his family and with a "boring" profession. Strangely chosen it to lead a secret anti-terrorist group, composed of a series of characters so inexperienced in the "art" of killing like him. Finally, who are the real terrorists?This servant he disliked Munich, however, could my tastes be very wrong, because the Academy has awarded five nominations: best PelículaMejor direction - Steven SpielbergMejor adapted screenplay - Tony Cushner and Eric RothMejor EdiciónMejor MúsicaLa performance by Eric Bana is in my opinion the only thing (or more) salvageable of the film and it has not been considered in the selection.I think that my review career en route to the Oscar isn't very promising. Usually the Academy and I tend to be quite agree, but this year it seems so far. We will continue to see.</body>
</review>
