<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El perro mongol" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will fill the heart of great lover of cinema that seeks, among so much trash so fire and artificial, a quiet trip to another world. Charged to the film. Go to remove and put in place a Cobblers.</summary>
	<body>He insists frequently to sign the film which lacks media oozing wit. This argument is not monopoly of the seventh art, but says it with more bombastic evidence. A study not left a paste him/her in a film if you suspect that the product can waver at the box office. Exceptions there are, of course.We are very acsotumbrados to see American films that smell money in each frame. This is not new. What it seems to me new is that a new European cinema of commercial approaches very similar to those who estilan in Hollywood there is. The film is art and business. Or even business and, occasionally, art.As I've been a lot of time without seeing art in recent films, I tend to distract me reviewing classics. Magnificent invention home cinema and dvd. He shadowed one in house conditions which would like to film, which is usually (in addition) contaminated annoying noise of vertiginous popcorn and febrile melodies of semitone in the nine row.This is a case because I just saw a movie which, in essence, is European, but also is Asian. It'll never compete at the box office with posh majors. Very rarely will be executives in the coffee talk at eleven, but it will fill the heart of great lover of cinema that seeks, among so much trash so fire and artificial, a quiet trip to another world.The film in question is called the mongol dog and more than film in the classic manner of the term, is a documentary that invites us to think otherwise. Not should the film do that occasionally? Trafficking in a girl (Nansal) who takes home a dog that has been found in a cave, a puppy, in reality. The father insisted not to host it as it imagines descended from wolves. Superstition occupies all the familiar imagery and the plot focuses on imposing the ancestral superfechería a sediment of reason.The conflict is not entirely Mongolian: is universal. It is entangled in the popular religiosity and take your Ribbon, vigorously, to the most intimate of human feelings: the belief that there is another world and that our soul does not die. In the absence of Christian heaven and right of the father, the Mongolian nomadic believes in reincarnation and arcane somehow suspected that when he died, his spirit will tour plants, trees, and small animals. until giving with a dog, and from there you can jump to a man.The most exciting of the mongol dog is its character of rare bird. Upon seeing her, we know that we are witnessing a unique fact, to the transition from one world to another. Mongolian nomads are doomed to look for the city, which is an extension of the Western City, food of dizziness, fevered by its moral dissipation, geared to grow at the expense of the man. And the alien to that death rattle Viewer is literally stunned by the strength of feeling that the film exhumes. To GLUGs. This is art. Mental detoxification. Opening an old language, but which we are not accustomed lately.I did not see the story of the weeping, the same mongol Director camel. I promise to go to the video store and catch her.Case is not (and that my video store is a jewel among the jewels for the fan film) I will come back home and put some Iranian movie of those lengthy levels and hypnotic music, when not absent. I sleep thinking that all the lights of my people becomes chrysanthemums.Charged to the film. It will be removed and put in place a Cobblers of any niñato posh with hook between the females amphetamine II and hormonadas.</body>
</review>
