<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not the best work of this director and also maintains the rhythm of?Heat? and?Collateral? but it is a very interesting proposal for the current film scene.</summary>
	<body>Michael Mann is responsible for bring to the big screen the adventures of Sonny Crockett and Ricardo Tubbs, who were already accustomed to seeing in the 1980s and that thanks to the Internet we can recover wherever we want. As well, the successful "Heat" and "Collateral" director presents the adventures of this pair of policemen, who unwittingly drink it or are involved in a drug trafficking network, which gives them the possibility (which do not hesitate to accept) deal with a much more important case that had a hand. So begins this new work by the creator of "The dilemma" somehow.This has had two major actors, one acting level and another at the box office level mainly, such as Jamie Foxx and Colin Farrell respectively. In fact the second has surprised me more, as demonstrated by the recent winner of an oscar (by Ray) of what is capable in many occasions and records. Well, both on-screen tuning is good, especially with their respective wives, and here comes one of the strengths of the film: Gong Li. This attractive actress presents a very interesting character, which Sonny Crockett will start to play and you know who is playing with fire.Continuous Mann with the visual style which we already presented in Collateral, alternating film cameras with high definition cameras, thus providing a distinct sense that somehow brings us closer to the action at time that the illumination level in these conditions, relieving him and streamlining a complicated shoot him surely much facilitated. The participation of the Spanish actor Luis Tosar is interesting. It seems that Mann likes the villains incarnate by actors in our country, as in the film starring Tom Cruise, and the own Foxx, resorted to the great Javier Bardem. It is a shame to not have seen "Corruption in Miami" in original version, because we had thus been able to enjoy and better capture their expressions, even more so when there are many in our language, is something to what we already are accustomed, even if everything is true, the role of Tosar nor has large dimensions, but still performs.The film begins with action and ends in the same way, and there in the "palomitera" action is no longer a very interesting product, in which the characters operate by these jungles, knowing all kinds of characters. Very good, although typical, scene of "gimmick" in which Colin mounts the show to one of the bad guys so that agree to work with them. An example of this saw him with the above-mentioned Bardem in "Word of mouth" applied to the casting. Returning to the film before us, Mann gives a lull in the action, showing us the developments faced the characters, motivated especially by the opposite sex, it is one of the engines of the film.It should be noted the final sequence, consisting of two main locations: the caravans and the port where is going to make the delivery. Mann, with pulse, positions us in the body of Ricardo Tubbs, and we share the feelings at a fact as has before and after weaker in the Sonny way, although they achieved one of the best excerpts from the film. Final "corruption in Miami" is not the best work of this director, and also maintains the rhythm of "Heat" and "Collateral" but nonetheless to be a very interesting proposal for the current film scene, although it is clear that for viewers more "palomiteros" who expect big bangs this version of "Miami Vice" can be decaffeinated.</body>
</review>
