<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Superman returns" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The return of this character was a huge challenge, required almost divine touch and intelligence but is very clear that the goal has been achieved.</summary>
	<body>When I heard again the main theme (improved by Williams, the original author) I encogí in the armchair and I escurrí my bum down, I needed some privacy as the tears of emotion not long in coming.Superman is the súperheroe most imitated, revered and loved by all. The return of this character was a huge challenge, required almost divine touch and intelligence but is very clear that the goal has been achieved.This director is headed by Bryan Singer and led a very successful X-Men, Star Trek: nemesis, King Kong (Peter Jackson exhausted by the filming had to ask for help because I needed sleep and Bryan was presented at New Zealand and helped him directing a good chunk of movie.)Go that if helped him), also this director by I see it everything that touches becomes gold that he has directed some episodes of HOUSE, the famous television series that is causing a furor at the moment in Spain. and most importantly, the actor. They could have chosen any other proposals (such as the guy from SmallVille) but I think they have successful flatly in his election. Has an identical to the defunct Reve Cristofer feel, it is an authentic Bonbon, a man with the face of man, a man of those who are close to you and you enter the cold sweats, is 27 years old (his meets is October 9), the is Brandon Routh.Este chico (as all the beauty) went without penalty or glory for several television seriesHere I leave a link on &gt; some sad appearances. Was clear that he had to get Bryan Singer to give him a decent role. This is one more than cases of actors sentenced to oblivion for having a good physical, have already spoken of the vulgarity and normalcy are latest fashion, and an actor of the truth of the old, like this guy, could only be where it is now, making Superman.El Coaching work is very good, because they have managed to make more credible to this Superman. Look in as he places the hands (come that this guy has received classical ballet tables) when you fly as he interacts with them, correct that are their positions, their attitude, it's perfect, it's a terrific job by the actor.Being Superman is not only be high and guapo.es gameplay more, must know the character, as it would move as he imagines as physically expresses a superhero, is complicated, there are very familiar with the world of comics and of course being very geek (that is why I never tire of saying JAMES CAMERON YO SOY LA ACTRESS perfect for your PROTAGONIAR new movie "alita")(", ANGEL of combat", choose whether you want to to any tontita that surely that does not know not who is the author of the famous comic Japanese. anyway) and this guy was was an absolute fan of Superman, well, there is the result, round film.I only have 2 things to say not as good as the previous ones, the first is that the date of the esrreno seems terrible, that they had left him for October or so they had ahead of may, but July. pathetic, hence failed marketing. The second, is the makeup, it is very bad, but by God, are noticeable translucent powders, make-up Superman.horrible.Bryan eyebrows: Farewell to the make-up team.The plot of the story and the screenplay seemed good. Furthermore this whole issue is intimately linked with the producer I gather to preferred, leave the open script to assume future sagas, because now that Superman has a son, now is when Superman is to bore.</body>
</review>
