<review author="Bloody Will" title="Mi super ex novia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He could have stayed even as a film of infantil-familiar Court, but the sex scene wild revientamuros become prohibitive and uncomfortable for children.</summary>
	<body>If the director Ivan Reitman tried to become funny the phenomenon of superheroes on screen, we could say that it has not come to pass. "Ghostbusters" and "Kindergarten COP" gave him success. With "Junior" or "Evolution" it proved the bitterness of the box office failure and with it, as well I reported last week, it has been found with the thud of the year.It is not for less. This crossing of "Superman" with "Fatal attraction" is predictable from start to finish, and could not assure you that you are going to laugh at not being able, because this comedy is so easy to digest and forget. Reitman attends what more result you gave with "Ghostbusters": comedy with special effects, however lacks something basic: actors and history that carry it forward.The way in which Matt (Luke Wilson) and G-Girl (Uma Thurman) are known has no feet or head, is rather absurd. As their relationship develops it is even more absurd, and really the Thurman not becomes crazy unless they cut with it, so the reason to break the boy's are really pathetic. Finally, all forced to reach that hopes to the Viewer: a jealous and spiteful superheroine with a simple mortal, which moreover Pyrrha by another (Anna Faris).A from there perhaps starts the most interesting and funny to say the least, of the film, but ends up diluting in something more convoluted with a lex luthor of all one hundred and even more, a fitting end for a Superman of all one hundred.Uma Thurman was the only one who could save this film. Draws a new Glenn Close with that nasty giving who has been musa Tarantino. But of course, if you put it to Luke Wilson, which has the same expressive collection of vases of Planeta DeAgostini, nothing can be done. This actor is horrible in every film that participates, and begins to be a cheap solution when you can not hire Owen Wilson. Anna Faris is your online: flat encephalogram.What you want I say more, this is not "Alatriste" or "Memento". It could have stayed even as a movie infantil-familiar Court, but the sex scene wild revientamuros become prohibitive and uncomfortable for the menores.¿Es to recommend?, well, as they used to say in a comment of "Alatriste", in the film is cool, there are popcorn, and for whom it is autonomous will make you to forget the day October 20 must be palmar VAT. If you go with the idea of paying off the ticket price, I assure you that in two months will be in your cashier of DVDs for rent.</body>
</review>
