<review author="Bloody Will" title="La increíble historia de Caperucita Roja" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do it is equally funny that?Shrek? or perhaps even higher. I do not remember that the Green OGRE and company make me laugh both as whole group of characters who in this film share dialogs in a distributed manner.</summary>
	<body>That nobody be fooled with the name. This is the best adult animation film. Her will understand children and even is so it will be good, but not so children will attend a series of dialog boxes that are as hilarious as intelligent. Nothing of cheap jokes. This appearance of CGI animation of all one hundred is supplied with an idea so original and well resolved that should shake to their competitors. do Acusarías to the tooth Pérez of extortion and housebreaking?. So here we have a C.S.I. mounted after the famous scene of "grandmother, that larger teeth have". Of course, in this story all are suspects: Red Riding Hood, Wolf, the grandmother and up the woodcutter passing by. Technically, in animation, the film is light years from any of Pixar, that is quite clear, but the argument and its screenplay leave behind most of products pixelated which have been released without ton or over these years.The attempted robbery of the grandmother recipes as main offence leads to the not so sweet hood to tell the story from a perspective that you had never imagined, not counting that the Wolf has a paid profession, grandmother far from being entered into a senior citizens residence, and the woodsman has more artistic aspirations that remain all his life throwing down trees. The plot contrivance to get sweets monopilo must be resuleta by a Commissioner of bulging eyes and some policemen of pig aspect (cogeis metaphor?). But not only the main protagonists lives this film. When he appears in action the goat and his banjo you are going from, without forgetting the squirrel oscuras and a rabbit something chinchón.With clear references to "Matrix", "Kill Bill" and the Chevy Chase Fletch detective series, the film relies on continuous flashbacks that Iran comprising as you will tell the same story from all those involved. Tell you more about the film would be muss you several surprises that must not be disclosed. I could tell you that it is just as fun as "Shrek" but it might be even higher. I do not remember that the Green OGRE and company make me laugh both as whole group of characters who in this film share dialogs in a distributed manner.In short, you can see with a child in another seat, or no child, because her you will enjoy in the same way. In a word: brilliant. This is the only film that I anxiously hope a sequel.</body>
</review>
