<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Una llama en mi corazón" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It seems a reality show bad that a director ex officio, but genius, has become a film for the benefit of his ego. It is not film. It is a hoax claiming injunction with the fashion of a modern European cinema.</summary>
	<body>Love, such as loneliness, as fear, has its intimate, undisclosed calligraphy. In A flame in my heart, one attends the absolute sacralization of the impudor of methodical pornography of the fugal soul of his wisdom. Tanner, the French director, the provocateur of this depressing spectacle of the human heart, never has been characterized by a consistent filmography. Usually fall into the trance of love of his muses (Mezyeres is the last, but there were others) and like good French worship, dress of intellectual curls bald evidence of his film romo.A flame in my heart is pure pseudocultural formalism: a long dramatic tic is a spiral of emotions that, in free fall, vie to avoid spreading the burst viscera on the sidewalk. It seems a reality show bad that a director ex officio, but genius, has become a film for the benefit of his ego. Above, the leading lady is not neither actress: it has an actress, confined to be carried away, to impose a few gestures without dramatic Foundation to exhibit a body broken by pain on screen. The body perhaps actress and we are prevailing, suddenly, with a new film language. I do not know: I have finished noqueado in the viewing of the tape.His black and white burnt, it is not at all unpleasant, it can already lead to evidence of where the shots go in this fabric of lost worlds and wells with predictable funds. There is no (I think) in this type of average movies. Or we adhere to it with passion and engolosinamiento of lover or repudiate them viciously and warned his ineffectiveness as a vehicle for entertainment. Because it is not film. It is a hoax claiming injunction with the fashion of a modern European cinema, with hints of cult, which just rummages in the rotten and saca of the spectator, between the drowsiness and disgust, hastío.Because this is a gem for taste when tiredness that produces the American film abochorne us taste and want, at midnight, to go to bed with the stomach well raised strong feelings. Ah, the gentle reader will be asked to what comes (being bad) my dedication, the minutes that you ofrendado to see and then write about it.It is that I saw, years ago, Jonah who will be 25 in the year 2000. And I liked it. They were times of University and had then one eye accomplice and innocence to baskets. Any night her restores the 2. With subtitles.</body>
</review>
