<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="Mi super ex novia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a masterpiece nor is going to change lives. But it is a comedy and get what should get the comedies: making people laugh from start to finish.</summary>
	<body>Does Uma Thurman and Luke Wilson star?My super girlfriend? (?(My_super_ex-girlfriend'), a film by Ivan Reitman, one of the Kings of the eighties film comedy with titles like?Ghostbusters? or 'Meatball'. It is curiosísimo that this film premiered on our screens yesterday, exactly the same day that came out?Thanks for smoking? (?(Do Thank you for Smoking?), directed by the son of Ivan, Jason Reitman. Matt Saunders thinks that he has finally found the perfect bride, beautiful Jenny Johnson, who happens to be the superhero girl G. When Jenny proves to be too possessive and a little crazy, Matt does leave the relationship? But how to break with a woman who can fly, lift cars and make holes in the steel with its thermal vision?It was time that we could laugh with something of all this what called comedy, since this genus name is used for everything, even when products do not have even a funny moment in throughout his life. I get very heavy citing examples, but it is that they are so fresh, I can not help:?Do separate?,?The friends of the groom?, etc. With?My super girlfriend? not so. There here is very funny and very abundant points. If we evaluate with a fonómetro we could verify that the laughs are very high, especially in a particular scene. We also see that there is a very respectable amount of moments that make us laugh. But maybe we could check is that they distributed evenly until the end, because until now, comedies that could do to laugh and much during a short period of time, when they had already exploited the outrageous premise, turned in conventional films or even geeks and here the examples are not so fresh but clear:?Like God? do and others of that style or? what think women?.? This default for many movies, not only due to the sentimental message, also occurs because the writers start from an idea good, even great, but who have not can be exploited during one hour and three quarters. Rather than learn to flip that continue to make grace after exhausted, so exploit what they can and not get more ideas. In?My super girlfriend? they have been able to find humor both to the moments in which go out together, moments after cutting and even a reconciliation. The film is well shot, has a fast-paced rhythm. Reitman far exceeds the quality of his films of the 1990s, and manages to renew his style, which had only given good sample in the 1980s. There are directors, such as Ridley Scott, with those who can still smell lacquer of the 1980s in its filters and levels. Although Ivan Reitman made their major works in that decade?My super girlfriend? He has been fresh, youthful, contemporary. Yes saves then what that spirit to which I have already referred by which everything takes it a joke, which have no problem to do something fun from beginning to end. This film does not need to stop doing humor to show the ñoño message. A true romantic comedy must know combine the sentimental part with the fun, no turns: I now do jokes, now put the part of love. Predominates here comic, but love is an essential part of the plot and is not involved with shoehorn, or consists in that that makes the protagonist change in way of being and thinking for the worse. The actors are wonderful in their roles. Physically they are very appropriate and, in addition, interpreted of Vice. Luke Wilson is perhaps that stands out. We have already spoken this actor, comparing it to his brother, the un-poco - more-famous Owen. Luke, without being handsome, has a more normal face, so it can do roles of galán's comedy, which is where he always is. Fortunately, it also has a tremendous comic vis and achieved, on the one hand, to believe us that it overcomes the impressive Uma Thurman and on the other, we laugh with each of their gestures, while it conveys what he feels and what he thinks. UMA also plays a very suitable, the impressive G girl, who flies with miniskirt saving the city. The moments where you have to be scary, gives it and when it has to impose, imposes. Do do even manages to impersonate lovely girl looking for? as the friend of Luke describes? Librarian demure on the outside and ready to give a tumble on the inside. And that I speak of him, Rainn Wilson is the best in the side. Not is the brother of Luke and Owen (they have another, but is called Andrew). Her role is the friendly rogue of the protagonist, which boasts what League and encourages his colleague to also do so. Anna Faris, actress known by the?Scary Movies? It is also well in his character, is suitable and has much capacity for comedy. Wanda Sykes, who also came in?Clerks II? It has a tertiary role, but funny. And the supervillain Eddie Izzard, although it is not as good as the previous ones, is also very funny. Even dubbing is good. In any cinema in Madrid they put v. or, so I had to settle for the dubbed version, but I have to say that I not pulled from the movie. Another merit, I guess it will be a responsibility divided between the script, direction and performances, is both you be credible that Luke likes Uma as that, very shortly thereafter already find too crazy for him. Many times, when you want to a character change of opinion with respect to another, what they do is turn the second and show a lot of aspects which were not seen and that even contradict with what had appreciated until then, which is not only cheating, but it also prevents the identification. Here is achieved that it should move from fascination to rejection without problem. Even in a great film like?Do Manhattan?, Woody Allen, I find hard to believe me that he leave like Diane Keaton. Do if she enters a little inside the type of girl who represents Uma Thurman, still more clear examples would be the of?The beast of my girl?,?Yeopgijeogin geunyeo? (?(Do my Sassy Girl?)?Something wild?, etc. The theme of superheroes also needed to dust a little off their excessive importance and dealt with jokingly. ?The fantastic four? is it approached the Institute comedy, but not laughed so much of the subject like?My super girlfriend?. And also it was box thing that had to put the subject of sex in these movies. Who has not asked once what result given the superpowers in bed, especially since the Bandon Routh and Hugh Jackman, among others, performing for gifted beings? Here you can see what happens. And just after that demonstration when the best joke of the film takes place. Brilliant parody to the religious and unbearable moment of?Does did do Superman Returns? film that removing those things, I like?, it is said, that in which he is flying over the city and says that everyone ask for shouting a Savior. Here, when Uma Thurman takes Luke Wilson to fly over buildings, it hides other intentions. Also laughs a little Superman films with the issue of hidden identity. You must be blind and deaf to not realize that Clark is Superman. In?My super girlfriend? its appearance changes considerably more, but even she prevents him look at her when she rescues dressed as a superhero, as he knows that even the dumbest would realize. It is very funny about that superheroines costumes consist, not in more comfortable to fly robes or layer, but simply in sexy outfits more sexy than those who took jobs previously. If analyze well superheroes, in reality the go dressed in LaTeX is by mark, since they need nor the layers or not earn so much aerodinamismo with the leotards. But if fit, which conform. For me, there is no problem. I do not know if you know the term "Jump the shark". Applies to the moments in which the television series become delusional at all because they no longer know what else to do with their plots. At that time, you get something absurd and thereafter, the quality of the series lapses at all, so, either lost interest or it acquires a kitsch interest. For example, if in a SOAP Opera given by taking out aliens (do and this has happened, at least I remember of?)(Do the Colby?). He is called "Jump the Shark" because in the earlier series 'Happy Days' a character jumped over a shark when he was water skiing. In 'My super girlfriend' they do it literally. What better to declare openly that you are drawing a shark that nobody accused you of doing so? In the series?Does lost? (?(Lost?) also there is a moment in which "jump the shark". This joke metalinguistic alone in a scene already, hilarious, is another of the highlights of the film. If we already profound, even could be sublecturas in this film. The fear we feel people about relationships, to retaliation from the abandoned the commitment ex-amantes, etc? It could represent so magnified in this ex-girlfriend which is has powers, superoído and Super-speed. It is saying, you know exactly where you are, what you say, what do you do? and you can get in a heartbeat to where you find to destroy you. Even with this metaphor, the movie does not load to women nor comes to call them castradoras. Nor (the end of this sentence is A light SPOILER) resolved leaving the protagonist with a demure, sweet and weak girl as he sees in many film that is the perfect woman. (HERE NO LONGER THERE ARE SPOILERS) For an overview, I conclude by saying that this film is a masterpiece not going to change lives. But it is a comedy and get what should get the comedies: making people laugh from start to finish. It is often assumed to do comedy is very easy and therefore is the most reviled genus, but already say authors legendary and masters of the genre that is the hardest thing to do. And that is why it is necessary to appreciate products that have. So only with that, because it is much more advisable than those others I mentioned above. Maybe if everything that we sell as comedy they were comic things, because I would be 'My super girlfriend' and I think it is simply another more, another comedy that laugh and have a good time. But of course, after all the films that carry the label of comedy and then do not laugh even once, get one like this and it is a tremendous breath of fresh air. Is that we are, salts of euphoric cinema / or and happy. And there are times that is all what can ask you a film afternoon. If what you want is another result, tilts you for another film. But if you want to laugh, this is what to do. </body>
</review>
