<review author="Torbe" title="Spiderman 2" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Putting to give birth a movie that has nothing</summary>
	<body>It is a pain this film. I'm already going with fear. Second first by long queues, see who you get to the side, and third by the scripts each time more gilipollescos is curran. Film is falling sharply, as TV, as the publishing world, where any gualtrapa that only leave on TV you "write" a "book". Spider-man is to take the Director and give four Ostia. Do but beside the point that gets you so much philosophy of healing in the mouth of many characters in the movie?, we want to let a little live?. I am going to the cinema to see Spider-man as trashing bad guys, not to enmierdarme in their private lives and their psychological problems. Suda me her girlfriend of Spider-man, that lerda, with face of pastora de los montes of Usurbil think he fucks not never, and it is a pretentious which tells at the end that will save lives, and he rides a chicken because it has not been able to go see his shit play. But what kind of character is this? Menuda subnor? And the old? A menace that not to give consejillos in plan Reverend Smith, go to give advice to your fucking old Woodcock! Put the TV and leave me in peace, heavy. And Spider-man, often tontolava, a superhero that does not have a fucking hard. Learn from Batman, that this forrao in the batcomputer becoming straw without doing anything to spying on the neighbors with camcorders is that already get me to the eggs, be devoted to catch bad guys and instead it is not capable of doing that they seized the House to his aunt May. Anda and give you ass, mediocre. Beam as octopus, steals there something and leave us in peace, llorona, which do not stop to give the pain in the ass the movie with that face of mico you, hijoputa. It is revealing that not leave the cloth of spider, that in my town is called gatillazo, and is that it is normal, it is a fucking freak, a lerdo. It is someone only when Gets the mask of Spider-man. It is as many people in real life, which is not nobody but gets a remarkable thing in the movie "mask" is the action that is of puta madre, and when Spider comes and goes by the buildings flying. And bumps of humor, there are several, primarily starring the Editor of the newspaper, a character that perfectly represents the typical cabronazo agarrao not giving anything for nothing. Brilliant the good observer vera that the movie alterna action-relationship. Fucking great action, come paqui palla, however when it gets the absurd and bland relationship between the pastor and the mico, the movie falls limits up unexpected. Dan embarrassed the two, as they can be so asshole? Is it that they do not know the meaning of the word blowjob or Castilian pajon? Not, in these movies not sex they get nowhere near, are all about bows and give ass all the time, but clear, guys want to reach everyone, and they understand that children have no sexuality, when in the 1980s, when many of us we went to the cinema or TV saw, saw things more jevys, or what the helltoday itself, any put TV at 6 pm and you will see a lot of poison incredible beings anonymous talking about how he fucked with this or the other. I will not talk about this movie, sorry for this desproposito. It pisses me off having paid for such mierdon, the next time down me the internet and pay movie supu. They give to Spider-man, the idol of my youth in the comics, is going to see Spider-Man 3 his cousin of Atapuerca...</body>
</review>
