<review author="Red Stovall" title="Gracias por fumar" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Correct, with enviable technical quality, but not wet all what make us see.</summary>
	<body>We live in times in which the power of the word is everything. Continuously bombard us with lies that we believe because we have been told them well or they have simply been kind while they told them us using beautiful words. Demagoguery is one of the greatest evils of our time, because of it we are able to justify murder, rape or invasions to a country. A perfect speaker is the King of the world in front of a camera saying great phrases and putting thoughts into the heads of the stupid who do not know or want to think for themselves. Of course, that there are good speakers and other bad, those who say the truth and those who lie. All this could be the item dealing with 'Thank you for smoking' but framed within the tobacco industry and its relationship with the people, potential consumers and those who are not. Is it good to smoke? It is bad for the health? I will leave my son to smoke? I sue the tobacco company if I discover I have to bring my life cancer smoking? do I see you a thousand times 'The dilemma' to know what I have to do? On these stupid questions, except the latter course, it this film with satirical touches.Nick Naylor represents the tobacco industry in the USA in the face to the public. He tries to inform the society of the outcome of the studies on tobacco by large companies. His work is not lying, but disguise the truth, filter it diverting attention, something that always has been given very good coming out triumphant of all the problems that have been involved. One day he meets a journalist who wants to do an interview to find out his secret weapons. At the same time, an important Senator intends to present a law requiring tobacco companies to put a label on cigarette packets that puts the word "poison".The film has been directed by Jason Reitman, son of one of the most infumables directors of the Decade of the 1980s, Ivan Reitman, which has few notable films. It is still early to tell, but it gives the impression that the son has not inherited the talent of Fr. Fortunately. Reitman does demonstrate a use of the pace really exemplary. The film does not have even a downturn and progresses as quickly as the protagonist speaks. And it is that we are talking about a movie in which the word is everything. The central character would be lost and would not be as interesting if not a master in the use of the words. And while it is the typical charlatan is presented to us in a way that we like and we care about their personal problems, because at the end and the place is one person like other anyone. And behold one of the successes of the film, although many will say that no, a character we should hate for what makes us like. The film achieves the same as his main character, he convinces people that the tobacco is not bad. The film convinces us that he is a good person, a leader, someone who we need.' thank you for smoking ' is full of familiar faces, more or less famous actors which do all good work, especially Aaron Eckhart, absolute protagonist and perfectly made up a character who knows what to say at all times always using the right words even if you know in advance what defends is wrong. Maria Bello in a very short role is also very well, like the other characters, some of the most curious, as the agent of Hollywood portrayed by a funny Rob Lowe (who would say that this actor could do something good); William H. Macy as a Senator obsessed to destroy the reputation of Nick, Katie Holmes as a reporter that bundles with Nick would be the only weak point of all the cast, and is that Mrs Cruise has never been very well endowed for interpretation; Robert Duvall showing all their experience into a character a tad missed, Cameron Bright as the son of the protagonist and first time this actor not interpret a rare child, Sam Elliott makes the cowboy that appeared in an advertisement for tobacco ill with cancer, and which indeed is the all think, but with the name changed and the brand of tobacco also, and j. k. Simmons who is splendid as the head of the protagonist.But the film is not much less perfect. Despite his excellent pace, its well-kept phrases in the script and his almost successful cast, the film stays halfway in its intention of being different, daring and scathing. It could you have been much stronger than it is, having gotten the finger in the wound to the bottom and not staying on the surface a little digging. On the other hand, the story is somewhat predictable in its final part and some topics that make you lean towards the usual: character with dubious profession but with incredible talent to do so and to question their moral principles. I think that the film should not have followed this path and Yes more inquire into the part of the story shows us what is a tobacco company capable to defend his business.A correct movie, with enviable technical quality, but not wet all what make us see. Still, it is an interesting and very entertaining product within the current film scene in the USA, and of course makes us have the watchful eyes on its director, I hope not engaged in antics that made his father, who by the way has released among us 'My Super girlfriend', which if approached me to see it will be only to see Uma Thurman.</body>
</review>
