<review author="JohnTrent" title="La máquina de bailar" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not, at all, a good movie and I do not think that it intends. Do that, is certainly atypical comedy within the so-called? patriotic humor?, and that is welcome.</summary>
	<body>You have never gone through some recreational and you have seen a handful of people watching (some laughing, others flipping, others without knowing very well what happens) to poor characters dancing in a machine and putting face to something as well as a dance contest winners? Well, this here is thing, as I have already said, a few guys, but back in the country of the rising sun appears to be a real phenomenon which has up among their ranks experts and competitions. "Dancing machine" it comes to tell all this.It is curious as Spanish cinema has evolved in recent years. The almost unanimous trend from the pathetic Academy has been put less than green film is done in United States and prevail above that the quality of the Spanish without giving reason to believe them. As well, seeing the latest proposals of the Spanish film, even to speak about things very patriotic "Alatriste" or "Salvador", you notice a tangible approach towards, precisely, the American film to box office.We will, that criticize much to not get anything clear and at the end, try to imitate the criticized enemy. But ojo! view "Alatriste" has almost nothing to do with movies such as "Gladiator", "Kingdom of heaven" or "Trojan", but it is a kind of "The dog in the Manger" with two or three pseudo battles that stays halfway all kinds of claims, both artistic and show (and the three films that I have appointed is not that they are peliculones precisely)(, but are even superior to the film directed by Diaz Yanes) and the most controversial of all, do so if they get both with American cinema, hire to interpreters Americans to star in his films with eagerness to make box office?. "Because, in reality, they are the same that they or at least they try and want that their cinema also reaches the masses.""Dancing machine" is another case of these comment, although I doubt that its director be has sworn to American cinema, moreover, he is a declared fan of teenage comedies made in that country. Therefore, it is not uncommon to see many of the clichés of this type of film, and even more, a lot of cinematic cinéfagas references to mythical classics from the seventies and eighties that much like in this blog as "Rocky", "Karate Kid", "Battle Royale" or other more dubious as "Flashdance" in this film. All seasoned with a style close to the of the Farrelly brothers, with its eternal losers who are not so, these "pringá you" that end up doing great things (Santiago Segura is a clear example of this, a character very close to which be construed Whoddy Harrelson "Go couple of idiots").But, beware, "Dancing machine" is not the typical Spanish comedy type "Torrente" many just wait to see to safe between its protagonists. Nothing of the sort. In reality, are facing a rather bittersweet film, which alternates the madder surrealism (this giant snake which ends by exploiting, "flash back" which recalls the accident of the Segura dance partner when he was young) with degrading and sad moments (the successive times in which the villain role, played by Corbacho, strip full of shit W.C the ring so look it safe or lonely coexistence of this last)(, with dolls released by way of family).It is not a film of laughter, but smiles. It is not a humor crazy, but something strange. Probably for these reasons, the film won't work too well at the box office (although even this to be seen), by far, without being much, than rather than nonsense as the third installment of "Torrent" or other comedietas starring Santiago Segura lately as "The amazing world of Borja Mari and Pocholo" or "Isi Disi". It is possible that the proposal is risky in terms of expectations can arouse in some sector of the audience, but it is a risk that seems assumed by those responsible and by the same safe, away from his typical roles.After this Oscar Aibar cameras, a few years ago directed the interesting "flying saucers", also starring Jordi Vilches (that, no mistake, he is the protagonist of film over Segura, and this may be another factor in that the public did not react as expected) and a film that I pass quite unnoticed entitled "Quagmire", who paints really surrealWhat seems to be a constant in his career.The most notable of this proposal lies in the magnificent picture of Mario Montero, that has nothing to envy to greater invoice films, giving the impression that the results at the technical level in the Spanish film do not have to see many times with the spent budget or available media, but with an average budget can do things that are similar to the"return, American cinema.""Dancing machine" is not for nothing, a good movie. Nor do I believe that he intends. We are, that if, before a certainly atypical comedy within the so-called "patriotic humor", and that is to be welcomed. A film which speaks of pathos from an optimistic and even heroic side that many of these "geeks" arcades or those who put the ears of Captain Spock in each new release in the series "Star Campiña" will show reflected, although it is not very well defined if it is to make fun of them or to give them a tribute.</body>
</review>
