<review author="Silvia Giner" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is very well directed, is very faithful to the book which I thank, barely there are at least a couple of differences that I warned...</summary>
	<body>For anyone who reads the book, see the movie can be tedious. In addition to knowing what is going to happen is a film of these that my friend Katie called "Insultantes for the Viewer" that explains each scene to a level of detail that one just wondering if the director of the film will think that your audience is lerdo. Well this is not true as and as I see it because what was involved here was sending a message to the may number of people as possible (if still someone was after the amount of books that sold Dan Brown), and all do not have the same sharpness or simply there are many people going to the movies of brevas figs and find it difficult to continue an argument represented as it is done now (I think there is in fact) (several studies "applied to films" on the subject of the perception of 1 same thing in different people, the result is always different). so I gather that the director/producer thought that it was best to adapt the message to language more possible "didactic" (by call it somehow).Moreover, recommend that they see the film in original version if you do not want to die from an attack of deafness with the "grrr ggggññ" of the folding of Audry Tatou (terrible dubbing due to the forced French accent, not by the folding).But. the film is very well directed, is very faithful to the book which I thank, barely there are at least a couple of differences that I warned one of them is that replaced the visit of Robert to the library by an "original" doubt with the new technologies in a bus, thanks to which discovered another new track.What I liked: 1 - the end with this endless and repetitive hanks kneeling before the Roslyn ancestral assuming that it had become the new guardian of the secret and therefore in the new Grand Master of the Priory of Sion. 2 - the flight in the smart.3 - Silas, who in the book is a being bland, in the movie occurs under the spectacular port of Paul Bettany, which to my taste is too handsome and impressive for the role, too much charisma uff this man in every movie is better (for those not ye, Bettany played the poseso doctor traveling on the ship's Master &amp; Legeais and some say that it is a nod to Darwin). Supposedly in the book this character is not, but anyway, I like the bet made by the director, greatly improves the character and thereby to history in general. Positive balance in general.</body>
</review>
