<review author="Torbe" title="Alatriste" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie begins with all players sunk in a pond, and that premonicion more clear of what he was going to see...</summary>
	<body>If I went to see the movie in the cinema, which I don't hardly ever unless you are ready to see winning horse, i.e., any movie of interest general or that you have said many people that is sublime.If lei the first book of Alatriste of the Grump of Perez Reverte, a writer than not I just catch at all but it's an I jarto and so cool. The book was not evil, aventurillas and such. Jure read the second but the pornete and the life crazy that I has not allowed me to return to pages of this capitan to lived a time with a great attraction for me, I am passionate about all this cycle of the Americas.Y suddenly I hear that they will make a movie about Alatriste. And you are going to lead the Diaz Yanes, a director that I met in a Seville Holy week ago a lot of years and it left me with the talking. A guy very nice and accessible, so I wish you all the luck in the world with his movie.Then I see the movie finally, accompanied by a Romanian pussy and writer David Beard and I go both the sea of curious.At the entrance, buying into fucking me to sneak an infamous fat. He tells me that they have given 2 tickets and you are 3. His movie began at 1030 and the mia at 10. And were the 10!.Tell him that if he doesn't mind to wait for it to remove my posts because this begins already, and the aunt gets it edge by saying that no, that have given wrong your entries and bla bla bla.Before his idioticia, the force. I say that it will not happen before of my. Indeed, leaves which was front and she tries to get the ringleader, but I I am goose, I interpongo as the referee that it sits between two furgolistas that are being ostiar, got my tickets, the aunt calls me Digimundo and I the say a resounding "that I forget", by not reading the card or mount a chicken, as the movie began.He began well experience Alatriste, lives Dios!.The movie begins with all players sunk in a pond, and that premonicion more clear of what he was going to see!Ostia, which movie disappointment, as I bored! DiossssY that the first time not bad, but halfway, when it appears the Ariadna Gil throughout the movie will join in boredom more absolute. Do I have nothing against this great actress, gorgeous by the way, but is that?. Diossss than sovereign pain in the ass.I when I get bored in a movie and I have a pussy on the side, start to get besucon and heavy. I spend at the premiere of the movie Pret a Porter, pain in the ass that's the Altman. Had one known to the side and the di the movie, because I super-heavy ponia trying to get her hand. Later I saw her presenting a news and could not fail to forget that night. Average projection Pobretica.en decided to buy her drink and shit to the Romanian pussy because the poor was saying that I wanted to kill, as had led to see such movie. Luck was the beard Professor because to the less could discuss the play with the. I go to the puestecillo of sweets of the film and I find Manolo Escobar! DiooooooSSSSS! Do JajajajajaLe greet and say:-man Manolo, you remember of my? Do we saw in the hotel Calderon in Barcelona (is that is that you months has I saw him to Manolo in a hotel and greet him saying that was a living myth and about my car and all that)-man, Yes, haha, man? (I recognized!)-That incredible that you see here, you saw yesterday on TV, some time ago in Barcelona and now a puestecillo of the film. "This is a sign, Manolo-(the good man is laughs and something tells me so) who knows if there is something there, who knows.""Who knows if there is something there, who knows". Big words from a great Spain. subliminal message which bears relation with the movie I'm seeing. "Who knows if there is something there, who knows". I think that in Alatriste little had. The departure of nardo with Echanove Quevedo, that this highly successful with these hairs from jevy and these gafillas than him towards the Chinese eyes, the scene of the gold of the ship and, the final battle. And of course the costumes and sets, which is where has spent the Peel.And I wonder, this is not a movie of adventures? So by that not put more rhythm? Some gag, pussy, in the movie there are no chistecillo or gracieta. I hate the movies that could get chistecillos and not put them. What's going on? That by not putting humor the movie is better?The Romanian made an odious comparison, I said that days before had seen Pirates of the Caribbean and that you had liked, and this movie instead not. The pirates has humor, rhythm, things happen and it is not as unpleasant as the of Alatriste, which do not stop kill all God in a pretty nasty way. And the role of the aunts in the movie? Os you have set? All chungas or whores. Who hates women? Reverte or Diaz Yanes? Because often seven that have made them to the female gender with this movie. And no feminist said nothing.And to finish, a special for Vigo Mortenssen mention! If Swedish seemed! Do not fuck with me! If the Spanish only is the name, Vigo!Hell, if you want the movie to seem Spanish 100%, gets a prota Spanish!. Ernesto Alterio or Antonio Resines, among others. But it looks if there are players out there. Do anyway, we live in the country of the here is everything, so queeeeeee worth? that you give ass to all!</body>
</review>
