<review author="Torbe" title="La máquina de bailar" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A sinsorgada as would say is my grandmother, but is full of deliveries and very funny situations, put less patriotic film when you want to do the respectable laugh...</summary>
	<body>It debuts the latest movie of Oscar Aibar, a young man who comes from the world of the comic like me and happened to piniculas with much success. The machine dancing, is a sinsorgada as would say my grandmother, but is full of deliveries and very funny situations, put less patriotic film when you want to do the respectable laugh.Directed and produced by the buddy Santiago Segura, will be another success assured as I said that newspaper on cover. That has the buddy that everything he does turns it into gold?Script a boat soon: some kids need pelas to buy a snake, and have to get it won a contest of one of these machines dancing there at leisure some of those and that is that in Japan they are know. Toni (Santiago Segura) they encouraged and training to achieve its mission. Gets the character of the Segura, nothing to do with what we have seen before.A good assortment of great actors they accompany the Segura, a fucking great script. Attention, because he has done the screenplay is a well-known in this House! Miss Jimina Sabadú, if that 18 year-old who told us their stuff does muuuchos years on this website. Seeing is believing, as people the way is looking for and is getting along. I'm glad a lot for her, because he has really done an excellent job.And another that has emerged, which has a brilliant role in the movie is the mythical and wonderful woman Josele Roman, also was interviewed in this weich. That makes well the doomed, as talent!. My reflection is that there are many more good actresses and actors to directors or writers, and it is a shame because we have a fucking great quarry. Too bad that so many truño per square metre in the patriotic film become.But this is not the case of this great movie, the machine dance. Yesterday I could go to the preview and saw many famous in Gran Via Madrid, and I greet among others, to the buddy of Bilbao who worked on this great program that I lift you blisters called "go semanita", to the screenwriter Jorge Guerrikaetxebarria, large type, several of the actors from the movie "one of the zombies", to actor Eloi Yebra, and many more buddies. Also greeted to half a dozen fans who had good to greet me. Good laugh with everyone, I am a type accessible, so if you see me out there to greet me, children.Everything was full of good aunts, because as the movie is dance, because there were a lot of dancers who were as freight, mazizisimas them train. After copazos at Havana, and to end the night, of putilingas in the Hot of Plaza Colon. Never before had been there but not bad. A few very rich and stylish aunts. I went with a Romanian that seemed a doll with an ass for framing in house salon. Great powder, if Mr. Alli also I recognized, as no, great jajaUna night, a good movie, with the buddy, and sleep pastry nattering. Livin la vida loca</body>
</review>
