<review author="Caty" title="Brokeback mountain" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A beautiful love story regardless of the sexual preference of each</summary>
	<body>Many of the great stories of all time love in literature as in the film they revolve, mainly around of couples who, possessed by a love and a ravishing passion, are required to maintain separate aspects social, political or social conventions: Brokeback Mountain, the new work by Taiwanese filmmaker Ang Lee has one of these storiesthat revolves around two people who, unable to take in front of everyone what they feel for the other, processed differently their feelings.The point that the lovers in question are men is a mere detail. It is obvious that an affair between two Cowboys, iconic figures of the imagination of the American cinema, would be something difficult to describe, however, the beautiful script by Larry McMurtry and Diana Ossana(inspirado_en_el_relato_corto_de_Annie_Proulx) this obstacle becomes a story in which the relationship between the two characters has a natural and sensitive manner: hired to save a herd of sheep on top of Brokeback Mountain, Ennis of del Mar (Heath Ledger) and Jack Twist (Jake Gyllenhaal) are taken to isolate themselves from the world for a few months, taking only the company of the other. Initially reserved (especially Ennis), establish ties gradually, first becoming friends, confident then and, to the surprise of both, in lovers. This connection is already established, the Cowboys begin an impossible affair which, through decades, will be becoming increasingly more tragic depending on the conflict between two such different temperaments.The film portrays the relationship between Jack and Ennis as something more than a simple sexual desire: prisoners in realities that are hostile, the two men face their sporadic meetings as opportunities to relax and feel happy, complete. Married and converted to parents, they exchanged confidences about their marital problems and other heterosexual encounters. Fleeing from stereotypes which can degrade the characters, Ledger and Gyllenhaal offer fundamental actions for the success of the narrative; as Ennis, Ledger maintains a position always tense and expression constantly closed, as if he was eternally defending himself from an attack that can come at any moment. Introspective and repressed, just difficult to express their feelings, embrutecido by a miserable existence and by abandonment, Ennis is protection in the silence - even when, the mouth speaks barely opens him, as if that would represent an awesome effort-. Thus, the intensity of what he feels for Jack represents, for, a blessing and a curse: on the one hand, with the cowboy it feels free to express se(aunque_no_mucho), on the other hand, the burden of guilt and fear caused by an environment full of prejudices transforms it into a figure haunted by what he is feeling. Jack Gyllenhaal, for its part, embodies a Jack Twist as a person frankly more emotional and willing to accept (and express) the own feelings. When given says that he feels for Ennis is sincere and is love, no doubt to suggest that they stop their wives and live together, although they run the risk of becoming victims of violence inspired by intolerance.In addition to this, one of the issues that most fascinate me of Brokeback Mountain is the respect for the nature of the relationship of Ennis and Jack: while the latter is obviously gay, showing sexual interest in other men, the first ever denotes a similar attraction. The impression that Ennis falls in love with Jack by the mere fact of being a man is therefore, a mere coincidence. When you are away from Twist, Ledger's character never appears to repair in other men, showing clearly more attracted to the opposite sex. On the other hand, the only heterosexual relationship that we know by Jack is his wife, showing a strong personality from the moment in which arises on the screen, and to confer on Jack the status of passive half of marriage - even sexually, that the initiative address it is hers.This is why that Ennis would not tolerate know about other homosexual relationships of Jack; for Ennis, this situation represents something unique that it only affects them, and discover that Twist maintains relationships with other men would be a blow too hard for the. Unfortunately for both, Ennis isn't capable of taking what feels in a comprehensive manner, and is not only regarding the relationship with Jack, but it also becomes inaccessible to the wife and daughters.But not only the male cast that shines in this film: the tortured wife of Ennis Del Mar, soul (played by Michelle Williams) builds a character whose lack of culture and intellectual sophistication, allied with the machismo of the society in which he lives, prevents adoption of a stance more determined in relation to the romance of her husband with another man. And if Anne Hathaway has the opportunity to demonstrate her dramatic scope during a difficult conversation keeps with Ennis by phone when his character is forced to recognize hard truths which always sought to ignore, the veteran Roberta Maxwell, as the mother of Jack, offers a very good scene in which shows his pain and its compression simply through the eyes, in a performance that deserved (almost more than that of Williams) a nomination for the Oscar.Envuelta by the beautiful instrumental soundtrack of Gustavo Santaolalla, shown as intimate as the interpretation of Heath Ledger, Brokeback Mountain also has a subtle but effective work on the artistic direction: observe as for example, the House of Ennis and Alma features colors always sad and oppressivereflecting the gray existence of marriage, and as also the residence of Jack and Lureen is clearly decorated with the taste of it, helping to display the character of Gyllenhaal as a stranger in your own home. Elements like these help demonstrate the sensitivity as a filmmaker Ang Lee, who is also right to establish a pace slow, contemplative, allowing to know the characters with the necessary calm. It also must be said against that Lee should have demanded a makeup for Heath Ledger, that his ageing, despite the optimal performance of the actor, not convinced much to say.Leaving aside the homosexuality, love story told in Brokeback Mountain comes to be universal. It is perfectly possible, for any viewer, identify with the pain of the protagonists, regardless of sexual options each. That's why, in the list of great tragic romances in the history of the cinema has to leave a site also for Jack Twist and Ennis Del Mar.</body>
</review>
