<review author="Plissken" title="El viento que agita la cebada" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps too refers to his another major work, but the intensity and the sadness that evokes the whole, beautiful photography, and inspired music make 'The wind that shakes the barley' a more than worthy winner of the Golden Palm, Cannes.</summary>
	<body>I do not care to acknowledge that Ken Loach is one of the directors that I has more excited with his films ('Ladybird, ladybird', 'Raining stones', 'land and liberty'.). Many accuse him of excessive didacticism to apply their leftist thesis in his films, others complain of manichaeans who are its characters. To me, what they want to tell you, I get a knot in my throat in most of the time. It will be political affinity (over the years, increasingly fewer) or simply identification with the characters, of humble origin and flesh and blood. The case is that with 'The wind that shakes the barley' (2006) Mr. Loach again achieve. Another llantina in the film 'The wind that shakes the barley' tells the story of two brothers, Damien (very successful Cillian Murphy) and Teddy (Padraic Delaney means…) O'Donovan, who are immersed in the struggle for the independence of Ireland in 1920. What at first is a fight against the invading English, becomes later in civil war, to divide the Irish side between those who support a peace treaty that subordinates them to United Kingdom and those who think that the Treaty should file the English king in its Augustan rectal cavity inside. Damien and Teddy will find themselves at the crossroads of cease fighting and accept the Treaty or pursuing the ideal of a Socialist Government for all Irishmen, blood and fire.Unlike 'Land and freedom', 'The wind that shakes the barley' focuses not so much on the political side but the effects war has on people. Damien, a medical student, becomes leader of a column of the IRA in the absence of his brother, having to make decisions that mark of by life. Also his brother Teddy, savagely (very wildly, one of those scenes that make a cover eyes) tortured by the English, becomes a defender of the Treaty of peace with his enemies. The families of the rebels suffer the punishments which may not inflict on the nationalists. English soldiers, after the nightmare that was the first world war, are killed by the IRA. Here, in more balanced way as 'Land and freedom', shows the objectification of all conflict, and the consequences of such objectification. On all sides.Loach also reflects on the use of violence, that is, terrorism. While in the first part of the film justifies this armed struggle by the violence and injustice of the "black and tans" English in the second part of the film shows us a few characters who, in his own words, "have crossed the line", and believe that turning back from the violence used there is not. Some other politician should see this movie to realize that the end of violence is not matter that someone tell "have stopped" and is already. But that is another debate, beyond of the film 'The wind that shakes the barley', altogether, perhaps too refers to his another major work, and perhaps the brutality of English mercenaries may seem that it is only to justify the armed struggle, but the intensity and the sadness that evokes the whole, beautiful photography (work of the great Barry Ackroyd), and inspired music (from the no less great George Fenton) make 'The wind that shakes the barley' one more that worthy winner of the Golden Palm, Cannes. 8.</body>
</review>
