<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Tristán e Isolda" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie is good, unpretentious and finally after although Iseult of wanting to vomit, the movie fulfills its purpose of entertain.</summary>
	<body>Tristan &amp; Isolde is one of those infumables stories of love that my my stolen the heart and although it is full of all the topicazos and american screen play of hollywood I have to admit that I enjoyed as a dwarf (in the background I will shit XD).The story is based on a Chanson de Geste which even has come to represent in theaters, ballets. i.e. the Director not to discover us anything new, even there are legends that cross this love affair with the adventures of King Arthur, where it is said that Tristan was one of the brave knights of the round table, only exceeded by Lancelot.La movie, made me entertaining. Well dressing rooms and locations even have epic moments, soundtrack that goes unnoticed and the big moment arrives to speak of.The actors, God, as James Franco, sisi, that chavalín makes friends with Peter Parker in Spider-man, son of the Green Goblin who will end up inheriting the role of antagonist has grown. My God the kid looks like musculito, Shales, carita, will a babes in power and I say this already is significant pq approximately 4 years ago that any guy calls my attention. and this has done. We have a more adult, improved, picarón, weeping, James enamorado.confieso I am fascinated (James I invite you to the fair XDDD). and can say of Isolde? I have consulted the trajectory of this actress and it can be described as trivial or if non-existent or completely empty of interesting projects, will that if I had offered to my paper would have been better. Isolde passes without penalty or glory by a movie of love in which their lack of chemistry with his partener is almost "insulting", for not commenting that the creature is absolutely tasteless, has bags on the eyes and seems the mother of Tristan rather than his love interest. Patetic. how not may have chemistry with James? Well perhaps it is that it is deeply believed and asshole, often with the handsome guys and more, if they are actors and whether or not. fijensé in the scene in which Tristan and Isolde are in the cabin and she heals him the wound with a hunguento moment in which plays the abdomen of James and this looks (not from the character but from the same from James Franco) with picaresque sum (a time when I thought vibrate as a quinceañera stupid) as telling, what baby, that I am good question?, by God.Do one thing that would highlight as garrafal failure and is que.¿nadie her explained to James as walking through medieval men? they were warriors, safe, strong men. I say walk of the actor seems a University guaperas in plan "I'm the King of the girls" but in any case its attitude as a warrior is credible. (What I'm sorry James, you know that I love you but there her you cagaste).Would a reflection. have been a better Darth Vader James Franco? My answer is Yes. We'll discuss this later.Amen all this my assessment of the movie is good, unpretentious and finally after although Iseult of wanting to vomit, the movie fulfills its purpose of entertain. Although there will always be silly like me who emerge love of Tristan.</body>
</review>
