<review author="Robgordon" title="Monster house" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Captures the essence so well knew translate Zemeckis and Spielberg in the 1980s and is separated from the, ever more recurrent, spoof tone of computer-animated films,</summary>
	<body>Robert Zemeckis has always been a guy with huge curiosity for the evolution of special effects. The cartoons mixed successfully with human beings in "Who framed Roger Rabbit?", evolved techniques in the failed but appreciable "death I feel so fine" or becoming old images in "Forrest Gump". Zemeckis has always been fascinated by these means, managing to be one of the pioneers in the proper use and progression of them and composing fantastic stories that used the technique to create huge results and excellent entertainment films.In its latest evolution of technology, Zemeckis filmed "The Polar Express", tape in which, for the first time, the director saw as the technique is ate the content, leading to ruined Christmas good intentions of this film and the hope of his company, Warner Bros.. raise high figures with this product, something coming from a director as Zemeckis was, a priori, unlikely.With Tom Hanks as cobaya, Zemeckis used in "The Polar Express" the technique of performance capture, it was based on "scan" and literally digitized actors, thus achieving an entirely animated, but captured the live-action film. Despite this failure ("The Polar Express" was a film so managed as boring técnologicamente), Zemeckis decided to continue putting into practice this performance capture with "Monster House", in which gave the gallons to rookie Gil Kenan. "And next to them are Spielberg, in the role of executive producer.""Monster House" captures the essence so well knew translate Zemeckis and Spielberg in the 1980s, and is separated from the, ever more recurrent, spoof tone of the films of computer animation, established as one of the most successful films of this genre in the past two years.The history of "Monster House" is simple, but effective. A haunted house inhabited by an old malcarado devours anyone or anything that SBI with approaching her. A couple of curious children are continuously monitoring strangers and dangerous movements of that House.With this plot, which leads to a new spot the genre of the haunted houses, "Monster House" is dirigiendonos by a dizzying roller coaster of fun and joy to the purest style of the cinema of the 1980s. A film by lyrical, luminous and beautiful moments and sometimes scary, dark and evil. But always with a sense of the enviable rate.The screenplay by Dan Harmon, Rob Schrab and Pamela Pettler contains very well described characters, such as its two young protagonists, "D.j." and "Croquette" (a sort of "Gordi" of "The Goonies") that complement each other perfectly, with these fears of childhood and his desire for maturity, as well as its picturesque range of side as the old man Nebbercracker (excellent name for a character of a tape of these features)the pimping nanny or zamanfou this boyfriend. And also, with a beautiful "flashback" about women of Nebbercracker, who is a true delight.All this, together with its dialog boxes, the succession of exciting and attractive sequences that give rise to the full showcasing of motion capture technique and good do its Director, Gil Kenan, "Monster House" makes a wonderful and joyful work. Debtor's "The Goonies" but also to the cinema of Hayao Miyazaki (especially "Howl's moving Castle"). A tape with personality, that uses creativity and ingenuity in its blend of horror and adventure, forming a product of taste of small, older and especially those bred in between 1980 and 1990, which you can find the elements and the Basic constants of the film of his childhood and adolescence in the characters, situations and ambience of this film.Technically, "Monster House" is an admirable, and its background, truly rich film. It is one of the most original compositions from "Monsters, Inc." and an unstoppable divertimento as it could be this. There are no known actors or famous television in dubbing, or is used to parody easy. We have the tape of the year in the field of digital animation. And it is this that Steven Spielberg and Robert Zemeckis appear as Executive producers is always a pleasant news.</body>
</review>
