<review author="Dragon negro" title="Shinobi" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film entertains and appeal to lovers of gender feudal loving of the manga, and Japanese although the film, as we have said, is half in all its goals.</summary>
	<body>In 1614, the Shinobi are ninjas with special magical abilities that make them superior to the common man. The Shinobi are trained from small in two small villages, Kouga clan and the Iga clan and are staunch enemies from long ago. The two villages live in peace because the Emperor banned the war between them, but decide now facing two villages in order to choose a successor to the throne the outcome of the match. Each village will elect five of his best warriors who will face on a whim of the emperor. Gennosuke of the Kouga and Oboro, the Iga, are two young men who fell in love in the time of peace and now capitanearan two teams that face, the destination takes them to the fight between them and they must choose between love or death. Shinobi, based on the popular manga, continues to be another of those movies of the feudal Japan dressed with fantastic dyes, because their Samurai possess different powers that make them special. The film part of a quite simple argument and despite the complicated names and initial history credits one quickly enters the plot and understands it, and also the film is aimed more towards action than to large filosofadas to which we are accustomed the Japanese, which are two points in its favour. But the film is missing something that just does not work and is its inability to move and that we identify with the characters. Already alone the love story to the Romeo and Juliet is lack of spark and naturalness everywhere, battles are well but without being all spectacular could be wait and one is left with wanting more, it shows a limited budget, of course. The lack of good and bad, none of the two clan can be defined as such, the Viewer does not end of siding with either of the two sides, with which the battles he fail to involve him and left quite indifferent. Villages resemble Naruto, with children train Ninjas, warriors remember superheroes, X-Men with some of their powers and even Spider-man when they nodding hanging by a thread. The film entertains and like the Japanese feudal genre lovers and lovers of manga, although the film, as we have said, is half in all its goals, the fight scenes are unable to move, the love story just does not work and the film itself fails, except counted as the final moments, get you in the history.</body>
</review>
