<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Gracias por fumar" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite err on the side of some irregularity, 'Thank you for smoking' satire works... and fun</summary>
	<body>Tobacco has always had great importance in the world of cinema: classical actors who not stopped smoking on the big screen, coming to turn into something 'sexy', consideration that reaches our days are numerous. 'Thank you for smoking' reflects not only the film power levels and social customs which can produce films, but it also delves into one of the most discussed by Western societies fear in recent years: smoking or non smoking, that is the question. Since some time ago, tobacco companies have suffered a major offensive by the health authorities, as well as the Government: he began with the withdrawal of advertising in various media, and has been reached (for now) be prohibited smoking in any public place. There are views of all types, but in a State of law, someone has to defend the interests of tobacco companies, and that is the work of Nick Naylor, played by a good Aaron Eckhart. The film not only emphasizes this, but it deals with problems of all kinds, such as relatives, but above all, labour: director, over and over again, insists make us see that the greatest concern of people is to pay their mortgages, with employment that is, and with greater or lesser involvement in the daily life of each. Perhaps this is the message of this satirical film, which, far from being a genius, not at odds in no time, and ends up leaving a good taste.The plot is based on an original and interesting premise: you have several ingenious points and are poured moderately vicious criticism, both to society as the Administration, world emrpesarial, and even to the film. As the film develops, there are a number of small ups and downs, which is rather due to too long sequences or the repetition of the same arguments. However, this should not remove merits to Jason Reitman, who besides directing, adapted the screenplay from the novel (by Christopher Bickley) of the same name which is based the film on the other hand, is his first work for the big screen, after having triumphed with several short films.Aaron Eckhart comfortably meets his work: adds appeal and mischief to his character, which appears on the other hand, made to suit. The rest of the cast performed a good job, with correct Maria Bello, Robert Duvall and William H. Marcy consigned to a background, like most of the rest of performers, given the absolute role of Eckhart.Probablemente could have given more than itself, but in these times, with achieving that flow, already is a merit. Therefore, and in spite of err on the side of some irregularity, the satire of 'Thank you for smoking' funciona.y fun.</body>
</review>
