<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="Shinobi" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very bad pelîcula that ademâs has a whiff to second categorîa pelîcula in all aspects.</summary>
	<body>'Tiger and Dragôn' became fashionable the pelîculas asiâticas of jumping wrestlers that jumping jumping, are hitting right and left everyone who will put ahead. And although they were previously was after the Ang Lee film when came us a true explosiôn of similar caracterîsticas tîtulos, some who managed to cross the borders of its paîs, and many others who have stayed inside but then they have reached us in dvd format. 'Shinobi' is estrenô last week in our paîs and not in all cities of the country. Seeing it one understands why. Y es que hay pelîculas merecerîan sleep the sleep of the righteous forever and not be released or edited on dvd. Clear that if that does not happen cômo can find out that they are bad? Always us quedarîa the doubt in case of not seeing them. I have seen 'Shinobi', and I can say that it is a complete waste of time. Did expect me? Not me I have caught on? Tampoco.en a was in which the ninjas walked by the Earth to suit, two clans were enfrentarân to death because sî, which is the best razôn to face death with someone. To this end both sides elegirân two small groups of experts warriors so they face and are they to decide the outcome of the fight. The problem of the matter is that the lîderes of both groups are a kind of Romeo and Juliet, both very lunatics on the other one. That obviously repercutirâ of form drâstica in the evolution of events, and that both lovers do not see lôgica the fight and however has faced. God, how nice.The pelîcula is appalling, but not technical cutrez, but mâs well temâtica. The plot premise is mâs well mînima and never develops enough cômo to make an interesting story. On the other hand treatment is totally errôneo, because they want to make us believe that the pelîcula does not give importance to trying to spectacular scenes that prime the intimate. The trouble with the theme is that the spectacular scenes are the best of the pelîcula, and for that not all, and întimo resolved estâ very chabacanamente not proving creîble at any time, as the love story deflated by all sides to be stuck to shoehorn and poorly explained. Then try during the proyecciôn be natural and make us see that these two love estân each other. For this they use long sequences that seems pure postcards that influence negatively the pace of the pelîcula making it aburridîsima.The best scenes of acciôn is to discover the skills of each Warrior, that I might add me recordô to the X-Men, but ahî just everything. In fact some of the sequences are confusing and one does not know much. Ademâs does not give time to learn a little characters that will removing us them in the Middle at the speed of lightning. The Visual effects are mâs or less acceptable, but fail to engage and fascinate as do the films of Zhang Yimou, for example. Apart from the happy plot inconsistencies, because if many of these tîos can almost fly and move forward should, do to what the hell they pick up a horse that van slow oft? And on top mounted us an escenita of equine persecuciôn. What are giving supersaltos, man!The actors walk across the film with hermetic faces without excepciôn. Jô Odagiri is fairly deadpan and his interpretaciôn has no force required. Yukie Nakama is very pretty but as an actress aquî leaves much to be desired. The case is that the actors seem to all as desganados, as if not trust in what estân doing, and no wonder, because getting into such producciôn debiô be desperate.A very bad pelîcula that ademâs has a whiff to second categorîa pelîcula in all aspects. I'm not saying B series to not insult a kind of cinema that has left me very good flavors of mouth in fantâsticas productions. Ten Shimoyama has worn by creating a film for the râpido forgotten. Habrâ to wait for other options in this type of cinema and desire to not take to arrive.</body>
</review>
