<review author="Matías Cobo" title="La noche de los girasoles" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is one of those pequeñas-grandes tapes that our film gives us from time to time and who come to corroborate a maximum of good cinema: before that money and the abundance of means, the most important are good ideas.</summary>
	<body>The film is often nurture of clichés that, despite its repeated use, will not stop working. Does do one of them we know it very well and even more in recent times, with? remakes? recent as the Texas Chainsaw Massacre or the hills have eyes. I am referring to the terrible events in harsh, almost unpopulated location, where the days pass with a dull everyday life. On the night of the sunflowers, rookie Jorge Sánchez-Cabezudo puts his account at one of these sites, in particular, in an Avila village typical of a rural Spain endangered. In this calm scenario, the story of the film details the details of a typical event, increasingly more bulky, black Chronicle of news. And to maintain interest, the story is told in a fragmented way, style of Arriaga, and introduces an interesting twist in his plot to the spectator recompose the puzzle of the facts.The discovery of a cave in the village is lived by neighbors with anticipation. The single possibility that the underground cavity has some archaeological value awakens the illusions of a few people getting that ansian back "on the map". As said the Mayor of the town, not without some ingenuity, the key to achieving this is "rural tourism". So the arrival of the espeléologos is received in plan Bienvenido Mr. Marshall. Before that happen, Sánchez-Cabezudo has already sown the concern in the viewer with an event narrated at the beginning of the film: the rape and murder of a young woman occurred in the vicinity of the village. Thus this plot and the espeléologos seem to flow along similar paths and with common characters, but the script will likely play a smart dismissal followed with interest.In the ensemble cast of the film, the best-known face is of Carmelo Gómez, who complies with the common solvency in its role as one of the cavers, stands out a secondary always plausible, Celso Bugallo, and surprising the bella Judith Diakhate interpretation. Manuel Morón, that usual face in almost all productions, large and small, our film is perfect in the role more unpleasant and complex of the tape.The night of the sunflowers is one of those pequeñas-grandes tapes that our film gives us from time to time and who come to corroborate a maximum of good cinema: before that money and the abundance of means, the most important are good ideas. And despite being attached to own the thriller conventions, his story also offers interesting insights into a rural Spain devoured by the mass exodus to the city and that, practically, is poised to become an echo of the past. If it crosses it in a bulletin board, not her dispose with the ease and lightness, that sometimes we sneer at our cinema. It will be rewarded, and more than the price of your entry.</body>
</review>
