<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It neither chicha nor another. It stays halfway all their intentions.</summary>
	<body>Not wanting to read many comments to not go to the conditioned movies, but that I have read and heard from flick after Friday put me on guard. And truth be told, although he wished that wasn't so, Alatriste is a film which remains half way at almost all of his intentions. It tries to be a spectacular and bloody battles of the Siglo de Oro Spanish ambitious film, but it weakens in this regard; it pretends to be a hard drama that portrays the life of a few brave soldiers despised by compromising, inept rulers, but it barely moves in a pair of intimate sequences. His obsession with recreating the era because Yes, and without justification in the story, the pace of the film, sleeping at times it lastra. All these issues are added a couple of stories of impossible love of which only highlights a pre-credit sequence between Diego Alatriste y María de Castro (a splendid Ariadna Gil). It is not a bad film, but no, not even close, the great quality of our film that all blockbuster had hoped and some, as it is my case, we would have wished.Alatriste suffers in the visual, of an abuse of the postalitas. Some scenes are authentic calques into frames of paintings of the era, such as the surrender of Breda Velázquez. However, is conservative in the use of the camera and little daring in its Assembly. In this aspect, the truth, are still taking us several bodies Americans. And in a Ribbon backed with a very large budget, you might expect much more in the use of cinematic language. The choice of locations does seem accurate, especially in the case of urban scenes filmed in Baeza and Úbeda (and I do not mean to sweep the land), but the war sequences are poor. It is praise this desire for the verismo in the choreographies of the struggles, bloody and cruel, but also more flexibility in their development would have appreciated. I do not know if it will have been the own Díaz Yanes who was responsible for filming the war scenes, but in productions of this kind, it is normally the case that this function be delegated to specialized directors. Either way, the result not convincing.But if we consider the tape as a drama of characters, like a sour portrait of an empire in decline, this nor accomplishes its mission. Do do just give off emotion a couple of sequences and some dialogue, raised as a? tour de force? acting between opposing characters, they are quite flat and do not emit sparks they should. I have not read the novels, so I do not know if the accommodation is good or not. But if as I read, the main virtues of those reside in the development of a few plots and sub-plots of some complexity, have structured the script as a biography of Diego Alatriste does not seem very successful. Thus, it seems that Díaz-Yánez, despite having put their best intentions, has made a chaotic "copy-paste" of the five novels and his script as a whole is more deslavazado.And it is a pity, really, because in it some of our finest actors are involved. Although some shine at more height than others, I'll stick with Eduard Fernández in his role of brave soldier, taciturn man and loyal friend of Alatriste. I would also highlight Javier camera as the count-Duke of Olivares, above all in a final in which, already aged, sequence Hamas remains stubborn to recover the glory lost with an own disposed leader contudo. Also protruding Ariadna Gil, as a lover of the hero, and Juan Echanove, effective in its interpretation of Quevedo. With regard to Viggo Mortensen, who no doubt as efforts to build this character of chiaroscuro, had everything to be Alatriste: presence, intensity in the eyes, face of epic hero, but his work comes to pique when performing a strenuous effort to imitate an accent that does not have. That is why their phrases are a whisper that tries to hide its Spanish of porteño accent and anglophone vocalization.I not mistaken to say that much of the movie buff public put high expectations on this tape. Just take a look at some of the views that I linked at the end of this comment. If I would add is because I usually rely on the criterion of those who sign them, and realise that their views only respond to a single criterion: the love for good cinema. Do confronted these views with the conventional press, well, now seems that others have seen?Alatristes? different. I'm not saying that media criticism has been agreed, but I am surprised this unanimity of so strongly favorable views. I understand that you could want commercial success to a costly tape produced here and inspired by facts of our history, but common sense, when assessing, should not be clouded by the desire to lend a hand. Or, I don't know, maybe we are wrong who do not see in this film neither chicha nor another.</body>
</review>
