<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Monster house" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A single objection I can put this story of adventures and fear, able to be funny to children and adults alike.</summary>
	<body>Monster House is, at least for those who subscribed to these lines, the best tape released animation in what we carry year. And I think not exaggerate if I qualify her as a pioneer in the assumption of a, the horror genre's own aesthetic and thematic patterns, just employees so far in the animation. I.e., that Monster House, still a tape suitable for all audiences, would be the first of its kind filmed as if it were horror film. Without leaving aside the usual aventuras-humor tandem in the animation of the past years, there are continuous winks to referents film of the genre of fear in Monster House. Haunted House, fear a mysterious neighbor suspected hide terrifying secrets (reminded me the crazy not to kill the neighbor, with Tom Hanks), anonymous and threatening calls to the telephone, the concurrence of strange events on Halloween and some other aspects, such as the setting and camera movements, are debtor a very different from the animation film.Even jobs to look for more Parallels, the hat-trick of researchers formed by these pre-teens reminds the endearing Goonies, with very different profiles for each character. DJ would be brave and skilled researcher; Croquette, stocky, funny friend and little supporter of exercise of Hero instead of risking his own skin; and Jenny, the girl which both long and who will put some sanity in the group. The own characterization of Nebbercracker, an old stooped face enjuto and fearsome and dressed in harapientos clothes, also we are familiar. And the comic point exploits through picturesque side as the geek-pizzero Skull, a twenties specialist in video games and comics that will attend DJ and company to ask for advice, Kangaroo Zee and her boyfriend Bones or a pair of clueless cops.The graphic treatment of Monster House demonstrates that, in digital animation, there is always room for further surprising each new film. Apart from the magnificent treatment of textures, this film stands out for their agile movements of camera and a careful atmosphere perfect to introduce in its proposal of mystery. But the main virtue of this film directed by Gil Kenan newcomer, and chartered by the Fox of Spielberg and Zemeckis (who missed with Polard Express), lies in its magnificent and intelligent script. A single objection I can put this story of adventures and fear, able to be funny to children and adults alike. Although go to stereotypes seen in hundreds of tapes of terror, the true story behind this monstrous House is quite original and unpredictable. If you want to discover it, accompanying DJ and company during his singular adventure. The fun is guaranteed.</body>
</review>
