<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie best wrapper that content. Even so, compared to others of a similar genre, the Michael Mann film exceeds the average thanks to his very personal and recognizable style.</summary>
	<body>I don't know where I heard or read that the way in which Michael Mann wheel its action scenes is more plausible. And the truth is that, if we take a look to Heat or Collateral, their two most comparable tapes with Miami Vice in this regard, we agree that their bullets and gunfire do seem sound, and develop, as the truth. In them there is no trace of that exaggeration so characteristic of the film by which you can shoot a shotgun barrel cut to a hand without its bearer the pulse, or that other that the bullets of the wicked only refresh them the neck shaking you some reckless opponents in their actions. In addition, his scripts for this type of work nor tend to ascribe to own the tape action of conventions. Heat could be almost considered an urban western raised as a pulse between two colossi as De Niro and Pacino. And the argument of Collateral is more atypical even: Tom Cruise, a Hitman, and Jamie Foxx, a taxi driver, the vehicle agree on a great job rush for the first night. However, the scripts of both outweigh the flat and unoriginal story of this Miami Vice, based on characters from the series of 80 which the own Mann was executive producer. That itself, apart from having used the names of the agents?Sonny? Crockett and Ricardo Tubbs and the title of the series, this film little or nothing has to do with television production created by Anthony Yerkovich.Y already not only because the aesthetics of Mann diffused any possible parallel with the series, which only shares the luxury of Miami environments, but because he sees little of Miami andeven less, of the portrayed in a series that perhaps seen now, could already seem a tad casposa, despite the acclaimed which resulted in those years. Therefore, this free adaptation made by Mann stands his peculiar nocturnal photography, with a marked grain on screen we already enjoyed in Collateral, tape that Mann began experimenting with the use of digital technologies, and the additional possibilities provided by them for the filming of night scenes. As well, some Miami panoramas shot in closed night offer a sparkling beauty. Little action of the tape, concentrated at the end of his extensive footage (almost two and a half hours), yes carried this particular rubric of Mann of which spoke the principle is also remarkable. But that fails in it, in my opinion, is what happens in his knot. Its history wants to focus on how develops the infiltration of two policemen in an embedded criminal network equipped with powerful tools of Counterespionage. In addition to detailing the intricacies of a mission of this caliber, Mann delves into how the second identity of the agent can sometimes pollute to the true. But the development of all this plot, the truth, it is slow and, at times, poorly explained. In fact, the tape begins with the death of two officers infiltrated a police force other than Sonny and Tubbs due to a tip-off from one of the security agencies involved. As well, in the outcome, once two Miami policemen to resume the work of his fallen teammates, is not resolved the worrying issue of the tip-off.Acting work, Colin Farrell convinces as the charismatic Sonny, Foxx is effective as the brain?Do rich?, surprised in her few appearances Luis Tosar as bad content, as it highlights the sensual presence of the beautiful Gong Li. And the music choice is right to accompany the night sequences by Miami or the locations of Haiti and final Cuba.En, a film best wrapper that content. Even so, compared to others of a similar genre, the Michael Mann film exceeds the average thanks to his very personal and recognizable style. But its history already have told other many times and, even better than here. To cite some examples, infinitely better are the police tapes based on James Ellroy scripts.</body>
</review>
