<review author="Matías Cobo" title="La joven del agua" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This particular director is on track to become works of cult film, judging by the excitement generated by each new release.</summary>
	<body>The director of Indian origin that the story of the young woman of the water began to develop in parallel to the forest has. At night, Shyamalan told him his daughter the story of this nymph emerging from a swimming pool and as he progressed in his account, was incorporating various mythological elements to adorn this story whose final, like everyone, has moral. And in contrast to the forest, where the message is more pessimistic about the man and his life in society, the moral of the girl of water makes a sediment of hope, of faith in the possibilities of the man to reverse its current bleak situation. If the characters of the forest, reject a world perceived as hostile, the protagonist of this film, the character of a prodigious Paul Giamatti decides the opposite path, despite having suffered like those, the cruelty of this world. To him, as other characters of this story dressed in contemporary clothes, he challenges the need to continue believing in something. They want to, they need to know their mission in this world. The mysterious nymph, which puts face one Ethereal Bryce Dallas Howard, placed them before questions that will change them during the search for the answers.With an aesthetic and more personal choice of plans, Shyamalan shows each new film a recognizable label of author, both by the choice of their topics and for the manner in which it decides to develop them. Use the fantasy genre to tackle current issues and, therefore, their characters are not extraordinary neither possess superhuman qualities. Do many may not like this style as as a kind of cat for a ride, to sell horror film in the? trailers? and offer a story well away from the conventions of the genre in the movies. But you have no doubt that this particular director is poised to make his films in works of worship, judging by the excitement generated by each new release filmed by him.And as usually it happens to other directores-autores, or one entered the game for Shyamalan film proposals or stays outside and frustrated. To me I hooked this film out at the tail. Everything about her is in place: the work of the actors, the magnificent soundtrack by James Newton Howard and the narrative pace of the story. Only blur perhaps comes from the decision of Shyamalan's autoreservarse a role of so much importance in the history. It is that, in imitation of Hitchcock, make a minimum appearance during the story, but here it has gone hand in hand. He is not an actor, and it shows too much when it shares some emotional scenes with those who are. And finally, the comic wink of this tape, on account of a literary critic and cinema, has a lot of reckoning staff, given the little appreciation which is received the work of Shyamalan in your country. Indeed, weary of both drubbing, the director has dropped the idea of not work over there and come to shoot Europe. Here, like other artists of their species, sure gets it superbly.</body>
</review>
