<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La increíble historia de Caperucita Roja" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Miramax executives have given in the diana: have rewritten the epic tales of yesteryear with modern dressings.</summary>
	<body>What brings head to the multinationals of the entertainment made in USA is to provide with the magic formula that leads from hand to parents and children to the tail of the film and then leaving all cheerful entertainment, happy as tambourines at a village fair. Until Shrek, to my mind, nobody came up with this potion. Walt Disney opened gap. Nobody discusses worth movies Wizard of the cartoon, color correction, his workshop of future geniuses, but there has been little intergenerational consensus and when it leaves the joyful father, the child is bored. Or vice versa. It is very difficult to harmonize vices.Now this is style: multifamily cocktail, domestic gazpacho. This little Red Riding Hood is a smart jumble of several ingredients, all of which are intended to be content to a section of the tribe, which acoquina the quarterfinals without metaphysics to entertain the afternoon of Sunday. And if it rains, better still Freud, clearly. And the deconstruction of Derrida, if we bother to the intellectual who, reluctantly, comes to the film to the amusement of his offspring, but ultimately, is an animated film, and well done, of course. Very well made, I would add, but it is missing a good dramatic sense and does not forgive the go puzzle of doctored personalities. Gags are the righteous, and some had already heard them before, but we don't remember in what movie.Everything well, artificial and cold, without content in excess to anyone, but enjoying it as strictly necessary to all. And there is some humor. And even his pinch of sex, conveniently lightened of thickness so that it enters the domestic baggage without excesses. Miramax executives have given in the diana: have rewritten the epic tales of yesteryear with modern dressings. The possibility that one day end up so modernity gorger and want our children to see on screen the original hood, the original Wolf and the three little pigs before.Critical consequence that some spend, the incredible but true story of little Red Riding Hood will be a speech experiment, an absolute boutade not suitable for purists, but I insist (and lately I have this concept quite clear) that the film is, above all, entertainment.As it is not del olmo to ask pears, be it in light entertainment, but our movie fan concern not fed with wolves and grandmothers: prefer harder, much more addictive drugs pearls of Orson Welles with texts by Shakespeare, superb interpretations of Max Von Sydow in Swedish films of the sixties, robberies in racetracks filmed by Kubrick, who do not have wine and bottles which Hitchcock used to revive the Philo of the cold war and the nazi resurgence... Anyway, you take their children to this multicultural Frankenstein, telling them that when they are older, the film will them happy and that this happiness will to them, also, more intelligent, more free. If the gentle reader not have progeny that sit in seat, see Alatriste, which is still running. More exploited euros – is that it is longer. Ah, the protagonist talks weird. The characters of Perrault, not.And there is always the dvd for the saddest nights. I think Blade Runner to be Replicants dreams.</body>
</review>
