<review author="Yul B." title="Click" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a tape with surprise that you must not miss. Especially to see how dangerous it can be to have a remote control.</summary>
	<body>Michael Newman (Adam Sandler) is a very busy architect that trafficking in advance and have time for his wife Donna (Kate Beckinsale) and their two children. Its objective is to become partner of the company in which working and enjoy more of his family, and so he dedicates hard and long hours so its desagradecido head (David Hasselhoff) recognized someday their invaluable contribution to the business.Newman fails to make progress in its goal. However, at the time of greatest frustration, and by a cluster of coincidences, buy a remote control to a strange salesman, Morty (Christopher Walken), it seems that not only lets you control your TV or your garage door, but virtually all his life.From that moment, Michael dreams will come true, although not everything will be as he had wished. ?Click? It may seem a comedy to the use. Do after reading his synopsis, can think that this is more of the same, but with the variant? original? of the remote control. Because you are right half.The plot takes place as the rest of films of its genre, with some to other ups and downs (do very few, one of them the way in which get the? do magic? apparatus), and with many great points (priceless moment in which the head of Newman tells him in his Office that he has not yet appointed partner; I revolcaba on the ground). Up here, everything just like always, but pretty fun.However, there comes a time of the tape in which the history gives a dramatic turn of 180 degrees in which makes you a lump in the throat. And this is where it differs from the rest of comedietas, and where its virtue.At that point you're wondering why such a radical change, when everything ran so cheerful and superficial. Even you feel uncomfortable with that part of the film.But at the end of the film, after another round of tortilla, you understand that what has been lived by Newman what, in some logic had to occur (within the logical thing which can be which controls your life with a magical remote control). Do and somehow grateful that?Click? It is so consistent tape in that regard (I insist, within the coherence that can give to the issue of the command). However, the lump in my throat it dashed awhile after leaving the room.As for the main cast, Adam Sandler is the maximum and absolute protagonist of the film. The other actors are a mere accompaniment. Everything revolves around his character. For this reason, it is possible to see him on a series of records until now unusual in it; In addition to the usual House brand, offers some drámaticos that fits quite well with the moment in history in which they live. His performance does not reach perfection, much less to give an Oscar, but appreciated that this actor wants to take his career in a more serious direction.Kate Beckinsale is a vase. But, Hey vase!. The beauty of this actress is enhanced to the fullest, and above, has a feeling with Sandler beyond the screen. Although I found it strange that he has accepted this as secondary work.Christopher Walken is also a vase. But ugly over not being able to. His performance seems custom: comes to scene, drops his roll, and leaves. His role could have done any.And that has surprised me has been David Hasselhoff. Coast that criticize me his detractors, his character I liked, and their interpretation is effective. He gives what he has to give in its fair measure, without being ridiculous; Hence the success of that character, and as a result, the draft to continue playing in a TV series based on the film.To sum up?Click? It is a tape with surprise that you must not miss. Especially to see how dangerous it can be to have a remote control.</body>
</review>
