<review author="Dino" title="Orgullo y prejuicio" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The best British film of the year</summary>
	<body>There are moments in life in which cold solves better than heat problems. Lock in oneself and traverse a copious snowfall becomes solution to avoid issues that caused in the head and the heart. For those moments where the icy winter blows forcefully invented movies such as "Pride and prejudice", in its most recent version, and that is, long, the best British film of the year. They are complete, undefiled, bright stories from beginning to end, free of faults or points. This does not mean perfection, but it comes very close. While I must admit that I have not enjoyed the mini-series by the BBC starring Colin Firth (highly reviewed by some people close), I can not hide my absolute enthusiasm for this tape of Joe Wright. For the delicacy of its images parading the purity of Keira Kinghtley, one of those thin, simple beauties of disturbing smile by his candor and, at the same time, complicity. Levite through the exquisite rooms where to set history with a gracilidad unique, semi-divine, to what accompanies a performance perfectly suited to the role of Lizzie Bennet. more beyond the unspeakable charm of its protagonist, nominated with credit-worthiness Oscar for best actress, there is a commendable cast of artists. Since the shy gaze of Rosamund Pike up the powerful presence of Judi Dench, without forgetting the sweet Mr. Bennet of Donald Sutherland. But my favorite, even though it sounds like a cliché, that stretched, proud, rational and conceited noble of Mark Darcy, despite all their prejudices just in love with who should not. Ignores any obstacles (jumps them), any mistake (attempt to correct them at any price), any disagreement of its environment (face plant) to deliver their feelings to this unique creature found on Elizabeth Bennet.Junto to all this delicious music Dario Marianelli (also nominated) piano and the photography of Roman Oshin, warm, delicate, accurate. Maybe my circumstances influence too much when a judgement of value about this film, but even so, I think that he deserves my recognition as one of the best things I've seen lately. Simply, a film pleasure for all the senses. and for the heart.</body>
</review>
