<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="La máquina de bailar" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A history quite dull and simple, which despite having a couple of good moments, not leaves a good taste in mouth. It is a failed comedy that will not delight the public, except the worshipers of Santiago Segura and some other very complacent Viewer.</summary>
	<body>The truth is that the new production of Santiago Segura has a good hook: he. From there and with a trailer made me want me by this new proposal, I approached the room for what I thought was going to be an interesting comedy, but nothing further from the truth. The film of Oscar Aibar becomes a history quite dull and simple, which despite having a couple of good moments, does not leave us a good taste as us happened in previous proposals of the director of Evilio.Y one of those good times, is the starring actor and Cantabrian director Nacho Vigalondo. As a cameo and in the same underground games room which developed shock (his last film), embodies the leader of a group of fairly macarras snobs. The truth is that it is a good point of the film and more when he had no knowledge of its existence.Johnny (Santiago Segura) is another character that can provide us with a smile, but which always meets and far is Enrique Villén in a very small role.Alongside these players we have the main cast consisting of Jordi Vilches, Bárbara Muñoz Eduardo García as members of the team that will face Championship machine dance, and finally a José Corbacho become a jealous son of a bitch, well played.As defects, say that those who have played once with the "carpet" which gives us the playstation and know what is the topic, will find that he agree not for nothing his dance steps with what appears on the screen of the game, except in cases where show inserts flat machine details revealing the results and points that are getting. For small (or large) this bug, the truth seems is who might have tried to correct otherwise, from learning some theme of the game to perform the choreography or masking it more, and I say this because the choreography and the steps that mark are very professional (some made by doubles to only see the feet, but others can appreciate how the actors have had to learn to move and coordinate their movements).Ultimately "Dancing machine" is a failed comedy that will not delight the public, except the worshipers of Santiago Segura and some other very complacent Viewer.</body>
</review>
