<review author="Juan Nadie" title="World Trade Center" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Stone achieved a masterpiece of about 45 minutes lost intensity as it progresses the footage to recover the tone towards the end.</summary>
	<body>September 11, 2001. A plane of the company America Airlines United Airlines are abducted and scrambled against the World Trade Center. More than 2,000 people were killed in that attack from Al - Qaeda which shocked the world. Only two dozens of people were rescued alive from the debris of the twin towers was came down shortly after the collision. They will Jimeno (Michael Peña), agent of the authority airport of the Department of police of New York, and Sergeant John McLoughlin (Nicolas Cage) are two of those victims who managed to leave with life, after 24 hours half, to be able to tell the world that occurred on that fateful day. Director Oliver Stone has been responsible for bringing to the screen the story of these two men who fought against the death to get out of the hell of rubble and flames that were. But not only their history, but also of those hundreds of men and women who fought to find any hint of life amid the prevailing chaos.Everyone knows by now that occurred five years ago at the World Trade Center and also how lived in a city that was collapsed by the magnitude of the events. The novelty of the film is to know how experienced citizens and, above all, the security forces, who received only part of the information. They thought that it was an accident. Who came to help the first attacked Tower did not know that the same scene had been in the second. The chaos that was experienced in the scene of the tragedy is alternated with continuous images of how saw it the family and the rest of the world before the television. This part is the most interesting of all the film narrative. Stone shoots a magnificent beginning of the movie that falls when it focuses only on the lives of the two protagonists. It is not to fall in (on the other hand predictable) sentimentality but for the way in which recount the things and how the flash-back of their lives are linked with their situation under the rubble. It is too shocking and lost the drama. Although it is just recognize that this remedy is necessary to avoid the tedium of a same ongoing delirium image two people semienterradas wanting to get out of there, but they are gradually losing the hope of achieving it.Cage outboard his role seriously and little sympathetic, but his man of his duty until the last moment. While Michael Peña, touches him the role of chicano fun that some point should take charge of the situation to lend a hand to his sergeant. Both are correct and sober, but best performance is Maggie Gyllenhaal (Allison Jimeno), the wife of officer Jimeno, which reflects to perfection as it must have been the agony of the families that they did not receive news of their loved ones. Aesthetic quality (which is a lot) and narrative (slightly less) movie apart, more emotion that manages to boot Stone the Viewer is the memory. A feeling of deep sadness appears to return to see images of people launching into the void to escape the flames or the chill that runs along the back to contemplate as the first tower collapses. And, inevitably, even though it is not the intention of the director, is the memory of the Madrid bombings. The chaos, fear, outrage, solidarity?Stone achieved a masterpiece of about 45 minutes lost intensity as it progresses the footage to recover the tone towards the end. Worst of all is that for those who are not American that eternal exalted patriotism, even here, a bit exaggerated. A former marine who moves to ground zero to help in the search for victims is responsible, as no, giving life to this somewhat stale Americanism squeaking even in the midst of a tragedy as well. His final sentence to the phone says it all: "Do again?" No, not yet. "Here they will need many people to avenge this". The best, without doubt, happy for the protagonists, although only end in part.</body>
</review>
