<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Salvador" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Vibrant, emotive, splendid story against the death penalty, not in the abstract but very notably, the of of this chico dreamer who made a mistake of dream and ended up landing in a nightmare.</summary>
	<body>In 1974 the Franco regime ajusticiaba their penultimate political prisoners; and I say penultimate, and not last, as the official oblivion has been saying from this film, because we must remember that in the following year, 1975, in September, still ajusticiaría to five inmates more. It is possible that the confusion is that, while the here biografiado Puig Antich and Polish (which turned out to be the East German, reportedly) Heinz Chez were executed by garrote vil, of 1975, members of ETA and FRAP (clear, who now remembers the FRAP, and not mention of what it meant its acronym?), were shot. Out of that nuance, there goes another: this film is entitled "Salvador Puig Antich", and is thus registered in the Ministry of culture. Therefore, holder her, in plan buddy, "Salvador", as it is commonly the case in the media, is not correct. And go with the film: I have to say that I was a pleasant surprise. Expected me the typical life of Holy layman, as today, with the consequent political plan tostón pamphlet, is so common and I found, however, a film that, although their first twenty or thirty minutes do suffer from these shortcomings, with ideologization antiquated butt, from the moment in which Puig Antich is arrested, changes radically: we are then faced with the tragedy of a man certainly wrong (the utopia that pregonaba the Iberian liberation movement)(, Thousand, to which he belonged, was a careful marcianada), but that, even in the case that, as it seemed, had killed a policeman in a fracas, was had been die executed. Those who read Criticalia know of my uncompromising stand against terrorism: I am that, as said Gandhi, is of the view that there are many causes which they worth the penalty die, but none that would be worthwhile kill. Having said that, no one, not even the State, can assume the power to kill anyone; is another thing that some (which these days give the song after a fence of methacrylate?) is deserve to rot in prison? "Salvador Puig Antich" then becomes a vibrant, emotive, splendid story against the death penalty, not in the abstract but very notably, the of of this chico dreamer who made a mistake of dream and ended up landing in a nightmare. The tension will accumulate through the successive moments in which his lawyer and next are trying to avoid the finger of fate, which fatally drawn to this Catalan guy, and whose confirmation as reo's death would be given by the assassination of Carrero (which the regime decided to give a warning, although Salvador and his group had nothing to do with the famous Txikia command of ETA)(do, which was who ordered the heavens the Admiral?) It will be the point of no return. All of this is given with emotion, but without incurring the tear. The heart shrinks, but not so the central characters, only they do, AWE by terror that lies ahead and can not, even though they want to avoid crying. Beautifully recreating the era, based not only on costumes, hairdresser and props, large size (cars, locations, posters), but also of small details, the film narrates with great likelihood that deaf fear that lived in the Franco regime, when the police was not perceived by the population as a protection, as it is fortunately the case now, but as a threat. That deaf fear reflected in the face of Leonor Watling was which was then a fear insurmountable but perfectly understandable: is that stems from fear towards the total impunity with which the State, which should theoretically ensure the citizen however harassed you permanently. Brilliant realization of Manuel Huerga, since "Antarctica" is not put after the cameras – although with some perdonables bugs, is yours an address visually very creative, also with a good rhythm narrative. Performers, with special mention to Daniel Brühl, who embodies perfectly this kid got a scrubbing that overcame him; quote to Leonor Watling, always so wonderful actress, also in a little grateful role must also be.</body>
</review>
