<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="Click" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very bad movie that can cause ulcer how horrible that is. Also play with the Viewer as if this moron, from comedy to drama so inexplicable.</summary>
	<body>Mmmmmmm. click! eeeeeee. buff, yuck, argh, buff, clik! Ouch!. buff, andaaaaaa!, re-buff. I believe that it is the consistent thing I can say about 'Click', the last monstrosity starring the hint of actor that called Adam Sandler, that Yes, has many followers throughout the wide world. These precisely I would say to continue not reading the sentences that follows, the rest of the post are going. I don't want to hurt deep sensitivities, although at the end and all, to Sandler fans gives equal what I or anyone else with a head on your shoulders, can say against famous comedian (jajajajajajajaja, pussy, because it is true, makes people laugh). And given how like what stated against Sandler because you can read everything that comes next. But then do not want problems or questions of the type "Hey, and what you meant when you say that it is a plagiarism?".The argument of the thing it is very simple: we have happily married father of family but you don't have time for your family because it is clear, waiting for an important ascent in the company you are working (architect). Therefore it is not happily married. One day being desperate is helped, how magically, by a hidden clerk in a department store, which gives her a universal remote that can organize absolutely everything in his personal universe. You can download the volume to all those with which pointing with the remote control, you can make everything go slow, and you can also skip chapters of his life and go to what really interests you. Before you learn the lesson of his life it fun as nice with the mandito of the noses.Sandler must have some problem with the Frank Capra film, because it has already resorted to him on more than one occasion, putting a day (so to speak) one or another classic of the great director. But of course, there is a huge chasm between the two. Sandler did not understand the Capra film and it is likely that you have never seen, and no mistake, Sandler is not James Stewart or Gary Cooper, real heroes solitary in a type of film that today day as much as you want, and except for very rare occasions, it is not known to do. 'Click' isn't that you plan the shadow of 'what Bello is live!', it is virtually the same story, adorned with the nonsense of the command and some plot details. The nerve with which the authors of this monstrosity have plagiarized the mythical title that all Christmas us broadcast by television is duty court. Attentive to the final part of the film (well, if you see), of an embarrassing that pulls back and clearly invites get the room throwing pests. Capra is stirring in the Tomb, I have not the slightest doubt.And you me you can ask surprised, or not, but what you expect, what was good? and I can answer you that no, did not expect me, but it kept some hope with the detail of the mandito, original detail, it must be said, but badly exploited and developed. Once dissipated the doubt that the original idea will be ruined soon begin the screening, could not expect me nothing good of a film directed by Frank Coraci, who had already directed to Sandler twice, and the last, 'The Waterseller', was a very forgettable title.Script runs absolutely all topics of this type of production, and of course does it without any grace or claw. The characters are all photocopies of photocopies of the clones of the imitation of other so many characters in family ñoña film where crush us again and again that the family is the greatest thing, something that obviously is very well teach to others, but the film does not have the slightest consistency to everything stuck to shoehorn and there is what is called dramatic progressionlook at you where is what there was in the titles of Capra, which proclaimed the same moral values. But of course, things have changed a lot. Now to spread a good message the protagonist has to throw a few huge farts in the face of his boss, watch how dog fucks always the same plush (by the way, a totally accurate custom), etc, etc. The humor of these comedies kind, so call them, is poorer and less intelligent, clearer and less worked, more eschatological and less subtle. True to the film: shit, man.In its cast are the only thing salvageable from the film. No, I do not mean to Adam Sandler which continues with the same face of always playing the same role that leads his life playing and does not change or the least. Until it is likely the phrase of her character may be perfectly interchangeable in his films (okay, not named "Punch Drunk Love", hence the thing is different, but to me I look like a failed film). Kate Beckinsale walks around here as I I walk every day of my house to work and happened it to me better. What this actress has no name, but its presence is completely dispensable in this film, because her could have played it any. Moreover, there are actresses of the age of Beckinsale with many more resources than this very limited actress.Fortunately, we don Christopher Walken going big in the extent of what can, giving us his peculiar sense of humor with a character that is could have removed much more party, but clear, to Sandler should not overshadow him. Although this almost succeeds David Hasselhoff, Yes, Yes, see it to believe it. The legendary Michael Knight is splendid as the head of the main character, laughing at him/herself at all times, although in the end they forget altogether from it. The appearances of the two actors, especially the second, are the best of the film. Of course, this fails.A very bad movie that can cause ulcer how horrible that is. Also play with the Viewer as if this moron, from comedy to drama in inexplicable and totally incoherent way so many pull the cleenex and excited with a history full of nonsense. Buff.</body>
</review>
