<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="World Trade Center" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Such is my disappointment and my bemusement after seeing last night World Trade Center, Oliver Stone, I do not know where begin to narrate the multiple reasons...</summary>
	<body>Actually, such is my disappointment and my bemusement after seeing last night World Trade Center, Oliver Stone, I do not know where begin to narrate the multiple reasons.First and foremost, for which they have not seen it yet I would recommend that you siguierais not reading this post in the first place because some may fall another spoiler (although what happens in the history is already known before) and then because if watching it without prejudice is already unbearable, I do not think as it may be with some slight negative idea in mind.I have to admit that the first half hour of World Trade Center (the same as enthusiastic in Cannes) is spectacular, reflecting the widespread confusion and lack of information and resources available to the forces of order, that they had never been able to imagine that in a city like New York happened an atrocity, and.Although it is already beginning to glimpse an apparent progressive estrangement of the facts, to focus on the characters actors, which are buried beneath the rubble of the building. And when I say seeming fall from grace, is not by chance, as the film omits such highlights as who conducted the attack, under the pretext of narration only what has happened to the policemen, but there is no shortage of television images of Bush proclaiming that no one can with them, nor other phrases featuring a marine (that comment more widely), who are embarrassed.We have buried heroes, their families, suspecting that they will not return to see them, and from here on, the film is limited to show a time to some, a time to others, just so that you do not sleep with any of the situations, so repetitive and boring, that one comes to feel guilty finished yawning to some events that were actually so terrible.I have no doubt the veracity of everything what it has Word Trade Center, but it cannot be for almost two hours to two types buried under rubble, repeating endlessly "Not you sleep" while their families go the day eating, without the slightest relevant comment, no comment on what is happening, or speculate on the situation, as if had a donkey earmuffs, which prevent them from see to its around.On top of the credibility, the victims and their wives, that as it is logical to think each other constantly, and vice versa, at the same time, share the same memories with a photography bathed in a sort of lighting whitish, worthy of the worst telefilm of a Sunday afternoon.But if there were enough with the monotony, the film includes also some shameful and ridiculous moments, even to provoke laughter in the room which taking into account the theme that I was trying to, sadly take it to the extreme of absurd parody to which leads it Oliver Stone.La first scene to forget, is when appears Jesucristo with a bottle of waterbetween colored lights, in the purest style Super Star, to make matters worse, repeated twice, if someone had not been still embarrassed. Certainly in the situation that was, the police saw Christ, and what did lack, but it was necessary to display it as well? Or better said it was necessary to display it?Apparently Yes, because what is clear as is advancing the film, it is that God is with the Americans, at all times, to manifest themselves even by a former marine, listening to your call in a church, under a huge cross (after seeing Bush on TV) and rushes to the hairdresser to shave his head, surely it is very useful for a rescue.This unfortunate character, is the hero of World Trade Center, because it is the find policemen (thanks to the warning of God), bypassing all the recommendations of the rescue teams. Do to make clear its position, in his first appearance on screen we see it proclaiming "Gentlemen, we are at war" (or something similar) and the last talking on a mobile (assume that with other marines also guided by God) to avenge the sucedido.¿Era necessary to put God in this? Because I understand that you name you for issues of faith, that is at all times already that ante despair praying most of the characters, but to talk about revenge? Find it me quite outrageous, especially taking into account that Oliver Stone has not tired of repeating that did not want position politically. Goodness! Because if it comes to position itself, would have left Bush doing the final barbecue, where all are happy, and that Nicolas Cage drops a speech on evil men, and good, that serves as a perfect icing for size nonsense.In the end credits, inter alia appears that the marine in question went to the Iraq war (which had already been quite clear), and finally the film dedicated to all victims of the offending, but at that time it is too late, because the majority of the people has left the room, after seeing a typical americanadathat did not no need that was located in the 11 September attacks.When learned me he was going to make this movie as soon, seemed not very right, because still latent footprint that remains of what happened, and if something is appreciated to Stone, is not having fallen in the morbid, nor having hurgado in the wounds with lurid images or shocking. For that we have already had the reality. But to do what he has done, nor it seems at all, which has been worthwhile.</body>
</review>
