<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="La increíble historia de Caperucita Roja" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sins of irregular, because the balance leans towards the first hour: intense, rapid, with spark and turning around to all the referents of literature and cinema.</summary>
	<body>As Shrek this entertaining production unleashes our ties to the universe of legends, making that it tambalee. When we have already visited this area of fantasy accompanied by traditional guides, comes to meet ingenious and courageous proposals, i.e. outside almost all the clichés and prejudices, causing our cognitive acuity.By the way make the argument, the incredible but true! Little Red Riding Hood story reminds the of who framed Roger Rabbit? but not being of Comic characters in keeping with that in his day raised tapes as the Princess Bride and the recent the secret of the Brothers Grimm. Begins with an alternative to the classic story of the girl entering the House of his grandmother, solving an enigma that has little to do with expected: someone is boycotting the network of bakeries of the forest; the suspects include a journalist, an aspiring actor, a distributor of sweets with other sights and a not so anchored grandmother in her role. This police plot formed the genesis of the story that we all know, but the child classic has been revised. If it were a dish, the result would be a deconstruction of the traditional ingredients product: are the same, but presented differently. This exercise of animation in 3-D peca of irregular, that the balance is tilted towards the first hour: intense, rapid, with spark and turning around to all the referents of literature and cinema. Rupture of schemes that is not continued during the denouement, flat and predictable, a simple resolution away from hilarious original research. Altogether, the incredible. It proposes a fun trip to the forest imagined thanks to thousands of oral stories and reflected on paper first by Charles Perrault and later by the Grimm. The adaptation takes the premise of "not missing nor a detail": the grass moves with the gentle breeze, also Caperu double basses. It rewinds the action and the versions of the same fact review with ease, including winks to pursue the laugh. And we do not forget irreverent characters such as the goat sentenced to eternal singing make their appearance in the adventure. As usual, the weight of the dubbing in the Spanish version is entrusted to very known as Leonor Watling, Amparo Baró and Carlos Latre actors, but Anabel Alonso, the famous Dori in finding Nemo, who better lends his voice to a minor but essential character: an accelerated squirrel called Balita, as all the characters, contributing to associate the traditional tale in contemporary audiovisual narrative schemes employed in video clips and TV spots.</body>
</review>
