<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Vete de mi" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Knowing that in an unfair manner, the title will pass unnoticed in the stream of releases on the Bulletin Board, we can only strongly recommend attending this homemade war as an observer in no man's land.</summary>
	<body>Ingredients to make a good cake: three solid actors, a conflict situation and a director with accurate look ready to roll without brake to interpretive flow. Join the idea that there is no argument more interesting than life itself, so the actors are puppets in a little theater which we know well. One of them takes the role that receives the slaps on the face of the other two. It is Juan Diego, which makes us believe that you dealing with the situation posed you, because it even has occasion to focus on acids winks to the theatre and the leisure industry. This is a bittersweet film of parents and children: is the second Director of the pupil by José Luis García Sánchez and trace a problem of enormous proportions when a child decides to occupy the House of his father. A from there, the existence of pathetic as we know it, with their misery, grace, and their successes, which also cause laughter. Few tapes exude a humor so subtle and real as this exercise featuring a not so young compulsive liar and an adult whose life falls apart, or arranged, as you look at it. The melodramatic tone connects with the idea of fun is responsible for the more unfortunate that glory excellent? his debut as Director and screenwriter. Meta-Theater Gallery of secondary characters supports the comic moments, but beyond this, their reactions are all stunned witness logics. We are too: see how the family, unstructured once, is dissects member to Member, the head of the family including lover. The naturalistic, realistic, approach is not diluted until the end, with a curious and suggestive sequence that we will not give more details. It is of course veteran Sevillian actor who now is the role of father lost in its principles. It supports almost the entire weight of the footage, without forgetting the plot skeleton designed by Jonás Trueba. Knowing that in an unfair manner, the title will pass unnoticed in the stream of releases on the Bulletin Board, we can only strongly recommend attending this homemade war as an observer in no man's land.</body>
</review>
