<review author="Verolindapechocha" title="El diablo viste de Prada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am sure that will male find so hilarious this story as the girls.</summary>
	<body>Again, the lovely actress Anne Hathaway (diary of a Princess / Brokeback Mountain) is measured with an artist of weight as the great Meryl Streep, who this time portraying the devil, a cold and ruthless editor of the most costly and influential New York.The Devil Wears Prada (2006) fashion magazine, translated as the Devil Wears Prada, it is the story of Andy (Anne Hathaway)a young journalist graduated from the University, who seeks to open up the way in some written form of the big city, with her boyfriend (Adrian Grenier), a contender to chef.Here should be something separate to say that guy Grenier not him reaching or heels to your partner's screen. I have the impression that the Lords of the casting too focused on the female performers.In the end. Andy after sending many resumes, is called by a publishing house, which among other things manages the aforementioned magazine, commanded by the cruel and scary winter Queen, Miranda (Meryl Streep), a name that is synonymous with everything the big fashion icons represent. A word yours, a gesture can mean the rise or fall in Tailspin of designers, models, photographers and anyone engaged in the ruthless world of fashion.Human resources "mistakenly" sent to Andy for the post of second personal assistant of Miranda: literally be your 24/7 slave, not ask questions and always wear fashion. "Andy is obviously not a girl on cover (vale would in desgreñar her a little, however, in my opinion, it still saw very beautiful) is not at all interested in the frivolities of a job, but need to work to pay the rent and thinks that this magazine in a good way to start contacting the world media in the city.""Any girl kill for this work, if raisins a year you can here, working in the environment you want," warns the first Assistant of Miranda, Emily (Emily Blunt), another of his slaves, whose only dream is to go to Paris for fashion week and get the most out of designer wedding dresses.Little by little and to survive, the sweet and innocent Andy is changing in a seemingly as cold as the rest workhólica, no time for her boyfriend, his friends, nor to write. I do not more because it is worth seeing her. I am sure that they have so much fun as I do. Although it could be catalogued as a "chick flick" I would recommend it to everyone. I am sure that will male find so hilarious this story as the girls.Interpretations of the two protagonists are great, it is rumored that Meryl Streep would be nominated for an Oscar for this role. Really Meryl rectified outweigh its mediocre role in the also recently released and included, Prime.</body>
</review>
