<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El viento que agita la cebada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Without being perfect, is very good. And, above all, necessary. As necessary are directors and writers who, like Loach and Laverty, still believe that another world is possible.</summary>
	<body>When Ken Loach presented his last and committed film in the last edition of the Cannes Festival, not provoked great acclaim among critics moved to the French Riviera. However, when he was awarded the Palme d'Or for best film presented in competition, nor was tainted no one hands to the head.And that may be the best summary of a film "100% made in Loach", with a heavy political burden, starring the village people, village in this case, which is obliged to take decisions, which discusses and defends with passion and vehemence his ideas, which faced the established power, fight, fights, kills and stands firm in his principles and beliefs.To tell part of the story of the IRA, when he was the real Irish Republican Army in the 1920s hard, and for narrating the civil war in which Ireland after the signing of the Treaty of peace with the British was engulfed, Loach and its header, also very committed Paul Laverty, screenwriter taking as protagonists to two brothers who, while they start fighting together, end up taking directions separate and independent in their lives.Personally, Ireland fascinates me. Everything that has to do with the Erin green, from its Celtic cosmogony to its music, its literature, its pubs, Guinness, its landscapes. and its history, of course.A beautiful and tragic history in that the green of the grass, unfortunately, has been usually dyed with blood red. And why a movie like "The wind that shakes the barley" had all the ballots to like me. And I like it. I like the point of view of adopting Loach and Laverty, staying always with a persons foot, rather than tell us the great epics of the recognized heroes and historical leaders. I like the realism that transmit their images, sometimes even too stark. I like the players who choose to play the roles, always so credible and confident in his convictions as tender and fragile in their performances. I like the mix of tenderness and hardness which printed some sequences and the feeling of deja vu that leave the black uniforms, once expelled the English persimmons. And I like the end: terrible, bare, without room for the granting or melodrama.And yet what I had liked in other Loach films, the protagonists in this Assembly and libertarian discussions end up getting tired me. By repetitive and too elongated. And concentrated. The Laverty and Loach want to give voice to all the characters, allowing each to explain their reasons and their point of view is very honest. "But, in the end, the film ends up being too discursive, by many and repetitive situations posed.""The wind that shakes the barley" is one of those movies that, without being perfect, is very good. And, above all, necessary. As necessary are directors and writers, such as Loach and Laverty, still think that another world is possible and that a film camera or a computer keyboard can be a weapon more effective than a kalashnikov or a uzi or both.For that reason, alone already deserve our consideration, respect, admiration and appreciation.</body>
</review>
