<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Palindromos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not let indifierente: cala in any type of public, even one that does not connect with a stimulating director as few (twisted) mind.</summary>
	<body>Solondz has an exquisite sense of risk, a self-satisfied responsibility that is narrative based on the journey of a girl. He is not a physical journey, although the film desmembra in a fantastic range of scenarios: what evidence is a very well trabada and staged denunciation of the world of childhood.It enlivens Victor, the protagonist, wants to be a mother. Straitened family life censors their desires for what it is bound to seek the realization of their dreams on the street. It will not be easy. In fact, it will not be possible.Solondoz pull a character who interpret many actresses. Trafficking (imagine) that everyone can feel us accomplices of their vital expertise. Attempts to (I insist) to create an empathy, a natural state of affairs, a sophisticated, but minimalist in the background, reconciliable exercise with all the vices which the spectator leads to the room so that the film leaves no indifierente: cala in any type of public, even one that does not connect with a stimulating director as few (twisted) mindwhich he explores in the human soul and extract from it the most sensitive material, the less contaminated by social constraints, political or sentimental.Using the figure of the Palindrome as the title of this cuasicircense Pirouette also has its Crumb. The Palindrome is the phrase that reads just as the right to backwards. "Ana brings to bear the hazelnut".It is the metaphor that we are all equal: that there is no journey, that there is no change.You will want the comfortable spectator, done so are you in the food mascadita. Here requires a provisioning of good intentions, some complicity ethical and aesthetic.Or is that this is a film of Championship, will not succeed in box, as did neither Happiness or Bienvenido to the wrists, the other creations of this unclassifiable author box. There is, however, an indolence in the portrayal of situations more dramatic when not scabrous, of the plot. Sees everything, sometimes excessively distant, cold, hieratic almost. There is no heat: is obvious the component by hand of human emotions, which is the naturalness. All very well compartmentalized, stanchion: everything ready so that we do not know if we are witnessing modern fairy tale or an urban legend.I have very clear is that when one has finished the movie, the runrún of its history colea in memory, hammering our placid bourgeois life of citizens pleased with the gentleness of this (false) the welfare State, cacareado by democratic Governments as seal of the House.</body>
</review>
