<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Palindromos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You may not like us, but there is the narrative capacity of a complex filmmaker, that puts us on the brink of the abyss to try us.</summary>
	<body>The director of the well valued Hapiness achieves its purpose of breaking us schemes with this story about a girl who wants to be a mother in a world full of fierce creatures. It seems easy to recommend a film hanging over paedophilia, conservatism and the desire for freedom in American society. Easier even if in addition it is well shot and has good performances. But in this case costs for one simple reason: Todd Solondz is an director complicated and quite exhibitionist, accustomed to introduce us in labyrinth or dreamy, frames that transform simple and palpable in implicit. And that, if played with the truth unpolished, gives too many headaches. We started by the literary game which consists of treasured words or phrases that read the same left to right, than from right to left. If Julio Medem introduced us to Anne and Otto in the lovers of the Arctic Circle, Solondz trust its protagonist, Aviva, six different actresses and uses the figure of metaphorical and less clear way. Funny? In itself it is the film as a whole: the main quality of the filmmaker is not exactly the indifference. Clarification of the title aside, what did realize us will be the mania of the filmmaker to nervous. So get going direct to the germ of history? the identity of one's self, which remains unalterable - although stopping at poetic corners where we want to convince that we are confused. The tone of fantasy isn't shrouded in bitterness and cruelty-free. As the most accurate fable and adult, he robs life of beautiful things and presents it naked. You may not like us, but there is the narrative capacity of a complex filmmaker, that puts us on the brink of the abyss to try us. The thing is that we like the idea that we threaten and removed the bandage from the eyes in such a way. Then, if we let go, is what proposes Solondz: in life, as much as one strengthen in change, always comes back to the point of origin. But that's another story within the flow of sensations that causes this unclassifiable film.</body>
</review>
