<review author="Plissken" title="Gracias por fumar" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Jason Reitman has surpassed his father (of agreement, was not too difficult) with only a comedy, coated fable amoral and provocative. Comedy of the year and serious candidate for the title of film of the year.</summary>
	<body>'Thank you for smoking' (2005), opera prima of Jason Reitman (son of Ivan Reitman), begins with a magnificent credit titles, a country song is that not going behind and first 15 minutes simply unforgettable, halfway between starts great 'Uno de los nuestros' and 'Magnolia'. "Exaggerated", you say. Not expect to check it on DVD, I tell you. There are more satire and venom in these fifteen minutes than in the rest of the world film production that far this year. And there is more.On the basis of the eponymous book by Christopher Buckley, Jason Reitman, it tells the story of Nick Naylor (Aaron Eckhart overwhelming), Vice-President of the Academy of tobacco studies (funded by the tobacco industry, of course) and official spokesman for the industry in United States. He knows that it is one of the most hated men in (North) America, but does not care, because it is the best in his work: convince the general public that tobacco critics are wrong. Naylor and his friends Polly and Bobby Jay (fun Maria Bello and David Koechner), defenders of the alcohol and armament industries colleagues, gather often to presume who causes more deaths per year. His twelve year son (Cameron Bright finally making "normal child") seems interested in follow in their footsteps. Its ambitious plan to bring tobacco to the film has been approved. The life of Nick is perfect, leaving aside the lack of values or the amorality of some of their actions. But the downside of being the type more hated in the country is that there are many people looking forward to fall.In just 100 minutes, Reitman Gets a dazzling formal and impeccable film in his speech, which is none other that support freedom of thought and choice. As non smokers, but each and every one of us, exposed to continuous handling media and pressures of all signs. 'Thank you for smoking' satirizes and challenge to all those involved in one of those "great debates" of public opinion, and achieved the same Viewer to understand the twisted logic of the protagonist, if it fails to adopt her: no position is inherently good or bad, only it is think and then choose what they want to defend, because everything is defensible in this manipulated world. Debatable, incidentally, also this last resort. But that is.And returning to the film: blossoms secondary players on characters with just a couple of sequences (the already appointed friends and partners of the "merchants of death Squadron"; the aceradísima criticism of the current Hollywood carried out by Rob Lowe and Adam Brody; imposing Robert Duvall as capo of the tobacco and Sam Elliot as cancerous Marlboro man; or the hilarious William H. Macy as Senator Finistirre cheater)elegant planning &amp; photography, design production as venomous as the text itself (the poster of the bar where they meet the merchants of death). All at great height.Jason Reitman has surpassed his father (of agreement, was not too difficult) with only a comedy, coated fable amoral and provocative. Comedy of the year and serious candidate for the title of film of the year. A 9'5</body>
</review>
