<review author="Plissken" title="Sheitan" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Enjoyable if you not compare it with recent summits of the genus</summary>
	<body>Sheitan is the Persian name for Satán. And it is also the name of the hip hop group punkorro listen to the protagonists in the movie called. 'Sheitan' (2006), first foray into length short French film maker Kim Chapiron which has counted with some godfathers of exception: Vincent Cassel (Executive producer and star of the show) and Monica Bellucci, nothing less.The film focuses on recent clichés fantasy film, and especially of the francophone. A group of young men lost in the French countryside (on Christmas Eve, once again) are witnesses of bizarre acts perpetrated by the no less bizarre inhabitants of the lost village.The argument should leave it there, although those who have already enjoyed more than recommended 'Calvaire' of the Belgian Fabrice Du Welz, 'The House of 1,000 corpses', playful directorial debut of Rob Zombie, or any of the films of the current 'number one' of the genre, Alexandre AJA, know by where they are going to go the shots. Too, perhaps.The hipervitaminado rhythm of 'Sheitan' works until the feeling of "déjà vu" prevent surprise with the history, unless the song moments walking towards the umpteenth re-release of 'Texas Chainsaw Massacre'. The function is only animated by the presence of the winding and completely hypnotic Roxane Mesquida, my particular discovery throughout the film, and above all by a guiñolesco and pasadísimo of laps Vincent Cassel. Otherwise, simply correct young "malotes" endangered, and sufficiently disturbing the "rednecks" French as to give bad roll. In terms of art and photography, new shows French of what you can do with four hard and visual talent, the style of the appointed AJA and Du Welz, although he is sometimes guilty of "astonishing".Sin_embargo, when the film navigates towards the more routine routine, that ubiquitous third act of "correcalles" of the American teenage slashers, Chapiron holds for us horny last six minutes that work almost alone, which makes you think that) the seventy initial minutes were filling; (and B) well look, it wasn't so bad, and addition is small, and in addition I have fun.By the way, like 'Calvaire', 'Sheitan' also comes loaded with religious, but less subtle symbolism. And could even be a theological re-reading the always clear. That step face Monsieur Chapiron if, I. Enjoyable if you not compare it with recent summits of the genre. A 6.</body>
</review>
