<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps pantry some things and the truth is that it is not very well resolved but we must acknowledge that one doesn't think too about it while it is fun, for more than two hours, with cinema entertainment good.</summary>
	<body>Although he followed regularly, the truth is that I was never a fan of "Corruption in Miami" (series). Even so, the name of Michael Mann as director is, to me, enough reason to go to the movies so I went to see "Corruption in Miami" (the film) hoping to find me with a good action film but without expectations of being before a masterpiece. Once again, Mann not disappointed me. I won't go into details of the synopsis because in reality it is unimportant. "Miami Vice", the film, could well be an episode of the series, because it begins with the end of a mission and as who says, ends with a mission without end. In such a way that, although it seems unlikely, not it would cost them nothing write the script for a sequel to the film.Isn't the story, I repeat, what matters here. What matters is that we we have a film for more than two hours filled with good action scenes, very well directed, which are very few in the film each year. There are also site in the film for intimate moments and a romantic story in which Mann gives rein to his capacity for visual poetry. Some levels are really beautiful though without reaching the height of this absolute masterpiece entitled "The dilemma".The actors are good because they could not be otherwise. Colin Farrell is a good actor but if you also give the role of guaperas cool it is not uncommon that it edge. Jamie Foxx making hard with heart will have not so been difficult to keep up, in the same way that Gong Li arrives with showing only a pinch of his talent to compose a mysterious and attractive character. Legendary Lieutenant Castle, Edward James Olmos in the series, is here played by Barry Shabaka Henley, supporting actor in which worth look because it uses wisely the minutes appearing on-screen in his recent films ("The Terminal" or "Collateral") for example.I can not mention the good role played by the always wonderful Luis Tosar in a short role, but enough to impress with his presence on screen. There are times in which authentic frightens. Anecdote for attentive spectators: in a moment of the film, his character appears reading a newspaper (seemed "La Voz de Galicia") news about Amancio Ortega Gaona and Inditex, in a clear nod to the Spanish public and especially Galician.You should not ask for anything more to this film, but already it seems to me little. Perhaps pantry some things and the truth is that it is not very well resolved but we must acknowledge that one doesn't think too about it while it is fun, for more than two hours, with cinema entertainment good.</body>
</review>
