<review author="Robgordon" title="Salvador" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The constant search for the tear of the spectator by the director, lengthens the film and makes it unbearable. In any case, and despite this final error?Salvador? It contains great virtues that make it one of the most prominent national films of this year.</summary>
	<body>Since 1995 Manuel Huerga was not placed behind the camera. It was with "Antarctica", starring Ariadna Gil, film which earned him a nomination for the Goya as best new Director. Despite the good reviews and recognition for his debut film, Huerga has left that eleven years transcurriesen to return to directing. "And it has done so with"Salvador Puig Antich,"which Huerga shows have evolved according to the times, despite its limited presence in the film world.""Salvador" is a film that is clearly influenced by the aesthetics and narrative of American cinema. Something (it resemble the yankee film) Spanish cinema has always tried to with an unequal luck and what now, Huerga and their "Savior" leave more than carry the day.It could be argued that "Savior" is tape successor Miguel Courtois "Wolf" and the first heir to the "Munich" by Spielberg, to which aims to look at all times.The history of this martyr of the last stirrings of Francoism was a material with many possibilities for the film. And taking the life of Puig Antich, recounted in "Cuenta atrás." «The story of Salvador Puig Antich» of Francesc Escribano, Huerga has composed a thriller and at the same time a prison film, as well as also, a portrait of that troubled time and a family drama with susceptibility to easy tear.During the first half of "Salvador" attended the youth of the future militant "M.I.L" (Iberian liberation movement), interpreted by a given Daniel Bruhl, wherein we know his loves, his family and friends, as well as its entry to the anarchist group and their subsequent actions. All this, this narrated with a good rhythm, a most perfect setting, and a suitable picture.And it is that in this stretch of tape, the good use of Visual Media, Assembly and staging of "Salvador", exceed much of national productions.It is also the first time to tape outlining the birth of personality and beliefs of Salvador, which led him to fight against the, still extant, Franco dictatorship. Huerga opts for a tone of tribute did the character, without going into a strong Manichaeism, something that moves away it of becoming a political film. Note that the interest of its director is another. Flees documentary tone, introduces a voice off and narra flashbacks, which makes "Salvador" a biopic of the taste of Hollywood and atypical in our country. "Something that has brought complaints from some sectors, which have been used for the figure of Puig Antich commercial purposes, and on the other hand, been to the liking of the public at large.""Salvador" in addition, as a historical document of the last years of the Franco regime, works by inserting events, situations and repressions, taken from that context and perfectly assembled in the film gear, something that gives a great result to Huerga.Ya in the second half, "Salvador" becomes a prison tape, and with it the appearance of Leonardo Sbaraglia as one of the jailers. The relationship to be established between Bruhl and Argentine actor, is the best of the film. A high-flying interpretative duel, in which once again, Sbaraglia composed a good character, which is intimate and emotional in the evolution of the treatment with Puig Antich. Too bad this is the only success of this final part of "Salvador", which is missing completely losing its last half hour.The constant search for the tear of the spectator by the director, lengthens the film and makes it unbearable. Huerga strives to prolong the footage unnecessarily, with long sequences of the Sisters of Puig Antich, recurring appearances of his lawyer (another good performance, in this case of Tristan Ulloa) and fanfare Visual (such as rain and wet in the cemetery Roses), do not do than spoil the good work carried out during the film, giving it a forced tone cakes.In any case, and despite this final error, "Salvador" contains great virtues that make it one of the most prominent national films of this year, as well as a good demonstration that Spain is possible to make a film that does not have anything to envy, as your invoice, to movies yankee. A Ribbon recommended and in a way, a small but significant, step forward for the Spanish film.</body>
</review>
