<review author="Taliesin" title="Vete de mi" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Juan Diego acts so naturally that it seems at times that you're continuously improvising. A simple and nearby, story based on a script with good pace and some magnificent performances.</summary>
	<body>On the one hand we have a son, portrayed by Juan Diego Botto, than to his thirty and few years all that has been done is paste living the high life at the expense of the money from his mother. On the other we have to his father, who gives life Juan Diego, a stage actor in the twilight of his career that his sixty long years living a quiet life with her partner. A morning son is encaloma in the father's House after many years in which just have been. From there is renewed a relationship that never really existed. This is what counts Vete de MI. No more, no less. There are other actors in this movie and do very well, but the two Juan Diegos are those that send on screen. No matter that they are in the father's House, in a bar or in a brothel, this Opera is written for two characters and they could be talking about the weather, keeping the interest of the Viewer. But it is that, in addition, they say things. Not trying to big issues, limited to talk about themselves, but with an interpretative force that makes that not matter. Without diminishing the work of Botto, you notice the tables of Juan Diego, who acts so naturally that it seems at times that you're continuously improvising. When this happens it is because the work of actor and director close to perfection and so is in Vete de MI. Among the secondary luxury, apart from José Sazatornil Saza, is Rosa María Sardá. With a discreet role that it has only three or four sentences, Catalan actress shows that follows in the form and we have wanted to see it in a role protagonist in their category. Ultimately, Vete de MI is a story simple and nearby, based on a script with good pace and some magnificent performances. Combines with much success humor with more dramatic moments, that reach the pathos. Without doubt, a great job for the first feature film directed by Victor García León (son of Rosa León, of the mouse found Martin). And above all, it's further proof that Spanish cinema has nothing to envy and that there is life beyond Alatristes and torrents. Curiosities: The work of Juan Diego has received the Concha de Plata in the latest edition of the San Sebastian Film Festival. Recommended audience: it's a film based on the interpretation and the screenplay, with zero percent of action. You know where you get, but it is worthwhile to go with something different.</body>
</review>
