<review author="Dino" title="Brokeback mountain" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Me you will think that the Academy gives this film the Oscar to the best of the year</summary>
	<body>You will think that the Academy gives this film the Oscar to the best of the year. It is the first of the five nominees that I have opportunity to see, but not let the bar too high. Me has been, to some extent, a slight disappointment, because despite all the good that has had the movie, just three noteworthy things: a premise striking to sell at the box office (the love story of two Cowboys), the consistent interpretation of Heath Ledger (decent for the Oscar) and the fabulous direction of Ang Lee. Yes, the story is told with the mastery of the Taiwanese director; another story is the content of his fabulous ways this vacuum or, as in this case, very cheater.The story is, as the English would say "tricky", cheat. It is not fair to the Viewer. Tries to create in us the feeling of the heterosexual lives of the cowboys are miserable, boring, insubstantial, pesarosas, and living in them forced by a reality of the 1960's unfair. And of course, their torrid encounters on the bare mountain are the escape route to achieve happiness. That I call it conditional to the Viewer so that it justifies an action that needs justification on the other hand. They say that the story speaks of love. PSE. I do not think that Jack Twist in Mexico would love.Let's go by parts. What try us have the film? Apparently, he tries to sell that love is superior to any circumstance or condition, and is able to sprout between two rough Cowboys. I saw no need to paint the western rose, but if we want to see a treatise of love, just look at how John Wayne looks at the woman of his brother in "Desert Centaurs", looks full of feelings, but with the heart shrunk to know is his sister-in-law, and that above feelings is the family. Note, with a look we understood as well as seeing to Ennis and Jack inside the tent.And as in itself history account nothing more, besides the Treaty of film tempo and photography which itself constitutes the tape, the rest is empty, pure emptiness intended to be filled with our digestion of doses of unpleasantries that Ang Lee we will prescribing sparingly. Certainly not I has enthused, but it seems not a horror film. Perhaps look at it so that when someone comes with hard enthusiasm to speak of him, we know exactly that it is not for both.</body>
</review>
