<review author="Ana" title="Nueve vidas" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Anthology of short stories interwoven very subtly.</summary>
	<body>Five years after "Things you can tell just by looking at her" [things you can only say looking at] Rodrigo García has a very similar film. "Nine Lives" [nine lives] is also an anthology of short stories which are interwoven but very subtly. Composed by tension-laden moments that through a fraction achieve show you a life. "Every woman is a universe". This film format is unusual in the manner of the collections of short stories and shares much of the intensity of their language. García participated in the scripts of Sundance lab and is an independent film because to major studios, like publishers, do not like risk.The premise of each story speaks of how we are connected to each other. A couple is reunited in a supermarket there is something between them, there is no room in their lives for approaching, and at the same time do not want to let go. A woman getting ready to enter the operations room download his anger with her husband, trying to get away to the nearest person in a difficult time. While "Things" is a film of disconnected characters; "Nine Lives" is about what that connects us to each other. And it does so using a direct language and dialogues with strong emotional loads. Underlined with intense non-verbal language, which is and can be understood.A character watches a documentary about animals and says that "this Lion look to the zebras." "But the truth is that the zebras were filmed 2 weeks later in another country." Not in this film. The story of each one of the nine players in a single take approximately ten minutes. And the shots are interesting, which means that they are carefully choreographed and planned to walk into a supermarket and a funeral. Also a time in which two couples have a conversation is ingenious and you can see all the characters because behind the couch where these sitting a couple there is a mirror. Long shots maintain continuity and created a peculiar rhythm. Although some of the texture of the film not term I like and I thought that it would be digital, but filmed in Super16.Este film was low-budget and seems that the escritor-director has won this cast based on complex and interesting characters for an actor. So many great actresses: Dakota Fanning, Holly Hunter, Glenn Close and Kathy Baker. Everyone wins.</body>
</review>
