<review author="Silvia" title="Separados" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More bitter than sweet, separated is the portrait of an episode in the life of one couple either. A step beyond in the genre of romantic comedies.</summary>
	<body>Boy meets girl. They fall in love, argue, are separated, but in the end love can with all the problems and the couple ends together again at the beginning. So are the majority of romantic comedies that have passed through our screens. But not you ye have wondered never what happens with these couples a few years later? How they sobrellevarán the routine? Or, what happens when there are hobbies, reproach or the daily small quarrels?Separate part of the moment when a couple decides to leave their relationship after two years of cohabitation. So, the movie - despite the issue of the relationship between parejas-no remains the classic plot scheme of romantic comedies, so it becomes a romantic anticomedia.The film tells the story of Gary (Vince Vaughn) and Brooke (Jennifer Aniston), two people who, despite being diametrically opposed (she works in a gallery of modern art and he is bus tour guide) happily share their lives. Everything goes well until one day, after a trivial discussion, end up breaking the relationship. Pride, none of the two prisoners will be ready to leave the apartment they share, by which he dedicated to boycott in order to throw to the other apartment. In this peculiar war remain, are given the most comical situations from the film.With a quite brilliant dialogues for than usual in this type of movies, separated a step beyond in the genre of romantic comedies. The film could be categorized as comedy-drama, although in my opinion, has much more drama to comedy. Of course that there are moments of humor, but are short breaks of the bitterness that emerges from the history. What is surprising this kind of films - such as the highly recommended "The man of the time" - is the enormous capacity we laugh the outside misfortunes, a smile that fails to be cruel but causes by the contemplation of the vital disasters of the protagonists.Bitter sweet, separated is the portrait of an episode in the life of any couple, with real scenes as life itself, without idealizations and late romantic fairy tale. The viewer who feels to see the history of these characters has the feeling to be attending the actual breakdown of a relationship.</body>
</review>
