<review author="Berto" title="Mi super ex novia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A real shame, that a movie with a very good starting point, taking advantage of the huge amount of films about superheroes, is wasted in such a way.</summary>
	<body>Ivan Reitman had its moments of glory by the 1980s with these easy comedies that were so successful. Ghostbusters, dangerously together and the Twins hit two times were directed by him and had a more than acceptable success at the box office. Since then and except for 6 days, 7 nights and evolution, it hasn't have any drinking project between hands.It is a genuine shame, that a movie with a very good starting point, taking advantage of the huge amount of films about superheroes, is wasted in such a way, but above all and as always say usually be from the screenwriter of turn that stays in the easy joke and fails to go a little further. Who is never imagine how it would privacy both superhero? As ligaría Wonder Woman or Elektra? Because from here part the film, presenting us with a girl G, which would be the envy in any Marvel superhero powers, but that head the truth that this theme very bad. In addition, situations that develop in the film are totally naïve, on the basis of the way in which both are known, as the reasons why the protagonist leaves her. Luke Wilson is totally unbearable throughout the film, the roll that brings now I like now I dont want to is so poorly defined that makes very little credible to her character, besides the fact that it is not working the most minimum to give a bit of personality. Uma Thurman, great among the great, performs a salvageable normalito, only role by these ready savages of madness and jealousy that give from time to time and which are in terms of performance of the film the best of times. Anna Faris, star of the films Scary Movie this much for this to show off captivations and little more, more stereotyped she could not her character, stereotyped as the best friend of the protagonist, Rainn Wilson, as forgettable as the rest of the film. Separate chapter deserves Professor Beldam, Chica Némesis G and which could not be the copy more simplistic that a good Lex Luthor might have been, any bad of a Van Damme movie has more presence than this supervillain (lo super is a say?)The bad script nauseam, starting very well with the approach of mixing Fatal attraction with any superhero movie, is quickly reduced to a gracieta no sense in which the only thing interesting are notable special effects as regards powers of girl G. Ultimately, a pity the movie from a great idea has become a very simplistic comedy.</body>
</review>
