<review author="Berto" title="La increíble historia de Caperucita Roja" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very entertaining film that demonstrates two things: that neither animation is exclusively for children, and stories, by well known they are, might be counted in a totally fresh and surprising way.</summary>
	<body>The cinema of animation has always been considered for a child audience. Do since the advent of Shrek on our screens, many people changed the chip insofar that I publish this kind of films, is directed which knew well already fans of the anime?The case is arrives to our screens, and under the envelope of what would be a review of one of the children's classics more loved by all of us, little Red Riding Hood, or as her call in this film, Caperu, from now on, the incredible but true story of little Red Riding Hood, takes already with the title, that although it is animation, hides more than typical amusement for children.The film baby sources of great classics of all time in terms of narrative structure, now come to mind, Rashomon, captives of the evil or Citizen Kane, since the story this told from four different points of view, the lumberjack, the Granny, the Wolf and the own Caperu because as if in a chapter of CSI wereThis police in full investigation of an evil that is dedicated to stealing recipes cooking throughout the forest, and at full scene of the crime to try to discover that it hides each one of them and if anyone really is behind these terrifying thefts who are leaving to forest with nothing sweet to carry to the mouth.The film is not have an excessive bad milk, can be easily seen by the kids of the House, but if that can mislead them the history itself, because the relationship with the original story are the protagonists and little else? Tucked in the garlic have an actor of ads, an undercover journalist, an addict to the risk, and of course a bad malísimo that only in the last moments of the film revealed their Machiavellian plans James Bond style. In the movie there continuous winks to other titles more or less known, being one of the best dedicated to Triple xXx, although it may even be a game to discover details of other films that the filmmakers have left throughout the footage.In short, a very entertaining movie, which shows two things, that neither animation is exclusively for children, stories, by well known they are, might be counted in a totally fresh and surprising way.</body>
</review>
