<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Serpientes en el avión" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fast film food in its purest form. A solemnity bad movie. I escuece when we see it and escuece hours later when we wonder what dark reasons we move, on occasions, to betray our faithfulness to the good movies.</summary>
	<body>If by something we must remember snakes on the plane in the future will be for his back more that the same film in itself. Esfast film food in its purest form: a pizza four stations that we eat in a serious den, but we devour with gluttony because, besides the fact that hungry, move us lower passions, not comentables vices. We all have, at bottom, an aftertaste cuasimasoquista to see film garbage, and along the way, enjoy of its pathos, of his resignation accepted quality. Snakes on a plane is a solemnity bad film. I escuece when we see it and it escuece hours later when we wonder what dark reasons we move, on occasions, to betray our fidelity to the good cinema, cinema who says things and tells them in Nice shape, with beauty.The back to which I refer is his trap, the starting point for their misleading script as it turns out, dear reader of this page of cinema, which nobody has written the screenplay has been written by all. That is, New Line Cinema, parents of the monstrosity, the novel perpetraton idea dig screenwriter in the network, offer bits of the film that the surfer, true depository of the ruthless machinery of Hollywood, contributes his bread crumb or his entire according to want to bar, as wit.They were blogs, and not the narrative ability of a kind locked in the attic of his house, which discussed the puzzle of the plot, although missing pieces and those that are are manidas, oxidized, eaten by a lethal rust. If this is the way that they will go the shots in the cinema of the future, I head back to the glorious past, which both pleasure it has given to my concerns. Back to the classics and to those who, not so, exude honesty, wanting to check a decent product that can entertain (the film is many things, but above all is entertainment). Snakes on the plane will be remembered by his back door (I insist) and because our Elsa Pataky, blonde Bonbon that Garci knew how to take advantage of Ninette, appears in three loose of the footage in its first USA.Plethoric youth of adrenaline that wants to be dumped to a roller coaster of ophidia assassins in a unusual framework (! a plane!) will be satisfied their demands. Others, which come, young or talluditos with more than one finger in front and three quarters of mastermind to not admit that they fooled them with so much effrontery, not go to the Chamber: not dilapidarán euros of sacrifice.If we explain exclusion the bizarre apparatus of marketing that secunda, snakes on the plane had entered directly on the shelves of the video shops in neighborhood, along with Jackie Chan, Steven Seagal and that muscular Pleiad of actors of fifth category that thicken their accounts with foxes viewers that do not ask much something as serious as it is the cinema. We ignore if aware of a this draught pigswill swallowing irreparable mode affect the palate of the teenager who is her swallow, without French fries or half a litre of coca-cola light.There is even a snake that sneaks under the skirts of a sleeping Lady, between dream and dream, think see your fantasies clitoridianas served. Here (in this metaphor of the crude) the true symbol of this thing. I do not know if forgive to Samuel l. Jackson, who I really dazzled in Pulp Fiction, which I loved in Jackie Brown (ay Tarantino, that you are at all), but the hand opens single and $ fall like manna from heaven for the ignorant. Up Anaconda, another serie B neighborhood video store, entertained me more. It will be by Jennifer Lopez.</body>
</review>
