<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Click" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In some parts of the footage, I thought, in its minimum transcendence, a curious, acceptable, entertaining movie, extension of like God or trapped in time, best films with the same mimbres...</summary>
	<body>Click is not a comedy to use, although its traces so prefiguren: lacks the rudeness of the comedy to use, that is, the story that unfolds around inevitable gags, good or bad, drag your drive despistan the Viewer to, led, premedita and sibilinamente, to the consent, to consider what has been the most innocent way, naïve and frivolous possible. Masters of the modern comedy (the Farrelly brothers, put for example) you press these precepts and not disappoint in theirs, in their house brand. Perhaps by this Click is not a mediocre film: bears witness to the world in which we live and tells the life of who to see fulfilled their dreams uses a magical object (remote control) which makes him a little God of his cosmos of fantasy.Adam Sandler meets more than in a role that has done too many times. His comical is already known, not flees from it: it sucks, does it predictable and, therefore, makes us laugh less. Not being a bad actor, nor does. Another case to highlight is Christopher Walken, an absolutely brilliant actor, one of those faces that are sculpted in flesh so that screen amplify and we look and we drill with their gestures, looking, but here friend Walken patina, hence to boredom and unconvincing. Long has already ceased to excite us. I remember now (and I'm going by the branches, as my I like) a role often, but impressive, in the desaprovechada catch me if you can, the Spielberg master. In the end.Click is a film of summer that has fallen into this autumn novice. Also get the icon of tacky, the King of the hairy chest, David Hasselhoff. They have not cut into production when it comes to pull this myth of crappy television, which has probably enjoyed as a Cossack in the wheels of the press in Europe. Be bored, I guess, without its table of beach salvation and his fantastic car.The gentle reader will be giving account Click has little chicha that these lines roam it, her evade, avoid entering the mud of its warm efficiency. It is quite true. It has, however, its sediment of sorrow, evidence cuasimetafísica that life cannot be reduced to a zapping and time, his final Squire, does not support frivolities. For this reason, in some parts of the footage, I thought, in its minimum transcendence, a curious, acceptable, entertaining movie, extension of like God or trapped in time, best films with the same mimbres.</body>
</review>
