<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="World Trade Center" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>And may have been an explicit and tough film, it is a friendly and minimalist vision of an act that has positioned itself, by sad merits in the patriotic landmark in recent American history.</summary>
	<body>Best of the last film of the controversial Oliver Stone is that it doesn't have a film by Oliver Stone and moves it away from any possibility of that can link it with the controversy. Isn't the American oven for rolls and the wound of the 11-s is still open, and gangrenando, in their own way, the geopolitics this nebulous concept of game of chess between rulers where one wrong move piece can cause a cataclysm in my town, put by case.World Trade Center avoids entering the barbarity of terrorism. And may have been an explicit and tough film, is a friendly and minimalist vision of an act that has positioned itself, by sad merits in the patriotic landmark in recent American history (world, I might add). Do not see the aircraft impact on the twin towers: perceive the rumor of the impact, the dull and gloomy sound producing. Everything gets rocked by a sense documentalist advancing in excess to the sweet pamphlet of a Discovery Channel with much budget. All us sounds like soft: would like perhaps a tougher vision, best narrated, more attached to life. World Trade Center is a film of Bill flat that not hooks with the reality of the emotion, while film Oliver Stone, that scourge of the yankee tradition, that traitor to the stablishment that same is dropped by Cuba to take a cigar with Fidel Castro and make another laudatory pamphlet that questioned the assassination on Elm Street giving a punch on the table of the Orthodox.One could abstract already learned iconography (impact of aircraft, bodies falling from the upper floors) and see World Trade Center as a catastrophe movie more. The two cops (McLoughlin and Jimeno) are characters in a drama content. They are partially credible. We believe, however, the collapse of a way of life, the evidence that those debris will be born a century new and that we will see the delivery. We saw him on CNN, live, or the gentle reader favorite chain, but Oliver Stone now gives us one turn of the screw and mounted a show between the irrelevant and sublime of the lives of a number of people who are struggling, above all, save life. Why we abstract us and consider that the film is a fiction and that there is behind a reliable correlation of facts that we all know and all, in one way or another, we were.Excessive footage could have been reduced if they had eliminated the trash of the sentimental life of the cops, not interested and make us lose the primary sense of the film. All this the impression that Oliver Stone would have gotten in a room to warn him. Have said you: "Look, Oliver, you're a great guy and is already well in making films that put the staff of bad milk." Give yourself a break. Tell the country that God exists and that he was there, among the rubble. For the world to know that Americans are noble people and good people. There is a hidden truth. There is a conspiracy theory. Oliver, uncle, rest a little. To maybe even gives us benefits, which is high time "." And Oliver, man, forgives, abides by the request and we loose this tale that is soft, proper, sober, but without that bit of bad grapes we all ask.In very small accounts, those who want the Oliver Stone film, we do not gustaremos of this movie. Paragraphs fans of the film, the film is good, clean as the Sunrise which close.World Trade Center, in the hands of Stone, with Nicolas Cage's tiny and domestic hero, smacks of redemption to liturgy. If Michael Mann had been in charge, we would have an accelerated, hyper-realist, extreme version without falling into al gore, and it of course, exempt from any religious point. I wonder what would make Tarantino. It would be very curious to see what these towers of faith would be our friend Quentin, where to stick the kick.</body>
</review>
