<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Nueve vidas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nine short stories, nine entertainment on sophisticated voyeur, nine dramatic devices which, strictly film, are a poignant conciseness.</summary>
	<body>Nine short stories, nine entertainment on sophisticated voyeur, nine dramatic devices which, strictly film, are a poignant conciseness. Rodrigo García, son of Nobel García Márquez, explores the female world for the second time after things to say just by looking at her, and does so with the same narrative apero: not sophisticated discourse, just you a solvent casting (shocking, in some cases) and a few stories from absolute minimalism, but they play the chord of a spectator than ever, in any case, it is alien to the emotions that you are arriving, episode to episode, demoledoramente.Nine lives is a simple film because it does not require the monstrous cinema still brand Hollywood to which we are so accustomed. Cinema, say some, although authorship is very bombastic label which requires very carefully specify its scope. What is nine lives is cinema of quality, intimate, guilty film in a chapter of an artifice that hits us, but to forgive. The shots are direct, brutal planos-secuencia, camera arm, fleeing from the Assembly, which would alter the spirit of the film. Rodrigo García knows exactly what should be so what counts is not burdened by a hollow, dramatic, presentation away from the small print of the lives that are counted.Me excited the episode from the supermarket, where a plethoric Robin Wright Penn, never better exploited, attached to the seat, leaves us moved, altered in a deep substrate of our sensitivity, so demolished by various astracanadas and mauled by all sorts of films-blockbusters, understanding by those calling for shouting preferential placement in video shops to continue his glorious portfolio of income. Without forgetting to Glenn Close in the cemetery or a Kathy Bates with touches of comedy in his prison hospital.Prude García in this film of brevedades, tells in an interview fuck on the fly on the Internet that he love to deal with a long history. We hope therefore that it dealt with. We'll see if her it permeates the veracity of the first two. Life has its instructions for use: the film has among its many functions a fundamental explain these instructions, make them close, help us to live with them. Art added purists.</body>
</review>
