<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Los tres entierros de Melquiades Estrada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Crudísimo drama full of fine and grumosos black humor jokes</summary>
	<body>Well, Titus Chinchan, as the winner of the contest of microcríticas of the world, left yesterday for the preview of this strange film, so my readers asuduos can be the first to read a few critical lines in this respect. By the way, if you invite to an event in the Roxy cinemas, do not need that you forth the tupper for the leftovers from the catering, which did not give us anything. Oh, and bring you a cojincito, that the seats are a little uncomfortable.The film is about the three burials that had a "wet back" called Melquiades Estrada. Died in strange circumstances, close to the border between Mexico and United States, his only friend in the country (Tommy Lee Jones) Decides to investigate a case that doesn't matter to anyone. Quickly discover the murderer of his friend and forces him to pay for the crime.Tommy Lee Jones made his debut as a director (producer, actor, co-writer and botijero) with this dotted with black comedy drama, but black, black. We must highlight the quality of the picture, which does not but highlight the deeply furrowed bodies of expressiveness. The script is quite curious, but seeing the characters, we may consider it more than credible. The actions of the protagonist is superb, the expressiveness of the same impresionandome. And that gesture, that face same applies for a funeral for a gala cocktail. What I was not far from clear whether the film is a drama, a comedy or a tragicomedy. The argument is a crude, crudísimo drama, but is full of fine (and grumosos) jokes about black humor, which makes me doubt the intentions of the own Tommy. I recommend that you go to view it as a comedy, as drama is very it lasts. By the way, most of the film is with subtitles, given that it is recorded in English and Spanish. Special attention to Tommy talking about Spanish, which would need subtitles rather than when he speaks in English.In short, better go to see a company that only. And cheerful mentality, but you're going to have a bad time of three pairs of noses. kisses.</body>
</review>
