<review author="Plissken" title="Los Borgia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The feeling I have is not of anger, but of sadness, "another misspent cartridge". A 4, because the director strives, at least, get a good job.</summary>
	<body>Antena 3 has done again it. It was not enough with this series of Santi Millán paparazzi or the bochornazo of 'Them and the weaker sex', not. Do I had to invest 10 million of? in a miniseries (I hope, already speak of the topic later) on the intrigues of the family Borgia in Rome from the 15th century. And release in film, to give more cache.If this is the future of directors like Antonio Hernández, go side by here. 'Los Borgia' account the turbulent events that surround the family Borgia from Xativa, since the appointment as sumo pontiff of Rodrigo, the Patriarch of the clan, until its fall in disgrace. An history comparable to the Corleone (Mario Puzo acknowledged being inspired by them for his legendary saga), and that could be real game on-screen is reduced to a faint story about the corrupt power of the Church of the time, and the war of interests around the Vaticano.Y all due, in my opinion, to two key factors:-The role of the strong man of the clan (Cesare Borgia) falls on Sergio Peris - Mencheta, young actor from the quarry of 'to get out of class', which gives a lesson in why not all actors can do a role. It is not so much that it is bad (to me seems it, yes), is that it is an I want to and I can not constant, it is unable to hold the movie by him. If the election was conducted by the producer, already okay them; If it has been bet the director, has ruined all the prior work atmosphere, photography, documentation, etc., because everytime Cesare Borgia appears (and almost always appears), is going to the Horn the dramatic tension, historical reenactment and everything. Or some efficient side (Poncela, Dechent,) sometimes Lluis Homar can save all the function-the script: Antena 3 has been prepared, I bet whatever, a miniseries of at least 4 hours, that perhaps makes sense as Chronicle, but of course, how are brand new in film four horazas of historical volume. So I guess he asked Antonio Hernández to use scissors to leave it in a reasonable size (sounds les play?) for what is the style: two and a half hours. Are the beginnings of the Borgias in Rome? No. do develops the love story between Caesar and Lucrecia? That is Intuit, vale. What about Jofré, the "Fredo" in the family, and Sancha, his wife? Apparently, it is not relevant to the Viewer. Go, and point. Total, understandable part, and a sindiós at the end.The feeling I have is not of anger, but of sadness, "another misspent cartridge". The production is acceptable, but by the standards of the television, the national and current, say. Nothing to do with 'The rogue' or 'Fortunata and Jacinta', for example. And with the cinema less. A 4, because the director strives, at least, get a good job.</body>
</review>
