<review author="Jose Contreras" title="El diablo viste de Prada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>How it moves from a woman of flesh and blood to be a maniac of the catwalks, trademarks and the size 34?</summary>
	<body>The Chinese mandarins had the habit of reducing their girls toes after carefully breaking the bones, burning women have a few rings that are added to the neck until the cervical are separated completely. The Westerners have size 34. Beauty, it seems, has to be accompanied by some kind of torture.There is no denying that fashion has its appeal, but I think that fashion that is there to attract the opposite sex does not require such waivers. "The Devil Wears Prada" talk of the obsession by fashion and the thinness to be at the height of a head and a cosmetic Empire, as it is that of the fashion magazines. "Women of the film have been disconnected in order to first fashion, taste, and have entered the maniaco-compulsiva spiral of unpronounceable names and gateways.""The Devil Wears Prada" is the story of a simple and careless girl who enters, to its regret, in the scene and discovers that he has to choose between this and his private life. Discourse zarandea the custom predatory, common in enterprises, stepping on to the of to the side for climbing positions. I would have preferred that it despellejara that another custom, the film provided with indifference, confused with domestic service employees. The protagonist does not complain of having to seek a publishing innovation before it comes on the market for the daughters of the great head! not having to do the work of cole!In fact such insurmountable evidence are the key that explains the abduction of Anne Hathaway. How it moves from a woman of flesh and blood to be a maniac of the catwalks, trademarks and the size 34? As you go from interesting to level enefalograma? Made it with evidence. Just that something cost that we forget ourselves. Once abducted gives equal to talk of a carving, a small walk, a long neck, earn more than the neighbor, win a tournament.</body>
</review>
