<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El diablo viste de Prada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Halfway between the soft comedy and sentimental drama, the tape is as predictable as little incisive in the approach of their conflicts.</summary>
	<body>The presence of Meryl Streep in the cast or its original poster took me to discard the idea that this would be a topical movie about Affairs so repeated as the dichotomy between personal and professional life. But I was wrong. The Devil Wears Prada account view history already hundreds of times in the film and does so with the lack of originality of this kind of movies. Halfway between the soft comedy and sentimental drama, the tape is as predictable as little incisive in the approach of their conflicts. Anne Hathaway plays the role of the inexperienced and pretty girl who lands on a job interview to be eligible for the post of Secretary of the Chief Editor of the magazine's fashion reference, the surreal world of this publication Runaway.En, where the despelleje partner is the daily bread of those who work there, Miranda Priestly (Meryl Streep) directs "runaway" as if it were the cómitre plaguing a galley rowers. And its employees are a characteristic of the middle ages vassalage. In a unique world, the labour requirement begins from early hours of the day, when employees of the magazine strive to fashion dress and dress with the most exclusive accessories. After presenting this particular world, the plot of the film follows a more predictable development. The girl inverorsímilmente landed in the Runaway universe is a good daughter, a good friend and a good girlfriend. He says not to feel part of all this 'troupe', but the challenge of overcoming the demands of his labor slavery will seducing him by this "dark side" to media which becomes more effective and resolute.So the conflict is served: the more he implies in his absorbing full-time work, its principles and more personal life will be scuttled. You must choose between good, his personal life, or the vicious, the superficial world of egos that seems to have been abducida. Manichean and stereotypical, the film not delves into none of the issues placed on the table and the profile of his characters is as prototypical nor worth valuing the work of sharing, simply effective. The Streep makes bad malísimia head, but as the movie is very squishy and so well-intentioned as all of its class, in its moral the medium rescue of the diabolical glow which had enveloped during all the footage. And the beautiful Hathaway, whose background can only emphasize his work in Brokeback Mountain, learn the leccioncita of life of rigour. And it makes sense that the tape is so flojita and relama both in the world of 'glamour', because its director, David Frankel, has hardened in the direction of episodes of series like sex in New York or the Entourage.</body>
</review>
