<review author="Matías Cobo" title="La increíble historia de Caperucita Roja" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With the already usual winks to the musical, this comedy Adventures is not a luxury in the visual but did provide some good moments of laughter and fun.</summary>
	<body>Changing times and the classic stories for children follow them. Film, with successful films such as Shrek, has been able to get enough out of this update of tales incardinated in our collective imagination. If multiple versions of this classic have deambulado between the moral of sexual Court by Perrault and the happy ending of the Brothers Grimm, this film advocates a less dramatic and more like an action-adventure approach to the mission impossible with Matrix ramalazos. Even judging from the structure of the script, the tape keeps certain concomitancias with Hercule Poirot stories born from the pen of Agatha Christie. Do in the case of the incredible but true story of little Red Riding Hood, the detective Nicky Croac exert alter ego of the famous Belgian researcher and the four protagonists of the tale?Red Riding Hood, Wolf, Grandma and the woodcutter? they would be the four suspects will bring the facts different visions.All hide after Yes amazing stories: Riding Hood is not the happy girl that delivers delicious sweets from their grandmother, they get bored in an increasingly solitary forest; the grandmother, after his portrayal of venerable old Baker, hides his facet of recidivism risk extreme sports specialist; the Wolf is an investigative reporter who uses disguise to discover news facts; and the lumberjack is a Tyrolean aspiring actor who rehearses his role of Cutter logs for the 'casting' of an advertisement. But none of them lie. The insightful Nicky Croac must gather the pieces of the puzzle spread for each of the four stories to solve the mystery about the theft of the recipes for sweets has been forced to close most of the forest pastry.With the already usual winks to the musical, this comedy Adventures is not a luxury in the visual but did provide some good moments of laughter and fun. And witness how the revision of the stories always receives the direct influence of our society today, so impregnated by omnipresent media culture.</body>
</review>
