<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Los Borgia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is reduced to 3 master interpretations, and Cesar Borgia, because more than the history of the family, is the history of this dark character, who inspired the Machiavelli himself in his work?The Prince?.</summary>
	<body>The Borgias is presented with a masterful performance by Sergio Peris-Mencheta, followed by a spectacular Luis Homar and a more than credible María Valverde. The rest of the cast loose, excluding clear Eusebio Poncela, Antonio Dechent, which as always is great, and good ok, let's also save Sancha (Linda Batista).The ten million euros that has cost this does Spanish overproduction? Do thought initially how TvFilm, in addition to in the salaries of the players? gone go to the costume (Bravo Luciano Capozzi) which is the very best that has this movie, interiors, flat General few but decent.What is certain is that this vision of the Borgias is a so particular, I think that for what this family got up at that time has been short the plot and moreover too Benévola, I believe it is a greatest common divisor of the most relevant writings on these controversial characters, leaving a velvety version of the story resulting. Although we can never be secure nor the most atrocious of the written stories, real evidence of feats no exist as.The representation of Cesar Borgia is the brighter you are going to see in this film, no doubt the best role of the young career of Sergio Peris-Mencheta, an actor undervalued in his interpretive talent and that finally has been given the opportunity to recreate in a great historical figure, arriving to our days with a relevance such, many of the Renaissance paintings where appears the image of Jesus Christ, they could have taken the physical image of Cesar Borgia. What is certain is that for Sergio, it will have impact. What most caught my attention to this interpretation, is it isn't overshadowed by Luis Homar (Rodrigo Borgia), or Maria Valverde (Lucrezia Borgia), form a triad that, tension and scenic karma are alike.If however the performance of peace vega, is absolutely overshadowed by Sergio, in normal terms "her eaten", too actor for an actress, each more national day (with the consequent loss of charm) and more predictable in its interpretation, and be foreseeable to an actor is the beginning of the end.I have only 1 thing that criticizing Sergio in its interpretation and is, that, very bad ride a horse, most of the time going crooked because it carried no well-regulated Stirrups and that well because surely (do tells me my experience as Amazon?) lacks the necessary balance, but peace that is a good is much better on the scene they share together on horseback when they are back in Rome. Not be as not you corrected this because really is pathetic, in all the scenes, is that all this horrible horse. But well this is fault of the director and if there has been coaching the coach?Cannot be displayed a beautiful floorplan with a few riders so bad, sings much, a little more practice, and it would have been great.Good and we are with horses, criticizing the casting director, the election of Miguel Angel Muñoz, too close to its role as Robert in "A step forward" to be credible. At the end of the film when he appeared on his horse, I didn't know if he was going to start to give stunts on it or sing "Sámbame". I had to laugh, I could not help it and why I love Mr Muñoz, but in this case, it hit anything, despite what his fans think.I can not describe the film as a bad job that is not. In fact represents a breakthrough for the Spanish film but nor is it a masterful film, let's quit normalita (I liked more the old "intact" for example). But indeed there are things that I stress of the film as the little signs continuous "12 years earlier", "1 year after"? at least 8 of these posters told something that seems excessive. I have to say that I liked the treatment that has been given to the sex in this movie, as well as avoid the bad taste to see pubis as mink (see my blog entries film Rasurado I and II) scenes are not explicit with which I think the plot WINS much, for that does not have to continuously pull of tits and asses to attract the Viewer, although they show, is done in a sensitive way, at the end and at Cape is appreciated, because easy sex have in almost any tape.María Valverde, is wonderful, but there is one thing that shocked me and they were his hands, they were descuidadísimas, by God if at that time the ladies were passed the day smearing the hands with the famous aromatic oils, as the director can give by valid an outlet where the hands of Lucrecia look full of cuticles and broken nails! honestly is not the image that has given the history of a great Renaissance Lady of the stature of Lucrecia Borgia.Como I said at the beginning, for me, the film is reduced to 3 master interpretations, and Cesar Borgia, because more than the history of the family, is the history of this dark character, who inspired the Machiavelli himself in his work "The Prince".</body>
</review>
