<review author="Natalia Eseverri" title="Click" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Click has the problem that happens to most of the comedies, if you like Adam Sandler, as it is my case, you love, and if not, not worth going to see.</summary>
	<body>There are many times that people ask me why I go often to the cinema and sometimes not is to answer, simply say that I like to spend the afternoon in a room imaginandome every one of the stories that appear on the screen and putting me in each of the worlds and perspectives that alli is offered me. In short, a metaphorical response plan and spiritual that I can not argue when I spend five dollars to see crap that is not worth the trouble and that nasty I leave thinking that me them it could have spent in a jersey that I would spend that cursed winter Barcelona.But on Monday, again remember why cinema is so important in my life, I am not going to dwell much to not tire you, but my Odyssey to find floor is not proving as satisfactory as you might expect, is perfectly at first it would not find, I have to look far, compare prices and qualities and everything else, but when you awake an illusion and a shit of site as it is the Bank you truncates in five minutes, the truth is that it ends with the most beautiful smiles and the congratulations and illusions that a person could have.So that Monday afternoon, needed to clear me and better site than a film and there we had to go to click, a comedy by Adam Sandler, which I will now analyse in depth but notice how important that was in my life that insignificant film, that the first thing that appeared on my face when I left the room was again a smile and a slight but promising hope that everything eventually will do well and I lograré as a workaround. So to all those detractors on the big screen that consider that a waste of money is to go on weekends to watch a movie, I can tell you that sometimes those five euros you can change the life or not, not what, but at least they help to make it more beautiful and I that love him every day.As for the movie, Click has the problem that happens to most of the comedies, if you like Adam Sandler as it is my case you love and if not not worth going to see. Never can be in term medium, it has such as extreme touches in their gags and its ironies, that it was impossible to stay unnoticed, you like or you don't like.In my case, I love but also seems to me that it is appreciated that a person committed to a kind of cinema and take it out without being influenced by the fashion of the moment and with the sole purpose of making people laugh and have important things that happen in everyday life.As always, it is accompanied by a nice actress such as Kate Beckinsale which is spectacular in this comic branch and relies on a story very common but that thanks to the gags and the development of the plot itself makes it constantly fun and also that you feel reflected although overly counts in some of the things that it represents.The downside of the film is that you going of fun moments to dramatic moments in a matter of minutes and perhaps would have been more convenient to rationalize this dramatic burden so that the story would have been more fluid and the viewer would have followed her more easily. I prefer not to mention David Haselhoff, judge for yourself when you see. And by the way where is Rob Schneider? I was not able to see it.</body>
</review>
