<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Los Borgia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film only works as valid testimony of the wanderings of Rodrigo Borgia and its offshoots during the time they landed at the Vatican as a bull in a China shop.</summary>
	<body>Apparently, not so-called patriotic film we seem to make good historical films. Without so many previous expectations with Alatriste, the disappointment that produced me Los Borgia has not been so capitalized, although the poor result of one and the other is more or less equal. This film directed by Antonio Hernández thinks something very similar which to Elías Yánez: supremely bored during his extensive and unjustified footage of two hours and a half. The film is most flat in the development of a story that could almost qualify for Protocol. Starts from one of the recent events to the once dreaded and powerful family Borgia, now developing an absolute decadence. After being imprisoned Caesar, the eldest son of the now deceased Borgia Pope, the tape back us several years ago, until the coronation of Rodrigo Borgia as Pope Alexander VI. We know, because we have just to make it clear and it's a historical account, that glory newly acquired by this family of Levantine origin would be dispelled by the hatreds and jealousies planted by its members. But leaving the film in the country is its unoriginal way of narrating the events. One can assume that there will be betrayal without scruples, incestuous bed scenes and war vicissitudes, but what is desalodador is cyclic succession of sequences of this type that we are witnessing.Ascension and subsequent sinking of an anxious family of settling scores with the Princes of the neighbouring territories can give to much, even more so when those who star in the action are members of one of the families of nobles more rivers of ink generated between essays and novelados historical stories. But the film, to be good, needs good management of some springs to convey emotion in the Viewer. The dialogues have to be force, images and how it fitted, also, performers have to get into the skin of a character that copper real life thanks to his work. The most obvious things, but that, if they fail as a whole, they make the viewing of a film tasteless. And this happens to Los Borgia, another national film premiered with the bells have been expensive? 10 million euros? and count on outstanding actors of our cinema. By the way, my attention how media have both excelled in Alatriste as Los Borgia the many millions of euros that have cost both productions; as if millionaires disbursements ensured the quality and artistic success.Note that they have spent the money on costumes, filming in exterior and Interior which ambientaran the time, in the few minutes of footage of war scenes, and the result is convincing in this regard. Luxury and pomp of the Vatican facilities is very well portrayed, but the battles sequences are an I want to and I can not. With levels very closed and without great luxuries in the camera movements, these scenes well could have been removed; total, if the film goes over the atrocities perpetrated by the Borgia family from the powerful armchair papal than of anything else. Some of what you give good they have continuous intrigue and gossip of alcove, used with insistent repetition in the tape. Ultimately, the film only works as valid testimony of the wanderings of Rodrigo Borgia and its offshoots during the time they landed at the Vatican as a bull in a China shop.</body>
</review>
