<review author="José Córdoba" title="Los Borgia" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Example of how a good direction can camouflage many defects, but not save a project when things as important as the acting and the script, play against.</summary>
	<body>Alatriste comes another Spanish historical production of "great" budget: Los Borgia. Big-budget is a saying of course, because little more than ten million euros for a historical film is very little. He had certain hopes for the film for its director, one of the best and least recognized there in Spain, Antonio Hernández, director of Lisbon and in the city without limits (also of the great Martian, but that explains why it was one of the creators of the program of TV innocent, innocent). Although it also had my misgivings because the film is a reduced version of a miniseries A3 premiering soon. The result is grey.The Borgias narrates the history of the saga of the Valencia family since the appointment as Pope Alexander VI until his death. A story full of palatial intrigue, violence and sex. It would today be a Venezuelan soap opera, we will. For more than two hours attended the ins and outs of the corruption of power, carried out by the Borgia, but most notably in one of the sons, Cesare Borgia, played by Sergio Peris Mencheta, character that served as a model to Machiavelli to write "The Prince".A film of these characteristics comparison with its precedent Alatriste is inevitable and plays in his favor, since the film, as a whole, Hernández is superior to Diaz Yanes. Also, perhaps, one tends to be more condescending to a product that has received less than half of the budget of the other. Well, as positive and last, point the direction of Antonio Hernández. It is successful, with many Visual ideas, is not happy to put the camera where less bother. Scenes such as dinner in the House of the Orsiny or muerte-nombramiento of new Pope (with the zenith level) show that the filmmaker has been involved in the film, which is equal to the best of our paísa, albeit unfortunately an unknown to the general public. Also sections such as costumes and art direction are also very accomplished, but it also helps the fact of having shot in the city of Rome itself. Photography is functional and little more to add, in this case "Alatriste" was more successful (in spite of, as already pointed out in its commentary, some scenes). The music of Ángel Illarramendi is present during all of the footage, and still remarkable, isn't at the height of his other works as the zeal, also suffers from resemble other works, if not for the melody, yes your orchestrations and other elements. But even with everything, gives packing the images, also aided by the fact that the scenes have not been comebacks, destroying the music as it occurs in Alatriste.En the downside the fact it is the reduced version of a television series, so several plot threads are left unfinished, although this is a detail in favourthe plot does not appear episodic, owing mainly to the leadership of Hernández which gives the narration of an enviable fluency. The performances of the cast are more diverse. On the one hand, Lluís Homar which performs a very risky approach to his character, touching the madness but without exaggeration (although there are moments which resembles characters played by Leslie Nielsen in their parodies), is difficult to categorize and perhaps for this reason cause controversy; on the other hand, Sergio Peris Mencheta leaves not stopped the lance, her performance without being exemplary or spectacular, is not negligible. Side as Antonio Dechent or Roberto Álvarez, are always well. But the rest of young faces proves to be the great mistake of the film, in fact, many of them, they are bent by dubbing actors. Special mention for María Valverde and his Lucrezia Borgia, a character which is able to detach from the legend, making it appear a girl's dad ñoña and silly, but at least she not has been dubbed. The rest of her teammates cast, with the exception of Ángela Molina and Paz Vega, have been. Perhaps they sought only beautiful bodies because abundant female nudity in the film. On the other hand, the script nor deepens in the plots or characters, being more oriented to the folletinesco side of the plot that delve a little on the characters.The film, despite the laudable efforts of Hernández, would need a larger budget to have a pack, a visual Bill much better. In short, it is an example of how a good direction can camouflage many defects, but not save a project when things as important as the acting and the script, play against. The funny thing is that even with everything, it is a pretty decent film.PS: I would put two and a half stars, I think that it is better than mediocre, but he would not consider her a good movie.</body>
</review>
