<review author="José Córdoba" title="Camaron" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is an episodic film because it summarizes more than forty years of life in less than two hours of footage, it sweetens the character, she takes pity on him, so it seems that company never anything bad.</summary>
	<body>The film narrates the life of shrimp from his childhood so far that returns in the United States.UU. After being diagnosed with terminal cancer who ended up killing. The film is therefore part of the biographical genre, "biopic" as the Americans call it. Unfortunately not leaving its standards, falling into each and every one of the endemic ills of the genre.It is an episodic film because it summarizes more than forty years of life in less than two hours of footage, it sweetens the character, she takes pity on him, so it seems that company never anything bad. Shrimp appears drawn as a genius martyr, unable to do any harm. In addition the film, does not show the artist's creative process, just gives some strokes, but too limited, especially taking into account that shrimp was a revolutionary in the world of Flamenco. The characters appear and disappear over the footage, case of the of Veronica Sanchez who plays his wife, a character which is introducio in the middle of the footage, showing us love and the subsequent wedding, and disappears until almost the end of the footage. The characters are one-dimensional, as an example the first girlfriend of shrimp, a girl that only thing we know is that it is capricious, nothing more. The film is also continually seasoned with songs of the artist, but not using them to advance the film, which would be logical, but as scenes of performances by what has just looking like a great playback, with many media, but a playback, especially screeching differences in the quality of the sound when the characters sing. Interpretive level the movie is very good, although I do not think it fair prizes granted Jaenada by your interpretation, because it remains an imitation, a camouflage. Carlos Latre makes it continuously, to another level of agreement, and why not give awards. The original soundtrack, which also has, is unobtrusive and demonstrates once again how very few Spanish directors know make use of the original soundtrack.As positive, discover the music of shrimp, will seek his musical experiments that seem interesting, but unfortunately have little reflection in the film, which basically focuses on his drug problem, although displays it without claw, so the hell crossed the singer appears too anti-aliasing. Finally, a curious detail, the shortage of Roma actors in the film.</body>
</review>
