<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El diablo viste de Prada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Satire of the fashion world? Little. I have already said that this funny Elm, but in its hollow half pears can be ordered.</summary>
	<body>Just as the poet said, the Moon is the imperfection of the darkness, comedy is the frivolous reverse drama. I have a friend who warns drama in all the movies you see: all watches his sad poso, its decay, its crust of tragedy. The Devil Wears Prada will be for my friend a huge drama. It exceed to argue it and not I restaré a portion of reason, but tiny.The Devil Wears Prada is the traditional, graceful, lightweight, comedieta sandwiched in a colorful costume and brand that will like the friendly public wishing, among so much bombast and sordid eschatology, a bit of evasion, a walk in the park with their bare feet. This sweet sensation of well-being contributes a Meryl Streep in State of grace, and that it is not my prayer book santa. A Meryl Streep, I insist, outboard a very appetizing role and that it could have done with utmost efficiency, Glenn Close and Sigourney Weaver. It shines in equal measure Stanley Tucci, an actor who has not yet found the role of his life, but time has.Cartoon that we find is syrup and melted chocolate, how not, but underneath beats the heart of darkness, bad milk that the human being possesses for when the need calls. And lives Dios that comes here. My friend feels, at the end, understood.Life represented here is raw and hard, life the trench of the social escalafonato: with their gashes and his eyes arteras, its infamy and his hander. What happens is that all screened with the sieve of fashion, which is nice and that breaks out in colours, and the writers care in giving us a few certainly elaborate dialogues, causing the Viewer does not feel, as usually these comedies, deluded.Smells like everything in excess Pret-a-porter, but we explain exclusion the aura of false intelligentsia that had the work of Altman. It fares worse in agility, in outrageous. Is related more with arms of women, the 1980s Mike Nichols film, but the Devil Wears Prada less rummages in the psychology of the characters. Well, the truth is he rummages really well little.Take one in lack recreational artifacts in this manner. There are comedies of this Court that arroban the boredom or dress of rudeness. Here everything is conducted with a casual, clean, free from unnecessary dramatismos style.Not confused the friendly Viewer to the mix of genres. Then touch many and it is not tuned in any.Demos a generous treatment to the film by David FRankel, but nor do we arrojemos to the Duero the bells of Notre Dame, that it won't all this to any list of successes in the history of cinema. Box office, at least, will do. And the colors are very nice. Satire of the fashion world? Little. I have already said that this funny Elm, but in its hollow half pears can be ordered. Cakes for all.</body>
</review>
