<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Fuera de control" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The argument continues well and the thing works. Possibly if her it would have been entirely and film would have another opinion.</summary>
	<body>Sunday afternoon, the child half bad and on the street a cold that motivates to stay at home. On TV it begins a peliculón, those good, good. Begins the movie, cries the child, play with him, when view gone the air controller and a lady comes from the future with bleach (could come with the original), take advantage to make popcorn. When come out Angelina Jolines with a chest out, gets you the heart of emotion, but you disimulas so that your half melon does not tell you anything "because it is not bad" say blatantly lying. The movie continues, you traspones, you play with the child, talks with your partner, suddenly begins another movie and you're thinking "I have seen the movie?".The film is about air traffic controllers, stressful job where found them. The protagonist is one of them which is on the crest of the wave, and appears a more rare that he type. The latter begins to remove role, for what the first decides to tighten his wife (Miss Jolines) but the second do not care you. These women of the first learns and is a good lia. Then go flying by the slipstream of a plane and are given a hostión. And hence not be what happened that I saw not.Well, little I can say, given that I saw little bit. Since then the thing promised, given that we know little of the life of air traffic controllers. Now is that married many times, earn a lot of money, commit suicide much, and if the shit 3 times in two years and a half going to the street. Things. The movie is good, especially for a Sunday afternoon, with actors some traditional and some less. The argument continues well and the thing works. Possibly if her it would have been entirely and film would have another opinion.In short, for an afternoon at home without football on the radio and with the bad boy. To me I liked.</body>
</review>
