<review author="Ana" title="A scanner darkly" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It captures the sense of a graphic novel and an epic futuristic at the same time. I can't wait to see her again. It is that Linklater released another movie this year incredible?Do Fast Food Nation?, my expectations are huge</summary>
	<body>Based on the personal experiences of Philip k. Dick (Blade runner) with drugs, this film is a wonderful hypnotic trance. Animated with a process of rotoscoping, the film builds its own visual language which lies in a magical point between photography and the animation; the real and the imaginary. Between life and the dream as was the subject of "To waking life", the previous project with this style of director Richard Linklater. Once again achieved an extraordinary experience both in the narrative and Visual, as the film should be.In these times, it is difficult to push the boundaries of imagination. We have seen so much that we have a sarcastic and detached from the future and life look. Why it works very well to talk about science fiction this work prefer to place in the near future. Everything you pose perfectly fit the neurotic life style of the era of terror in which we live and we know that technology is advancing so fast. Few elements of high technology in the film no longer exist. Except, of course, the decoder guise of identity that used the police to be unrecognizable. This element is the Summit of the visual style and at the same time captures the central theme of the film. Bob Actor (Keanu Reeves), an undercover agent, must monitor their own lives through a system of espionage by video; Since that has been implicated in the world of drugs that supposedly is doing him the guerra.¿Estamos so separated from ourselves that we can not recognize us? And if someone or something can see everything about me, including all personal information, does arrive to know who I am? I get to know myself? Or who looks through the mirror makes it in the dark, just as I see my own life? The title of the film comes from that phrase of Corinthians "we now see by mirror in dark;" but then we will see face to face: now I know in part; "but then shall know as I am known", updated at the age of bar codes.Develop a particular language would have no value if it were not forged to say something. Here he presents an important document of the problematic of identity today. In addition to not get lost in the Nebula, this film is full of humor and real and sincere dialogues. Above all the Group of jonkis with paranoia walk at home. Linklater to tested because it makes a sharp ear in "Before sunrise/suset"(Antes_deel_amanecer/atardecer) and "Dazed and confused" for sincere talks that resonate with certainties. Complex characters with dishes outstanding wash, i.e. real and this world. Actors enrich these characters, particularly Robert Downey Jr. The fact that humor works owes much to the naturalness of the rhythms of the cast.Captures the sense of a graphic novel and an epic futuristic, at the same time without leaving out to the black humor environment to paranoia. I can't wait to see her again. It is incredible that Linklater released another movie this year "Fast Food Nation", my expectations are enormous.</body>
</review>
