<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Los Borgia" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After a somewhat dubious beginning seemed skidding for the elemental in the central characters, it soon lifts flight, adensando is, constructing an almost Entomological portrait.</summary>
	<body>It seems that the film of time (medieval or del Siglo de Oro) again to fashion in Spain; a few months ago premiered "Strained the white" (by the way, with a costalazo at the box office of very careful), later "Alatriste", which has functioned well commercially (though a far cry from the astronomical figure of its budget), and now "Los Borgia", another megaproducción that has been implicated to Antena 3, co-producer of the film fund. It must be said, input, that perhaps the effort was too large to do in cinema: the life of the Borgia Pope, Alexander VI, and their children, over the eleven years that lasted his papacy, is filled with events of all kinds, to the point that have been necessary two and a half hours of footage to tell the vital life of this peculiar family group. So, better would have been to shoot a television miniseries, as it will probably end up being shown on television (do in Antena 3, clear?). However, the challenge, with the inevitable faults of rhythm in which footage so prolonged ago incur, has paid off with a positive outcome. Because "Los Borgia", after a somewhat dubious beginning seemed skidding for the elemental in the central characters, soon raises the flight, adensando is, constructing an almost Entomological portrait, in which not take party in favour or against, a Valencian family arrival to absolute power in the Vatican, at the turn of the 15th to 16th centurya powerful historical moment (just discover America, Spain is already a unitary State and is poised to be an empire, ends the dark middle ages for entering the bright Renaissance). This family Borja or Borgia, to speak with the Italian spelling that happened to posterity, made their own interest the end by which the Vatican would be governed and, thanks to its spiritual, but also temporary power (at that time, Stalin could not say that wicked irony of "how many divisions had the Pope"? because them had), the rest of the known world. Ambitious film, that properly combines complex conspiracies trumped by the paterfamilias of the Borgia Pope Alexander VI as well as the sorrows of his sons (the blood, effervescent Caesar tarambana Juan deferential Jofré; the recklessness and finally so scalded Lucrecia, here very far the portrait of matahombres that informal history awarded), nursery scenes of action and a broad deployment of resources, is no stranger, yet beautiful film details: the crying of the Pope before the death of his son, splendidly given by a Lluis Homar transmitting as only they know make good theatre actors; the overhead map of the death of the Pontiff; the final scene, with the suicidal charge of Caesar and that zoom until the lens disc which confirms the secret love he felt for her sister? details of exquisite and creative filmmaker who is Hernandez, who leads with solvency are a great film device like this, a mammoth enterprise that has reaped a brilliant result. Another thing is that it works well at the box office: the absence of flashy actors can do run aground a colorful commitment and a huge effort that deserves another treatment. Special mention to that volcano still pending to erupt which responds to the name of Sergio Peris-Mencheta, reminiscent of the first Javier Bardem, and not only physically: has the power of the protagonist of "Mar adentro", although perhaps not their ductility? Hopefully I'm wrong.</body>
</review>
