<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Azuloscurocasinegro" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The classic script for Hollywood knows that you just concentrate gunpowder at three key moments, the two turns of the first and second Act and the final. This oblivion can explain the box office, but does not take away an iota of value to a huge film.</summary>
	<body>With the large one has the feeling that their journeys are nothing more than an excuse, sometimes a distraction to take us to their land, to speak to us in a way, with a tone. To speak to the ear, as does Shyamalan, to confess before us, as he likes to Mankiewicz, to release your unbridled vein as Almodóvar, or to tell us things calmly, calmly, that is tone that runs throughout the film by Daniel Sánchez Arévalo. The vicissitudes, incredible at times, unexpected always, stop each character about to lose your temper, but it always ends in a more surprising than the previous play, and it assesses sober, sensible, serene.The film is built with a regular rhythm in Spanish film, which distributes the research over the footage. The classic script for Hollywood knows that you just concentrate gunpowder at three key moments, the two turns of the first and second Act and the final. This oblivion can explain the box office, but does not take away a bit of value to a huge film.George, the protagonist, take care of his invalid father, and with memory problems, leads the goal and tries to find work with his title of business that it has taken at the UNED. His brother is serving his sentence and falls in love for the first time in his life of another convicted. She needs to get pregnant to change flag. The friend of Jorge spy from the terrace of your building to a massage gay.While Hollywood makes heroes without any sign of fatigue, Spanish film never tires of cure to your audience. It heals your intransigence of its impropriety. AzulOscuroCasiNegro faces hot topics as sexuality within the family, homosexuality as part of sexuality, sex without love, inheritance among siblings, who takes care of the elderly, the labour market. These are all issues that the film avoids, because they are not easy, and they are depressing. AzulOscuroCasiNegro illuminates them with a look amazing and amazed by a Sánchez Arévalo which speaks not to give us lessons, or for susurarnos, carrying everything to its terrain, and just hablándo in that delightful, sober, sensible, serene tone. The only lesson, the thesis is his incurable romanticism. No doubt the tape that deserved to go to the oscars.</body>
</review>
