<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the best Spanish films in which del Toro is revealed as a narrator able to combine in the same story, the magic of the Fables and most horrible of the human condition.</summary>
	<body>He knew the facet of Guillermo del Toro as strong an action-horror film director that always permeates his particular and imaginative vision. But this magnificent film, that advance, is one of the best produced this year by the Spanish film, I found a great Narrator capable of bringing together, in the same story, the magic of the Fables and most horrible of the human condition. El laberinto del fauno is a film so atypical as bold in its dual narrative proposal. If the monsters of tale Ophelia (magnificent Ivana Baquero) is facing in his adventures are terrifying, not less so are some of human beings with whom person in a hostile reality. His mother Carmen (Ariadna Gil) tells him that it is more to so much "zarandaja", but she clings strongly to his personal universe, to the point of living almost abstracted from the ungrateful cotidianediad. Beat with commendable value tougher tests for his fable while living with dread new developments surrounding his life, his mother and his yet unborn brother.The use of imagination as escape from the most shocking reality, therefore, is one of the proposed issues by del Toro, who suffered the cruelest side of life firsthand during the abduction of his father. The film puts US in the coinciding with World War II post-war Spain. It is 1944 and there are still pockets of Republican troops, known as 'maquis', refugees in the mountains fighting against the Pro-Franco army. A splendid Sergi López put face to the despiado Captain Vidal, who command a few troops aimed at ending the Group of insurgents wagered on the slopes of the mountain. Carmen is a tailor's widow and the mother of Ophelia, a 13 year old girl addicted to fantastic tales. As a means of survival, Carmen married remarried capitál Vidal, who seems only interested in the welfare of the child which Carmen carries in her womb and is about to be born. And treated with contempt his wife and stepdaughter, sentenced to treat him slavishly to deal with these years of national famine and famine. Both travel to the mill where Vidal has its center of operations. There, Mercedes (large Maribel Verdú) directs the service of the House and the Doctor (Alex Angulo) takes care of the health status of Carmen, recently arrived after a long and hard journey along with Ofelia.Ofelia, alien to the ruthless hunt for Vidal (the interpretation of Lopez is the height, for example, of Ralph Fiennes in Schindler's list made of the sadistic Amon Goeth)You will discover the ruins of a maze in the forest. There you are with a Faun who recognizes it as a Princess. Although disbelieving at first, she agrees to face the three tests which returned it to his reign. It will run all sorts of dangers, but none aterrará you both his padastro and the dark world it represents. The State of health of Carmen is compounded as approaching birth and she is trapped between duty to attend to his mother and the evidence to be complete when the full moon arrives.Grim aesthetic and sometimes repulsive, El laberinto del fauno isn't a film the Chronicles of Narnia-style, despite having fauns and fairies in its history. Extreme violence shown or suggested by the ellipsis in the real story, as well as the aterrodora setting of the dream-like part, prevent that this is suitable for a child audience tape. But it is highly recommended for the rest.The Ribbon, its corollary, vindica the world of the imagiación and dreams as an antidote to the worst face of reality. Del Toro, here, it is almost a declaration of principles on his own vision of life. According to the Mexican, literature, film, or other art forms can facilitate us access to so exhilarating world, but, as noted in the tape, it will only be open to those who know to look. Why, maybe need to look through the eyes of a child.</body>
</review>
