<review author="Txapulin" title="Scoop" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After the risky but perfect Match Point, Allen returns to his comedy more classical in a seemingly simple movie, but so well made, nice and pleasant to see that it may end up being one of his best films.</summary>
	<body>Scoop can be translated as exclusive or scoop and is a word that applies to the world of journalism.In Woody Allen's new film, the scoop is revealed to a novice student of journalism (a Scarlett Johansson that personally reminds me Marilyn Monroe in one of their Candida and innocent interpretations) since a spectral appearance of the more beyond: a journalist recently died learns during his journey to the Otherworld (beautiful and dark image of the ship captained by death) that a ricachón London may be the perpetrator of a series of murders that occurred in the city and happens to give the exclusive to the young journalist. During its investigation, that will help a conjurer on tour (the same Woody Allen), the young will fall in love with the alleged murderer and the plot is served.Scoop connects directly with the superb murder mystery in Manhattan (1993) within the master Woody Allen filmography, especially by the mix of genres (comedy and intrigue police) and placing inexperienced characters to investigate murders. The novelty is that here the character of Allen, the magician Splendini, remains completely out of the plot romantic to only offer the typical comic and ducks counterpoint to his characters, by the way, that the end of his character can give that talk, depending on how you interpret.After the risky but perfect Match Point (2005) (envelope which is not disputed whether it is or not work master, that's no doubt, but if the movie is more than any other alleniana or represents a complete change of style) Allen returns to its more classic comedy in a seemingly simple movie, but so well made, nice and pleasant to see that it may end up being one of his best films.</body>
</review>
