<review author="Marta" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Guillermo del Toro has managed to unite two stories of reality and fantasy with admirable skill</summary>
	<body>I leave it clear from the outset: without doubt, this is one of the best films I've seen in recent months - if not the best. As for the script and direction, "El laberinto del Fauno" is brilliant. Guillermo del Toro has managed to unite two stories, the "real" and the "fantastic" without no end with the other have not become inconsistent. A drama about the civil war and a magical tale. A totally balanced, so that the Viewer does not know if you are interested in more one or the other, and without that the film becomes absurd. Either of the two would be enough to hook if same, and here are the two perfectly integrated, and leaving space so that each can decide whether he prefers to believe that magic really exists or everything is Ophelia in the imagination of its protagonist. Personally, I went into the film thinking that the first five minutes ramifications on the surface, so to speak, and the rest in the labyrinth. Nothing further from the truth. The film is jumping between the two worlds through its protagonist without involving any problem with admirable skill. I believe that few Directors would have overcome that problem unless the film is sometimes forced. Guillermo del Toro gets as if such a thing, and ends by joining the two worlds in the best possible way. Much of the merit lies on the actors, since then. I start my Predictor of the Goya prefiguring that Ivana Baquero will take one (so wonderfully and we know that having only 12 years helps). By the way, it is physically surprisingly similar to Ariadna Gil, his mother in the film. And it would be unfair to forget the interpretations of Sergi López, in the role of Captain Vidal, Maribel Verdú and Álex Angulo. The image is fascinating. The fantastic part obviously owes a lot to some impressive special effects. Here is when you say: "And this is a Spanish production?" "Go, go". The scene of the second test with a monster that could be in the worst nightmares of anyone, is unforgettable. But that's not all. That part so magic can do that not is it valued as it deserves all the atmosphere of the Spain of the 1940s, which is conseguidísima. And a warning: the film is very hard. A lot. That no one comes to mind take a child thinking that it is a cuentecillo, which traumatizará of life. There are very violent images that make you away view of the screen. Is it free? That is what we wondered out of the film. I think that not. The story is telling is tragic. The images accompanying the harshness of the narrated situations. The hardness of the war. To be picky, put two "buts": firstly, I think that the history would have won if the villain had been a character with more nuanced. Someone who showed some humanity sometime and who was not so easy to hate. And, secondly, I think that they could have shown the happy of the labyrinth Kingdom without Federico Luppi gave the feeling of going to throw candy at any time from the float of the Magi. But well, they are just totally subjective details.In any case, an essential film that you will like to anyone. Who likes the fantasy genre or the lover of dramas. Who likes suspense or who simply want to entertain an afternoon. Do me case, do not miss, is worth.</body>
</review>
