<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Batman begins" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Still not not going more, maintains at least the suspense and is successful</summary>
	<body>In the film I saw at the end of the eighties the first Tim Burton BATMAN. I still remember that summer with the cities flooded with the Batman symbol announcing the film in an advertising campaign, at that time, amazing. The film I liked enough, but already with sixteen seemed also pretty child. And it is that Burton feels predilection by these dark and Baroque scenarios but always with this atmosphere of fear for children tale. The character of Batman was important, but most were the villain, brilliantly portrayed by Jack Nicholson, or shadows and the mystery of the same city of Gotham, who took a leading role and served as a Gothic scene for the adventures of man bat.Arrived several sequels, BATMAN RETURNS, also by Burton in 1992, BATMAN FOREVER, in 1995 and BATMAN &amp; ROBIN two years later, the two latest hand in hand with the insufferable Joel Shumacher.Y have taken eight years to achieve rescue the saga of this character of comic and so I returned to theaters to watch another episode of Batman. I've always thought that Batman deserves a dark, scary and violent environment and any of the films too provided thereon. I have not been able to finish watching me three other deliveries or even on TV, but I went back to recover the interest and curiosity with this new installment due to the choice of Christopher Nolan (MEMENTO) for the direction, Christian Bale (AMERICAN PSYCHO, the MACHINIST) as Batman and that dark and realistic look of those trailers and promotional posters so promising.The movie, loosely, I quite bored. One enjoys an interesting that estiradísima first part and really wants to see Batman in action. This is the part that I like best. A tormented protagonist and an approach which, still not not going more, maintains at least the suspense and is successful. In favour I will also talk about secondary actors of luxury, an attractive look and a production more or less to the height than expected. But sooner or later we must discover the Mise en scène of Batman, have to see the hero in action, and is then when the plot is no longer exciting or original, and just stays in monotonous and complicated (by pulling to confusing) and where, also awaited action scenes, are perhaps only worthy of a pilot episode of a bad action television series. The choreographer hired to plan the fights was during the shooting of the film on vacation and in return, put two monkeys addicted to the caffeine behind the camera. Result: Not seen a pepper. There is more than a go and come flat and see to move the wings up and down with the bad guys while flying through the air, while Batman flies again to below, takes the pistolita, flies again up and our eyes we escuecen, we feel dizziness and our yawns betray some poorly hidden torpor. You can do a lot better. Christian Bale has to his credit a cult film, unknown to nearly everyone, EQUILIBRIUM. In this film demonstrates how Yes can be done with Bale, and even with a much tighter budget, a few exceptional aesthetic, choreographed fight scenes, adrenalíticas and very exciting.Add also that I am not of those who hate the new design of the Batmobile, because I believe that flee from those other models so admired and coveted by funeral companies more daring, and away from the only airship with a fantasmada propulsion as tying the car underway to lampposts to curves. buff. Much better as well. However, so forced persecution with the Batmobile garrafón is repetitive, and not get surprised.The Gotham City is dark, corrupt and foul as it was also to be expected, but isn't well portrayed or with depth and never seems real truth. It seems impossible to believe at all that someone wants to live there. Before and after Batman.Por across the pseudo-existenciales frasecitas by Lian Neeson, Jedi style, squeaking quite. Some of the only Batman lapidary phrases come with shoehorn and it irritates me even not knowing that since costume so drastically changes the tone of the voice. But worst thing about the film is zero chemistry between Batman and his girl, the menace of Katie Holmes, with its caritas and his crooked sonrisita not painted by absolutely nothing at all in this movie. (Seeing her act I am afraid that not in any other.)Still and all, I think that the direction taken is quite right, and now only expected to keep to the always tormented and mysterious Bale as Batman, that comes as a ring to the finger. Keep this new look more serious and dark and hire a Director more skilled with the action scenes for the next installments of this prolific and millionaire saga. Although, what to my terms, I fear that these will already be, in the best cases, future meat of the video store below.</body>
</review>
