<review author="Bloody Will" title="El diablo viste de Prada" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps a little longer towards the end, but I give my first excellent of course. The surprise of the year, so far.</summary>
	<body>When I finished watching the film I was under the impression that had seen a revisitación of "Weapons of woman", without that have nothing to envy to the classic Mike Nichols. The action seen thousand times of "women seeking the top" achieves a freshness in this film makes me understand why has been the "sleeper" of the summer in the USA: a great fundraiser for a film that deserves it. Finally something of consistency.I know that girls will be most identified with the theme, so cruel and aggressive competitiveness among them, but not you you frightened the boys of boring there's nothing. Its light male version might be "In Good Company", but lacks the nasty and funny situations that "Devil" gets poured.Hathaway began with "Princess by surprise" and that has given background to make a comedy like this. The girl falls nice and responds impressively against this monster that is Streep. It starts being the "Yo soy Bea" magazine, and you think it, to become, by necessity, the best candidate for this programme of four model. You can think that it is superficial, but it is a truth as a temple: Ascend do everything. That is what shows Hatthaway, and the outboard. Nor by far is ridiculous with her partner multinominada, which is that is out.Meryl Streep gets her you hate until the bowels, and you're done thanking God for not having a Chief/to like this. It is the best villain this season, well above Lex Luthor, and with that I say everything. The actress, in a ways and looks impressive technique, crush without mercy and without ever raising the tone, how many people have to their around a form that appears to completely lawful. Ask her everything and does everything to annoy and bring to exhaustion suffered attendees still have to thank him for his time. And who can interpret this role better than anyone?, Streep, of course.I laughed a lot with the vicissitudes of the protagonist to get book 7 of Harry Potter for the daughters of the head. Shows that the ego to get us more can all a "you're the best" that our own personal dignity. The protagonist will travel that road without return which is sell your soul to the head, knowing this that has come very cheap.The side does not disappoint. Stanley Tucci is the Stylist of the magazine that has their own dreams of flying, and Emily Blunt is the Secretary which sells for a good party. Two great performances are at the height of the entire film.It is without doubt the comedy of the year, and it would not be unreasonable thinking that Meryl Streep could get his nomination number 14 on his career. Required viewing for those who want to see a comedy well made and with good performances. Perhaps a little longer towards the end, but I give my first excellent of course. The surprise of the year, so far.</body>
</review>
