<review author="Bloody Will" title="Serpientes en el avión" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sex, drugs, violence, gore, shooting weapons, poisonous reptiles, painful actaciones, plot requetevista, bad CGI, breaches of elementary physics, in short, everything you need a bad really bad film to finish diviertiéndote one hour and forty minutes.</summary>
	<body>The worst thing that has a film that does not give much of itself, is that pass from the beginning, and that it will give you equal. This film is the result of the largest campaign of promotion launched this year. Since February they began with rumors about the content "light" of the scenes with snakes, and that the director shot new footage closer to al gore. Then showed us the most crappy poster of history, and I think that wanting to people to take over the production company and create more excitement. When they began the previous passes everyone posts excellent critiques and they saw it as milk. Everything what: finally seeing a by-product that entertains, but by-product.So much expectation ends up taking a toll, and I think that not I find anything if I tell you that every situation you can see in this movie have seen thousand and one times in others. I speak of "54 passenger &#8243; with crossing of"anaconda"." The special effects are not to throw rockets. Snakes undertaken with CGI technique has embedded them the most rookie company of Hollywood, and they supplement the deficiency with attacks that exceed the limits of bad taste. It was clear that if not, there would not be way.The story is more simplistic: A kid (Nathan Phillips) witness of a settling of accounts will be escorted by a police officer (Samuel l. Jackson) from Hawaii to Los Angeles to attend the trial. However the aircraft that travel will become a deadly trap when thousands of poisonous snakes are released in order to not leave anyone with life, nor witness to God that he accompany him.Sex, drugs, violence, gore, shooting weapons, poisonous reptiles, painful actaciones, plot requetevista, bad CGI, breaches of elementary physics, in short, everything you need a bad really bad film to finish diviertiéndote one hour and forty minutes. Is not going to find deep conversations, or coherence in the argument (the villain of the principle goes more in the film), snakes are not until well after 30 minutes of the film, even Samuel l. Jackson in "Pulp Fiction" is a mirage of the past, but still so, you are going to be from stone when hundreds of snakes of all one hundred commit their particular massacre. B gross b series.I read somewhere if you not enjoy with the movie is "you have vagina". It is the coarseness and largest stupidity can conclude from "Snakes on a plane". This film is a perfect excuse to hang out, and already is. You will like if you didn't have anything more important to do and bored with who left behind a thesis to see. Everything else is trying to elevate "masterpiece" a film that falls into oblivion after 20 minutes of seeing her. For otherwise it is "Crank", that with identical aim of entertainment flat encephalogram, far surpasses her.I know that I can repeat, but lately grabbing movies that are visionadas with the Group of hooligan buddy who can not get into the room of "Volver". Willingly I had been a cubata in half of the film, but is not plan, then I confused the plots.If you expect me to decide on the participation of Elsa Pataky in the film, is that still not have seen. NOT THERE IS INTERPRETATION. The girl is confined to wander through the aircraft with a doll and singing a lullaby to some children still do not understand how to survive the massacre. The Yankees have had to stay stoked seeing her walk down the red carpet for the premiere, and would be saying "Will be the girlfriend of some steering?".Conclusion: expectations of seeing a peliculón leave at the door of the cinema. For this film you need popcorn, feel like messing and extensive experience watching terror-serie B. So what you pasaréis pipe.</body>
</review>
