<review author="Plissken" title="A scanner darkly" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A demonstration of how to use a support to enhance a story which, without it, would be more boring. But also an example of scattered narrative, which distracted and lose interest at times.</summary>
	<body>'A Scanner Darkly' is expected (by me, at least) turn of the rotoscoping technique to the big screen after failed experiments of Ralph Bakshi in the 1970s. Richard Linklater has chosen this means to adapt the eponymous story by Philip k. Dick, and seen the outcome the election has been more that appropriate. 'A Scanner Darkly' shows us a very near future, in which 20% of the American population is addicted to a very powerful drug, "substance D". Amidst the increasingly lost battle is Bob Arctor, Member of a special anti-drug body infiltrated the home of suspected traffickers, struggling to discover the original source of the "substance D", and also the fight against the devastating effects of his growing addiction. Do you can achieve Arctor win two battles facing them?Told so, the truth is that the story does not give much: is the typical story of the infiltrator caught between two fires told a thousand times (one of my favorites is 'Rush' of Lili Fini Zanuck). The novelty in this case is that the factor paranoia takes over completely from the film, to the point that we have doubt both of our perception as the same protagonist. This is the great success of the Linklater film, turn us into junkies amazed during the one hundred minutes that lasts, thanks also to the peculiar technical rotoscoped. But at the same time, is the great weakness of 'A Scanner Darkly': the main plot loses interest progressively, to the extent that ceases to tell a story and just telling a sort of collective madness, shared by Bob Arctor and his companions of skullduggery. What begins as an "undercover movie" with high technology of medium, becomes a tragicomic showcase of human miseries. And given that it was the intention of the writer of the novel as the Director, because objective fulfilled. But the loss of interest in the plot is somewhat frustrating, at the end.Acting work, despite the disfigurement resulting from the rotoscópico process, is notable. The animated image of Keanu Reeves is much more convincing than the image real (come on, serving up their "cartoon" best). Wynona Ryder defends, and the 'stars' of the hallucinogenic function end up being this strange couple of junkies (caricatures of themselves) are Robert Downey Jr. and Woody Harrelson, which appears to left of the bowling alley in the neighborhood of Jeff Lebowski. On the other hand, the recreation of that do future? in which everyone is under continuous surveillance, even the security guards themselves, it is austere enough to be credible, even recognizable today.In summary: a demonstration of how to use a support to enhance a story which, without it, would be more boring. But also an example of scattered narrative, which distracted and lose interest at times. A 6'5.</body>
</review>
