<review author="Taliesin" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A fairy tale during one of the toughest moments of the Spanish post-war.</summary>
	<body>There is no denying that Guillermo del Toro is interested in fantasy and science fiction. In all of his films (Blade II, backbone of the devil, Mimic, Hellboy), fantasy has a very important role. The difference from other creators is the concern to establish a link with reality. In his films, Guillermo has things that we know are not certain, but the account in a way that they could be certain. This magic is causing the desired effect on the Viewer, either fear or the illusion that what you see on screen is something that can happen.El Laberinto del Fauno, the Mexican director takes the Spanish civil war as canvas to paint your fantasy, as it did with the civil war in the Devil's backbone. But if it was then a ghost story, now we have a story that could well have signed Tim Burton himself. Ophelia and her pregnant mother arrive at a mill taken over by franco's troops from where you fight to the maquis that hidden in the mount still offer resistance to the fascist army. The reason that a woman about to give birth trip to this place of nightmare is that her husband, Captain Vidal, is responsible for the troops of the mill and wish that his son is born where is his father. Between your little baggage Ophelia brings a few stories bound with a leather strap. She soon become protagonist of a short story by Princesses and kingdoms delighted, those starting with a "once upon a time.".The main virtue of El Laberinto del Fauno is mixed with skill the cruelty that exists in a scenario in which there are two sides that each other ruthlessly with the fantasy lives Ophelia. In this case it's more scary the real part the part fantastic. Much of the credit is about actors whose work is outstanding. From the Mercedes played by Maribel Verdú, continually on the cutting edge of the knife to be Assistant Captain Vidal and collaborator with the maquis at the same time, until the own Captain Vidal, masterfully played by Sergi López. This clear that this man is given well the roles of redomado bastard and on this occasion borda it. Thinner than usual, it has a bearing on screen that creates a ruthless character, but without falling into the caricature of the bad malísimo. The rest of the actors accompany perfectly and each with his work gives weight to the plot, what glimpse of a magnificent work of direction.For the fantastic part of the plot, it is technically correct, though some aspects may be improved. In any case, it's a story and realism is sacrificable to provide even more contrast. Curiously, this part of the film must not reach the half of the footage, but in the trailers seems he addressed almost all of the tape. Note that Guillermo del Toro has drunk from sources as disparate as the work of Tim Burton, the black paintings of Goya or Alice in the country of the wonders of Carroll, but creating a style in which reality and fantasy are mixed with harmony.In short, El Laberinto del Fauno is a story that takes place in a site and a historic moment in which the harsh reality left little room for fantasy. And, as in all story, in this there are adventures, happy moments, sad moments, and a heroine named Ophelia he shares with the viewer the illusion that beyond our senses there is a different world, one in which the acts of individuals have their fair reward or punishment. It is just a fairy tale.</body>
</review>
