<review author="José Córdoba" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For a long time he enjoyed not so much in the film. Guillermo del Toro has made his masterpiece and for which writes the best film I've seen this year.</summary>
	<body>I've seen, finally, the most awaited film for me the year and, despite my high expectations, I was not disappointed, is more exceeded them. It is without doubt the best movie by Guillermo del Toro and one of the best, but the best of the year. And she is Spanish (though in co-production with the United States and Mexico, while the technical and artistic means and most of the money si bien los medios técnicos y artísticos y la mayor parte de el dinero son are Spanish).El laberinto del Fauno narrates the arrival of a girl and her mother to a unknown place of North Spain where the expected the new husband she, a general Franco decided to quell the rebellion of the maquis in that area of the country. Once there, the girl discovers the entrance to an ancient labyrinth that will serve as refuge for events that will continue.Guillermo del Toro is a filmmaker firmly anchored in the fantastic although in some of his films he has made approaches to terror (Mimic) or western (El Espinazo del Diablo). In this film he returned to mixing reality and fantasy, placing the action in the years after the Spanish civil war, as it did in the Devil's backbone, while the stylistic approach is very different. This is a dark film, where evil is painfully real, that takes place in a mysterious forest with an oppressive atmosphere.In this film with influences of "through the looking glass" or "La history forever", evil is not something that comes from the more is not there, something intangible. An ogre, a human being, a soldier played by an exemplary Sergi López, represents all the unrighteousness of mankind, shows how far man can go to achieve their objectives. It is a unforgettable, disgusting, disgusting, real character which, of course, becomes the best villain in recent years. In contrast, we have the innocence, the purity, the imagination of little girl Ophelia performed by Ivana Baquero, who takes refuge in her fantasy world to escape the very painful reality. To your teem around other most secondary but equally important characters played by Ariadna Gil, Maribel Verdú and Álex Angulo (these last two are a nuanced, credible, impressive performances).The work of del Toro after cameras is tall, of a director who knows what becomes. The film runs from reality to fantasy, in a continuous manner, without cracks. The director gives the account of a rate increase and oppressive, not know where you are going to wear, but intuyes that there is no light at the end of the way although you harboring hopes of the Hague. In addition all sections, badly called technicians, rub perfection from the claroscura Photography Guillermo Navarro to the music by Javier Navarrete, passing through some incredible visual effects, taking into account the not very high budget of the film. But Guillermo del Toro, is situated above as a great director of Orchestra who knows how to bring out the best of each party to get a whole bright because the film excites, involves. Each occurrence of the Faun, each act of violence, love, repugnant, are interested in.For a long time he enjoyed not so much in the film. Guillermo del Toro has made his masterpiece and for which writes the best film I've seen this year. Only a detail, to me inexplicable why was not in the list of candidates by Spain for the Oscars? In Mexico they have had more eye and he is their candidate to represent them at the Academy in Hollywood.</body>
</review>
