<review author="Illaq" title="Los Borgia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Entertaining, but excessively long. It is worth to see it, even if only by the aforementioned ambiance and the music that accompanies the action.</summary>
	<body>I've seen a generally entertaining film, although, at times, becomes too long: get me the feeling you spare meters. However, it maintains the storyline; the setting is very careful; the picture is decent; the music is very well embedded in the film, but... The first thing that occurs to me is that the title is wrong. I think it would have been much better, by short and striking to be called: "Borgia", because, in reality, the protagonist is not the "family" Borgia or "the" Borgia, but "a" Borgia: Caesar (Sergio Peris-Mencheta). Alexander VI or Rodrigo Borgia (Lluís Homar) is "the cause" of Caesar and the role; brothers, John (Sergio Muñiz) and Jofré (Eloy Azorín) Borgia are comparsas of the protagonist; sister Borgia, Lucrezia (Maria Valverde), is accompanying. In any case, the film begins with Cesare Borgia in his moment of misfortune with a Corella (Antonio Dechent), the hitherto arm executor of his will in the shade and having seen the Machiavellian image of a Julius II, the previous Cardinal della Rovere (Eusebio Poncela), newly-elected Pope. Then the action back to the arrival of the three brothers Borgia to Rome to attend the election and Coronation of his father, Cardinal Borgia as Pope Alexander VI. From there, he attended the vicissitudes through which passes Caesar, created Cardinal, exempted the purple, named general in Chief of the Papal armies until the death of his father, surpassing the chronological time of his apprehension and ending with his own death. At the formal level, the setting of the film is formidable. Partly filmed exterior in Rome, the greatness of the eternal city is very well accompanied by the plans of interiors. The picture is good and the direction of Antonio Hernández, in my opinion, impeccable, taking into account the script that works, signed by himself and by Piero Bodrato, and the alleged existence of a miniseries for Antena 3. There are memorable moments, such as the overhead map of the funeral and election of Julius II, the the dinner scene with the Orsini, or even the death of Caesar (even if it is, in my opinion, a little artificial). But, it is assumed that a film whose title alludes to a Valencian and important family in the context of the Papal States at the end of the 15th century, with Castile committed to your overseas company, Aragon with his foot in Naples and his enmity with France, which will be supported by the Borgia, will have a large percentage of story of characters, and here is where the movie starts to disappoint me. In general, the story is very superficial, superficial without showing none of the complexity of the characters, starting with the same Cesare Borgia. The image I forwarded by Sergio Peris-Mencheta is a bully of aupado district to a very important post, with a strategic projection and a tactical action critical to the Papal States. And it is difficult that a character so had been able to "inspire" Nicholas Machiavelli to write Il Principe. Not accompanied, in my opinion, the performance of the actor, which strikes me as more corresponds to the role that I say that a strategist who uses force as a means for achieving other ends. The character of Alexander VI (Lluís Homar), on the other hand, is reduced to the minimum term: their love, their parties, their intense feelings toward their children, his mafia sense of family. However, Alexander VI (not in vain spent most of his life in Rome) was a cultivated man, patron of the arts and great politician who knew how to play his cards of ruling, both inwards and outwards (the kingdoms of Castile, Aragon, Portugal, France and Naples, the Republic of Venice and a long etcetera), although some of this is Yes grasping, although with almost picturesque strokes: the Orsini, the Sfroza. In any case, yes seems to me remarkable performance of Lluís Homar, with moments frankly good, as in the scene in which communicate you the death of his son John. Lucrezia Borgia (Maria Valverde), so named in popular legend, appears completely blurred. At least, yes her occurs as a kind of toy of the family, "dad daughter" that dad requires certain efforts in exchange for their status, regardless of their feelings for the alleged benefit of the collective. María Valverde performance seems to me merely discreet. Worth noting the work of certain side and the first is Corella, the executive arm of Cesare Borgia, masterfully played by Antonio Dechent, actor whose dramatic vein I know for about 30 years and it is good shows what there is Curran the matter to be actor in this country. Also, a Eusebio Poncela, who embodies very appropriately, in my opinion, to the cardinal della Rovere and future Julius II. It must not forget to Burkard, the efficient Secretary to Alexander VI, well played by Roberto Alvarez. As for the rest of the cast, Paz Vega, as Caterina Sforza, plays a short with a discrete, predictable interpretation perhaps. It is not, certainly his best role, although Yes it transmits the indignation of the illustrious dam before the omnipotent Caesar. Ángela Molina plays Vanozza, the mother of the Borgias brothers. His performance on also short paper found me also unobtrusive, although it fits well in situations where appears and transmits the delicate situation of the displaced in fact by her man and his sons mother. The rest of the actors, perhaps deserve highlighting Linda Batista as Sancha of Aragon. Eloy Azorín as Jofré Borgia and Sergio Muñiz, as Juan Borgia, have given me the feeling of being filled. Diego Martín, as Perotto, simply not liked. I don't know if under the influence of his role in the television series here no hay quien viva or by circumstances of its interpretation, not transmitted me at all the dramatic nature of its presence. Moreover, the real story is schematised to such an extent that it gives the feeling of Rodrigo Borgia has fallen in Rome as a "UFO" when they elect him Pope, ignoring the fact his long stay in the Vatican intricacies and its precedent Callixtus III, which would have their part in the Roman network of friendships and enmities of the great families. In summary, Los Borgia seems to me an entertaining film, although excessively long. It is worth to see it, even if only by the aforementioned ambiance and the music that accompanies the action, although perhaps missed an opportunity to make a film that is more focused on the character that serves as a common thread or, Alternatively, certainly spectacular political and military circumstances of the era of Alexander VI.</body>
</review>
