<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A free movie, which wasted imagination, that can be enjoyed in every one of their frames and fails to be a teacher only because lacks it a point of emotion to finish snatch to the Viewer.</summary>
	<body>We must be very well placed balls to imagine, write, draw and shoot a film as "El laberinto del fauno", that cruel, bloody and sinister reality gives the hand with the most boundless, imaginative and unbridled fantasy. In addition, should be much genius and great talent for mixing the Post Spanish Civil War, the maquis and the Francoist repression with a fairy tale. and leave with good of the challenge.Guillermo del Toro is a prolific, protean and Homeric, equipped with an unsurpassed ability to imaginative and visionary, flying free, filmed what pleases and almost always does it masterfully. From "Cronos", wonderful making it the day of the myth of the vampire and the struggle for immortality, until this "Laberinto del fauno", del Toro has left his personal imprint on so intimate as "The Devil's backbone" projects or so supposedly commercial as "Hellboy" or "Blade" products. "And all these movies end up leaving a nice and delicious aftertaste in the Viewer.""El laberinto del fauno" is a fantastic tour de force that, since his sonorous and evocative title, leaves no one indifferent. A car of the Phalanx progresses, barely, by a bad country road. A mother tells her daughter that you read too many books fairy. When the car arrives at its destination and the girl he meets which is going to be his putative father. all of us understand that his only refuge will be, precisely, in this world of fantasy that will open to its around. Because the masterfully played by the always genial character Sergi López is a piece of bastard of a piece, as long we saw not on a cinema screen. A bastard who knows that he is, that enjoy being so and have not the slightest remorse for being. The counterpoint, paradoxically, is that threatening fantasy world in which, however, the little protagonist can find more warmth than the existing between men.Baroque and, at times, bizarre, the oneiric universe which introduces the girl will have consequences in the real world which flees. "So, through the tests under the endearing Faun, small"achieved"that knife that will be critical to Mercedes, will learn how to escape from the villain of the piece and, with their innocence and determination, will bring a ray of hope to make the real world a little, only a little better.""El laberinto del Fauno" is a free film, which wasted imagination, that can be enjoyed in every one of their frames and that fails to be a teacher only because lacks it a point of emotion to finish snatch the viewer and make that tears in the stalls spilling. Although well thought of having it done as well, for sure it had accused of del Toro's sentimental and dramatic. In any case, we have an outstanding movie that confirms that, when there is genius, personality and talent, everything else, including budget, it is secondary.</body>
</review>
