<review author="Ricardo Marquina" title="Paura Nella Città dei Morti Viventi" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film was released not complete in any country, because the work offered to the censors of the time was not trivial...</summary>
	<body>A priest, somewhat tempering, commits suicide by hanging of a pine tree in the American city of Dunwich, city settled on an old settlement of witches. This is the signal that the gates of the underworld are opened, releasing the dead of eternal sleep, making them return to the terror of the living world. Meanwhile, in New York, a journalist saves a beautiful young woman, to which all breed dead after a session of Spiritism, of being buried alive. The journalist and the aforementioned young will depart at the difficult work to avoid the dead to dominate Earth.So is "Paura Nella Città dei Morti Viventi" (fear in the city of the living dead in its Spanish Edition). Film directed and written by the incombustible and opportunistic Lucio Fulci in 1980, who achieved this time its more compact, smooth and interesting film.Well done and enjoyable course, "Paura Nella Città dei Morti Viventi" is a film poor in nuances and blurred in his argument. Although well developed, was missing many "ques", leaving large unexplained part of what happened. Mediocre performers and delirious, the Italian Fabio Frizzi music, are the worst of the film, however, her do not detract at all, dating back the interest to blow good gore, explicit and free of charge, from the hands of the master Rossi.Y Gino is that Fulci after nausea without reason, (a) the major displeasure and the restless startle. So much so that this movie not released complete in any country, because the work offered to the censors of the time was not trivial. In fact you can find it in the network, complete, Yes, but with scenes in German, other Italian Spanish. an international cutting as escape censorship.By harsh scenes has a few, as it shows a button: when the zombie priest "hypnotizes" a young hacéndole vomit all his digestive system. Wow, must be made casings heart.There is no doubt that Fulci is an opportunistic pig who sought profit in the wake of the pull of the zombie genre, but was not the only, in addition to do well and give us many anthologies scenes. It will be a son of a bitch, Yes, but it is our son of a bitch. Without a doubt the best, or least bad for some, Fulci creature. Good luck with it.</body>
</review>
