<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="La guerra de los mundos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spielberg has become, and I reconnected to enjoy</summary>
	<body>They defenestrarán this film for its end. But is that probably many not know the plot of the original novel with the same name by HG WELLS, the radio adaptation of Orson Welles or not saw the original film by Byron Haskin of the 52. The screenplay by Barré Lyndon unfortunately already rushing in the last third and also surprised us with a final for nothing complacent. There later was 88 a television version in format series, 48 chapters in one hour under the title: "The war of the worlds" the second invasion. To reach this new film from extraterrestrial invasions of the hand of Spielberg, we passed by many others before and some of them very notable. There is a film four years later, in 1956, "The invasion of the body snatchers" by Don Siegel, very similar to the original "The war of the worlds", and he narrated an alien invasion also terrifying and virtually unstoppable, very consistent with the background of the war cold in those years. It was a remake in 1978 directed by Philip Kaufman, without happy ending and with the title "The invasion of the ultracuerpos". (A very good remake and for me, without a doubt, the best of the three.) Abel Ferrara finally directed the last remake where everything was at a military base and recovering the happy ending in 1994.In 1985 the series of science fiction "V" also caused furor in half the world. (In our country was a real hit while in other European countries no one remembers her.) There are others, "The Arrival" (have come) 1996 or "The Faculty" in 1998 by Robert Rodriguez, but was 96 when became "Independence day", by Emmerich, which calcó with nerve invasion reported by HG Wells in a new more modern version, not sold as such, which already changed, as in this another remake of Spielberg, the stage of the old England (as a former world power) by the currently powerful nation of the United States. Spielberg, who was made a few years ago with the rights of the original script for the adaptation of Welles, delayed the project by the success of "Independence Day", where even the final outcome spoke also of bacteria and viruses, although in this modern version was a computer virus responsible for ending the malevolent plans of the invaders.Many people still do not know what Spielberg returned to change the date for the filming of his own remake, but this time to advance it. This is due to the beginning of a new official version of the version of HG Wells by an independent production company Pendragon Pictures. This version, much more modest, but even began filming well before, its premiere he already planned for this same spring. A disproportionate career legal and tough competition has existed, however, secretly between the mega project of the colossi Spielberg and Cruise and these independent producers. There is no trace of the release of the version of Pendragon Pictures. Apparently, this time have Goliat defeated David.David Koepp and Josh Friedman, the writers of the version of Spielberg, after so many movies, versions and series similar, they have not wanted or they have failed to evade too much of the original and have not been able to give us an ending that does not precipitate and not disappoint. At the time of meet with huge expectations created during a first master time, history is forgotten gradually give us answers to some basic questions (the reaction of Governments during the crisis, red plants, the sprinkled blood, etc) and the plot has just lost in a complete cloud of confusion during the appearance on the scene of the character played by Tim Robbinsto finish in a forzadísimo and nothing credible happy-end.But none of this matters. The progressive appearance of the storm with some great sound effects and the formidable musical work of John Williams throughout the tape. The sudden and terrifying appearance of machines, destruction, powder, (thought see something resembling a remembrance of September 11), suspense, impotence, tension, a few special effects very realistic and terrifying, thrilling, sober and masterful action. Scenes such as the conversation during the flight in the car, with a disturbing and impossible camera movement. The bodies floating in the River, the American population turned into refugees, in desperate "zombies", chaos in the boat, clothes falling from the sky as an apocalyptic rain and very remarkable and outstanding performances of Cruise, Dakota Fanning and all the rest.Spielberg returns to M. Night. Shyamalan with his "signals" to your site. Shows who is the real King of the suspense, it reminds us that it was, and not anyone else, who already in his day aterrara the world with "The devil on wheels", "Shark" or even some excellent moments in "Jurasic Park". Spielberg is not always in the most recent "The Schlinder list" or "Save the soldier Ryan" and fails to keep the regular expected by so many fans (including myself) <>but the truth is that, since the release of this remake (which improves with a vengeance to his original) "Independence day" and only seems a fair carousel. One of the most dark, violent and dark of the great master works we have now in billboard. Spielberg has become. And I'm back to enjoy.</body>
</review>
