<review author="Ivan R. Gonzalez" title="Jesucristo cazavampiros" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is bad on purpose. It is a modest and casual film limited to successfully deliver on its promise of fun Disney.</summary>
	<body>A plague of vampires is stoking while sending with all the lesbians of a small town. The priests of the place cannot afford more time this massacre and decide to ask for help from Jesus to save the herd. After a first defeat, El Santo and Mary Magnum help the son of God in the sacred task to exterminate these creatures of darkness based on stakes and call.The fact that this film is the 2001 wake up not a few suspicions. It is not for less, in recent years all the "freak" seems to have become fashionable. Many have climbed on the bandwagon of "freak" and it has been used as an excuse to fill a little pockets at the expense of making fun of people. Fortunately, the movie before us is more a tribute to the demented El Santo films and similar to a simple opportunist illusion. The "film" (the quotes are not free) perfectly emulates every aspect of the ochenteras b series. Actors more bad that hitting a father, music sinte salchichera, lysergic script, low quality cameras. After an exercise of such care mimesis, it seems incredible that it has been filmed in 21st century.This Canadian production contains everything you can ask for a lover of dandruff: a hilarious story, unlikely situations, awkward kung-fu and shabby blood. In addition, permitted flirt with music on a couple of occasions, with rather sad results, the worst of the film. Even more unfortunate is the unfortunate decision to cut the hair to Jesus at the beginning of the story, throwing overboard the charism of the character. On the contrary, this fat version (more) of El Santo is a success leveling balance of the couple protagonist, a success as evidenced in the hilarious scene of the bar. Never mind the rough direction in a product like this; in fact, it is bad on purpose. It is a modest and casual film limited to successfully deliver on its promise of fun Disney. As a curiosity, it is said that Mel Gibson wept upon seeing her. I do not think that it is true (I doubt even that good Mel know the existence of this movie), but undeniably the sacrilegious nature of the gem. And we all know funny are the sacrilege.</body>
</review>
