<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="The host" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>With a recital of clichés in this manner he garnished us Korean time and average remaining where boredom will be the protagonist of a stretched, languid, disjointed, chaotic footage.</summary>
	<body>Encouraged by a brazen and provocative trailer where a beast of a river tilting slow motion against the surprised citizens, I went to see this movie in Sitges, where also its director introduced announcing that the sound effects would not us us to sleep while this began at eleven in the evening of a Sunday her.Best thing about the movie is its initial part and see how it goes straight to the point. A very bad doctor, the only American who appears in the film, of course, ordered to throw a few chemicals down the drain in his laboratory. Six years later there is a monster sunbathing in the adjacent River. It is not original at all, but no matter. People discover what scuba diving and the beast comes out to play with the people to the "you her wearing". The monster campa to full light of day and we can see and enjoy its physiognomy and their skills superbly thanks to some effects made these Yes, in Hollywood. Images of the beast, generated by computer, during the first 20 minutes are absolutely sweeping. Clear, and I while I wondered there sitting in the cinema. If in twenty minutes it has taught me this Korean everything that a movie of this kind usually me give in all their footage complete, what I will teach now? Well then, we discovered that the protagonist is a regrettable Muttley and we were stunned when the beast abducts his daughter and then leave the family to complete (up to the abuelito), to look for her. Thus, as if they were hiking to the pine forest. The mix of genres is something dangerous and if humor is East because the contest is even more complicated. Imagine that a monster kidnaps the son of Aida, the series, and from there we see like her, accompanied by his entire family of Yahoos go to rescue him. Because it would be a comedy with Monster. A comic horror movie. Now imagine that the family of losers and jokes are Korean and that the best of the Fireworks is when the grandfather says that you can identify the State of mind of his son when this pulls a fart in the caravan. So if they are going to see this movie already shall not imaginations. Many people laughed at in the room for funny things in the movie that more are good only for our Western minds and that they actually have to do with how to act, react or strange traditions and Oriental rituals. I remembered that cinema session a few years ago, with the room full of teenagers from the box to laugh with the remastered version of "The Exorcist". A movie which made cry of fear of entire generations, now had become a comedy for teenagers that could not drop the laugh, for example, before the ridiculous pints and connaisseurs hairstyles of the actors.Returning to "The Host", soon they teach us that the sister of the abducted girl is Olympic Sharpshooter of arc and that sadly only get the bronze. And we then know who you trigger the monster final arrow to try to win the gold. With a recital of clichés in this manner he garnished us Korean time and average remaining where boredom will be the protagonist of a stretched, languid, disjointed, chaotic footage.I could give some to another cabezada despite sound effects. The movie lasts two hours and to tell the truth, perhaps with that fabulous trailer would have left.</body>
</review>
