<review author="Javier Saz" title="Saraband" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Ingmar Bergman us giddy with truths as fists, naked humans, put out of their misery, our miseries.</summary>
	<body>"Saraband" is one of the films that has most impacted me in recent times, not be as qualified, whether melodrama or Horror. Such is the impact on my memory. Ingmar Bergman us giddy with truths as fists, naked humans, put out of their misery, our miseries.The grandiose Liv Ullmann (Marianne), reunited after thirty years with Johan, a former ex-marido (returning to the characters of "Secrets of a marriage"), and in the House also spend the summer the son of Johan Henrik, the daughter of this, Karin. Relationships are conflicts, hatred between parents and children, humiliation, lie, fear. Bergman seeks the worst of human beings and shows it shamelessly nude. Johan despises his son Henrik for its soft character and appearance. Henrik hates his father for his humiliation and contempt. The women of Henrik died two years ago, and Henrik has failed, only relies on her daughter Karin, which teaches to play the cello. Karin wants to go to the city, to the Conservatory, but knows that if his father leaves this die from penalty. Uff, and this only approach. Then contains really chilling scenes for you hard and naked show emotions, with a clean look that frightens, a delight to the eye.Saraband in its most common meaning is a dance for two dancers, and the film is divided into ten chapters, preceded by a prologue and an epilogue, and all of them are conceived as a dialogue between two characters, less the prologue and the epilogue which are monologues of Liv Ullmann.No boasts formally, although he is allowed at the beginning and at the end Marianne talk to the Viewer, directs actors all masterfully, unrepeatable moments, emotions overwhelmed, revealed miseries.With what I've seen of Bergman happens to me that I love or let me indifferent, and this goes next to them that I like, next to "Person", "Wild strawberries" or "The seventh seal".</body>
</review>
