<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="World Trade Center" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Boring and predictable story that us splatters with continuous flashbacks and parallel actions, as the footage moves sleeping way.</summary>
	<body>Oliver Stone returns to behind the camera to narrate the fatal events that occurred on September 11, 2001. The special thing of this proposal is that it focuses on two members of the port police that they were trapped and they were rescued alive. Starting a home right, with a presentation of the attack which is almost the best of the film, Stone shows the experiences of a group of policemen led by John Mcloughlin, Nicolas Cage, who go to one of the towers of the World Trade Center to try to help, but after a few minutes login, have the misfortune that the building will collapse on top of themas all we saw in the chilling images that gave us television. From this point, the film is set in a live of the families of the two affected, who are wondering if their husbands and fathers are (respectively) live without. These roles are Maria Bello as the wife of Cage and Maggie Gyllenhall of Michael Peña. As you can guess, their characters are quite typical women distraught by his party and by theirs, police trapped beneath hundreds of rubble waiting for getting help and giving mutual support to not fall asleep, fearing not wake up if they do. Because of this, the screenplay by Andrea Berloff becomes a boring and predictable story that us splatters with continuous flashbacks and parallel actions, as the footage moves sleeping way. A fact which surprised me and I see no justification, is the fact that Maria Bello takes why those so cantosas blue contact lenses, do not know if there will be any rationale for this, because in any other of his performances has resorted to this. Let these anecdotes to continue with World Trade Center, and say the new Oliver Stone movie is not surprising for any site, which obviously has some very good moments and arriving in the chord of the spectator, as when you Will Jimeno (Michael Peña) asks the rescue team to act more quickly to help McLoughlin with its consequent result, but apart from that and some more, we find others fully exposing the viewer of his armchair, making that smiles and comments raise about the sound of the screen, and a clear example of this is the appearance of Jesus Christ in one of the hallucinations of final Jimeno.En a faithful account of what lived the two survivors, but that cinematically leaves much to be desired and that it might have been differently, although he had to slightly alter the events, because although hard to say so, the film is focused to the public and not to the delight of the director exclusively.</body>
</review>
