<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Los Borgia" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It empacha very much and is saved by a few great actors. Tibia has been the experience. Fu or fa, said my grandmother.</summary>
	<body>They have some commitment to sanctify Spanish Cinema: climb over the French, which was always the benchmark with what espesitos dialogues, black-and-white of Fable in the Paris taken by lovers and the nouvelle vague, which was an invention of a film very in spate magazine. Others have a unhealthy habit to stock and argue that their precarious health comes by the ailing initiatives of the State, which does not give a euro for this patriotic film. All of which come to place Los Borgia in this limbo of imprecise definition of films which, without being round, nor are lunchrooms. Which strives to destroy her will find arguments. Who pontifiquen his virtues, arguments there.Mine are all warm. Tibia has been the experience. Fu or fa, said my grandmother. The trailer is the best of the footage. No to swallow more minutes. Its splendor is oxidized soon. Fails, for example, in the obvious: in the near. It is not credible. Takes no risks should be, and so everything is left in a threshold of intent which not coagulate, but they spared no (who doubts it) infrastructure, logistics, staff, people of talent, but then the brilliance, talent and all that trash of Hispanic genius is lost immediately.Film that empacha very much, is saved by a few great actors. What we say. They are people with a few tables and knew that Alatriste was behind and that the public wants war and history, and potatoes with a dark past and Vatican machinations several. That enters the eye. And the music is great.We grant you an exquisite time that I, at least, lack increasingly to leisure. I came to see that he would leave the shot for this stock, had come to walk the streets of my town, that have their charm. I had plugged my Hi-Fi equipment and he would have lost golosamente time on the first Genesis, before Phil Collins albums. Or had seen again evil thirst. What more good movie. How beautiful is the cinema.</body>
</review>
