<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Buenas noches y buena suerte" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Spectacular pestiño where the tension and dramatic rigor are conspicuous by their absence</summary>
	<body>Some I odiaran without delay to attack a movie of el guapo Clooney, some not understanding the liberal and critical message of the tape, and others for not knowing appreciate the taste of a movie shot in black and white in the classical style, or for not giving up before its current recognition in Hollywood. The tension and dramatic rigor of the film are conspicuous by their absence. The camera effectively tells the story in black and white, but isn't "Schindler's list" or a lot less and, in this, the cinematographic language and the Mise en scene do not pass of mediocre.The actors do good they can with a flat, tedious and predictable script. David Strathairm poses very serious all the time, with adequate sobriety. Clooney appears very elegant, very correctito and nothing else. And the history between Robert Downey Jr. and Patricia Clarkson is so unnoticed, which does not reach another something that to be absurd. Actors smoke, that Yes, much, that we know that in the classic Bogart film already remained very well and also to try to go against, what better that exalt the tobacco in a society in which currently points to kick the habit.Television can be a tool to educate or to evade. Television is easy to handle. Already, Yes, and what? Therefore, nothing more. Or a dare to really portray the witch hunt, or the era Mc Carthy, or risk to address one critical sincere, serious or interesting about nothing at all. "Good night and good luck" is a spectacular pestiño. Which sat in the cinema by my side, after the first twenty minutes, slept like a baby and then survived the long-awaited final plugging your mp3. I envied for this reason, although I decided to deal me in until the end, even if only to be able to write about it today here. What huge disappointment with a film of which expected much more. The best, without doubt, was that, thank God, the ordeal did not exceed the hour and a half.</body>
</review>
