<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Pret a porter" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Robert Altman in Pret a porter does not make film: makes a movie where they leave Sophia Loren, Julia Roberts, Kim Basinger, Marcello Mastroianni, Tim Robbins or Stephen Rea and a heavenly cohort of weight mannequins look palmito.</summary>
	<body>Now that the Devil Wears prada announced in the bus stops, with his homicidal heel, with its clean claim perfect beauty, I again see Pret a porter, the tape of Robert Altman that looks distantly over the fashion world portrayed in the picture of Meryl Streep as (forgive the redundancy) fashion.I really not dazzled in his day and the review last night remachó the little lair that fills my memory to this film. Very true that Robert Altman is a director of height has given very notable films, Mash, three women, the game of Hollywood, Cookie's fortune and, above all, Vidas cruzadas, but here has patinated in excess, although it has surrounded the cream of the world of the gateway and has portrayed with vigour and with some excellence of style their hustling and their meanhis power and glory. What is Pret a porter is script. You don't see anywhere, and that is a huge SIN for a film. It is a huge Sin a simple conversation of neighbors in a ladder without script. The script is the meat that makes that the skeleton does not fall to the ground. The script, the film narrative, is the reference absolute. One can find portentous frames, a sublime picture, a few interpretations that rozen perfection, but if there is nothing attention is losing, and then we are not witnessing a round film but more or less well bonded images consenting that they can, in certain circumstances, be appointed with the generic name of Cine.Robert Altman, Pret a porter, does not (then) film: makes a movie where they leave Sophia Loren, Julia Roberts, Kim Basinger, Marcello Mastroianni, Tim Robbins and Stephen Rea and a heavenly cohort of weight mannequins look Palm and rub shoulders with flashy players. Underneath this costume so recently, there are huge gaps: are so great that some overlap others and form one larger holes so much footage during what we see is a wasteland, a wasteland, a lunar landscape in which a director with absolute competence and well-deserved prestige salda with verve accounts we are unfamiliar with the world of fashion. In the end, you trivialize, it ningunea, so hence it towards the limits of the foolish.Pret a porter is amoral and is acid because something has to be or because the talent behind should be evident in some feature distinctly intellectual. Choral poetry of Vidas cruzadas (Short cuts in its English original) desmembra in Pret a porter in a few rhymes of drunkenness that four friends with some literary background make up to entertain the way back home. Everything in Vidas cruzadas knew to fresh air, very interesting novelty, Pret a porter is boredom. You may not entertain a tape where nothing happens or where very little happens: what happens in addition interest relatively.He would have liked to Altman film flow by the police course that principia the scene in which dies the steward of fashion in Paris and Mastroianni, stunned character, attends, but obvious all the police film material and extends, with violence almost, in the field of comedy abrasive and bubbly, giving way to a Vertigo of banalities that does not fill the appetite of the friendly Viewerunless it has lately seen short film or except that it is a voracious eater of sophisticated, hollow and notable artifacts.The American Syd Field, recognized among the authors of manuals of screenwriting, authority establishes rules for his writing: each page of a script equals one minute of projection on screen. I can not imagine that Pret a porter had 130 pages in your script. Or much less. There are some dazzling, that Yes: this home where Altman teaches us a blowout showcase incredible brands and high fashion, but we are not in Paris or nice. It is Moscow. Robert Altman, elderly, complainant, with that look of old bad milk that still cela treasures, talent and ingenuity as to fall in love with new generations and deserve the applause of those who already had him in esteem did in the key, slipped: he portrayed a world difiícilmente retratable, despite the flashes, flashes are your daily subscription.I imagine a Blake Edwards in his good time aboard this custom. 80 Pages of script, i.e., or hour and a half of film, would suffice but to me it is that Blake Edwards I like a lot and I see more incisive, much less heterodox that Altman, concerned in excess of not content to many to satisfy a lot a few. The Loyalists. Doran le that the pill. I doré le in Vidas cruzadas. And that argument had three hours of pages.</body>
</review>
