<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Zombies party" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>100% Hilarious. The zombies, slower than el caballo del Malo are continuous laughter.</summary>
	<body>You have to see the amount of movies from zombies that record lately. If Resident Evil 2, that if dawn of the dead, that if 28 days. And each more and more bad. But this was another very different looks. In the photo on the cover, a guy in an elevator with face barmy and surrounded by zombies with face of Kumar. The movie promised.And go that if promised. The movie is a descojono continuous, such that if you estornudas you've lost three points. He is a guy with face of lelo who has trouble with his girlfriend. Lives with a fat fumeta (fuck, see all me are fumetas) which is a dirty and a guy with bad host. And spend life in a bar called "Winchester". Suddenly, with good reason, the bride lets just when a virus attacks the city. Of course, the lelo don't realize that half the city is zombie until you they don't try to bite the jugular. And decides that he must save the bride and her mother.100% Hilarious. The zombies, slower than el caballo del Malo are continuous laughter. A detail that made me laugh. Attack them on the porch of his house a few zombies and say "what do we do?" "Sit to drink a tea" and sit on the couch at home while the zombies drool-worthy window. Asks one to another "still there" and rises the fat, remove the curtain are restregandose zombies by the glass and says "Yes" and sits down again. At the end go to kill them and begin to launch them cooking utensils. A colander, a funnel, the toaster, etc. As do not kill them it (leave the zombies on the same site) (a) the record of the lelo collection. And so the entire film.I recommend it strongly, but then I don't want to hear that if the movie is a truño, that if I am an asshole, if I you're going to start with the legs and things as well. To me I liked so much that I've seen twice.</body>
</review>
