<review author="Yul B." title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am a rare bug between such excellence, but I risk to say with sincerity and respect the rest of criticism, that this film has disappointed me quite, at the risk of having to leave the country and go into hiding.</summary>
	<body>I have overwhelmed all the criticisms circulating in blogs, portals and forums moviegoers referring to this film. Her they describe as "masterpiece", "risky", "the best film of Guillermo del Toro", or "it is going to be the winner of the 2007 Oscar for best film of non-English speaking safe". And as to the interpretations of its actors, rise them to the category of "great" or "sublime", with an unforgettable Sergi López. I am a rare bug between such excellence, but I risk to say with sincerity and respect the rest of criticism, that this film I quite disappointed.Am assuming that the promotion of the tape (Jesus said be trailers) is totally misleading. It only shows the fantastic part of the story, forgetting (can that intentionally) what really reflected in this film: a passage in the history with a capital of Spain, specifically after the civil war, "softened" with a tale of fairies, princesses and strange creatures. Up the same poster of the film confuses with those letters in the "Harry Potter" style.Ultimately, that to really find out what the film, and it does not lead to deception, was essential to have read at least before the first paragraphs of the official synopsis. After reading the rest of this overview, we will be a global idea of what features the film, although we continue to believe that this is a fantasy story located in a clever and different way at a turbulent time in Spanish history.Nothing further from the truth. Who go to see this movie is going to find with the umpteenth and charisma film about the war Spanish Civil (explicit miseries included), in which for scarcely half an hour of the two that lasts us transports to a fanciful and unreal world as cruel and interested as the real world which is reflected in it. For some parents, abstain from taking your children to see her because of child there's nothing.Promotional deceptions aside, I think that this film has been short for expectations. It is true that the picture and music are very good, and the script is acceptable, but Guillermo del Toro is able to create fantastic worlds best and more far-reaching than that seen in?The Laberinto del Fauno?. Having to deal only in 120 minutes two complex stories, reality and fantasy, although related, it is only possible to be brief, rapid and direct, so should not be excessively extend in flourishes.Perhaps it would have been more effective, and even dramatic, that the fantasy world that we see it would have locked up more footage and had traveled roads more edulcorados than the one shown, to create a strong contrast with the real world, represented in a very cruel, violent and bloody way. But of course, then this product not had signed of the Toro.En regards the main cast of the film, for my taste include interpretations of Ivana Baquero, the girl protagonist (although in some scenes may seem a bit repellent), the of Maribel Verdú (in the incredible line of his later works, this time with appropriate thin) and Alex Angulo, although the latter has had other work with better results. The Ariadna Gil seems very normalita, pulling to mediocre, and that of Doug Jones, as the Faun, adds nothing new.In regards to Sergi López, here I going to throw around my neck: the encounter significant but not remarkable. Its interpretation is based in the visual, and in this regard, López has built an evil sadistic, bloodthirsty and unscrupulous; But why we cannot think that you it's the best villain in the history of the Spanish cinema.The evil is reflected in other aspects, and when Captain Vidal did not commit atrocities which explicitly teaches us, the character is portrayed correctly, as one among all.By cash, qualify this film of "regular", at the risk of having to leave the country and go into hiding.</body>
</review>
