<review author="Ricard Marcet" title="Palindromos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The feeling of discomfort, relocation, seizes the room during all the footage with a mise en scene dealing with familiar characters and situations vetoed in the film more to use.</summary>
	<body>The last work of the controversial American filmmaker Todd Solondz has come to our screens Palíndromos, two years late. Once again, as it already did with his previous films, it will be capable of dismay, in one way or another, to all kinds of public.Palindromes trafficking history of Aviva, a girl of twelve years who believe to see in the fact of being a mother, the solution to their emotional problems. It will soon become pregnant and parents force him to abort. After the traumatic events, Aviva will escape from the House of his parents and will undertake a journey solo (from those that, in principle, changes life?) for a world strange and full of possibilities.It often refers to the work of Solondz as a critical x-ray of American society (and, by extension, Western) and in turn, as a walk along the border that separates the drama of humor. This definition falls short to Palíndromos, I understand, his most personal work in which expressed an intimate philosophy, intuida but not developed in his previous works. It is from the constants of the film Hollywood (often through his denial) that the American director develops his personal narrative, his own poetry. A concrete example can be found in the use of music on the soundtrack, introduced in the dramatic moments in the more conventional way and suddenly cut, unsettling the Viewer. It is this feeling of discomfort, of relocation, which takes over the room during all the footage with a mise en scene dealing with familiar characters and situations vetoed in the film more to use.The journey of Aviva, as if it were a story, will be explained through a series of episodes. The viewer accustomed to uplifting trips in which the character gives meaning to their existence, will accompany the kind enlivens (and it seems that for Solondz, goodness is the result of ignorance, of unconsciousness) by a few adventures which eventually where started. It will be Mark Wiener, computer scientist and alleged pedophile's deterministic thinking, who, through a few words that seem to exits from the mouth of the director himself, will remind enlivens their inability to change. Nothing will serve the protagonist played by six different actresses, because its history will end at the point from which departed in the same way that occurs with your name and any other Palindrome (for Solondz, metaphor for human nature). In the myriad of characters that accompany the girl during his trip, the viewer intuirá something very familiar not perceived in the heroes of the conventional cinema. In its ambiguity existential, often hidden under a fierce double morality, we see reflected our innermost fears. Thus, these creatures that at first we antojaron grotesque, recall us our most immediate reality. Used to identify us with ideal characters who choose, they transform and give meaning to their existence, Todd Solondz us wakes up from our sweet dream of freedom Earth throwing large speeches that try to justify humans, provide it with meaning, and reminding us of the nonsense that surrounds us. Before such drama, so only we can only laugh.</body>
</review>
