<review author="Ricard Marcet" title="Grizzly man" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Through selected material from the nearly 90 hours shot by Treadwell and interviews with their relatives, the German filmmaker builds an intimate portrait of the protagonist and uncovers the ancient ghosts that governed his life.</summary>
	<body>American Timothy Treadwell, lover and amateur scholar of grizzly bears, lived with these fierce animals for thirteen summers. Convinced of being the only protector of these beings representing, in their eyes, the perfect life expression, not you hesitate camping in their territories and constantly omitting the law prohibiting recede less than 90 meters. Become a celebrity following his numerous visits to schools and their television appearances won the enmity of researchers and biologists, and it would be seen by many as an obsessed disposed in a risky and incomprehensible altruistic work. Criticisms not broke the will of Timothy that in his last five expeditions lead with a video camera to record his adventures and immortalize their life experience. In October 2003, the worst expectations meet: Timothy and Amie Huguenard, his girlfriend and occasional companion, would be despedazados and devoured by a large grizzly bear. His death would not surprise to almost anyone and even a segment of the right policy tacharía, with chilling cynicism, "typical death of a Democrat". Diametrically opposed would be the attitude of Werner Herzog who, from a perspective which respects, intuiría in the history of the grizzly man a latent drama, a dimension unknown by most. Through selected material from the nearly 90 hours shot by Treadwell and interviews with their relatives, the German filmmaker builds an intimate portrait of the protagonist and uncovers the ancient ghosts that governed his life: handsome and sporty teenager with a promising future, the young Timothy discovered the bad life at the University. After flirtations with drugs and incubating an incipient alcoholism, decided to turn his life and be an actor. However, after being rejected for a role on the series Cheers, it would fall into a spiral of self-destruction and deep depressions. His life being a host of unfulfilled promises, he again felt the need to reinvent itself. It is to look back in search of shelter when you will recall his personal rosebud, the hobby to the teddy bears, which will awaken in him excessive passion for grizzly bears. Timothy will depart from the society and refugiará in the natural reserves of Alaska where will forge an ideal world next to the bears (in his eyes, incarnation of goodness). Treadwell autonombrará guardian of this simple and harmonious world, and a non-existent poacher, representative of civilization that rehuyó it, will be their only enemy. His tormented spirit can momentarily find peace in this idealized nature and your camera will her embalming. However, this utopian world is soon crumble. Werner Herzog, who has granted an important papela nature, both in his life and his work, and spoke of the sensitivity new age and esotericism as diseases of civilization, takes the material shot by Treadwell to expose his ideas on the relationship between man and the world. Thus, caring nature displayed in beautiful landscape portraits and friendly drawings of bears, accompanied by pleasant notes of guitar, initiating the film, proved as a result of a confusing human to be faced projection to the outtakes to the material which Treadwell had rejected in a montage on their ideal world. The friendly gaze that sees him in the bears and that leads him to talk to them as if they were human beings, will vanish when he came across the remains of a Cub has been devoured by an adult male. The idealized vision of the protagonist, which will even come to worship the osunas stool, entroncará with the natural chaos and violence. The tragic death under the clutches of their beloved bears corroborará that the world of Timothy did not correspond with the indifferent (is chaotic, inhumane?) reality, the place which had been found to suit only existed in his films. Hand of Herzog, Timothy Treadwell crazy becomes a good-natured character able to win the affection of the Viewer. Vapuleado by civilization, their stubborn struggle for a company to failure becomes an emotional reflection of the struggle of man against the existential absurd, against vacuum. Werner Herzog transcend the beautiful images of the documentary-maker apprentice, making what principle are we wanted as a zany story and meaningless in a stirring speech. Always respectful, as corroborated by the scene in which calls for destroying the tape that recorded the shouts of Timothy and Amie being devoured (material of incalculable value for a documentalist unscrupulous), Herzog leaves aside the morbid to focus attention on the Warrior and passionate nature that characterizes Treadwell twinning it with other characters in the universe of the filmmaker as Lope de Aguirre or Fitzcarraldo. Surpassing the mere curiosity, the German director endorses the images of grizzly man to present, openly, his particular vision of the world; returning the film in this way, to the place that feel you better: a poetic place between language and reality from which is possible to explore the contradictory human nature. PS: "we should be grateful because the universe there outside does not know any smile." Werner Herzog in the Declaration of Minnesota</body>
</review>
