<review author="Silvia Giner" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good interpretation, magic management, very good special effects, a beautiful story to tell, an end to double dimension and the authentic brand staff of Guillermo del Toro.</summary>
	<body>I have to say, that "The laberinto del fauno", reminded me much "The Devil's backbone" as well as working with children again, the Toro again this vague feeling of two-dimensional final, i.e. a final that according to the dimension that you choose to interpret it is going to look like an appallingly cruel end or an end never better said, fairy tale. This is what happened to me when I saw the spine and again repeat sensations with the labyrinth of the Fauno.Es a film very William, with his personal stamp, without the pressure of large producers as it could happen in Hellboy and Blade II (whose second part is doing at the moment, release planned for 2008), has been fully released to be dropped into this magical world that has inside and that it has when wheel with freedom. Del Toro is possessed by his work and reveals a perhaps imaginary world, perhaps not, that rocks with a cruel reality for a time bitter in the Franco.Llega Spain the time talking about the fragile Ofelia (Ivana Vaquero), which looks like a lint on upper lip that I crave mustachioed according to plans (take into account light)(do, the foci? that increases or decreases the visibility of the lint) and have to shout from the rooftops that I constantly distracted and I took out of context. Because of this fluff, I had constant stomach protrusion. The question then is: why a director of the stature of Guillermo del Toro, misses the fact that there are some levels where the girl wears moustache?, please forgive me Ivana which is a fantastic actress, but this has no forgiveness, a director who cares both his aesthetics, I'm not worth the excuse that it was to give realism, because a girl of that age with a moustache is absolutely horrible, could be having put a bit of andina (dye for hair on upper lip) and having it to the less "disguised", the moustache been equally realistic, but more beautiful to be blonde hair instead of negrooooo!Sergi López? sublime, as always. Did me that grace the cameo of Federico Lupi, seated on his throne but very short time sequence is for a big actor. I have nothing bad to criticize the movie in general as well as the existential void that leaves you, because the end of double dimension.Good interpretation, magic management, very good special effects, a beautiful story to tell, an end to double dimension and the authentic brand staff of Guillermo del Toro, director that grows with each tape runs and for me one of the best currently in the fantasy genre. Round film.</body>
</review>
