<review author="Iñigo" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Traveling between the limits of shame and fascination.</summary>
	<body>The own Darren launches in the presentation of his new film the same warning I'll send everyone to read this text and is interested in "The Fountain": If you expect to see a new "Requiem for a dream" or another "Pi", best leaves the room.And which alerts is not traitorous. To view a movie of such spirit must go predisposed, prepared to open the mind without complexes. Pray even several sentences. Relaxation. Meditation. Whatever we want. But never prejudge.Without to obviate all valid clichés for these purposes, my opinion goes in several directions. They sometimes intersect, others collide. Some of them move away from the rest and not return. Many have heady power, other repulsive. Difficult task let someone be a slight idea, when one really not know what to say. Not bad? Not good? Maybe regular? Neither one nor the other. All that and nothing of the sort.Requires that we just let everything to one side and that we try to deepen the message, complex formally, that Aronofsky wants us to launch. Maybe the message it will have to start us. There will not be another option. The rest? When the end credits appear.The director of "pi" is a very high risk creating this film. He exhibits not only the hardness of the criticism, but that much of the public only sees travelling circus nonsense.Six years led him to complete the project. Six long years in which the world of the film and his own have advanced by leaps. There enough time for Brad Pitt (one of the actors in the initial Squad) long, so the stratospheric budget be reduced considerably, so reject projects such as "Batman Begins"? and so people are aburriera and mandara him to collect mushrooms. What was said. High risk. And more for a director with so little experience, although pampered by critics and covered by the public. Double-edged for the ego of Aronofsky.Ego that fires up close to the forbidden limits, creating a film so pretentious as lysergic, exciting, epic, mind-blowing and dangerously close to the exposure of the scariest ridiculous in the history of the cinema.Emotions confronted again. To see how the bald future of Hugh Jackman climbs the tree as a monkey if it were. To see how the mystical tone of the film seems to escape from the hands at times. See how the epic air seeks, is intended and magnified with face-to-face abuse of music (on the other hand, excellent) and impressive visual effects. To see how Rachel Weisz (currently director partner) moves from the precious to just right thing, like a slightly cardboard Hugh Jackman. Although sufficient for what we want to have more general that detailed.But also, confronted as I say, to see a few scenes so sweeping and so lifts. By suffer a love so strong, tragic and inevitable story so closely. By a very interesting issue as tricky for a nothing free in the background. And to make us forced participants and reflect. As the film of truth, good cinema.Thus, if you do not strive to understand the film, there is no film. You'll only see sequences of nonsense, well disguised as aesthetic, formal and musically, but nonsense out of some understanding to the end and all.Seeking think (Hugh Jackman) in each of their times, is what we constantly seek us throughout history. Eternal life, that damn "chalice" that heals and protects, seen that element from the religious (or cultural) perspective as appropriate.And most importantly. Looking for an escape, flee the so feared death. To heal the cancer of his beloved, but for own benefit also. But you can not escape from the inevitable, nor can find what does not exist. And if for some reason it existed? would it be what we believe? Do would be Xibalba continuum star reborn or the acceptance of the death and disappearance? Would be the eternal SAP tree which gives us life or give us death/life making us be inevitable part of our planet?While I think remains irascible and his madness is going more in the search for the drug stop cured his wife's terminal cancer (parallelism that can establish both its present and its future), she makes time which has accepted his death. Decision-making simply as a logical continuation, and all you want is her husband finished it what was left unfinished. To understand to move forward. It is the only way to survive and understand: accept death as an inseparable part of our being, as life itself.But think denies its reality, do not accept it. The pain is very strong, the frustration and the loss of his beloved invade his soul. It is blind. You must seek out blindly, through intuition and knowledge.Thus the roots of the tree remain upright (unforgettable scenes of the future in which are Hedgehog the beautiful tree). We can die in peace.Nevertheless, again faced sensations appear before me.It is true that is basically a message a both moralist, that what we know perfectly. But the packaging is very attractive if you let you carry. And they say that everything is invented in the film? least the way of telling it. And the film before us may be everything, but it is also exciting and innovative.If you try to take you seriously, do ignore monkeys climbing trees, several esperpénticas situations and excesses formal or esoteric, mystical, and forget that treatment of the soundtrack reminds of "the young of the water" Shyamalan by excessive abuse of the same to enlarge the epic nature of the film (pretentious?), you will surely get to understand the reason for its existenceyour search and its reflection. It will make you feel part of it. To the best up leaves you open-mouthed.You can guess even another fine resemblance. Formally, there is a light approach to the poetry of Tarkovsky (involuntary or voluntary?), obviously with a much simpler and less metaphysical background. But by far that Aronofsky will never be Tarkovsky. Or much less.Ultimately, and leaving aside ideas/associations of the film, en tus manos is describing the film as impressive, interesting or ridiculous. do awful, pretentious, shameful, beautiful, revealing? You have the last word.</body>
</review>
