<review author="Jesus Lens" title="El diablo viste de Prada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Delicious comedy made in Hollywood with all the attributes of genre cinema that takes advantage of overwhelming Yankee film machinery to provide an industrial product seamlessly, perfectly finished, wrapped and packaged.</summary>
	<body>Predictable. Wonderful and joyously predictable, "the Devil Wears Prada" is a delicious comedy film made in Hollywood with all the attributes of genre cinema that takes advantage of overwhelming Yankee film machinery to provide an industrial product seamlessly, perfectly finished, wrapped and packaged.Paradoxically, what I like most about this film is that, in theory, should get me: the Viewer always guess what will happen in the next sequence, and when it actually happens. glad. Because, like a blanket in winter or a fresh beer in the summer, there are things to be timeless, irremovable, indispensable. Like the script of a comedy, not by modern, is less classical.Let us in history: a young intellectual which drink wine and dine in warm bistros with other no less intellectual friends, goes to work as second Assistant a factotum of the publishing world of fashion, a universe that is not only alien, but laughable and, to some extent, negligible.But the ugly duckling, even with all the ballots to a labour barrigazo of órdago, begins to adapt to a universe that was not as stupid as it seemed. or Yes? We have the classic situations humorous that we have seen a thousand times, but so well resolved, with so much grace and freely bandied, that you can not spend the film with a permanent smile on the corner of the mouth. Scathing replicas, comical gaffes of leg, a little bit of love, unrequited love, beauty and style in spades. If mix class and the style of Audrey Hepburn in "breakfast at Tiffany? s" with life chaos of the other Hepburn, Katherine "The beast of my girl" or "Woman of the year", get that Anne Hathaway so special and attractive.And we have, of course, Meryl Streep, a genus in its own right. Streep, who was never what is said a beauty or a beauty, has been able to age better than all her companions generation. While Kathleen Turner drowns their arrobas in alcohol and the grandiose Michelle Pfeifer is missing in combat, Meryl has become a woman of arms taking, wasting class, power, force, vitriol and dressed in Prada, evil, hatred, cruelty, intelligence and, at a time, until your pinch of humanity.We have a film so simple and straightforward in its approach, as hilarious in its resolution. A movie that, without surprise with any display or tour de force story, is as effective as a tartazo full face, a slip in the middle of the street caused by a banana peel or a good slap in time. "The Devil Wears Prada" is a refreshing dive in the classic American comedy that, as we have been insisting can be enjoyed with the joy of a drink of water ice in a summer evening. Nice, tender, and happy.</body>
</review>
