<review author="Elena Suárez" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Within a so deplorable, the magic will be the vehicle of salvation to a fantastic world where truth has not only a road.</summary>
	<body>Not all Spanish films have to be equal, and films like this show. To begin, it is fantasy film good, with some excellent special effects and a strong argument. To continue, the structure of the script unfolds according to history and, therefore, we do not have the feeling that we are missing data or, on the contrary, we left over. Both the picture and sound are exquisítamente developed, nothing has been randomly and in addition, the work of actors follows the same quality film, highlighting the work of Sergi López. just as it did in "The Devil's backbone", Guillermo del Toro transports us to the cruel and dark world of the Spanish civil war (in this case, the post-war) to show us a bleak scenariowhere the powerful abused systematically on weaker indivuos. Within a so deplorable, the magic will be the vehicle of salvation to a fantastic world where truth has not only a path and is devoid of prejudices.And precisely, prejudice has sinned the director that the end result would have been much better if he had not insisted both on the issue of the cruel Falangist and we had more delighted with Ophelia and his incredible world. I believe that this is the biggest mistake of the movie it will mislead the public, which will be mostly manipulated by a promotional campaign quite away from the final product.Said Guillermo del Toro, at the press conference which took place a day after the presentation of his film in Madrid, that even today in Spain there was a deep divide in two and I would like to ask him if he does not consider this kind of argument to fuel even more wound and, therefore, the Division.Finally, warn of extreme violence in some scenes that made me withdraw the look of the screen, although I admit that I am rather sensitive and prefer not to get me to tolerate torture, albeit a few incredible special effects (unusual in national productions) product.</body>
</review>
