<review author="El mágico" title="Buenas noches y buena suerte" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Committed and controversial proposal</summary>
	<body>Second film directed by George Clooney (the first, "Confession of to dangerous mind" had a relative success of criticism but little reception from the audience), candidate to the Oscar in several areas, "Good night and good luck" is a committed and controversial proposal. If it is important, however, is a film concerning a particular moment of contemporary American history, happens in the 1950s and in it we will be witnesses of the anti-communist crusade led by Senator Joseph McCarthy with the House UN-American activities Committee. This Wisconsin Senator perpetrating an insane witch hunt that installs a heated in the United States debate, it is then when with the firm intention to communicate the facts and keep informed the public, Edward Murrow (impressive characterization of David Strathairn, strong candidate for his starring Oscar) and his journalistic of the CBS team, challenging the corporate and economic pressure to be able to examine the lies and scare tactics perpetrated by McCarthy during his hunt. The first thing to be said is that it is filmed in white and black (subtitling may be complicated to read, be warned!) and that "Good night and good luck" is armed with excellent material files and its narration has quite documentary basis, element that gives the tape a physiognomy that stands out it for its atmosphere and pace. The story is well armed, is agile, committed and respect the conventions of the time in which it occurred to strictly (the ads of the show are incredible), secondary are good (all correct, Clooney also nominated here) but what will remain to remind of this film are the lines which Murrow is going saying over the tape that they refer to the journalismthe role of politicians and their commitment as a citizen. Actor "Syriana" (also in billboard) now director top in Hollywood wanted to met this journalist and its value in a time where fight for the right of information is perceived as a chimera. "Good night and good luck" seems a self-centred and cut film at a time of American history, but it is the theme that is universal, the struggle of men committed to let the public know the truth of facts that cross his existence beyond the perceptible to the naked view.</body>
</review>
