<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="La increíble historia de Caperucita Roja" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The worst production of animation that I've seen this year, but no matter, because it compensates for everything with a witty script about charismatic characters and a devilish pace.</summary>
	<body>Often cited the lack of budget as one of the main reasons why the Spanish animation (I think especially in Dygra) isn't generally live up to expectations. According to this reasoning, lack of money would lead to a technical precariousness of the film that resulted ultimately in a poor film quality.These arguments are obviously false, but if you would need to prove it, "the incredible but true story of little Red Riding Hood" (Tyler) is a low blow to all those who defend. And it is that comparisons are so odious as sometimes necessary.From a technical point of view we are faced with the worst production of animation I've seen this year. The film, co-directed by Todd Edwards and Tony Leech, and directed by Cory Edwards is the impressive visual power light years to which Pixar has accustomed us. But no matter, because it compensates for everything with a witty script (a great tribute to the "Rashomon" by Kurosawa), charismatic characters and a devilish pace that not even the songs get break (although something free aren't anything annoying and, by the way, is very funny). I.e., quite the opposite of "El sueño de una noche de San Juan" (see Moonfleet criticism).The film immerses us in the life of the forest, where a mysterious character is killing the business of pastry base steal their recipe books. Little Red Riding Hood decides to save that of his grandmother taking him to it, but arriving at his house it is found to be locked in the closet, the Wolf in its place and a crazed woodcutter who bursts on stage. Arriving police in the forest, these characters will have to give their versions of what happened. Updates for that will be very different?It is obvious, reading the synopsis and seeing the film, that its implementation had been unthinkable not previously exist the success of "Shrek". But this not away merits to a humble, modest, risky and highly entertaining production that, despite all its limitations, becomes easily in one of the sympathetic released this year. Final rating: 6.5 out of 10.</body>
</review>
