<review author="Txapulin" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A very interesting point of departure, the description of a bleak future and a couple of impressively shot scenes is the best of the movie. The story and characters are difumunando by the way.</summary>
	<body>We have to thank Alfonso Cuarón have led one of the best Mexican films of recent years (and your MOM also (2001)) and the darkest installment of the movies of Harry Potter (Harry Potter and the prisoner of Azkaban (2003)). Now brings a futuristic story that part of a brutal idea: the youngest person on the planet, killed in a bar in Buenos Aires died in the year 2027. This means that for some reason unknown and never explained, 18 years ago that we are all sterile. At the same time, or perhaps a direct result of this unstoppable advent of the Apocalypse, the world is a mess. Do particularly in London, England, where the story unfolds, terrorism campa at your leisure, immigration control is total, and even encourages the cooperation of citizens with all kinds of advertisements, sects and fanatical groups emerging like mushrooms?, on the contrary, suicide is not only legal but that kits are marketed to remove life.This base plot and description of this terrible future is the best of the movie, but somehow it disappoints. Maybe because it gives rise to a history philosophically interesting, although they could have gotten more juice. But being a futuristic movie there are few details that tell us that we are twenty years later: there is no more and better technology, only a few adverts more and the description of a world that goes adrift. In reality we see today's world, with the current conflicts in London rather than in Baghdad. It is true that it makes sense, because that at birth the last child in the 2009 everything is paralyzed, but somehow my I was disappointed.The film has a couple of technical tricks that impress, although they could describe as vacuous visual display, I think that they are notable. One is the persecution with the car backwards pursued by motorists recorded from inside the car. Another is the impressive final battle made in one shot (or so seems it) with camera in hand. In these two moments, and some more, the director gets that we are immersed completely in the history as if we were one character.But despite the philosophical implications of the history and technical boast of some scenes, something from the film that did not finish I get. It is as if all the ingredients are ready to prepare a cake that I had to like much, but in the end it fails something and disappointed. The worst thing is that I can not even explain what it is. Perhaps history in Yes, that ends up being quite simple, or characters, that does not interest me too (certainly the most interesting two, and not going to disclose what they are, they end up being secondary and leave very little).In short, we are left with a very interesting starting point, the description of a bleak future and a couple of impressively shot scenes. The story and characters are difumunando by the way.</body>
</review>
