<review author="José A. Peig" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Toro is it mounted very well that a legion of unwary positively valued his film, but El Laberinto del Fauno is nothing more than a movie that he dreams of being a work of art.</summary>
	<body>In the exercise of film criticism there is a base difficulty: as regards the artistic value of a particular aesthetic translation, or an idea of the story, the story or concept to develop. That value depends on one hand on the sensitivity and the subjective scales of each individual and, on the other, of the consideration to be of the different theoretical currents concerning the philosophy of aesthetics and the narrative structure.If something should highlight the film by Guillermo del Toro, according to critics - quite favourable - which have been published in recent days, was by visual imagery and a lyrical sense of charming with sinister overtones. However, for a server, the only scene from the film with its own entity which is represented in the frame that opens the comment today, grisly oneiric Moor starring a creature that even in my worst nightmares I could even guess, eyes in the hands that make prey to a fairy of metal are devoured by the creature with a remarkable burden of bad milk and sense of the grotesque. Apart from this passage, which I explain - depending on ways to assess an aesthetic product - what kind of visual imagery manifests itself in labyrinth, the labyrinth, the grim aesthetic of an enchanted forest or metal amantis. In particular, in that stratum of the film, creativity is null. To explain me it.Del Toro in the entirety, you offer us a story - quite trite - about violence and the tribulations of the Spanish post-war, supported within a fantasy child, wrapped up on the girl child protagonist, which aims to combat the misfortune by resorting to the magic of his fantasy. Therefore, we have a story that combines fantasy and reality. The conclusion is quite illustrative of the intention of its author; in the tragic denouement, the last moments of the agony originating the last fantasy that become heroin to his protagonist. But that just prior to the last breath. In the end only death in the stark reality.I.e., del Toro is it mounted very well that a legion of unwary positively valued his film with formulas of the type "is a wonderful sinister fairy tale that beats from the underworld of a sinister reality" and the like that you can read these days. Indeed, shows us what an underworld inhabited by fantastic creatures that exist only in the imagination, but the problem is the lack of a connection between the fantastic facts and the facts, and the result is a disjointed film in this clear mixture even for the more profane. On the one hand tells us a story about the fantasies of a girl and on the other a story violent in the social and political reality of that historic moment. Lacks it a structure that articulates this whole. It was the only way to achieve an aesthetic and narrativamente laudable product (singular, worthwhile, as you prefer), that each of the two stories, separately, contribute little or nothing. Only at the end, when the girl dies in reality and was proclaimed in the fantasy heroine, is some light in this regard, despite the paleness of the set.Worst of all is the abuse of clichés and commonplaces: the fascist military (character, my God what grotesque), the pregnant woman and victim, revolutionaries hiding in the forest, the traitor. The realization of this rural drama in the post-war period, both script and visual representation plays with bases and elements too old; Let's be honest, there is no difference between the implementation of del Toro and which would give any movie or series Spanish that you address the same subject matter: there is a single frame or sequence of the Assembly to emerge no genuine meaning to show that there is an author behind the camera. And that is what find me unforgivable: "El laberinto del fauno" is intended to be a film original, lyrical and I do not know what more, and all you have is conventionalism and clichés insubstantial.The icing puts her free use of violence and sadism: what role exerts the blood and the detailed (exaggerated) description of acts of violence in the overall hue of the history? Apart from being of dubious taste, it is unnecessary: it is one thing to show violence in a sad, raw and violent history and other morbid and cheap exhibitionism. What where is the difference?. Compare with Sam Peckinpah and the matter will become quite clear.In the end, they had told me that this film was a work of art, but it is nothing more than a movie that he dreams of being a work of art.</body>
</review>
