<review author="José A. Peig" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do often gives the impression of not going beyond a visual spectacle, which comes to be a plagiarism of the so-called style - in many sequences-? hiper-realista? executed by Spielberg.</summary>
	<body>When the letters of the conclusion are and you you have to swallow so many images on characters in chaotic circumstances created by human violence in the near future - and eerily similar to the immediate present - could not fit another way than the instinct of praise addressed to this filmmaker named Alfonso Cuarón, who has already demonstrated a striking style visual in their great contribution to the saga of Harry Potter.Si started out thereall goes well. We have an overwhelming visual recreation of an apocalyptic world that justifies himself and becomes credible almost from the first minutes of the narration without offering an explanatory foreword, on the basis of a table in which the protagonist is situated in the Centre of a group of people referred to in the television the news concerning the death of the youngest of the humanclosing a cycle and increase the collective depression of a world trapped in his absence of expectations for posterity.That same character will die before the new seed, opening the way to hope, and comes to the storyline that leads us along the journey, used effectively, and denotes the good work in the structure by the director and his writers. Without a doubt, the aesthetic embodiment, the creation of an apocalyptic atmosphere, and the varied assortment of human profiles that guarantee a minimum poetic breath to a technically impeccable product, but that too often gives the impression not to go beyond a visual spectacle, which comes to be a plagiarism of the style called "hiper-realista" executed by Spielberg with all kinds of means and tricks of artillery in "Saving private Ryan" - in many sequences.The strength at the visual level and honesty in the development of the idea are notable, certainly, but at the end is an aftertaste to emptiness, because as indicated above: there is something else in this film other than an overwhelming staging?. In the stratum of the characters and the relationships between them, as already has been mentioned before, there is variety in the type of characters but the fact is that the story delves not none of them nor ends curdling the appropriate epic and dramatic tone in any of the situations developed (peca to omit the explanation of some facts and motivations)(for example, the viewer never gets to know the meaning of "human project," the ultimate goal of the adventure). It would seem that the representation of the different profiles is credible and works as idea of hitch a narrative choral on chaos lived in a community who are fighting for the survival of civilization or the ideal individuals, but the gaze of Cuarón on this set is too warm, not stressed enough the beat that whole dramatic human in a story about groups human being discussed between the fightthe inevitable defeat in appearance and the hope represented by elegiac tone and its symbolic, the cries of the baby for a few moments, manages to silence screams and bombs which is possibly the most substantial scene.Conclusion, if "Children of men" has failed to be a great movie is by the coldness and the warmth with which deals with the human drama of Fund, despite its excellent virtues in the technical realization.</body>
</review>
