<review author="Berto" title="Corrupción en Miami" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie quite good, without reaching the level of their previous masterpieces, but which ultimately is a new film by Michael Mann, not a film adaptation of the mythical series Miami Vice.</summary>
	<body>Michael Mann was producer and creator of the mythical series created in 1984 and was a success throughout the world, and since his intention was to bring an adaptation of that series to the big screen. It is now in 2006 in which embarks on this risky adaptation, that if, with many works to his back that turned the project into something more than a simple adaptation to earn money, because Mann is notable above all for its forms and his sobriety to tell great stories.For the choice of the protagonists has vibrant Jamie Foxx, star that is proving to be a real off-road in the field of performance and grows as it is premiering films, and Collin Farrell, actor that although it promises enough, still has not had a role that enshrined it in the same way as teammate in this production. That if these characters share with the original only his name, because from the locker room, way to act and others does not remember anything to the popular series.Is at this point where you can see the great failure, or success of the film according to tastes of the Viewer, because the film Miami Vice only relates to the series the name both itself and its protagonists? If had changed you the name well could have passed for a 100% movie style Michael Mann, Collateral plan or Heat and not to remind us at all to the series from which drinks (in theory) their sources.The visual style of the Michael Mann permeates the entire film is impeccable. Well shot action scenes and an argument quite careful, as already demonstrated in the above Heat and Collateral, although if it is placed is a script too focused on what he says and not the action, thing which at times makes a little heavy film, especially if we are expecting a style more than action plan shootings and persecution as passed on the series.As for the two actors to my I liked quite in their roles of Sonny Crockett and Ricardo Tubbs, although the less convinced me was Collin Farrell, more than anything by the elongated shadow of Don Johnson, although comparisons apart is not bad for all the footage. As revelation of the film highlight John Ortiz, right-hand man of the bad very bad Luis Tosar, which seems totally lost throughout the film. Unconvincing seems Li Gong as wife of Luis Tosar, seems both exoticism more than enough and they could have sought a Latin fixed had convinced a lot more, besides the fact that the couple Farrell-Gong is totally artificial and I find no justification in the plot, think that she is it they could have skipped completely.Ultimately, movie quite good, without reaching the level of their previous masterpieces, Collateral and Heat, but which ultimately is a new film by Michael Mann, not a film adaptation of the mythical ochentera series Miami Vice.</body>
</review>
