<review author="Ana" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie lasts two hours and a half but there is no time to take breath. Note the mastery of Scorsese and love for cinema.</summary>
	<body>The duality of the character told in two parallel lives. Two guys out of the Police Academy. One becomes police but is actually an infiltration of the Irish mafia. The other they close the doors to be police unless they accept impersonate gangster to inform them about Frank Costello (Jack Nicholson), but do not offer any support and for being a very secret situation even kept a file on him. It is a complicated plot. As it can be inferred that the two stories together in a point: the girl. Well, that is the only thing predictable. The movie lasts two hours and a half but there is no time to take breath.The film is never boring and takes an abrupt rhythm. The scenes are cut without a breath of dead air. But with Supreme ability to show what is necessary so that the history is understood, and sits. Play much with the form without losing balance. The plot is quite complicated and there are many characters, but does not lose you. That if there is to be careful.The film is violent. Very violent, but not too much. Although I accept that I have weakness by the mafia. And even if I dislike it exaggerated violence, when it comes to organized crime it is different. Especially because it's more about the character, the desperate to survive. When it makes perfect sense crash a beer mug someone on the head or grab fist, because it is violence born of correct an injustice that though this good is not the nature human. The first time that Frank Costello meets the character of Matt Damon is going to be his protégé covert has about 10 years; and Frank tells him: "At your age told us that you can become thief or police." "What I am saying is this, when you point with a loaded revolver, what difference is there?"Infiltrators is not a politically correct film, it is just the opposite. Probably it is not offending any group of people. But if you intend to show all the faces of corruption could not be otherwise. It is so authentic and proper as the soundtrack of anglicized with Irish bagpipes.The character of Leonardo DiCaprio is in a truly desperate situation. And it shows but his hands never tremble. The police doesn't offer any guarantee and it is obvious that at any time they could gut. You don't have anyone and she cannot sleep. DiCaprio embodies it with subtlety. Is the height, and this along with Jack Nicholson suit grey Leopard tie, content but obsessive.In a moment, but only a moment, this film came to remember me Cidade de Deus (city of God), which is the best movie I've seen in recent times. You can not say it is Goodfellas, but it is very good. Note the mastery of Scorsese and love for cinema.</body>
</review>
