<review author="Caty" title="Una historia violenta" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>film thematically ambitious and with sufficient strength to avoid simplistic answers</summary>
	<body>Tom is a quiet man who leads a peaceful life with his wife and their two children in a small town in the interior of the United States. Owner of a small coffee, account with the affection of residents and customers. One evening, while next time close, two strangers enter the establishment and armed, intimidate those who there is encuentran.pero before that they can fulfil their threats are attacked and killed by own Tom, who immediately becomes a hero both in your community and across the nation. is then when a face disfigured man comes to town andclaiming to know the protagonist, he tells his wife if he does not seem strange the alacrity and never acting as clean and as accurate of a man that has not killed a fly.Inspired by a novel by John Wagner and Vince Locke, the screenplay by Josh Olson explores inquiries about the "mysterious" past Tom directly, bluntly, avoiding creating a cheap suspicion through empty secrets. Instead, the story chooses to surprise the viewer simply by the own evolution of the events, which often assume one faster rate which you might expect from a film of the genre: when, for example, the Ed Harris character appears in scene, the audience automatically prepares for a tense confrontation that is certainly going to happen later, but such a first contact between the two characters making develops in a way quite different from that we might come to think. Directed by veteran David Cronenberg, "A violent story" has no intention of presenting as a revenge tape, its goal is more ambitious, that it tries to hook the viewer not to through the acción(aunque_esta_esté_a_veces_presente_en_la_trama), but the curiosity, because in the end who is Tom Stall? What are the relationships between all the threatening figures, from one moment to another, appearing in his life? He is lying or suffers amnesia? As we do not know the answers to these questions (in the same way that the Tom family) have no possibility of judging what the he did or left done years ago, but that we must form our opinion only on what we know at present.And this, precisely, is the main theme of the film, which makes it a very interesting film: are what defines who we, our actions in the past or our attitudes in the present? When you start the slide show, Tom already 20 years ago that they live in the community and is admired by everyone because of his sympathy and his bondad.en that his youth really has a part as oscura.¿Esto changes our perception about his character, or those two decades left suddenly for? Our sins are prescribed, and if so, after how long?Questions presented by Cronenberg arrive more than: do after how long a lie lived consistently turns in reality? In the end, if Tom was actually a different person, it is undeniable that the protagonist has finished happening almost as long as Tom to as Joey (the name that some say that it is true in the film). In addition, the filmmaker shows an immense interest in discussing the violent nature of the human being, manifested in greater or lesser degree in different characters: does someone with a really violent temper can change, or we are prisoners of what we were, although we strive desperately to suppress our instincts more low?Throughout the film, some of these inquiries are answered by Cronenberg, while others are left in abeyance. Anyway, it is fascinating to note as the director shows consisting of their questions about human nature, his filmography is often starring individuals fighting against themselves, against their interiores(en_algunos_casos_hasta_literalmente,_como_en_"La_Mosca") monsters. Also highlight as the photography of Peter Suschitzky illustrate this constant battle between man and his (in) aware or its past, as some characters always seem to be in the shade, semi-hidden.As Tom as an essentially ambiguous man, Viggo Mortensen offers a focused and full of subtleties interpretation: one of their decisions more weird is, for example, the adopted a tone of voice always low, highlighting the apparent calm of the character. In the same way, his serene gaze indicates a patient position in relation to the problems which faced and, occasionally, their eyes become cold and rabid, where we realize that it would probably not be very wise to provoke it.In a mano a mano with Viggo, we have Maria Bello, who transforms into a woman real and palpable, also expressing this trend in its internal conflicts when trying to understand what is happening around your marido(es_curiosa_su_reacción_ael_dar_se_cuenta_que_realmente_Tom_Stall_es_posible_que_sea_una_identidad_falsa,_y_que_su_apellido_y_el_de_sus_hijos_es_una_mera_invención). Despite all its virtues, the film has its specific setbacks, as the overly idealized way that David Cronenberg portrays the Stall family during the first act of the story. Looking for highlight the bankruptcy of an "ideal" family harmony will suffer, the filmmaker force this situation, reaching the point of including a scene in which father, mother and son rise early in the morning just to calm the infant daughter, who had a nightmare.Anyway, "a history of violence" is a thematically ambitious film and shows have sufficient strength to allow the viewer out of the film without being completely sure of the way in which ends all, and this, perhaps one of the greatest virtues of the film; avoid forcing replies where these undoubtedly sounding artificial and simplistic.</body>
</review>
