<review author="Caruco" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>El laberinto del fauno is the masterpiece of Guillermo del Toro. A lesson in wisdom of storytelling in film; the quintessence of the imagination; and a masterful performances.</summary>
	<body>It must be said already. El laberinto del fauno is the masterpiece of Guillermo del Toro. And who subscribes to this recognizes that mortally became bored with the Devil's backbone, or disappointed with Hellboy. So, Cronos to part, the bar wasn't too high, still and admitting that the Mexican director has this so-called own universe and a very special touch.Had their possibilities this story, hybrid between horror and poetry; and the harsh environment of the reality, that of 1,944 post-war Spain, and the internal fantasy world of Ophelia, the young protagonist. Especially after his triumphant passage through the last Cannes film festival where, unfortunately, did not obtain any prize. So what? Instead they got a standing ovation from the audience of. more than 20 minutes!And expectations are met. or rather, unfulfilled for the better. Because, ladies and gentlemen, in agreement that it would be best that anyone interested in seeing the movie her discover if same, but is that we we have: a lesson in wisdom of storytelling in film; the quintessence of the imagination; and a masterful interpretations, especially in this brutal captain who plays an incomensurable Sergi López, the face of evil incarnate in fascism; but it is also the girl (Ivana Baquero), doctor (Alex Angulo) or a housewife keys helps to rebel militias (Maribel Verdú); a good handful, not just two or three, sinó ten, fifteen, twenty, of scenes and absolutely extraordinary moments; and a mounting and pace that no lapses in no time.Anyone who loves the fantasy genre, and cinema, faces, now, already, a work which will be of reference, with numerous references to classic tales, especially to "Alice's adventures in Wonderland". It does take advantage of minutia, archetypes, and stories that seemed mil views, worn. And yet the bull so he reinvents.A story Baroque, sinister and dark as it has defined it its author, who also stresses, with acuity, yours is a fable for disobedience within a social framework in conflict and repression. In estecaso, within the framework of a divided and lost, Spain with an oppressive power and blunt contro anyone who will skip the rules. In the laberinto del fauno is a 13-year-old girl who runs away from the sordid reality that surrounds. Orphan of father, mother (Ariadna Gil) forced a marriage commitment with a sadistic and vain character, Captain Vidal, who is only interested in his son expect the wife, and that no doubt it will be male. Basically a poor man who only knows killing, or a bitter make life impossible for those who surround him, "Vamos Serrano is a very worthy of die form!", yells at one of his officers when they persecute the maquis hidden in the forest.For example, one of the scraps of the genius of del Toro is located in the same presentation of Vidal's character. Shown with mild, but accurate strokes: looking at a broken clock (a reminder of the obsessions inherited by his father) to complain about the inpuntualidad to get his wife; and shortly after the hand of bad ways Ophelia by a slight misunderstanding of it.And this rural and isolated framework conducive to the evasion of Ophelia, the only is form of comfort it and maintain the purity of his innocence. For this reason, in an environment as black, Ophelia dreams with bugs, pale men with eyes on his hands, with giant toads, mandrágoras chillan, fauns aspect unattractive or hadas-insecto. Wondering the viewer what to be real in all this.Without disclosing anything, the answer given by the film itself. Fantasy, imagination poetry is, of course, first and foremost those who know to look.</body>
</review>
