<review author="José Córdoba" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An excellent, dramatic but fun, human, film shot and written with intelligence, demonstrating, once again, that the film does not require large budgets or was stories to reach the people.</summary>
	<body>Here we have the road movie of the year. With other genres like horror, comedy, road movies appear as one because, while they can frame normally in one of the genres masters, by calling them somehow, Yes is true that structure, for purposes, all calls road movies share characteristics. Little miss sunshine represents is an exemplary film in the genre. We have thus family protagonist, a set of losers (losers) so typical of American cinema: the father who has designed a methodology on how to reach success in nine steps and constantly awaiting a phone call confirming that his book will be published, the little girl obsessed with beauty contests plump, involving Grampathe depressed guy with trends suicide, teenage son constantly reads to Nietzche and takes nine months with a vote of silence and, finally, the mother, the character who tries to put a point of sanity in the matter. The trigger for the history is a child beauty pageant for which the small Olive has been chosen after a small carambola. As the economy is not buoyant, they decide to take all, although with reluctance, his filthy van and go two States of the United States of the America's deep South, before the girl get her dream of participating. As in all road movie, the fate is not important, but the journey itself same. The movie, which could be described with doses of comedy drama, revolves around the frustrations by not achieving success. The father is a man obsessed with being a winner, striving in that his method is foolproof, stubborn in refusing to acknowledge that he is a loser. This behavior affects all those who surround him, starting with their children, the teenager who hates his family of losers and wants to become a fighter pilot and the daughter who lives obsessed with beauty contests. The mother and grandfather opposed assume his stopover in society, although they have placed hopes on the girl child, in, at least she did make a triumphant. Meanwhile, the uncle, brilliantly played by Steve Carell, has taken the opposite step, it has gone from being a winner to be a loser. Despite the dramatic dyes the film is punctuated by a multitude of fun and hilarious, moments like this dilapidated van that ends up being one character from the movie or the child beauty pageant. The script is a success, the characters, despite their bizarre point, they seem close, understandable, human. Also presents a very suitable pace alternating comedy and drama, introducing innovative elements so that the fabric does not decay. The actors are very well, it shows that they have a good starting material and know get juice. From Greg Kinnear, bright as a father obsessed with the triumph, until Alan Arkin, a real robaplanos as the grandfather involving and addicted to porn. The address is also effective, without abusing the rapid Assembly and making great use of the panoramic format, a risky decision, with which the film has been shot. Get levels really very interesting, helped by excellent photography. The soundtrack is also very encouraging, many of their songs being instrumental arrangements of popular songs that add a fun and crazy point. In short, it's an excellent, dramatic but fun, human, film shot and written with intelligence, demonstrating, once again, that the film not required huge budgets or was stories to reach the people. Incidentally, for anti people studies, anti American cinema, this film winning several awards of independent cinema and the San Sebastian Festival audience award, it has been produced by a major Studio: 20th Century Fox, but it has been through a subsidiary Fox Searchlight.</body>
</review>
