<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The trailer that so cool for girls entering the bark of a tree, the Faun, a man with eyes in the hand, etc, is not this movie? Yes, if it is, but that again we have deceived, insofar as this is not necessary for the development of the film...</summary>
	<body>Guillermo del Toro is like a box of chocolates without pork chop which is which. You can put the hand randomly and get you one of liquor, and the next time it is truffle. If you eat everything no problem, because all his movies you like. If you are more tiquismiquis, perhaps not you like both. To me personally, as daisies, "this Yes, this not".The film is a captain fascist in the beginning of the Spanish post-war. Its role is the exterminate the pockets of resistance remaining at that time, basically known as makis, hiding in the mountains. In these, it reaches the post his new wife, who has a daughter preteen, pregnant (woman, than you perdeis). And the thing takes place between see Captain methods to exterminate the makis and things that will happen to the girl with a Faun and a few more magical beings.Let's see, this has its Crumb. The film is the usual wars, in which there is a side superhipermalo (captained by fucking son of the captain) and a faction fighting for Justice and freedom for the oppressed. Go, as always. If add you to this that it is in Spain, then more of the usual. Then, so this looks not a Spanish post-war film, appears a girl who meets a Faun. The thing however, paint if the magical item not lasted a quarter of an hour, and the rest is dramón father. Then, the trailer such as cool for girls entering the bark of a tree, the Faun, a man with eyes in the hand, etc, is not this movie? Yes, if it is, but that again we have deceived, insofar as this is not necessary for the development of the film. Moreover, it could remove and nobody had heard. The film is a drama about the Spanish post-war and ball point. Very well done, but a tremendous and sometimes unpleasant dramón. In addition, action is well short.In short, that I feel cheated. It is a film about a timely moment in the history of Spain, flavored with a magical fantasy. But not a fantasy set in the point made. I thought a tremendous dramón, which is very well developed, but not liked too. Expect me another very different thing and that pisses me off a lot. Although I have to say that I was very thrilled and I cried when well wet magdalena in the coffee with milk in the morning.</body>
</review>
