<review author="JohnTrent" title="Serpientes en el avión" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Besides first and foremost being a form of entertainment that doesn't fool anyone if same, that it keeps you glued to your seat for more than 90 minutes and that, in their tenders, offers a correct show.</summary>
	<body>Development that happened "Snakes on a plane" was really funny and interesting. Of echo, has been one of the cheaper advertising campaigns of recent times, given that the same fans on the Internet (and even those not were not fans, i.e., those who criticized her and laughed her as project) began to create unthinkable expectations, initially, for a film like the before us.At first, its makers thought holder her "Flight 121". Moreover, Samuel L Jackson, the celebrated hero of the film, the script get you no title yet, just with a phrase that summed up what was the movie, i.e. snakes on the plane. Since they knew that the actor had decided to star in that film just for what snakes on the plane, without having read the script, began circulating on the Internet numerous jokes at the expense of that phrase and how ridiculous the show in images which could be. Both was thus the joke step to be taken seriously, and such was the expectation that I wake up at the expense of, the film term graduating that same way, "Snakes on a plane".The rest were a lot of false traileres, rumors, speculation about what might happen in the movie and the character of Samuel L Jackson. This last happened the funny thing and that, moreover, became a new example for Hollywood in the advertising field had never before been given which had occurred without lifting a single finger to them. The case was that, at some "geek" began to run the rumor that Jackson, in a moment of the film, released a phrase that came to be "I want to these whores snakes out of my fucking plane", similar it so to the mythical mafioso which I interpret in "Pulp fiction". The rumor became so popular in a short time that those responsible for the tape gave the go-ahead to add this sentence in the movie Seria this? which invented the great phrase.The issue not just here. Fans online, increasingly numerous, seen the case I was doing through the pages web, blogs and forums, decided to ask more gore, more humor, more sex and, in general, a film that could be described as R in United States, and not the initial PG-13 had its makers intended. We are going to be a movie almost suitable for all audiences and that it could have easily been in family, I finish making it show with a bit of gore, some swearing, sex and a tone that, occasionally, clears the absurd pure and comedy, and can be seen only by adults, or in any case minor accompanied by one.The great momentoTodo this happened before, during and up to the end of the filming. Thus, their leaders began to rub their hands before the, very likely, high sum of money which would be at the box office "Snakes on a plane". The film had gone from being a serie B more unpretentious spend a few weeks at the box office without too much stress and pretend distracted awhile who accept the invention, one of the event movie of the summer in United States, a tough competitor for the announced "blockbuster" and which, they said, could become one of the films over the blockbuster of the season, apart from surprise to many and create even more fans.But, as many times the early expectations can create a negative effect in certain films, "Snakes on a plane" was released with some indifference, far from the figures expected those responsible (and many people in the industry, that was interested in the promotion that had been launched quite a few producers). I finish raising more than 30 million dollars, i.e. precisely the millions who hoped that he only joined in its first weekend (during this period income half of that figure, to then descend abruptly.) (Come on, almost 50% of the total proceeds corresponds to the first three days).The problem was caused by excess air of greatness that came to him those responsible suddenly to see such acceptance on the Internet. In fact, were not few those who warned that with the support of the fans on the net, the film could enter no more than 10 million dollars, while the rest would depend on how to sell the film to "non-geeks", or people who did not know anything of it by other means other than traileres or ads on TV ordirectly, were not initially interested by a film as similar title.Finally the film drag to the cinema many fans (I understand that the first few days, there were even people disguised as Samel L Jackson in "Pulp fiction", including afro wig) to then be forgotten quickly, because it did not interest many other people apart from those who had already seen.Arriving at our screens, "Snakes on a plane" has wanted to be sold, again incorrectly, announcing her everywhere as the introduction of Elsa Pataki in American cinema, when in reality the dubious actress appears only a few minutes and its role does not have much relevance.As it was expected, "Snakes on the plane" did not succeed nor here, although proportionally it has had to make do with more mediocre numbers in United States, being relegated almost to oblivion as of today.But the film?So what you want to tell you?. Or both or neither. "Snakes on a plane" part first and foremost to be a form of entertainment that doesn't fool anyone if same, that it keeps you glued to your seat for more than 90 minutes and that, in their tenders, offers a correct show. Come on, that it is not more than a B series that well would premiere in the club video if it weren't for having Samuel L. Jackson's character and the previous expectation that woke up on the Internet. And has something wrong with this? Therefore at least for which this writes, not.But of course, when a film "which is what it is" and is not intended to more than entertain as a "monster movie" cheap and absurdly hilarious to see and forget, becomes one of the films which most expected this season, many are those who finally left disappointed and even insult to "how bad is the film". Would have happened of not having given so much hype to the invention? Let me it dude.The film opens with a totally festive and colorful, air far from what could be a film of the horror genre. In a matter of minutes we have submitted to villains, then act the main and secondary characters (known soon see them who will live and who died on the plane) and, suddenly, the snakes begin to seize the plane. Come on, accept that what we propose here (that if not has done it already to come to see her, not is making in the room) it is easy to find, in principle, a worthy pastime and where it can be, to some extent, what you waiting (and I say "to some extent" because not expect wild scenes of violence)(, nor to Samuel L Jackson handing out insults the snakes every two seconds, but the typical "accessible" gore of the commercial Hollywood and a single sentence, which already detail to the principle, with which Jackson establishes "colegueo" biased audience, and this phrase tells almost at the end).Later, and after the fun first attack of snakes, the film has some (unexpectedly) dramatic moments, most of what should be. This, added to a more serious volume than expected in a whole, suggest that either the screenwriter, Sebastian Gutierrez, has not quite caught the tone to the story either confusion has come with its director, David r. Ellis who, that if at any time it takes action with pulse, a correct and tension, despite the impersonality of his (apparent) address(, as entertaining "Collateral" and "Final destination, 2", his previous works after the cameras were already easy to recognize in "Snakes on a plane" details) or absurdity which may be the script, manages to create an interest in what happens in pro of the divertimento of the hearings, I repeat again, willing to do so (because not everyone entering the game to this film), by simple as it may seem. Prejudice against serie B? (Do high expectations for what I comment in the first paragraphs?).In the end, "Snakes on a plane" turns out to be an entertainment which is fast and is forgotten shortly thereafter. Is not, for nothing, a jewel of serie B as they have tried to say by many means (including large part of criticism in United States, not to say the audience, which the IMDB the brought an average 7.5), even is the film festival and "so cumbersome is good" that many others were telling to see, but rather a series with special effects (b) which is not far from other "monster movies" recent "Anaconda" type, but with more grace and rhythm, as well as better finish. A film whose previous comments have eaten and have continued to be release in all its freshness for enjoyment of a few fans to serie B with bugs or, without going any further, to the divertimenti without complexes.If something happened to the story "Snakes on a plane" it will be, as it was the case with "The Blair Witch Project" by its interesting advertising campaign. The difference is that, while the revelation that meant "The Blair Witch Project" achieved at the box office success spectacular and outside any claim of its leaders, as well as finish remain one of the best horror films of the 1990s (despite who gets upset), film starring Samuel L. Jackson (correct and charismatic)(, as almost always) has failed these purposes, on the other hand absurd given the basis on which sustains and own artistic results.</body>
</review>
