<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Vete de mi" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Poorly topped script that opens paths not closed, features characters that do not contribute anything and let in the absolute lack of definition to others.</summary>
	<body>It lacked references about this movie but its roster of actors and the fact of being an almost novel director (must support those who start) I decided to go to see her. "Without being a major error, I have to admit that it wasn't a satisfying experience."Does "Vete de MI", directed by Víctor García León tells the following story (extracted from the press kit): Santiago (Juan Diego) has never been protagonist of nothing? or from theatre, or cinema? not even for their own lives. But Santiago never thought that it would accommodate his slob son William (Juan Diego Botto) for a few days at home both change their lives? As was to be expected, the main dish of the function are the interpretations. Juan Diego offers a recital of the reasons why is considered one of the great actors of our country and winner, for this role, the San Sebastian Festival silver shell. At his side, Juan Diego Botto, without being bad, does not offer anything special because of a little and poorly defined character. In general, the rest of the actors gives the stature, especially Cristina Plazas by its naturalness and its serene beauty that become, for me, the discovery of the film.Everything else seems failed because of a poorly topped script that opens paths that not closes, features characters that do not contribute anything and that it leaves on the absolute lack of definition to others that we fail to know his motivations for doing what they do. For example, the character of Rosa María Sardá adds nothing to the story.It is very difficult to overcome the burden of a hyphen as well and the director, co-author of the screenplay with Jonás Trueba, fails. His style is sober and intends to not draw attention but that, with a bad script, as do the Hara-Kiri before the public. Nevertheless, I would like to believe that there are grounds for hope: the direction of actors is good, there are situations that could give lot of well developed game and also, there is a clear desire to offer an adult film for mature audiences.That Yes, while we look for triumph through boring low-budget tapes and no hook, as it is the case, it seems to me difficult away the crisis that permanently, seem threatening to our cinema.</body>
</review>
