<review author="Jesus Lens" title="La dalia negra" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a film noir in itself. It is a film that attempts to recreate the atmosphere of classic cinema, one that is cold and distant.</summary>
	<body>When it was announced that Brian de Palma would take charge of the film adaptation of "The Black Dahlia", one of the first novels of James dog wild Ellroy, a true regustillo toured me back. A regustillo not without concern, this is step. De Palma is one of these managers with their own personality, capable of the best. and the worst.As the cast was forming, interest was growing; exponentially when it announced the incorporation into the project of the unpayable, oscarizada, magnificent and suggestive Hillary Swank. And reached Venice. And the movie premiered. And I set out as a wolf to read what felt the Carlos Boyero &amp; Co. Y. oh disappointment! "The Black Dahlia" was much ado about nothing. Much of the continent and little content. Too much façade for so little Foundation.And from then on, all were bad vibes about the dahlia. NOVELPOL - the international Cibernético-castellana of the black gender - friends who attended the movie premiere were quite critical and only in a Blog I found some positive reference to the film.For this reason, when Sacai and I we planted Friday in the Neptune, my mood was contradictory. Prepared for the worst, even expected a positive surprise. And the thing started well. Palm quickly it contextualizes that Los Angeles violent and bullanguera, racist, active, unstoppable and exciting that Ellroy so well told us in his novels. In the same way, the main characters are well defined in the first round: two cops, long and ex-boxeadores, climbing on the bandwagon of success media to Ascend, two by two, the steps of the police ranks.But doubt arises me. If all those who have devoured the Ellroy novels quickly we are in situation with regard to these shady and contradictory, obsessive and obsessed characters by the ghosts of the past, violent, justicieros, drug addicts, ambitious, noble and so that the writer insufflated hectic and accelerated life to its unforgettable creatures, what happens with the spectators that come to the film Virgin of the ellroyano universe?In other words, do you get Palm that the movie characters are as interesting as the literary? Sincerely and lack of contrasting opinions, I think that not. The fact to see one of the Portas take bencedrina or lose the papers a couple of times during the footage, not close you to existential hell in which lives the characters in Ellroy. Honestly, during the screening of "The Black Dahlia", never got the emotional identification makes me hate, love, admire and despise, at the same time and at the same time, fascinating creatures from one of the best American writers of the time.I admit that the ambiance, the sets, costumes and music are very well made. History is solvent, is well told, some De Palma camera moves are spectacular, there are beautifully resolved sequences (the fights of boxing and the trap to the protagonist, for example) and I did not bored during the slide. Cierto.Pero in no time I was thrilled the film. Not at all. What I liked most was the recreation of Elisabeth Short, black and white; its tests for the film and, later, sequences of the pornographic film that had been shot. But I didn't feel the tension which should supposedly be among the protagonists. Neither the Johansson nor the Swank (and that tell me, please!) passed the sexual impulse of the great actresses of the American film noir.The problem of "The Black Dahlia" is that it is not film noir in itself. It is a film that attempts to recreate the atmosphere of the classic film that is cold and distant, without the heat of the great films of the genre and, since then, without reaching the dizzying chasms that Ellroy novels reading can cause in its staunchest readers.I insist on be a fan of the novelist can weigh as a slab when watching the film one of his major novels and therefore on this occasion and more than ever, I would like to know the opinion of who, without knowing anything of Ellroy, they went to see "The Black Dahlia" as one movie. So, friends. you have the floor.</body>
</review>
