<review author="Caruco" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Chronicle of?Children of men? It is not only a part of war. It is also a reflection of what us it frightens today same.</summary>
	<body>Before a film science fiction or futuristic, brought us images of flying cars, avant-garde buildings and people dressed in very tight and rare costumes. But now no longer.The future us embodies the Mexican Alfonso Cuaron, adapting a novel by P.D. James, is very close, too recognizable on any of the images of a newscast.Engulfed by the excellent photography, dark, filthy, but careful, Emmanuel Lubezki, what we see they are cities affected by social unrest, urban guerillas, terrorism, masses of immigrants that exposed persecuted, bars in which at least thought instantly explodes a bomb, Governments which fall into fascism and "State of siege", tanks and the army taking to the streets in their attempt to keep order. And people not already wears so rare form. Is the same as us.In this future that draws Cuarón, 2027, humanity already not can procreate. Women have become infertile. There are no children of men, and when he dies the last being live on the planet, will not be anyone else of our species.Committed to his own revelation, disorder and chaos reigns in the world. The youngest person on the planet, the Brazilian Diego Ricardo, just kill himself overwhelmed by the popularity. Women and men grieve desconsoládamente. But a very bleak picture also needs an outbreak of hope, and the germ of this lies within the belly of a "fugi", black, illegal immigrant. A young pregnant called Kee (Claire-Hope Ashitey).His involuntary guardian angel will be a disappointed civil servant, Theodore Faron (Clive Owen), with an activist past in favour of human rights. He should lead her up the small stronghold, perhaps only an illusion, that can host and use to Kee and his seed with humanitarian and non-partisan objectives. They must be before crossing places hit by government surveillance, by the struggles of powers within the same organization, the skirmishes. There will be mcuho slaughtered en route.The action gives rise to scenes of action so shocking as the attack on the car where travel Kee, Theodore and Julian (Julianne Moore), ex-wife of Theodore, activist still in full swing and protector of the pregnant girl. Amazing and superbly shot scene.And, although here the views will be for all tastes, Alfonso Cuarón is situated towards the end another summit of the film scenes. When an event does, once friends and enemies, den a truce, stop and leave passage to hope.Among so much sordidness, Michael Caine, as the hippie fumeta Jasper, undertakes to assume the moments more friendly, those who have some note of humor.But the Chronicle of "Children of men" is not only a part of war. It is also a reflection of what us it frightens today same. Floods of people leaving their country, tensions multi-racial, street protests, social phobias, systems dictadoriales masked hotbeds of international tension in the democracy? and a society (or "dirt") suffering from infertility to provide new policies, more resources, ideas, motivations, hopes.</body>
</review>
