<review author="Caty" title="Cuatro hermanos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>History of solid and infinitely more complex than it seems at first</summary>
	<body>During much of "Four brothers", I had the constant feeling that history passed in the 1970s, and it was only when I saw a digital camera emerge in a scene when I realized my error. For this reason, I am sure that my confusion was not accidental, filmmaker John Singleton obviously rather strove to encircle his film of a strong 70s atmosphere, from the soundtrack and the direction full of zooms of the era to the styling of the personajes.y also have the argument that baby stories of vengeance so common in films of the time mainly to the way in which the characters coexist with their angerHere there is no place for piety and for political correctness.Full of wrath for the murder of her adoptive mother, four brothers of the title do not trust in the efficiency of the police and decide to punish the killers on their own. In this sense, the screenplay written by David Eliott and Paul Lovett succeeds fully, allowing the viewer perceived that the protagonists (anti-heroes by definition) are so dangerous and cruel as the criminals pursued. Even so, these four men apparently so cold have a strong bond between them, link is not just a question of coexistence, but of true brotherly love.In addition, Singleton uses quite some time during the first part to illustrate the relationship between them, limiting simply establish the dynamics of this strange family. It is a risky decision, because somehow it interrupts the narrative flow, but it is absolutely correct in my opinion, since all the emotionally charged characters transmitted to the Viewer is thanks to these moments.In this same way, the script exceeds the expectations of the genre, showing how a story solid and infinitely more complex than it seems at first. Not to mention ever of his characters (even from the side) the writers are important functions for all people involved in the plot, which makes it more coherent and satisfactory from a structural point of view.And what is more admirable: none of the protagonists suffer one of these "transformations" artificial so common in the productions of Hollywood, where many characters become "good" overnight overnight. Elliott and Lovett characters know and respect them, although these are not exemplary citizens. With the rage of having to deal with the death of his mother, they do not show no mercy on its path toward revenge, coming to kill some of his enemies even though they are unarmed and finding defenceless. But they know live with his way of being: when Jeremiah, the only one of the four who seems to have a life more normal, argues that his mother "would be the first to forgive his killers", one of his brothers immediately responds "not everyone can be holy". There is another of the merits of history: the dialogues are, mostly, very well written.Exploring the potential of the script with talent, John Singleton directs with security action sequences, deserves a special mention a car chase that occurs during a storm of snow at night (today, make good sequences of persecution and shootings is very difficult, because we have seen almost everything in the seventh art). Apart from this, Singleton gets some very acceptable performances of the cast, emphasizing above all the of Mark Wahlberg's, although Tyrese Wilson (that escape the stereotype of beanpole gross and create a character that he knows think) and Tenerence Howard (as Lieutenant Green, which creates a very good dramatic moment during the entire fabric) you are not far behind.</body>
</review>
