<review author="Mario" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is clear that I am not objective with Guillermo del Toro, but even so, I believe that I am able to say that the laberinto del fauno is his best work so far.</summary>
	<body>With some filmmakers it happens? with many not the truth, but occasionally movie premieres typical director you know you did not disappoint. Not I am referring to those who have made the great masterpieces of the twentieth century? the same that later arrastraran in unfortunate projects, because Hollywood is well - and that you fail over and over again, perhaps because the degree of demand is too high. Rather speak of this caste of artisans of class media that normally maintain a level of consistent quality in all of his films; in my opinion, Guillermo del Toro belongs to that school of film buffs who always adhere to, which are able to deal with a big hollywodiense and carry the day out and at the same time make room for more personal achievements.Eager to spend a good time and trust that does not disappoint me, I went the premiere to see the laberinto del fauno, one of these projects in turn more staff that arise in black and boys vampire demon. Filmed in the mother tongue of the Mexican and euros and pesos rather than dollars, William returned to the pseudo-universo already raised in the spine of the devil, which is around the Spanish civil war - either before, during or after - and that both had pleased me in its previous edition. Everything pointed to a good session of popcorn? that could not wait was to find me with one of the best films of fantasy genre that I've seen in a long time.El laberinto del fauno is, above all, a story. A story of love and death, of tenderness and violence, that combines fantasy and reality as if a Martini with vodka were (not busy) the combination of a dream world with the stark reality is magnificent, the fantastic journey of Ophelia (the girl protagonist) with the maquis rough fight the fascist regime recently implanted in Spain we intercalamos throughout the film. Both arguments are interwoven and enjoy a power amazing, wanting to in each case, as a viewer, that action will not end to change the third.On the side of the mundane a magnificent Jordi López represents the typical archetype of the military fascist and Franco. Strong and strict, devoid of any kind of scruples when occasion requires and severe even with their loved ones; a real bastard that fills the belly of lamb while it decides to grant a single Primer of rationing to every family dependants. Do do the topic works perfectly, because every story requires of a? bad?, and Captain Vidal is a perfect son of a bitch. Many of the hiperviolentas sequences which stars give a great intensity to the story, intensity that I do not know until that point would have been possible if the roll had spoken in English.One of the strengths of the tape is the emotional part, concerns emerge during the footage: you feel the powerlessness of the massacred maquis, are aware of the suffering of some characters, you leave take the magical world that runs the girl and get to claim revenge on more than one occasion. Moments like the starring the stuttering guerrilla are simply excellent and make succeed the film where wrecked the Devil's backbone, that was a horror story that did not fear, in this occasion we encounter a fable that it excites. Much blame for this her have the actors, whom I greatly emphasize the doctor (Alex Angulo) and the maid (Maribel Verdú) while on this occasion are you not tits - which embroider their roles, being the Doctor, protagonist of one of the most exciting moments of the length.The technical Bill for the film is really impeccable, at the level of any Yankee production. The special effects are the best I've seen, combining digital technology with a traditional component of costumes, make-up and props. The Faun? who gives life Doug Jones, who interpreted to Abe Sapiens Hellboy - it is especially successful and some creatures, such as which has eyes on the palms of the hands are amazing. An example of know-how. On the other hand, the music, composed by Javier Navarrete, also charged prominence as it progresses the tape seizing virtually it towards the end.Definitely, and bearing in mind that I enjoyed a by-product as Blade II by the hand of the fat of beards (especially listening to their comments on off) is clear that I am not objective with Guillermo del Toro, but even so, I think that I am prepared to say that the laberinto del fauno is his best work so far, and that it is probably not the last.To finish only I ask that you remember the moral of this story: and is that obey, so no more? not have to be correct, at least not always?</body>
</review>
