<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Las partículas elementales" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is perhaps the film's love of the year, but there is no hugs sudados, nor looks lost in the foliage of the passionate rapport: there are emotions, resignations, risks, deliveries, vices and concessions.</summary>
	<body>The novel by Michel Houellebecq was intelligence, audacity and pessimism, greased everything so that the narrative machinery flow and bad milk and the eschatology of the author rezume by each phrase in the film of Oskar Roehler, rookie with pretensions of already quoted author, cut to frivolous reflection on the disappointment of the bourgeois man in the Europe of the welfare State, although not without its attachment of cynicism, his particular evidence of inconsistency of European society today.He is two diametrically opposed half-brothers. One, cultured and refined, triumphant nato, dump in his work (a molecular biologist). The other is eaten by various venereal fever Muttley. Both in an already talludita age, discover the love and the film is humming how love is changing them. Or in fact does not change them anything. Chance, fate, in the magnificent Houellebecq novel exerted a notable role, comes here to destroy this apparent life of galanteos when the lovers of both fall ill and must consider if return to previous life or (definitely) assume some responsibility and face the disease with fortitude and poise.There is a settling of accounts director explicit very subtly. The novel (again she insistently because this is a literary film based on a literary boom) did more blood. There was no sweetness. Here the character are delivered with much tact: guess them carnal, nearby. The feelings that move them are those that drive us all and neglect suffered in childhood is the abandonment which, on occasion, we all feel when the total weaning and enter hocicados, driven by an absolute fever, in the society for work, find an apartment, fix a hipóteca, having children, in short, that Vertigo only having already settlement in retirement or in the Tomb. And some would say not there.Elementary particles is a film of the disenchantment of sadness, but this ballast is left to be seduced by some hope. The author is distancing itself from the cruelty of Houellebecq: is your plot of madness, of humor also of verismo. The thickness of the book was lightened because this is film and is a very difficult task to make images the avalanche of ideas and concepts (politically incorrect almost all) than the novelist German reflected in his novels.It is perhaps the film's love of the year, but there is no hugs sudados, nor looks lost in the foliage of the passionate rapport: there are emotions, resignations, risks, deliveries, vices and concessions.Those who have enjoyed the book (like me), always see a film false, it is hence in excess of its argument approaches, but entertaining, clear, very well trabada and, by course, Rocky, acidic. Moritz Bleibtreu also makes a work unique, hypnotic. Only see him deserves to enter the game of its plot.</body>
</review>
