<review author="Yul B." title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film very good, a director at dazzling rise to glory, which will probably be among the best this year, but that has lacked a boil to be a masterpiece.</summary>
	<body>This is one of those few films that moves so unconventional paths in the Hollywood industry that needs to be analysed and matured once past the end credits.The conclusion that takes after the shock causes?Children of men? It is that Alfonso Cuarón has shot a film visually spectacular and realistic, moral tragic, although with hopeful ending, which forces you to reflect possible seriamente.¿Es that we agree so much decadence, and that this will lead us to a world so apocalyptic?, there will be no salvation in this chaos?.Do despite the full continent of the film, it has a number of shortcomings in the content that causes you to lose the qualification of? masterpiece?. Do do stays in? good?; Although that's remarkable considering the numerous film disappointments that we are experiencing in recent years.?Children of men?, based on a novel by the writer P.D.James, reflects a future scares. And puts it too next: in the year 2.027; in a barely recognizable London and in a time where the human race has lost the ability to procreate and faces extinction fight between the deepest misery.The only way of survival seems lost on the death of the youngest person in the world, a boy of 18 years. However, there is still a last breath of hope for the planet: the surprising existence of a pregnant woman, an immigrant that different circumstances Theo Faron (Clive Owen), a former activist emotionally crushed, will have to help to bring safe and anarchists groups guerrillas who want the baby for pure political interest.It is evident that the picture, sound, and the scenic setting and musical of the film are impressive, touching the genius. Do not saw anything like from?Saving soldier Ryan?.Cuarón masterfully exhibits an eerily real future, with devastating and shocking visual references of the most terrible phenomena socio-political of our century (terrorism, immigration and environmental crimes), whose effects we see on a daily basis, already gradually in the worldwide television news in images.How to shoot the scenes with long flat sequence, camera on his shoulder, resource in the beginning of the film may be sickening, but which then becomes vital to narrate the agonizing journey of the protagonists contributes to the realism.The ultimate expression of this reality is achieved in a somewhat disconcerting detail: a splash of blood in the House as a result of a street confrontation between the British army and the guerrillas. A very dramatic license that has a drawback: removed you the scene perfectly (was supposed that that detail would occur only in the case that a reporter was recording the incident along with the protagonist).To much accumulation of veracity chaotic and frenzied agony is appreciated before that exist during the film small moments of peace and rest, intermingled with scenes that take place in places represented with images placid, clean and quiet. Even the curious insistence of Cuaron to maintain the character of Theo tormented with shoes and his feet during your break you evades the harsh reality that is displayed.Do do do do as it can be seen, the words? realistic?,? real?,? realism? and? reality? they occur along this criticism. However, it's an adjective that could only be granted to the visual part of the film. Almost the rest of its components, he said, some fragments of the script, certain dialogues and practically most of the performances, are equally artificial, predictable and absurd, that the footage of any low category thriller.This fails the tape, unfortunately, fact that causes you to lose a step on his way to immortality.Focusing on the cast, only that is saved is Michael Caine that his role as Jasper, a last laps hippy friend of Theo borda. The other main actors are mere vehicles of the scenery, including Clive Owen, showing one dramatic charge less than his previous roles in this film.Julianne Moore is passable as the leader of an illegal organization that defends the rights of refugees. And Clare-Hope Ashitey, pregnant woman, plays its role without fanfare.In summary, a very good film, a director at dazzling rise to glory, which will probably be among the best this year, but that has lacked a boil to be a masterpiece.</body>
</review>
