<review author="Bloody Will" title="La dalia negra" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Palm has fallen into the same thing that would make a newbie: take care too much the wrapper and neglect in a sovereign manner about inside.</summary>
	<body>How difficult is to find a film whose atmosphere and climate is flawless. Just as difficult that mix with a good argument. Brian De Palma, which did so well in "The untouchables of Elliot Ness" and "Trapped by its past" has fallen into "The Black Dahlia" on the same thing that would make a newbie: take care too much the wrapper and neglect in a sovereign manner about inside.Film Noir is back in the hands of De Palma, and does. 100% effectiveness in all that area that most reminds us the great classics such as "Cayo Largo": the protagonists are lit one cigar after another, the guys are very hard, girls are very calentorras though recatadas, and best of all, Hartnett with hat in bed after making love. With an excellent practice in "The untouchables", De Palma outboard a Master how turning Los Angeles into a murky city of 47 with all elements of film noir in its right place, but I repeat, what a pity that the script and history will not be equal.Sometimes stupid and absurd discussions break the magic completely. Sometimes I didn't know if stop listening to the protagonists to expect that in the next scene we remontaríamos the thing. It is not so, because not back but all desboca until you reach the end. The argument takes place on many occasions with an apparent inconsistency, and finish by not join much on the go and come from the protagonist in search of the culprit. Maybe a second viewing would make me understand the film in a different way, but I don't know if I am with forces withstand Hartnett once more.Despite having put my hopes in that De Palma this espabilaría completely, the performance of the Hollywood short ends up confirm me that this actor is so linear as deadpan, and I cannot find enough because of the lack of connection to history. We could imagine a good handful of actors who had taken the ballot more airy way, why not understand very well that led to the director to make the services of an actor who hasn't done a good job in his life. If I wanted to surround himself with young people, it could have done so without that implied incompetence.Girls I don't no but, although perhaps I was wrong to think that Johansson would be more cruel. I can not say that is the interpretation of his life, that insurance is coming, but nothing disappointed me. Correct without more, but if I have to compare it with the role of Hilary Swank, it loses. The multi-oscarizada is the best of the film and I thought he would never see a shred of sensuality in this girl until her role as genuine Wolf has covered me mouth. Impressive how remaining pearls on the bed.The side most notable are Aaron Eckhart, which makes it a thousand times better than the protagonist, although it was not difficult, and Fiona Shaw, simply wonderful.Two scenes to remember: K.D. Lang singing in the club where a chorus of vicious dancers leave you breathless, and the scene where Hartnett met the parents of Swank and in which the camera moves at the whim of its director, which reminds me the best that had "Snake eyes".The health authorities will discover that De Palma has gone through the lining boards avoid scenes with too much fumeteo. In virtually all of the frames there is one cigarette, the other great silent protagonist of the film. What bad time for those who needed a cigarette in order to support Hartnett.Un great filmmaker with two loose ends: his main actor and his argument. The next time will be Brian.</body>
</review>
