<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Crank" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Action since the born until he dies. Well developed and well clinched, only suitable for lovers of films of action and humor black and lumpy.</summary>
	<body>Read the entire host critique, without breathing, possibly running as an asshole and giving the biggest screams out. Accessory to break things.The film is a guy who gets up and sees that he has a DVD with TV. It gets and is that they have punctured you a very dodgy shit that you will send to suck less que canta a rooster to huevón click of the balls. Of a result which is lia to run and kill to find the asshole that she wants to Apollo and touch the badajo. Runs and runs, chinga and chinga until the bullshit of telefilmada that we see it completed and sales with desire to run and kill any child badly whilst bitch that you see on the street.Cagon mother who gave birth to the great crap of the shell of his mother, what movie more asshole shots, drugs, sex and music to all estrozo. Fucking son of screenwriter us puts squarely on the tape, with cane since the start. At the end we amaricona and seems well bitch shit, but hosts, which we will have to piss her, right? The story takes place between jeringuillazos adrenalíticos, shots of all types, cuts of hands, hack, fucked, blowjob and racing. And all of this box of these well grumosos partimientos ("do Te made a hand?") and well cinicotes, of which us like males with hairs on the Dick.In short, that I shit in the said to be that it gave birth to the son of the great shit he did is adrenalítica movie, that I had a putísima mother. I leave that I have to go to charge me bastards.In short again, jajajajajaja, I had to do so the criticism, I've not been able to resist. That film, that cane. Action since the born until he dies. Well developed and well clinched, only suitable for lovers of films of action and humor black and lumpy. I enjoyed as a dwarf, although the movie is not a wonder. And also well small!In conclusion, to say that I think that the writer you will give the letter K of the academia de la lengua, by fluid and careful language that uses. K Kagon your father son of the great bitch, of course.</body>
</review>
