<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="El viento que agita la cebada" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The successes that defects are more numerous... Personal reflection overcomes his slow pace</summary>
	<body>To Ken Loach is called 'committed director' for his films of social character, such as 'Raining Stones'. Many are advocates, while others tend to criticize the lack of objectivity in his films, or rather, the feeling of being too notorious is his position. I cannot have an opinion too valuable because 'The wind that shakes the barley' is the first film that I see of the acclaimed English filmmaker, but I advocate that any position or vision to make a film: the film is art, and as such, must be personal. It is the diversity of all where wealth, which is why I think that filmmakers have to bring his vision, whether or not objective. That tape like less (or more) is independent. The tape shows us, with historical views that could be somewhat contentious for some, the birth of the Irish Republican Army, IRA. We are in the closed and green Ireland of 1920, in rural areas where lives the British 'invasion', where reigns the resignation and rabies. Although the reflection of the time, customs and way of life is good, highlights of the film is the confrontation between the own Irish, staged in numerous passages of the film: the reason for the origin of the conflict in their personal positions, and the absurdity of certain decisions. While 'The wind that shakes the barley' contains typical elements (tear moments perhaps something intentional or avoidable), does not deserve to be branded as well: its virtues are more numerous than the defects, among them could draw a somewhat irregular rhythm, or rather, unnecessarily slow sometimes. But far from being pretentious, the film achieves one (again) reflection in the Viewer, beyond the real plot, coming to ask if it has both changed the way of thinking of a century ago with the actual.o even with the centuries. The interpretive section at the head with the chameleonic and always correct Cillian Murphy seconded by a group of actors not too known to the general public, each fulfilling its role. The picture and the rest of the technical aspect accompany, without being an astonishing visual beauty, although not has become overshadowed by the rest of strengths of Loach. The problem of 'The wind that shakes the barley' is probably the feeling of not being entirely original, running times; but, avoiding prejudices and with some predisposition, one enjoys the film. Like it or not, objectively the result is done bueno.de, already won the Palme d'Or at the last Cannes Festival. Something will be.</body>
</review>
