<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cuarón gives a lesson in how to make a film, how filming sequences, how reflect many things, without leaving aside the plot. There is no other that applaud... This is good film.</summary>
	<body>Many directors have reflected the future, near or far, in his films: many times with optimism, other more pesimistas.y others really catastrophic. Apparently, Alfonso Cuarón is a really worrying chaos, and launches a fierce criticism of current Western society: we're going adrift. While the story might seem unfinished, the throw something in lack reasons for female infertility (although to be honest, it isn't the most important thing and devotes some few strokes), the plot is very interesting: 18 years without birth a child, (so current) problems of illegal immigration they reach implausible points, chaos takes over all world capitals. What's going on? What to do when you know that humanity has counted? Cuarón already received praise for making the third part of 'Harry Potter' to acquire a tone much more grim and somber than their predecessors (not very difficult era given child Columbus films), which was appreciated by all sectors of the public and critics. And now, not only returns to print darkness, but that the impressive setting is really priceless: never saw so well reflected futuristic chaos, with many details that they guiñan the eye to the spectator, both the visual and the clear message of Fund.If this premise you add a very correct Clive Owen that, without shine, fits the role with a very good performance (another one on the face of this interpreter between glamour and professionalism) as well as a degree of seniority with Michael Caine (another big), and the strength of Juliane Moore (one is wanting more.) in addition to the aforementioned paragraph technical (do had already said that it is formidable?)the result is one of the best films of recent years which, without being a masterpiece, will be classified as one of the best of this year by far. But, without a doubt, there is one aspect really succeeded in 'Children of Men': sequences of one shot that occur throughout the film. How much these images, shot without any pausa.tanto so well filmed movement appreciates the viewer get tension manages to penetrate the screen easily, to the extent that at the end of the tape, the feeling of being stuck to the seat is inevitable. Ultimately, Cuarón gives a lesson in how to make a film, how filming sequences, how reflect many things, without leaving aside the plot. There is no other than aplaudir.esto is the good film.</body>
</review>
