<review author="Plissken" title="Alatriste" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I hope that they conform with the box office success, because at the cinematographic level, the most awaited Spanish production of the year has been in a kind of trailer for two hours and a half.</summary>
	<body>There are things that can not be, as much as one try. Not to cover a trunk of Redwood with arms. Not to drink more beer than fits in the own stomach at a stroke. Five books in one movie can not be adapted. That is the lesson that should be drawn Agustín Díaz Yanes and his team of the final outcome of 'Alatriste'.I hope that they conform with the success at the box office, because to cinematographic level, the most anticipated of the year Spanish production has become a kind of trailer for two hours and a half, in which concepts as basic as the narrative pace, character development, or searching for the action/reaction is obviate almost altogether, grew the faithful followers of the literary with battering of the type "ten years later" and confusing to the ignorant of the Pérez-Reverte saga (myself, for example), to be assumed that "this the public already knows". This negative impression is accentuated because the director is halfway between the over-production of adventures and palatial intrigue of unspectacular appearance, with the film irritating to all sorts of audiences alike.On the positive side of the balance, emphasizes the powerful atmosphere (especially costumes) and care photo treatment of Paco Femenia, as well as the presence of Viggo Mortensen, despite the handicap of his accent than I cloudy, defends his character with great dignity; and unlike Sergio Peris-Mencheta in 'Los Borgia', you can with the weight of the film (or the trailer, at least). Enrico Lo Verso, Juan Echanove, Ariadna Gil, Francesc Garrido, Javier Cámara, and above all, Eduard Fernández, also take their roles in solvency. And some isolated chapter (the site of Flanders, personally is the part that I liked) serves as the point of what this film could have been, in other hands.Because on the negative side, apart from some bump in the casting errors (why Unax Ugalde can't put another face, still ahead of Elena Anaya or the French Cavalry? to what das Pilar López de Ayala, Pilar Bardem, Cristina Marcos or Paco Tous as insignificant roles? why Blanca Portillo doing of Inquisitor? why, just why?)(Do, Eduardo Noriega?), la palma is the absence of narrative that makes what you do not know if you attend a chronicle of the twilight of the Spanish Empire, a follow-up of the main character, a choral drama or a collection of highlights of the whiskered protagonist. He spoke of 'Los Borgia' throwing in face the precipitation in solving history. But this is worse, this is not what count.And the worst, knowing not how to tell it, because Díaz Yanes is limited to put us in a situation with a "Madrid, ten years later," and enter any of the "occurred" shows with greater or lesser success, without giving the opportunity to hear why everyone wants him to betray turn to profane in the universe of Alatristefor example, or why Íñigo Balboa is hired one day murderer and prisoner of galleys the other, or how Alatriste manages to convince the selfsame Conde Duque de Olivares that makes it a personal favor. Díaz Yanes suppressing the very necessary scenes of transition to readjust to the spectators, and achieved what the flojita 'Los Borgia' could not: get me. A 3, by the work of some actors and the setting.</body>
</review>
