<review author="Matías Cobo" title="United 93" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tribute to those who lost their lives that day the third suicide flight and demonstration of how the chaos of those desquiciantes hours reduced to useless all military measures autodefensivas.</summary>
	<body>The film is a concentrate of emotions of a couple of hours which increases and sublimates everything that happens on your filter. But the reality, may sometimes contain so many ingredients that reduce to superfluous any desire ficcionador. Paul Greengrass, making good the axiom that less is more, has followed this premise for a tape so masterly as honest. With an emparenantado with the documentary style, United 93 is the first of the films with a centered argued exclusively in the tragedy of September 11, 2001. Unlike Oliver Stone, who has filmed a laudatory with jingoistic violet, Greengrass decided to forgo any sensationalism. I wanted to pay tribute to those who lost their lives that day in the third suicide flight, United 93, and demonstrate how the chaos of those desquiciantes hours reduced to useless all the autodefensivas military action.Fidelity to the facts is such that Greengrass and his team interviewed on numerous occasions to the families of deceased passengers on the United to get closer with the greatest possible respect to those people and those who still grieve. Hence, the deliberate absence of familiar faces in the cast or have kept the real names of passengers as terrorists suicide. And in this line of verismo, the story of how we experienced the chaotic situation from the air controls and military commanders was directly based on the recording of communications made that morning from civil aviation. So that these dialogues are truffled of abundant technicalities relating to flight instructions, though incomprehensible to ears of the profane, also beneficial in this camouflage makes the story of the real event.Arguably, the film proposes a classic and without shrill narration. The evolution of the facts, from the routine boarding of passengers on the flight until the nervousness of suicide bombers prior to your action, it will be that print emotion to the tragedy that lies ahead. Here, the identification with the victims of the flight is absolute, because who you is not going through your head that a similar tragedy could happen on any other flight. And terrorists, rather than characterize them with the typical image of psychopaths lanza-discursos, appear as some insecure young though so tightly ideologizados to undertake terrible orders.Do and the magnificent script for Greengrass avoids falling in the tempting bombast or tired political entries, simply focuses on two issues: in how about passengers decide to confront, and rebelling some before the fact to die in a suicide flight, and how the rest of the citizens? including military? He attended the live broadcasting of the attacks with impotence. Thus, on the one hand, we share the agony of United 93 passengers when they realize that the end of their lives could be close, but also we are witnessing with amazement unable to response of the first military power in the world before the largest terrorist attack within its borders. It was clear that, with fierce determination to kill a terrorist, little or nothing they serve all the measures autodefensivas on which is built the idea of internal security.Although used in excess to the camera on his shoulder, this choice of levels is fully justified to portray the turmoil that morning and in tune with the realistic aesthetic of the tape. Those who see United 93 must forget stereotypes already seen in tapes of air hijackings. You will not find the tripulante-héroe capable of getting rid of the captors or to military salvapatrias, will see only ordinary people, as any of us, who did everything possible to save their lives. Because the logical survival instinct is that emerges with more strength in a very extreme situation.</body>
</review>
