<review author="Plissken" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lesson of nerve, rhythm, planning and direction of actors of Scorsese, whom he notices again at home portraying violence in the American suburbs.</summary>
	<body>It was time! He had not returned to have news of Martin Scorsese Film of fiction from the already distant 'Casino' (1995). Yes, it is true, since there is a type who has shot with his name 'Kundun' (1997), 'on the edge' (1999), 'Gangs of New York' (2002) and 'The Aviator' (2004), but that this was not Scorsese. It seemed, but it wasn't. Which has directed 'The Departed' ('infiltrators' in "modern Titrator"), that it is Martin Scorsese.Remake confessor (at least by Scorsese) of the acclaimed 'Infernal Affairs' of Wai Keung Lau and Siu Fai Mak, 'The Departed' tells the story of Colin Sullivan (Matt Damon convincing) and Billy Costigan (clear Leonardo Di Caprio), two men who are crossing their destinations on both sides of the law in the shadow of the pre-civil mafia boss Frank Costello (Jack overwhelming) (Nicholson). One strives to become the best, the other can only aspire to survive. Deception, death and betrayal deleted the fine line separating legal from illegal, in a territory where all are guilty in the eyes of someone.Lesson of nerve, rhythm, planning and direction of actors of Scorsese, whom he notices again at home portraying violence in the American suburbs. No one, not even the great Asian film (well, perhaps Tarantino Yes), is able to make you fall a sadistic torturer as the Nicholson character as well. Michael Ballhaus, pictured, recreates a South Boston dark and decadent by the criminals moving rats, which contrasts with the bright and sophisticated surroundings of the police elite. They are the two parallel worlds between which move both protagonists.The secondary function with as much energy as the protagonists: Alec Baldwin, Mark Wahlberg (the surprise of the movie, for me), Martin Sheen, Ray Winstone and Vera Farmiga surround the star trio of outstanding form.The unique buts that can be put on this return to the first division of Martin Scorsese is little dramatic weight has the love element in the plot of the film, and that repeated songs ('Gimme shelter' stones and ' I´m shipping up to Boston' of the Dropkick Murphy´s sound twice each), but this is a my paranoiadoes not affect the film. Incidentally, one of the best news of this 2006: Marty has returned. And what is best, recently announced that he is thinking away from the Hollywood industry because"to more spending, less risk you take". They will return the time of 'Taxi Driver' or 'The last temptation of Christ'? A 8'5, half step below 'Casino' and one and a half below the large.</body>
</review>
