<review author="Plissken" title="La prueba del crimen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cheat and irritating but entertaining and cloudy at the same time. What could have been and was not.</summary>
	<body>'Running Scared' (2006, 'Proof of crime' in the cultural ghettos in the world), directed by Wayne Kramer, is higher than the thriller medium. Up there, okay. The trouble is that gender has come to miserable levels in this beginning of the 21st century and be above average not you escape mediocrity. This could be thinking Kramer to write the screenplay, because it has details and moments that stand out, and much, by both above and below, of the hundreds of films with the word "crime" included in the title (Spanish title, clear).The plot: Joey Gazelle is a stressed mafiosillo suburb to which their (Italian-American, of course) heads charge you to get rid of his last shooting weapons. That same night, the gun disappears with his young neighbour and Joey must find the two before the police, the Russian mafia, their own heads or knows who do so.What we sold initially as a rampant search of happy "proof of the crime", becomes the flight of a scared child (hence the original title) through a forest full of ogres, monsters, witches, evil elves and any other fairy godmother (excellent end credits). And are, in length, the best moments of the film, with a couple of anthologies scenes. Gives the impression that the true story that we want to tell Kramer is this, and not all that gangster bullshit with confrontation between families and (for height) multifinal, authentic ballast of the function.The pace is so frantic as the kidding look of Joey Gazelle (Paul Walker pasadísimo), and the visual style is so bipolar as point of view, at times "ultracool" and full of effects that end up dizzy and sometimes direct, dirty and hard. Interpretations are not too, apart from an effective Vera Farmiga and the omnipresent "niño-raro" Cameron Bright. When Hollywood gives a child, it is that they put us it up in advertisements for refrigerators. Paul Walker defends his character three-quarters of film for then sank with the rest of the film in one of the worst and most incredible twists of script of recent times, which will ruin the credibility of the whole history, hitherto shaky and sordid as few. Total, than a 6, cheat and irritating but entertaining and cloudy at the same time. What could have been and was not.</body>
</review>
