<review author="Jose Luis" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do a maze with two outputs, in which I personally neither left me satisfied? None of the two, is totally beautiful and hopeful.</summary>
	<body>Initially fantasy and reality were the same, the fantasy was an excellent ally to explain the world, when the science still did not exist. Then when reality became cruel and intolerable, fantasy helped as a hideout. As that secret and magical place where one is can shelter black days and oneself. But? What happens, when you get to this world and it is just as cruel and violent, or maybe more?The new film by Guillermo del Toro, is torn between these two equally frightening worlds; a civil war Spain, but in which the hunt for Communists was equally cruel and a mythical, fantasy world. And it is Ophelia, the small protagonist, who lies between these two worlds, after arriving in the company of his pregnant mother to a military camp, where his stepfather lives trying to "clean up their Communist homeland".Ofelia discovers, in the middle of the forest, a maze of stone they say to State there since time immemorial, wherein the Faun meets and makes it know that she is the Princess of a Kingdom which is found under the Earth, but again needing tackle three tests and prove that his spirit not been corrupted by mortals.But do not believe that this is a tape in the style of the Chronicles of Narnia, on the contrary, it is not a film for children, which is completely clear in the first scene of the film, where the girl lies on the ground, wounded and bleeding. It is clear that no child would like to be in a place and at a time like that, any adult nor, but the escape the Faun offers does not seem to be the best option, since on the one hand it shows friendly and on the other its mystery creates suspicion. This ambivalence is a success because it is an excellent job of characterization and makeup, there is a human working behind him and is not the result of long hours of design by computer.The production is excellent; the alternate worlds are amazing though dark and scary, nothing here is nice, everything has a flavor somewhat twisted and bloody, including fairies, to which we are accustomed to seeing them as small beings bonachones and friendly, here their flight is fast and erratic rather resembling an insect that there is forced to flee.And that is perhaps the ambivalent and dark spirit that prevails in the tape, the innocence is trying to crush, innocence trying to find its way between good and evil, but in an atmosphere where both are mixed to such degree that it is impossible to distinguish it from the other.Del Toro has matured as well as its cinema, who since its inception has sought to further the various genres, horror, gore, fantastic and today has achieved it, creating an adult film, a dark fairy tale, in which in the end one has to choose, if it stays with the realistic part, with the fantastic part or a combination of both, and perhaps that's perhaps where the public loses a little tread, not knowing that the way the labyrinth to choose.Do a maze with two outputs, in which I personally neither left me satisfied? None of the two, is totally beautiful and hopeful.PS: This tape was selected by Mexico to compete in the Oscars, in the section of foreign tapes, however, I doubt that the Academy feels attracted by a complex Ribbon like this.</body>
</review>
