<review author="Mario" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I start to not properly digest the burden of implicit moralina that carry this type of production. To know how foolish that we and the origin of all the ills of this planet I don't have to go to the cinema.</summary>
	<body>We are all the children of men, but what would happen if the last of us had already born? Under this approach Alfonso Cuarón presents, in its peculiar and last film, a new story on hackneyed society dystopian which the human being has made to shit (again) and back, costs down and without brakes, to the State of nature. Typical and topical history, written and filmed hundreds of times, based on the novel by p. D. James, and that reminds both certain classics of literature of anticipation as to the track 1984 or brave new world, that already bored. Deformed viewing of a society as her our a few years older - years that would become evolve towards positions more radical and fascist today can imagine - already not impress anyone, especially when the development of the movie in question seems too close to any news of the three in the afternoon. In a moment of the film, a radio program click a song of 2003 and the announcer reads something as well as? the time in which the world was not aware of that everything was going to go to hell? I would say for him.To enjoy a good reinterpretation of this kind of subgenre of science fiction, I recommend V for Vendetta graphic novel by the great Alan Moore, much less Manichean and with really interesting proposals. A partir de here, and taking into account that the plot seems to me neither original nor too interesting, we can say that the film is dotted with light and dark.Sharing is one of the facets to highlight (despite the thymus which is see Julianne Moore in the closing credits) consisting, among others, a surprising Michael Caine and a superb Clive Owen; Perhaps the most charismatic actor of the current Hollywood which is just enough to sustain the project, even in their spare time more leaden. All of them say tacos and smoke fags which is very welcome. Another advantage is photography, more suggestive and right to transport you to a near future in which things are almost like now, but more ugly. Probably they didn't have to squeeze too much to find the locations, and this is one of the greatest successes of the film; in the middle of the final confrontation in which the protagonists are submerged, it is not difficult to recognize the same faces we see daily in Mogadishu, Haiti, Palestine or Baghdad. Recreation from eternal conflict entrenched and street is notable.But on the other hand the script loses in a succession of predictable and aburridísimos, events with very few moments of genuine emotion. The pace of the film suffers many ups and downs, even taking into account that the director (very wrongly IMHO) us tide with the camera on his shoulder during the footage; This technique has its explanation in a few minutes of the roll, but it becomes even irritating in others.Sometimes the impression that if it weren't for the good performance of Clive Owen, making current type to which life has been abused, the film became virtually unbearable. However in others (as in the final minutes, despite the tijeretazo which is the own end) the film is interesting and can be seen.Finally, I must say that I start to not properly digest the burden of implicit moralina that carry this type of production. To know how foolish that we and the origin of all the ills of this planet I don't have to go to the cinema, just with that I stay at home and look at me in the mirror.</body>
</review>
