<review author="Berto" title="Click" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Such an approach half seriously that they try to give at the end and grab the viewer completely confused, is the more successful that they could have done with it, that it was losing bellows alarmingly.</summary>
	<body>I went to the movies to see Click thinking that I would find a new Disney comedy very in the style of its protagonist, Adam Sandler, and the truth that the principle was very disappointing. As in all comedies in which usually participate Sandler, thanks are more or less based on "teta-culo - pis" and is the beginning of the movie, where place us him as an architect too busy to take care of his family, is based on these so past fashion gracietas that are no longer grace. When the "universal" remote enters the life of the protagonist, the film is winning some integers, although still with this pattern of scatological jokes. Is the long half of the film where things change, surprisingly better, and attempting to copy the Christmas story, Dickens, trying to teach a lesson of moralina the protagonist, recalling the transience of life, and for that there is no best thing in this world that seize every moment and not miss anything, because it can produce dismal results. This second part, which remotely I get reminded films as interesting as trapped in the time and like God, but that if, bridging the gap, I liked a lot more than the beginning, and that half-serious approach trying to give at the end that grab the viewer completely confused, is the more successful that they could have done with it, that it was losing fuelle alarmingly.Adam Sandler is in this film quite correct, in his usual tone, you will not give any Oscar but do to see interesting films would have not gone to see this, not? Kate Beckinsale, gorgeous as always if I liked a lot and is in the role of wife of Sandler the perfect vehicle for, without too strive, succeed in the interpretation. Christopher Walken, great actor deserves special mention and in their little speeches transmitting much strength to his character, something that for a film of this kind is appreciated not had taken his role too to messing. By David Hasselhoff little I can say, because simply seeing this face and the role of this great horny and macho head, although his character is badly exploited and the rest of the cast is the more loose without any doubt.In short a very recommendable to see film but want to see movies with pretensions, although an unexpected end and that "Carpe Diem" which distills the film make it highly recommended for a boring afternoon.</body>
</review>
