<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="La máquina de bailar" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another mierdón that puts "jeta" Santiago Segura, and which one is forgotten almost at the speed that view.</summary>
	<body>The New REC Park are an old arcade of the Centre where adolescents Miss afternoons in a world of neon colors and strident musiquillas. Among them, Dani (Jordi Vilches) and his gang, a group of kids of Fuenlabrada, are the masters of a singular game: La machine dance. Dani works in a supermarket. There a segurata pint of serial killer he is a good kid, so he asks that his albino boa (a caprice of nature) care during the month that will go abroad. And of course Dani, as well as monitor the animal uses the floor to organize a fiestecita with a friends and step to send the serpent to another neighborhood in an unfortunate accident. The gang it is not another remedy that seek a replacement animal, but the only are costs a paste. They do not know or where to start unless they discover the convening of the first national contest of the dance machine, which will be held in the Hall of the Manga. But they need the help of an expert choreographer, someone to guide them in the complex world of dance competitions to compete at a high level. Johnny, in charge of the New Park, was an old champion when disco music was all the rage. Moved by the kids (which remind him a little to himself), decides to prepare them.Every day, on the way to work, I was with posters strewn with Atocha station and banners of this "sensational" (Note irony) film, on the other hand, I do not know very well why, and although I always try denying this kind of unfortunate events, I just falling, and it is that here this sad mortal, prefers a sandwich mortadella to a ration of the most interesting delicacy, that is why today, and without it planned, and thinking about going to see another film, a part of me, maybe the more B (of natural and banana), me has finished dragging so lamentable spectacle.One envisages it knowing that it is before the worst that your eyes can see, and that Santiago Segura is usually nourish this, its cutrecine for kneading? at box office, of a cumbersome but effective way without doubt, with Jordi Vilches, pigeonholed as Michael Landon, in the role of young geek (which already repeated in "End of course", "Cymbals flyers" and any movie showing).On the other hand, the film seems a "publi-report" of the company KONAMI, famous not only for Pro Evolution Soccer, but also by those infernal machines hitting jumps and dance (for which our body is not empowered to such tremendous coordination), rhythm of unceasing music, heavy and machacota, brought from the East. Finally, another mierdón that puts "jeta" Santiago Segura, and which one is forgotten almost at the speed that visiona.Incidentally, also leaves José Corbacho, but better to be spent to films such as "Tapas" or casual appearances in "Buenfuente", because here is to forget his fronted.</body>
</review>
