<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Wicker man" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are aspects that highlight, except the art direction, which recreates a kind of civilization Amish, and locations, as the rest of the film, being very demanding, well could burn at the stake.</summary>
	<body>New trailers back to play us a trick. And I say this because we are tired of seeing films that are not what we expect. There will be people saying that it is marketing and have achieved its objective: to buy the product (in this case that goes to the movies). Well, on the one hand his manoeuvre is effective but it is also negative for them because you can make many people by the type of trailer to take back and if he knew on the other hand as it will be the film could have gone to see it.I have to say that The Wicker Man is another remake of a 1973 film, which I have not seen in this case. Well, the fact is that the trailer for this new version sells you pressure, scares, spirits and other elements of horror movies and all that then find yourself with a story brought to the screen that do not have any of the above ingredients. The home looked promising, because in the closing credits we read the participation of Nicolas Cage, Ellen Burstyn, Kate Beahan, Leelee Sobieski in the interpretation section and Neil Labute at the address. Apart from what I have read, the initial images also present a situation that could have been much more than Yes. Nicolas Cage, who plays a policeman Edward Malus, fails to rescue a girl nor her mother, that just burning after the car in which are (from a car accident). Afterwards, Malus, has hallucinations and is for sick leave, until he receives a strange letter from their exprometida asking you for that you help, that his daughter has disappeared. Until here everything normal, "paranormal" is that the girl who died is very similar to the daughter of his ex-girlfriend, that he has sent you a photo of the small. So the good of Cage, after ignoring the advice of his friend, decides to go to the enigmatic and mysterious island where she lives. There you will discover that they are a species of sect, but well I won't tell more. At all times you expect will happen something of what we promised in the trailer, but nothing at all. So the rest of the footage takes place seeing Nicolas Cage investigating and looking for the lucky girl by meadows and houses on the island. The truth is that there is no points that highlight, except the art direction, which recreates a kind of civilization Amish, and locations, as the rest of the film, being very demanding, could well be burning at the stake both respect the protagonists of the film, except the producers and some other involved none lloraríamos loss.</body>
</review>
