<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="La dalia negra" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There are times that a novel can be very interesting, but carried screen does not have the same effect. A quality product which was expected much more.</summary>
	<body>Everything did foresee that we would be faced with a more than interesting proposal from the director of trapped by its past, that with him we find big names within the film world, but still the Black Dahlia fails stand out as film.Josh Hartnett, Scarlett Johannson, Aaron Eckhart and Hillary Swank under the direction of De Palma and with a screenplay by Josh Friedman based on the novel by James Ellroy, (who wrote the magnificent novel L.A. confidential), we introduced in the 1940s, in the streets and the problems that exist in the Mecca of cinema, from the hand of a tandem of police and good fighters such as Harnet and Eckhart (Lee Blanchard and Bucky Bleichert/Mr. ice /)Mr. fire). A crime desatará vicious circles and the possible forks that must interpret the good Bucky to solve it. But one thing is to do the character and another spectator, that halfway through the film begins to be quite lost and that often envy policemen you see on screen, his book and his pen need to sign up and do the necessary schemes for end not disoriented. There are times that a novel can be very interesting, but carried screen does not have the same effect. In the technical section no objection, a good photography, art direction in line with the time and with each character social conditions and the area in which moves, costumes and others also comes into play to perfection. In the interpretive section the truth is that they are also correct, a good casting with many familiar faces and that we have already discussed. Many will wonder that then how it is possible that the result is not excellent? And the answer is simple: the script. Normally all movies we have professionals who manage the majority of technical sections are good enough to pass unnoticed, and when something fails or us does not end like us the film, usually by the same endemic: the script. Definitely a quality product which was expected much more. Fortunately next week we get new movies from other two masters such as Allen and Scorsese.</body>
</review>
