<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="The guardian" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Everything runs through old territories, although admittedly a splendid invoice and a quite entire argument fails in the complicity of the Viewer when it lives outside the USA.</summary>
	<body>Meritorious Escasemente, will not result in very sagging film career of Kevin Costner, ballast from dancing with Wolves, the tour de force of history of the United States, which broke box office and put the actor and director front-page film of the last stretch of the 20th century. As nobody lives of rents, Kevin Costner has been procesionando, with great sorrow and some cash instrument of glory, by tapes whose final hosting was the turn video store shelf. Never memory the movie buff. Here everything runs through old territories, although admittedly a splendid invoice and a quite integer argument, which fails on the complicity of the Viewer when it lives outside the USA and is not recognized in these adventures of bailouts on the high seas, which we here (truly) sounds like propaganda of the American spirit. And of this genre we are unfortunately quite supplied.The hero portrayed is admirable. Do not enter this critical in assessing the strictly epic aspect of the plot, which has. It is not acceptable to question this body of rescue swimmers of the coast guard: deserve our respect to that seen in the film. Da same they come from Sweden or the coasts of Florida.El role of Costner is greedy: is the rescuer expert (and there is no Cangurolandias) who live a dreadful experience (the loss of colleagues, serious injuries in itself) and which it is intended to protect young cadets that principian ways and desperately want to emulate their hero. At this point, nothing new. The thing improved a little bit on the treatment of personal feelings, how people are involved in carrying out their projects and how the educational spirit of Philanthropy elevates the soul of humans and makes it a top example of value and delivers to others. I know that this morass of good intentions is a pastelazo for the Viewer to seek in the film sensations of more intense depth, but The guardian contains scenes of action very successful and why (in that mixture of film to the Frank Capra and cinema to the Renny Harlin) the movie is not bad by principles.The topics handled by the argument are the topics of life, now amplified: converted in Catechism of the would-be hero. Andrew Davis to take the controls of this film guarantees at least a while entertaining, clean, devoid of folds, delivered to the enjoyment of a compelling images and a treatment honest from what he is narrating. Davis provides a very basic psychological profile of actors: can't reach more. It strives to play with imagine that reliable vision the world of this military body. The tape, in that there is no possible doubt margin, manages to involve us in the gesta of its members.In another order of things, or is the same, we deem that the life of Ben Randall, the role of Costner, is the life of Kevin Costner. This is hero come unless provided with commitment to drive other than where he was and where triumphed. The film. The life. What matter.The role of man already hardened in a thousand battles that Kevin Costner left the albur of his followers during his visit to Spain of promotion seemed very significant. I saw a man whole, conscious of its faintness, of decay, for their lack of perspective. Also of his honorable decline. Your comments, I remember some very humorous, emphasize what I say.So we have a film of living legends, that that both excites the public yankee.In Lorca, in Logro침o, in C칩rdoba, in Santa Cruz de Tenerife, The guardian will not arouse passions of those who we call universal. There are feelings very idiosyncratic. It is in an almost extreme mode, but there we have our Almod칩var, a genius, a visionary, making theirs, so typical, the intimate (manchego), universal.Wave to other recent films, The guardian is left poisoned by some fondness towards religion. It seems, in sections of the film, we are witnessing a homily at a liturgy of salvation, to a redemption of the soul through the tridimensionalizados set of wild waves. And hence to me me sobrecogi칩 and was much more impressed by the perfect storm.Ah, I forgot, there is also (how not, how not) romance between graciosito cabin boy and country girl. It takes longer.</body>
</review>
