<review author="Cp" title="La dalia negra" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Visually very well worked, with a lot of direction, but a script that never focuses neither get hooked us.</summary>
	<body>I imagine a film producer, with a script on your table, thinking: this film is going to be the second L.A. confidential. It could have been, but lacks a little detail, the actors with charisma, with presence on screen. The small detail is that also the script is not exactly wonderful. The history, the argument, it is good, but when he became a script, I blows altogether. They are a lot of loose sequences, which are jumping from one to another, maintaining a skeleton of history, but without realized at any time. The recreation of the time is great, the very good picture, even mount (if you like the style jumps) this very well, and all the work of direction is very good, but the film that promised so much just not fit all parts. As I've said before, actors, even without doing so poorly, unable to fill the screen, do not have the strength to impress as hard guys, femme fatal or murderous intriguing. I do not like to refer to other films to make a comment, but in this case the similarities with L.A.Confidencial are very large, to create a complex story that gives bits and pieces loose in a principle to mount them all at the end. While in L.A. were still three characters at different times, the strength of the actors who played them (Spacey, Pierce and Crowe) combined with relatively simple stories, whose grace required in as there were no tricks or excessively complex stories, gave us a perfect film, while in the Black Dahlia, with a single Narrator character who guides us through the historyWe lose the history altogether. The problem with the Black Dahlia, is that the end doesn't make much sense, and the motivations that led to some characters to act in certain ways have no sense, and the truth the mysteries ending unresolved are more interesting than what just discovered, you are always disappointed.In summary: visually very well worked, with a lot of direction, but a script that never looks or get hooked us, and above all, with a few players, that even doing well, not transmitted force, intensity, greed or even the madness of his characters. Not bored, but nor it latches.</body>
</review>
