<review author="Ibán Manzano" title="La dalia negra" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>De Palma the script he is big and finally decides to cover everything to catch anything.</summary>
	<body>I read once that site to the great stars of actors simple was the beauty of her face in ceramic. That is, the significance that reached his aura. In the last film of De Palma, Mia Kirschner, a.k.a. Elizabeth Short, the Black Dahlia alias is an aspiring star poses as actress, and that in part by strive to be first falls the second. In fact, in a few notable sequences of the film, an outraged casting director asks him why is unable to interpret the sadness. She says Yes you can but the frozen smile of his face betrays. Paradoxically, the only time in which Elizabeth Short looks pain before the camera is in the filming of a porn movie in which he never wanted to participate, but understood as necessary toll for their sueñosAsí in the same way that L.A. confidential, the novel of the Black Dahlia disfiguring also the golden age of Hollywood, basically because Ellroy followed the maxim of the black genre that defends that behind each crime always hides a tragedya story that deserves to be told. Why ficcionó the Black Dahlia murder even though Los Angeles police never managed to solve the case and it was used as a vehicle of a pitiless city, erecting is step in the great renewer of the American detective fiction. .Palm it seeks to the same in cinema through the stylization of levels, the tribute and simultaneously the modernization, but the problem of dahlia black film is that it has chosen a too complex story for his tour de force. Without deleting you subtramas, without ever knowing that history prefer to De Palma the script he stays big and finally decides to cover everything to catch anything. Captained by a group of stars that at least here have been far from being actors, the Black Dahlia is not so much that it is a bad film, as it is not authentic. In the end, it too has to do with this film served on silver platter with which Hollywood wrapped in luxury garbage and pornography. The same never could star in the Black Dahlia.</body>
</review>
