<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La dalia negra" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Disappointed by two causes: by the film itself (bad, no uncertain terms) and the cluster of good feelings and indulgent expectations has been building among the public.</summary>
	<body>The criminologist genre conventions are not many, but are solidly established in the collective imagination of film. Corrupt cops. Offices of detectives with immense black smoke curtains. Corpses on the shore of a river, preferably near a factory. Fatal, Blondes, women in many times. Film noir has nourished of these topics to affirm his nombradía in the history of the seventh art, but Brian de Palma has given them entirely aside. He's gone for the tangent, have been fool by a pedestrian writer that confuses the gender series black lands as you can, and gives us a pathetic our black film made to the modern, i.e. with media, with actors with hook, with an admirable picture, although desasistido in his most explicit evidence: the script.Part Brian de Palma a true story that is still attending its byways in posh criminologists and several fans to the mysteries of the classic Hollywood: the murder of aspiring actress Elizabeth Short, the Black Dahlia, found on a site, the body split in two, with signs of Burns and obscenely painted mouth to ear knife to another. The material is convincing, but marra of Palma in the treatment of the story. Dealt with in excess of the two protagonists policemen (pugilistic top is long, tedious and distracted too much) and vacate greatly characters think that they will have a weight, but later they leave, leave altogether and only colorín overlooking the plot (the role of the exuberant Johannson). Brian de Palma has wanted to compose an epic noir and has Loopy a boring collage whose decor makes us remember the glorious black series of yesteryear (or now: L.A. confidential, masterful).The film disappointed for two reasons: by the film itself (bad, no uncertain terms) and the cluster of good feelings and indulgent expectations has been building among the public, eager to return to a kind of films that (unfortunately) already not abound. It has been one hoping this caramel several months and then it turns out it is overused, old and the strawberry promised is not such but a bitter, sticky, bland flavor after several licking.They tintineaban in our memory admirable movies from the same director as the untouchables of Eliot Ness or trapped by their past, which also touch this topic, but here Brian de Palma has damaged the material of first order of James Ellroy (bore L.A. confidential, without going any further) and has drowned, knowing swimming in dangerous waters.Not worth its excuse that the script is dense and very populous characters. Not supported that the stylistic speech of De Palma refocile in powerful images, in a plot still familiar in his work. Not worth all this because we have already seen on other occasions that Brian de Palma has sobrado talent to aerate these drawbacks with undisputed creative effectiveness. Even products of one lesser in his extensive work order rezumaban, in installments, all of their quality. I remember their mission impossible, or Femme fatale, the pastelazo flags in total heater plan. Then takes one findings that do not support replicas: the man wanted to have lacked, or (as it is often the case) they have gotten hand on the project many hands and in the end went frog when it principiaba Prince, valga this sonsonete helpings. He came to say Woody Allen in a recent interview that in Europe his work was infinitely more autonomous because the producers gave him money and a blank cheque of ideas to go where I like to form wishing. Maybe De Palma has let fall by London or Paris and sign around here his most personal film. It may be.We have what we have: a missed opportunity, a disappointing film. This film requires more cloudiness, so somehow: calls for less contention in the forms, a more Extrovert air. It is not enough that the decorations are portentous. Nor with which there is a blonde dead and a fatal woman who blur it and enfanga everything.The best (to finish this quartering) is the part of fiction within fiction: the scenes in black and white of the aspiring actress Elizabeth Short, reburying then murdered, in its tests of casting. This character, in its brevity, convinces more than the other % and peak minutes of boredom. All very regrettable. All very sad. So I like Sam Spade.</body>
</review>
