<review author="Caruco" title="La dalia negra" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film cold and empty, whose soul emerges from time to time and where the form prevails over a dispersed and dreary content. No doubt?The Black Dahlia?, version De Palma, desconcertará both to his detractors (many) as (few) advocates.</summary>
	<body>The obsession of Brian De Palma by the stairs, and the scenes starring Mia Kirshner, whether same a short film inserted in another major. This, most any movie fan reference, and a pair of beautifully planned sequences is the only thing that interested me in the new film from the director of "The untouchables".An operation nostálgico-cinéfila to revive the spirit of classic film noir of the 1940s, as fans, know adapts the famous James Ellroy novel inspired by the rugged case for the murder of a young aspiring actress, Betty Short (Mia Kirshner), nicknamed "the Black Dahlia" by a journalist.The convoluted plot, and all this is one of the characteristics of film noir, links with other sub-plots, full of sex and crimes, to give us practically of the development dedectivesco of the argument and force us to focus our gaze on the description of more squalid and the ambiguity of his characters. A material, at first glance, perfect for De Palma, who seems to take seriously this to "we", because it manages to let within minutes of projection of interest us for what happens on screen.Do do contributes mightily to this its? miscasting? ("allocation errors") in which De Palma, part of its turgid camera movements, is also a (involuntary) specialist. Remember this adaptation of "The bonfire of the vanities" with Tom Hanks, Bruce Willis and Melanie Griffith, where no actor seemed the proper character.? The same applies here.Instead, the styling of De Palma manifests itself in splendor in the celebrated level sequence which links the discovery of the corpse of "the Black Dahlia" with a shootout. And also in a tense sequence with the two male protagonists in stairs of snail (in the style of "The untouchables").Also surprised that (grotesque) flat sequence developed in house objective (as if the camera were the eyes of the own Viewer) entering the mansion of the Linscott and presenting us with their eccentric tenants. Remember that one of the few films, and the most remembered, entirely made in "subjective camera" was "The Lady of the Lake" (Lady in the lake, Robert Montgomery, 1946). do and this fixation of Palm down the stairs? These appear in abundance. Made in one of the first scenes that their trio protagonist, Kay Lake (Scarlett Johansson), Bucky (Josh Hartnett) and Lee Blanchard (Aaron Eekhart) meets for the first time at the foot of a white staircase.Here are a framework for static meeting and transition. Because then we will see that Bucky and Blanchard, former boxers of completely opposite characters, "fire" and "ice", become inseparable friends, are the police inspectors, and Kay, the wife of Blanchard, and one? femme fatale? do in version? light?, will come to form an almost idyllic triangle.The stairs, with a nod to "Vertigo" or the "The Battleship Potemkin", have turned to De Palma in a perfect space to create suspense and play fears, as the aforementioned sequence of tension with Bucky and Blanchard in the spiral staircase.But it also serves to display the barriers between the characters. As the scene where Bucky regards Kay while you stripping in her room, above on the stairs, (an "object" prohibited by the wife of his best friend).But the set is pure artifice. A film cold and empty, whose soul emerges from time to time and where the form prevails over a dispersed and dreary content. Without a doubt "The Black Dahlia", version of Palm, desconcertará both to his detractors (many) as (few) advocates.</body>
</review>
