<review author="Guille" title="Brokeback mountain" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Love, what is love, there is no vestige</summary>
	<body>I reaffirm my comments that I made in my blog about this film. On what is love, I saw nothing more than looks and sensations that lead the romantic vehicle along the routes of the passion. Passion and desire are components of love but just alone are not the love.The master Ang Lee, director of the film, wanted to pay tribute to nature traditional history in a bucolic environment full of stunning scenery. The intimate music for guitar and folk-country meet its task to move the Viewer on the other side of the screen.However this does not help turn Brokeback Mountain, a love story. Love is not a force of nature: the story of the relationship between Ennis Del Mar and Jack Twist proposed as the backbone of the argument does not evidence any sign of love.If we follow chronologically the story of friendship of the two cowboys, we firstly, that gets a normal coexistence between co-workers to a meeting without that mediate a process of conversations or emotional approaches to prepare what is supposed to be that it will be a love affair. We do not know what is falling in love, but a mutual attraction. Once already "known", each married a good woman that founded separate families. In those years he was not well regarded to be gay, but it was not compulsory to marry; they could you have followed singles, and maintain a great freedom to organize its meeting calendar. Repressive society forced them to marry? Since the first villain in the history of the western (1903) to Clint Eastwood, killer desperate in "The unforgivable" (1992), matrimoniar it or get a girl was not an imperative, even customary for the western legends.The thing is that marriage and family, and keeping sexual relations with their wives, each "x" months under the guise family are still seeing that will hunt.What most caught my attention is that in all that time none of the Cowboys never shows the slightest interest in the life of one on his wife, children. throughout the existence of the "beloved" is like a negligible break between each encounter that is sexual hinted from each approach that does not have an interpersonal Exchange which tell us that you there is something more than "caresses". Looks brilliantly performed by the actors are not telepathic conversation.The Cowboys want to be alone, without that none of the actual circumstances of the personal environment of each might affect those encounters so idyllic nevertheless evasion. In fact, things degrade when Ennis has to deal with his daughter when his wife leaves him. Jack refuses to his friend fulfills its obligations of father and "break". In addition, when Jack passes time without seeing Ennis makes his encounters with another subject. In short, there is sexual attraction and passion. The dramatic action of the play is the fight against wind and tide to move the relationship, which would be the romantic. But love, what is love that well could "seek the happiness of being loved", there is no vestige.Although interpretations of Heath Ledger and j. Gyllenhaal are excellent, the packaging is too caramel to be credible. Especially humiliating is the treatment of his wives, specifically soul, victims of a double life full of lies and contempt for their own family. In my opinion what truly subverts in this film is not the fascist genre of westerns, but what is the love of couple and family (the black beast of sesentaiocheros liberation movements).Finally, being indulgent with my own aesthetic enjoyment, this story is a romance with little love, much of telenovelesco (where the beauty of the heroines and the heroínos aim to justify any inconsistency) and that it smells too cazapremios. I do not mean to offend my gay friends, but I do not think that this film should become its paradigm of love story. So I still prefer Sunday Bloody Sunday (1971) by Schlesinger.</body>
</review>
