<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film by Guillermo del Toro is an absolute prodigy, a spell of one hundred twelve minutes, a climb to the sky of the fairy tales and a descent to the hell of the human soul.</summary>
	<body>Ophelia has a chalk that opens doors in the walls of a rural house which serves as a national detachment headquarters. Out in the forest, are the maquis and a maze with a Faun and the fairies. There is a captain of phalangists that, in reality, is a demon, though he shaves with delectation and mimo, is cleaned with exquisite cleanliness their command and listening on a rickety turntable ' COPLA ' boots. Ofelia's mother is pregnant with her second husband, the captain. The son next has it sick. A plant of Mandrake bathed in milk Ophelia placed underneath his bed can cure it. This remedy is confesses the Faun the girl back to focus on its true mission: pass three tests.In one test, there is a toad. In the two, a pale man with eyes in the hands. The three, a maze. The film by Guillermo del Toro is an absolute prodigy, a spell of one hundred twelve minutes, a climb to the sky of the fairy tales and down to hell for the soul human, contaminated by the barbarism of the war, but the fantasy of Ophelia, his world of happy insects and portals that awarded for game play happiness in another worldit its real and overlaps it in such a way that what happens in one just by modifying the events of the other. Del Toro she wears with master these two tones, the adult and the child, and not fracture can be seen in the narrative fluidity of both.The actors are in State of grace. We have not seen work so to Maribel Verdú. Nor to Sergi López. Ariadna Gil, in his brief role, borda his mother haunted by welfare and sacrifice.Alex Angulo, the doctor. And can not not mind to Ivana Baquero, the girl that was for Princess and is stepdaughter of Captain fascita: makes a marvelous performance. Guillermo del Toro has had to revisionarla seventy times (!) and that she cried in the same scenes in each pass. I will have been the last españolitos who have stepped on a movie theater to see, but I'll be also hope that many who before they withdraw it passes again through box office and very gladly leave the euros of rigour to return to feel the same emotions, the same pain, the same feeling of incontenida happiness. Imitar me, please.</body>
</review>
