<review author="Plissken" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cuarón has achieved a balance between message and show, so rare these days that it is mesmerizing. If this movie had shot her a master enshrined at this stage many already speak of classic.</summary>
	<body>2027: there are no children in the world. The initial premise of 'Children of men', directed by Alfonso Cuarón, us is not given in a sign type 'Star Wars', or by a voiceover, or the characters get to speak directly about it. Cuarón leaves the futuristic thesis of the original story of P.D. James is simply the straw that has filled the glass of a world so deranged as, for example, that in which we live. And it develops all the setting of the story from that final desquiciamiento. Countries razed, prey to anarchy. Laws anti immigration carried to the extreme. Terrorism threaten all kinds of people, perpetrated by the very Government both radical groups. Fatalism and desperation in people, who know that the human race has only one generation of life.In such an environment, Theo Faron is a disenchanted more. Official of the British Government (the only country apparently on foot), resigned to the atrocities that happen around. He has also accepted the world that he lives. But one day is "recruited" to help Kee, an illegal immigrant, to escape from the country. That day it will change your life forever, and you will awaken a consciousness asleep wearing too long.Admittedly, the proposal of Cuarón is a story simple and already told. But it is that this is one of those rare occasions in which the film has more through the world of the characters through the characters themselves. The plot seems more an excuse to carry the latest apocalyptic consequences, we have set the path to the human race. In each general level, in each panorama, we found so much information that it is almost unnecessary to push forward the story through the script. Cuarón has built a world so real that all they have to do the actors is confined to (envelope) live on it. This is the great merit of 'Children of men': not just part of a suggestive situation to tell a story, develops a world from that situation, and makes that his characters lead us through that world, giving rise to the history.As well, very convincing Clive Owen as the disenchanted Theo; effective Julianne Moore as Julian; vulnerable and emotional Claire-Hope Ashitey as Kee; and phenomenal casting of side, with Michael Caine, Chiwetel Ejiofor, Peter Mullan, and Pam Ferris at the head. In my opinion, the characters are always consistent with his nature, and when transferred ownership do with horror that unfolds before them; what some call feathering characters I call attach importance, at every moment, what is interested in it. And Cuaron is clear when the protagonist is that monstrous world that surrounds Theo paragraph Faron.El technical, simply flawless. Comparisons with 'The war of the worlds' are merecidas, because Cuarón, as Spielberg, plays the trump card to let the created world speak for themselves. Other films, such as 'V for Vendetta', playing dystopia without showing her, making the characters talk about how bad that is all, Cuaron hits to put us squarely in this reality, for let us escape by hairs in each sequence. The picture, the costumes, the art, the FX, make-up, form a whole in which the most amazing visions are possible, from the famous giant pork of the Pink Floyd flying over London until an assault with heavy artillery to a suburb of southern England full of insurgents and refugees.And mention apart the work as director of Cuarón, spectacular during the footage, but scratching impossible multi-level virtuoso sequence; Although I'll stick with an image that sums up the philosophy of the staging of 'Children of men': a bus leads to the protagonists, as long as the pathetic fate that immigrants may suffer in this world we see through the Windows of the same. Without underscores, without drawings. Only the world through the Windows of a bus.Cuarón has achieved a balance between message and show, so rare these days that it is mesmerizing. If this movie had shot her a master enshrined at this stage many already speak of classic. For me it is. A 9.5.</body>
</review>
