<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Like almost all the films Anglo-Saxon?Children of men? part of a fascinating premise, a pregnant woman in a world without children is enough to make any film walk. Cuarón helps it to talk about borders, exclusion and illegal immigrants.</summary>
	<body>I have to thank all the fellow bloggers, and also to the critics by having advanced one of the surprises that Cuarón was kept in the manga during the first half-hour: that the girl was pregnant. Least menos desvelador wakefulness that is to say that in the near future, in 2009, they are no longer children, birth and that the youngest man on the planet, for 18 years, just die in the 2028.Theo, the protagonist has ceased to believe in mankind. It enters the story because his brother directs the Ministry of culture and can get a safe-conduct to the girl. Ironies of the film, the bureaucrat is dedicated to save works of art within little anyone can admire what sense does the art without the human race? More sense to save the girl thing in which working everyone else, although not for the same reasons.As nearly all Anglo-Saxon cinema, "Children of men" part of a fascinating premise, a pregnant woman in a world without children is enough to make any film walk. Cuarón helps it to talk about borders, exclusion and illegal immigrants. The United Kingdom has become an impregnable fortress, the last bastion of civilization, a police state where the greatest crime is not having papers. Something similar to what actually is. The expectant mother has no roles. An NGO wants to use it to put an end to segregation. We learn to hate all those who want to use it because we know that the baby cannot be a means for nothing. Unfortunately for the film, was not the best way to defend the thesis of the creators.It has two flat unforgettable sequence. Childbirth is shot without a single cut, so either actress gave birth in front of the camera or to the child was an infographic creation. The second is shot in the middle of a powder keg. Clive Owen is moving between bombs and shots while the camera to separate from him, while thousands of things occur and destroyed buildings and cars. If you want to, one can have fun imagining what would have happened if after spending so much is wrong in a line and must shoot the plane again.</body>
</review>
