<review author="Bloody Will" title="Infiltrados" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Infiltrators can be catalogued as arrogance. Superb direction, superb script and superb performances.</summary>
	<body>If Martin Scorsese fails no statuette this year by "Infiltrators", I delete the Oscar. The magnetic influence that they get the films of this director, when it pleases, they currently have very few equivalents. We can say that a director x made x good films. "Scorsese confirms me after seeing this film that is able to be attributed the better film career of 50 years, and I am not exaggerating at all.""Taxi Driver", "Wild Bull" and "The Cape of fear" sat precedents that so chaotic and dirty way to rolling. "One of ours" and "Casino" are two of the five tips for Mafia perfection with the trilogy of "The godfather". "Jo, that night" is a nearly perfect comedy, and "The age of innocence" taught us that it can also be romantic. Gather all the best parts of this list and have "Infiltrators", a film that will not find any but.Stating that I have not seen "Infernal Affairs", which Scorsese has made a remake or version, or rather I dunno, because after seeing "Infiltrators" me has antojado a huge curiosity by its original Asian, which I doubt has the closest that the argument based. "I have the impression that Scorsese has endorsed more than any other film so left as mere anecdote.""Infiltrated" can be catalogued as arrogance. Superb direction, superb script and superb performances. Of "Gangs of New York" expected me more, but never like me at all. "The Aviator" also failed in the set. This film, where you remain more than two hours hooked to a story of cops and robbers with personalities and most spectacular gifts of recent times is so great why.The hstoria is the best microbial for the mind of the Italian-American director. Two guys who finish the formation of the Boston police, although one of them (Matt Damon) will use his position to alert major capo of the city, Frank Costello (Jack Nicholson), who looks like his father, of all the movements of the body. In turn, the other (Leonardo DiCaprio), it comes from a cursed family, must undertake the difficult task of being the mole within the ranks of Costello. His works entrecruzarán until that the situation only allows the unmasking of one or another.Let the main: Matt Damon signed his best performance in his entire career, and already I would empower Bourne of the personality and strength gives him his corrupt COP character. Scorsese has become a ca ** to which admire with all your soul, by the coldness that is his sneak, and persuasion that uses with his superiors. His final actions are consistent with his soul. Leonardo DiCaprio is sensational, and finally sees the word "Scorsese" on his forehead after the failed "Gangs" and "Aviator". Acojonado at times and uncontrolled in others, can say without any doubt that his best performance was pulled out the tite Marty. Awesome from beginning to end. Attention to the scene of the shabby shop. Scorsese 100%.Jack Nicholson is another world. A piece of son of ** those that Scorsese is only able to draw. Amoral, without feelings, without confidence, violent, sadistic and sarcastic. It gives the best moments of the film, both dramatic and comic. I see with the statuette in the hands, because there is an actor that has left so much this year. Worth the movie just to see him.The side left to become genuine pillars of action. Martin Sheen perfect, irreconociblemente special Mark Whalberg and Alec Baldwin in the best of his life: and give him a beating the ducks turn poli. A passivity."Infiltrators" the genus of the mobsters reaches its cúlmen, with shows that charge is Scorsese. Nasty violence but that can not stop looking at. Each punch on the screen is a bite of lips in the armchair, no one knows if by asco or desire to participate you also. And maybe an end of anxiety where you discover that the director does not have to be conventional. For what if it has never been. Long life whom you touch, that the King is Scorsese.</body>
</review>
