<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Scoop" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Allen returns to its origins. To his comedies disparate, with this universal humor that only the known transmit. We have one of the most characteristic of the director New York films. Laughs, suspense... and more laughter.</summary>
	<body>After the master 'Match Point', had been much speculated on the new film by the film genius called Woody Allen. You knew that it would be a comedy, with his new muse Scarlett Johansson and Hugh Jackman. And in London, clear. Result? Modern view of 'Manhattan murder mystery'. with some 'Match Point'. Allen returns to its origins. To his comedies disparate, with this universal humor that only the known transmit. We have one of the most characteristic of the director New York films. Laughter, suspense.y more laughs. If you have ever been disappointed with 'Match Point', then this is the Allen you were looking for. And if you had been fantastic, Scoop you seem simpler, but it will not fail you like.London again, for the second (and penultimate) time the chosen scenario. An acierto.si already Manhattan so loved, now will be the British city who do so. No one as this director know reflect a city, from within, translating that live and these customs. And this is probably the best film of Allen: combine a good script with the visual aspect. But we have a masterpiece? No. Difícilmente (that not impossible) a comedy can be turned into something as well. And then? The movie entertains, and long. Like, and pretty. Not only complies with its mission, but that leaves you with a good taste.Scarlett Johansson change log with a comedia.y meets. Note that Allen has done the script thinking therein, because there are several scenes (and the comments) which leaves for his showcasing. And when love is mutual, the effects are great. Hugh Jackman outboard his role as rico and gentlemanly English galán, although really you always have to do the same role. And Allen? When this filmmaker acts, always makes itself: neurotic over not being able to, but with phrases great. 'Scoop' will delight lovers of the filmmaker. And also of those who only seek to entertain themselves. That Yes, no hunting for the genius of 'Match Point'. It is not perfect. It is only a comedy, so you have to treat it as such. And not one any comedy: is Woody Allen. There is no more claim that making people laugh. And in this sense, Allen returns to get away. We can only hope to continue to do its own thing.</body>
</review>
