<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Martin has known as lend the Ember to its sardine, and based on an alien idea, has released images much of his obsessions, inclinations, inner demons, you philias and phobias.</summary>
	<body>"Infiltrated" is a great film by Martin Scorsese. And with those eight words I would already be all. "But, as the butcher would say, let's go by parts.""Infiltrators" is the update, the occidentalizante remake of an Eastern, "Infernal affairs", which, I believe, are happening in Canal +, but still have not seen, so we can not compare the original product with its North American version. Personally, I don't care of will emerge where the inspiration of a guionista-director when writing - shoot his film, provided that do it well and interests me, involved and excited both what counts as the way in which does it. "In the case that concerns us, since then, Martin has known as lend the Ember to its sardine and, based on an alien idea, it has made images much of his obsessions, inclinations, inner demons, philias and phobias.""Infiltrators" is a great movie that lasts two and a half hours, is filmed with luxurious means, but very well exploited and features a cast of actors to remove the hat. A cast headed by the sober and excellent Leonardo DiCaprio and Matt Damon, the counterpoint of the excessive, always unique, wonderful and unique Jack Nicholson and the counterweight of the very measured, solid and perfectly characterized MartinSheen, Mark Whalberg and Alec Baldwin. A great film that has many things to a devilish pace, although it has a bump towards the middle of the footage that lastra somewhat the story and, therefore, not allowing us to the great masterpiece that we were waiting; lacks a point to be able to celebrate the return of the Martin hard and great, of the best film of the last decades. Much written, "Infiltrators" isn't at the height or of "One of ours", the zenith in the Filmography of Scorsese, and, I believe, nor at the height of "Casino", fuller, more vigorous, better achieved.That Yes, "infiltrators" is, undoubtedly, a film by Martin Scorsese. Its subject matter, visual images, by their camera movements, treatment by the characters that has created, and especially by the impressive soundtrack accompanying the film, even though it has songs from the Rolling Stones, Roger Waters, the Beach Boys or the Allman Brothers, has found its best music discovery is the impressive song "I am shipping up to Boston", of the Dropkick Murphys, a band so wild as toughest sequences of the film, which mixed the céltico-festivo air of the bagpipes with a phrasing punk that bands such as Rancid, the Pogues and the Clash did not put a but.Yet I still have a lot of things to say about "Infiltrators". As I write about it, the strength of many of the powerful images which has shot Scorsese grows. So I'm going to make themes for a second review. As the striking end of the film, which connects directly with another majestic final of "Taxi driver". I keep a few thoughts on the figure of the double and the loss of identity and other things, that one could be defined as heretical, on the undoubted influence of television series "24" and "The Sopranos" in this excellent "Infiltrated", both in the form and in the background.PD.-Do not fail to review the four songs that the Dropkick Murphys have hanging in your site on MySpace. Pure dynamite! Starts with the film "I´m shipping up to Boston". and it continues.</body>
</review>
