<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Cache Escondido" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Exercise voyeuristic with plenty of prospects and amazing details</summary>
	<body>I understand those who think that this film is pedantic, slow, boring and dense as a potato puree. I recognize that the dialogues are irritating for what little they have, by supposedly banal. The picture is also completely naturalistic, touching the video look domestically, although without the temblequeo typical of the camera in hand. The pace is heavy, lethargic, without concessions, in a long, very outstretched footage and with surplus scenes. In addition, is not this a story previously chewed and not warns the least effort to accompany the spectator towards a message clear, towards a particular end.I also share the views that they accuse Haneke take as the starting point of his film the intriguing principle of "Lost Highway" of David Lynch. It is really so. In both, the protagonist couple receives strange tapes where they and their home, are recorded by a stranger. But it is also true that cache away immediately and takes a very different direction. Cache is an exercise voyeuristic with plenty of prospects and amazing details, which also has under his belt with enough virtues, so at least, so has other many spectators, including I myself, they have experienced a feeling different and interesting, a very rewarding and intelligent cinema session.Cache not invited or camela for free to the Viewer. It is not a story portrayed from the best camera angles, it is not a neon advertisement, or a plate of hot food. It is a peephole which can spy on. A peephole in the cold Street, which can look through from a little comfortable posture. The actions are not going to the grain. Looking at, for example, as the protagonist enters the picture, drop you a coin, is served a coffee from machine, awaits you, him slurp, goes towards the window, left again and reflects. But who spy through the window, nor receive a summary of the best actions of its neighbour opposite. Who spy shares silences, complete action, dead moments, moments of apathy, images that usually we did not observe the usual film language. The same applies here to the talks. We never find specific dialogues, information necessary or concise.Also the moments that one does not select or that you can not choose, never tend to answer all our questions. They may not explain everything, nor necessarily provide a response to each of our issues. And in this case, and only at the end of the tape, we can come to understand about what they have actually tried the two hours of film. I think that cache is on the naïve child cruelty. On the, often terrible and inevitable consequences of our actions throughout life. How you load with our faults, mistakes and sins and, how all these then passed on even to later generations. Cache talks about morality, fear, guilt and selfishness. It is a totally neutral social criticism. Exhibited items without position at all.I could also sense a kind of parallel message on that, so far, I have not found reflection in any other website. Perhaps because this is only a personal perception: (refrain from reading here who has not seen the movie yet) while the couple discovers the disappearance of his son, there are background images on television about the current disaster in Iraq. Perhaps there is also no fluke that co-stars are also of Muslim origin. But everything could be understood also as a metaphor, where the rich and intellectual Western star, punishes, betrays and truncated in the past the life of the poor, and at the same time, the future of his descendants, for later, endeavour ignore and underestimate the possible caused pain and claim a victimizing feeling. The protagonist feels terrified, bewildered, aggressive, when the consequences of his acts dot somehow safe and wealthy lifestyle.Michael Haneke ask us: who is the real victim? Perhaps the terrorists are part of our family. Perhaps we are the terrorists. Our precious lifestyle perhaps not the most appropriate, just not perfect. The protagonist is insensitive to acknowledge his guilt and not hesitate to mislead his own wife, lying without delay to their own people, to hide the information that could be blamed. Our society, our news, our television, nor doubt on lying, in not telling whole truth, to invite us to consume, lazy, and continue all the time that possible with this our "American dream" of selfishness and evasion. At the same time, addition, observe images of attacks suicide in Iraq, while for co-star, the only possible way to carry out his justified revenge is implying and making a direct witness to the protagonist of his suicide.Cache are invited to reflect, to think, and to change does not yield one iota to the Viewer. I understand those who only seems to them a superb ass. And above all understand to speak here of a masterful film. I can only say that I went to the game, staked and enjoyed very pleasantly.</body>
</review>
