<review author="José A. Peig" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It has one of the most impeccable finishes that you can see in the cinema today. Not only triumphs in the form, also in the background, and that is what the difference of products like?Children of men?. It was time.</summary>
	<body>Martin Scorsese has always been a great technical filmmaker and their contributions to the contemporary cinema usually no leave indifferent anybody, even having done works as plúmbeas and failed as "Bad streets" and "The Aviator". In particular, I recognize that they may not interest me too her stories on Mafia and gangsters, but its narrative strength cannot be denied.To begin with, "Infiltrators", at the technical level, has one of the most impeccable finishes which can be seen in the film, wonder Assembly, pace, a sober aesthetic sense in the framing and photo, in the form of focus faces, the action scenes, the characters who die and those that shoot, the alternation between those who are in the foreground and those who are in the background, the perfect coral structure that develops to perfection, precisely thanks to this Assembly that the various facts of a quite overwhelming visual and plot set connection.Because so it is, "Infiltrators" not only triumphs in the form, also in the background, and that is what the difference of products such as "Children of men". It was time. The characters are endowed with a poignant human dimension, overcoming the difficult challenge of going beyond clichés, to show moral ambiguity either a complete lack of scruples, almost a trap between the will to be and what the reality of corruption ends up revealing: a chaos in which no one is guaranteed the stability in a world not governed by laws and a sense of Justice, but by interests and desires of power and purely macho dominance, in which lying is a subtle deadly weapon. The male dominance drive is present at all levels, both in the vocabulary of the characters the meaning inherent in the story, its development and its devastating conclusion: that gives the last shot is that already from the beginning intended to sit Chair by dint of arrogance and foul language. In principle, the central theme of the argument consists in fighting between gangs and police forces, but the look of Scorsese on this universe of struggle between groups is much more ambiguous, hard and complex, building a universe with a few laws, apart from dictated by law and common sense: there is a dividing line between the mafia and the forces who supposedly defend the law: at the end, the acts of some and others are the same, everything is a same spiral of violence and interests, as evidenced at the point of final encounter between the two moles, magnificently interpreted by Leo Dicaprio (do still remain doubts, leaving aside her eternal childlike face, as regards its notable dramatic resources?) and Matt Damon. The rat who walks by the railing of the balcony, at the last level, comes to confirm us the fierce message that leaves us on the palate, the bitter aftertaste of a world ruled by "rat", regardless of if the costume worn corresponds to one or other side.</body>
</review>
