<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Wild and peppered with kid black humor, The Departed is the best tape cooked by the DiCaprio Scorsese society.</summary>
	<body>Scorsese returns to the streets with a brutal bloodbath of frenetic pace. There is no truce in this film where violence marks from the House of the New Yorker permeates all the footage. Backed by a solid cast in which DiCaprio shows that, without doubt, is one of the great (I must confess my reluctance with him at the beginning of his career) and in which Nicholson rein to its more wild histrionics, infiltrates (The Departed) have left you is a lesson of film rhythm, a display of mastery in the millimeter using narrative elements. About perhaps began to find some 'but', is may branding little plausible some sequences, although the result of this film (based on the classic crime film Infernal Affairs Hong Kong) leaves no why be magnificent. His argument proposes a game of 'topos' infiltrated into two opposing camps: the police and a band of Irish mobsters.The two protagonists we are presented schematically and effectively in a brief exchange of sequences in parallel. If to Billy Costigan (Leonardo DiCaprio) always you stalked the crime of Mafia family, Colin Sullivan (Matt Damon) environment, on the other hand, he attracted the world of crime from small in view of how easy that was to make money by the side of that environment. Both entered the Police Academy, but if Sullivan hits get you with astonishing ease, Costigan will pass by a via crucis for overcoming his family legacy and prove his worth as a policeman. Between the two lies the ruthless mafia boss Frank Costello (Jack Nicholson); Costello sponsored since childhood to Sullivan and had all kinds of dealings with the uncle of Costigan, another legend in the world of organized crime. Alone and decided to not to approach the environment following the isolated example of honesty of his father, Billy will be forced by their superiors (Mark Wahlberg and Martin Sheen) to infiltrate the Organization of Costello to help dismantle her. But his work will be constantly sabotaged by the Fink of Costello in the ad hoc group of researchers that goes behind him, his godson Sullivan mention aside deserves the role of Nicholson, unleashed as long not he saw in a role of sadistic, womanizer and amoral accomplished that, given his own biography of Jack, comes as a ring to the finger. However, I did not finish convince the love triangle between Sullivan, Costello and the psychiatrist who treats it, Madolyn (Vera Farmiga).The aesthetics of the levels or the choice of musical themes, with the repeated appearance of the Shelter Guimme of the Stones, carry the unmistakable rubric of the perfectionist Scorsese. Wild and peppered with kid black humor, The Departed is the best tape cooked by the DiCaprio Scorsese society. Gans of New York was halfway of excellence, but it is a notable film, and would rescue the Aviator I only them some aspects, such as the deepening of the paranoid mind of Howard Hughes. When asked machaconamente if this year you will be finally Oscar, Scorsese responds that he only cares that his work like the public to continue working on new projects. I think, because it seems easy to make cinema in these times in which the industry has resumed with force control of studies. Therefore, is to rejoice that Italian-born filmmaker stays in such good shape, because so may continue exhibiting his film wisdom in future projects.</body>
</review>
