<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not intended to be a science fiction to use film, but it has really lacked a little more risk, the director would have to have contributed something to his film rather than simply adapt a great book.</summary>
	<body>Children of men, is an adaptation of the novel by science fiction writer P.D. James, like the film, narrates the anarchy that has plunged the world, in the not too distant future (2027) result of infertility women and consequently the imminent extinction of humans. Everything from the eyes and experiences of Theo, an ex-activista which will be involved in a dangerous mission, almost without thinking about it, a mission on which depends the future of humanity. Clive Owen (Theo), manly actor that we have seen in other titles such as "Arthurian" or more recently "Hidden Plan", again to seduce us with its organic interpretation in this film. I have to say, that the weight of the plot falls on their shoulders and holds it very decently, I think it was not a role for any actor, it was the profile of a hero, only Clive could hold in their eyes the time and space while walking between soldiers supporting the mother and her baby, only he can achieve that lookthat says it all without saying absolutely nothing. As an alternative to Clive, Russell Crowe, would have been a good option.I must point out that the effects (see fair labor scene frames in which the child is dragged outside the womb of his mother, the realism achieved), are very achieved. All scenes of the war are shot in very elegant and real, difficult thing when war comes, that some directors tend to exaggerate and dramatize too much, making losing importance to other things. Tension is maintained throughout the entire film, with blows of reality. Although mixed notes of humor, the slap of reality again over and over again, waking you from a possible happy ending.Open final in which could guess metal laughter, come from the interior of a ship "Tomorrow", the standard of the human project which will return the fertility to women and repoblar치 our world, meaning, that finally the girl is brought to where it was intended to be carried and the Mission has been a success.Highlight the great results of the steady-Cam, although despite all positive to my particularly the film not just me convince. I expected much more than one title which has been in a "quite normal". Not intended to be a science fiction to use film, but it has really lacked a little more risk, the director would have to have contributed something to his film rather than simply adapt a great book. In the trajectory of the director, Alfonso Cuar칩n, Mexican cradle figure prominently, the production of el laberinto del fauno (curiously enough endings of both titles seemed related) recently and the direction of Harry Potter and the prisoner of Azkaban (that's funny, another adaptation), and "Y tu mam치 also", of which he wrote the screenplay. This occasion Cuar칩n, guioniza, directs and monta "Children of men" who before expectations has become a disappointment.I had fun especially, Michael Caine, with his "finger Buscar", I think that it has built a character that could represent the anti-hero, but since then very comical.</body>
</review>
