<review author="Silvia" title="Scoop" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite the shortcomings, it must be acknowledged that the New York director films outweigh the majority of comedies as regards quality is concerned and is logical that with so many movies out of your imagination, not all become masterpieces.</summary>
	<body>The new annual installment of the great Woody Allen is already from today on our screens, at the same time coinciding with the release of the DVD of Match Point. To then say that intellectuals do not have business vision.This time Allen abandons the drama and recovers its most comical classical aspect to which we are accustomed. But although some situations scoop reminiscent of other comedies of the director as a mysterious murder in Manhattan or the curse of the Jade Scorpion, the new film is years light of those hilarious comedies.In this case, the comical point it monopolizes the character played by the same director, who gets into the skin of a flamboyant magician a journalism student who helps solve a murder case. The character played by Woody Allen, far from causing laughter has the risk of falling into the constant caricature, a histrionics that can be tired for the Viewer. Similarly, Scarlett Johanson seems to sit him better the facet of seductive to the Strip.The argument continues to be a thriller, in this case tinged comic film. Sondra Pransky (Scarlett Johansson) is an American journalism student found in Britain visiting some friends. During his stay in London, he attends a magic show, where the magician makes him climb onto the stage to perform one of his tricks in which she should disappear. While Sondra is waiting to "dismantle", is visited by the ghost of a deceased reporter, which will give you the scoop of the year. The spirit reveals Peter Lyman, the rich and attractive son of a well-known British Aristocrat, is leading a double life as "Murderer of the Tarot", a serial killer who takes time terrorizing the country. With the help of the magician, Sondra begins to investigate the news and get together some evidence incriminating against Lyman. The more aware, more dangerous becomes research, especially when he begins to fall in love of the attractive alleged murderer.Despite the fact that as usual the Director the argument resolved without abruptly at the end, in this case falls into predictable, something which subtract interest to the film during his viewing. In the same way, dialogs, strong point of the director, are in this case rather loose except for some brilliant phrase.An aspect to be highlighted in the film is the lesson of good investigative journalism that brings the director in the film by the character of Scarlett Johanson. Throughout the film is show us that a journalist must or must not do to get truthful information. The student must make efforts to deeply investigate the murder case to demonstrate that it has an exclusive on the authorship of the crime.The Allen obsession with the subject of death returns to be present in this film, as usual, in a comic way. Death is depicted as a trip by boat captained by a hooded with Scythe. The director often ironize about death because in the background it frightens. In an interview with the Sunday of El Periódico de this same Saturday, Allen confesses: "I terrified aging, because approaching me death, which scares me." Perhaps that is why I River both of it. "I've always thought that as more fear gives something, funniest are the jokes you can do on this topic."But despite the shortcomings, we must recognize that the New York director films outweigh the majority of comedies as regards quality is concerned and is logical that with so many movies out of your imagination, not all become masterpieces.</body>
</review>
