<review author="Caruco" title="Infiltrados" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Just a good film that contributes little to the universe?Scorsese? or gender. Accept their status as mere entertainment and employs the excesses (too) easily.</summary>
	<body>Martin Scorsese goes back to the "bad streets", and if in "Gangs of New York", mid-19th century, the fledgling metropolis was a hotbed of Irish, Italians and native gangs, certifies that 150 years later, even Boston rather than the city of skyscrapers, things have gone worse.The spectrum of rivalries has extended to African-American, Hispanic, Asian gangs (or Eastern). And that "rats", struggling for their piece of the territory, not only walk in the slums but also also in the highest levels of power.Something is happening to ensure American film registration either in political correctness or in anger and more radical violence. The drama "Crash" already we submergía in the Tinderbox of tension of the city of Los Angeles. And curious is that another very recent film, tiny budget, as "Crank: poison in the blood", a sovereign stupidity or an oscuras parodies of the genre?, share many elements with "Infiltrators" in common: from a hectic pace, to jokes easy about sex, violence without limits, foul language, blood, Adrenaline and even levels of cercenadas hands.Clear that "Infiltrators" is Bill bright, his impeccable rhythm, the cast of bells and their quality seems beyond doubt.Essentially, he has proposed us the game of cat and mouse between two moles, one within the organized crime, Billy Costigan (Leonardo DiCaprio); and another, Collin Sullivan (Matt Damon), within the police. Do the two sides of the same coin, and the difference between the? valiums? that takes Costigan and the luxury apartment and the bride of your dreams that achieves Sullivan.Convincente is DiCaprio, which already showed in "The Aviator" its worth for tormented characters and who plays here a gift anyone who can settle at any corner or bar. And equally remarkable Matt Damon, very committed, which knows how to hide the State of spirit and concern behind his eyes. Although the heart will explode throbbing, you need to know to maintain the strong pulse! Do and I would say Costigan/DiCaprio.Un point apart is Jack Nicholson, as the? capo? Frank Costello. Or rather, the festival"Nicholson, who enjoys as a child expressing themselves in grimaces and uncouth language, hinting the sadistic tendencies of his character, and both with their luxury amiguitas diviertiéndose as atosigando demure priests and nuns. The same Nicholson escaped the control of the William Monahan, director, and screenwriter rewriting much of their dialogue and expand the weight of his character. On the other hand, Mark Whalberg becomes the true revelation of the stellar cast.Do separate Nicholson should be noted than most moments and most significant scenes of "infiltrators", included a sudden and bewildering final surprise, were already in "Infernal affairs" (here titled "Dirty game" for its DVD Premiere), the film? made in Hong Kong? on which it is based.If anything in "Infernal affairs" spent years for the protagonists and they were identifying more and more with its surroundings and colleagues, making more explicit the phrase pronounced the mafioso Costello (Jack Nicholson) on which a loaded hand gun there is no difference between who is the thief and who the police. "Infiltrators", is of course, imprinted with the label "Scorsese". A show of more than two hours and a half very entertaining, is visually attractive, strong, full of nerve, manly, and a lesson in mounting, Thelma Schoonmaker, Scorsese collaborator. Also misogynist worldwide which portrays. Only correct is the main female presence, Vera farmiga, whose best scene is an homage, in flat general short, "The third man".The original English title "The departed", more metaphysical (the only time the word is in a tomb), refers to those who "departed", those who have left us. Speaks of the dead, but also the living of their own hell in the city, and perhaps embarked on a journey without return.But it goes "more" to "less". The expectations raised before a great movie or a masterpiece not met. It ends up being just a good movie that brings little to the universe "Scorsese" or gender. Accepts his status as mere entertainment and resorts (too) easily excesses or a mise en scene designed to dazzle.</body>
</review>
