<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Infiltrados" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Solid, well directed, film their usual fluent narrative and the estilazo which is their brand for so many years. Scorsese appears to regain vigor, but certainly does not reach the height to which we had () spoiled.</summary>
	<body>It is seen that in the end, Scorsese always comes back to the underworld universe, whether Italian, as it has happened on several occasions in his career, or, as in this case, the Irish. "Infiltrators" is an libérrima version of a Hong Kong film (which are already two sequels, no less) in 2002 directed by Siu Fai Mak. The new history scorsesiana poses a double infiltration: an Irish gangster, who has raised almost to her breasts to a pipiolo, manages to put it in the "elite unit" of the Boston police responsible for the fight against organized crime. At the same time, this same unit, the more absolute secret, and with knowledge only two officers achieve infiltrate in the heart of the band of the gangster to one of their own. Both moles will begin to do his work, until the two sides realize that there is a traitor in their ranks, and begins the search and capture of "the rat", as curious and commonly called cops and criminals to their respective infiltrators. In this closed and stifling universe of traumatic relations between police and crime, Scorsese recovers part of the pulse that had recently lost. It is true that fails to live up to its great milestones in the cinema of gangsters (see "One of ours", for example), but also that it is a solid, well directed, film their usual fluent narrative (and used extreme brutality of his characters, is also true), and that estilazo which is their brand for so many years. Is the plot advancing complicating more and more for each of the topos, whose respective salvation must be, theoretically, on the fall of the other rather than their own, although things do not necessarily have to happen thus? It is true that some actors do not help much: Leonardo DiCaprio does not give the role, as much that to make every effort to try to be a hard guy; the same could be said of Matt Damon, to which a high-pitched voice to the Spanish nor can say it will help much. Nicholson is masterful, as it is usual with him, and that which is quite restrained; Interestingly in this case makes his character a little "in the manner of" Robert de Niro, the actor scorsesiano par excellence. In the rest of the cast making Sergeant first with a tongue for ever with salfumán sticks not a repeinado Wahlberg, nor nor Vera Farmiga as unlikely psychologist, when rather have paints and model gestures (throwing to spineless, is true?). Ultimately, Scorsese seems to regain vigor, but certainly does not reach the height to which we had () spoiled?</body>
</review>
