<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El diablo viste de Prada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is halfway between criticize the fashion world or defend it as artistic and cultural movement, changing the position of a scene to another.</summary>
	<body>If someone believes in this film can be a surprise notice that in the following lines you will find some slight spoiler on the first half hour.This is a rebellious girl (Anne Hathaway) that comes with a chef who is rebellious and somewhat Bohemian (and rebel) friends. The girl goes to a job interview in the most important fashion of the World magazine (the rebels of today are as well) where is accepted despite the fact that he knows nothing of fashion magazine or his famous and despotic boss (Meryl Streep).At first things not going great for her, and for some reason that escapes me, everyone insists on say it is blind while it is clear that it is quite thin. The case is that the girl begins to dress up fashion and suddenly the professional success smiles (even see thin, after it). As his friends and her boyfriend are very rebellious give back to their professional success demonstrating that, moreover, they are a little memos. The rebel girl will have to face all these problems and find itself (whatever that).This is the theme of "The Devil Wears Prada" (The Devil Wears Prada), film by David Frankel was presented out of competition at the Venice Festival of this year (the shame falls on them) and that has had some positive reviews. The excess of alcohol in blood during the projection does not help to appreciate a film and thus leave criticism out (that if those critics the had seen, of course, everything there is).The fact is that the film is halfway between criticize the fashion world (a pathetic world where appearance is the only important thing and that is, at least, partially guilty of depressions and problems of self-esteem worldwide) or defend it as artistic and cultural movement, changing the position of a scene to another.The film works as a very basic entertainment for a later silly in front of the TV but nothing more. The only thing notable is the presence of Stanley Tucci and, above all, Meryl Streep in a couple of scenes leaves a few strokes of his infinite talent to fill the screen and convey emotions even in the most hollow productions. I hope that we can see her soon in a film to its height and not in a product like this, which is the more conventional which can be seen today in theaters.</body>
</review>
