<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The intentions are good, perhaps the message you want to convey is better than the means used to do so, in other words, a good content in a poor continent.</summary>
	<body>Imagine that humankind already cannot have offspring, that no woman can get pregnant, that the human species is avocada to extinction in the strictest sense of the word; What are the reasons of such evolutionary disaster is surely wonder. Well well, this is what I did during the nearly two-hour that lasts the film, since at no time explained me why an important narrative element.Little good is also the catastrophic vision of European mainstreaming towards migrants, not because in a few years we will have a list of problems of a consistent strength arising from an overpopulation used to demand and not give (spin the neck towards the neighbouring France and be careful where to park the car), but rather by the terrible solution that will supposedly take Europe: the creation of concentration camps (did know you that in some European countries like Germany or Austria the fact of denying the nazi Holocaust is crime?). In Europe we are too sensitive to create a Guantanamo? Fortunately for Europe, fortunately for the world.So, if it fails based on history, it is unlikely that we do share the same. I doubt if the novel written by PD James clarified us some of these points, the truth I have not read, so I do not know if it is a mistake to drag from the literary product or has been a choice of the film team (though by what I have read in some editorial I decantaría by first thing)supposedly the writer did with intention to talk about the consequences of a fact and not the Act itself? trap (trap).The truth is that the sensation that leaves the layer is a penalty because clearly the intentions are good, perhaps the message you want to convey is better that the means used to do so, i.e. a good content in a poor continent. What I have understood is that the nature of human beings is quite sinister, you're already alleged camp of how bad or the course side of the good, because all are assumptions and, on many occasions, the reason lies in being more selfish, who long ago decided to think solo in appearance.</body>
</review>
