<review author="Plissken" title="The Queen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The who was one of the starkest enemies (film, means) Maggie Thatcher in the 1980s, again look back towards a week which for many people changed the concept on the monarchy altogether.</summary>
	<body>Stephen Frears has begun the century attentive to what's going in your country, is more, looking for keys to interpret the topicality of this island that was once an empire. 'The Queen' is good proof of this. The who was one of the starkest enemies (film, means) Maggie Thatcher in the 1980s, again look back towards a week which for many people changed the concept on the monarchy altogether.On August 31, 1997 died in Paris Lady Diana Spencer, ex-wife of Prince Charles of England. Worldwide, shocked, mourns the death of Lady Di. The press raises the altars to the plebeian Princess. The newly formed Government of the labour Tony Blair meets a hot potato which soon becomes showcasing opportunity to the young leader. And the Royal family? On holiday at Balmoral, decides not to modify your protocol before the death of someone who is no longer a member of the monarchy. Elizabeth II, since its more than fifty years of reign, decides not to expose his (or his son, or herself) grandchildren to the whirlwind media and detain in his Castle until that the news happens, fall who fall. The bad news is that, this time, what can fall is the very same British Royal House.'The Queen' will structured as a sober Chronicle that mixes reality and fiction, probably become known by the excellent interpretation of Helen Mirren, who composed an Elizabeth II of flesh and blood, as capable of driving a jeep or ride a pink gown by the sumptuous summer residence and take a pulse to an entire country. She is the center of the function, although the shadow of his deceased and hated ex-nuera is very elongated, and is so full of nuances his character is a delight see each gesture (tuned to the hands in times of stress), every look, every sentence. Far from the cliché so relieved historical character in the biopics, Helen Mirren is in the battle for the Oscar for best actress.And there is more. Michael Sheen is a funny Tony Blair, though sometimes too cartoonish. James Cromwell as the King consort, Sylvia Syms as the Queen Mother and Alex Jennings as Prince Charles comprise a berlanguiana Royal family, may the spirit of the old debt ' Spitting images'. Roger Allam, Mark Bazeley and Helen McCrory, latter in the skin of a Republican Cherie Blair, have their moments of glory in an ensemble cast.On the other hand, the staging of Frears is an example of elegance and simplicity, except at a few tremendous levels from helicopter of the grandiose landscape of Balmoral, the Queen's private fief. For my taste, they compliment perfectly with the rest of the proposal. Otherwise, neat and direct style of Leicester, in the service of S. M. Helen Mirren.Como negative points, in addition to the already annotated lightness of the character of Tony Blair, a certain lack of claw in Frears to finish the film. The upside is the hilarity which is the clash between the Martian family ("the planet Zorg", suggests an aide to Blair) and the rest of the world. And also on the positive side, a question in the air: it is the useful monarchy into a democracy, or is the same democracy which uses the monarchy to not succumb to a revolution?Smart, funny, sensitive and wise (sometimes too): an 8.</body>
</review>
