<review author="Mario" title="A scanner darkly" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apart from the obvious moral, transcends a narrative of false appearances, whether personal or otherwise. Do we really know the person that sleeps beside us?</summary>
	<body>If there are really able to surprise you films, there is no doubt that A scanner darkly is one of them. Although the vaunted technique of interpolated rotoscoping (a sort of tool that allows you to draw on previously filmed real images) is already, in itself, quite unexpected; the least one can expect, is to find later, with a film of ci-fi not abusing (hardly used) of typical special effects or more crazy action sequences.A scanner darkly is essentially a film of characters, that, behind a curtain of black humor, reflects on issues so common such as loneliness or the prestancia of a one-man code of ethics.The plot revolves around Bob Arctor (played by the bland of Keanu Reeves, that rotoscoping makes a great favor) an agent antivicio that receives the mission to spy on their own friends, consumers of drugs of fashion: the substance D. Despite serious doubt, Bob agrees to infiltrate the world of junkies, closely linked, in the context of the movie, the war against terrorism. Do at the same time that substance D is seizing him, Bob will fall in love with a spectacular Donna Hawthorne (here the rotoscoping spare) that the most famous cleptómana of Hollywood, gives life and live a thousand situations? between comic and terrifying - ranging from the paranoid delusion to the most absurd situation.Richard Linklater directs the film with ex officio and knows very well administered doses of humor, so in almost no time lapses of attention. The idea behind the script, as always when talking about something that has to do with Philip k. Dick, is very original and interesting, with a final surprise of the more disturbing I have seen lately in the film.An excellent aspect is the approach to the world of drugs. The film derides until exhaustion of the scene of the consumption of these, both of the ridiculousness of the fight against them as of the unfortunate complacency of consumers (everything is parodiable, but this is more, if possible) and here is where can we find the strong point of the movie.As factors against perhaps I was on happy rotoscoping what need there? Linklater used it successfully (at least as regards promotion) in his previous film, Walking life. But on this occasion I wonder if the modernilla technique does not impose as an obstacle to the development of the tape.Although, as I said earlier, the comic moments are well managed, the movie leaves the vague feeling that might have come across. The spectacular bis comic of Robert Downey Jr. and Woody Harrelson is not squeezed to the maximum, and each sequence gives the impression you need another round of measures to stay perfectly adjusted. On the other hand, the story of Dick may not give for a feature film (the film is quite short) and some of their sequences appear lengthwise without.Finally, and despite some small details against, I think that A scanner darkly is a dignísima and original work of science film current fiction. That, apart from the obvious moral (if you drugs much you're asshole) transcends a narrative of false appearances, whether personal or otherwise. Do we really know the person that sleeps beside us?</body>
</review>
