<review author="Queralt Antu" title="World Trade Center" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is in the smaller moments where the movie shines. Stone has made a very cautious and emotionally flawless movie.</summary>
	<body>Oliver Stone has done a very cautious and emotionally flawless film about two policemen, Jimeno (Michael Peña) and John McLoughlin (Nicolas Cage) who were two of the survivors twenty rescued from the rubble of the World Trade Center in the 11 9.Lo we do not see is a film by Oliver Stone, no smell sarcasm of previous films of this directorThere is no mention of political conspiracies (Platoon, JFK, Nixon) nor is the film (Alexander Natural Born Killers) exuberance that characterized their films. Although his film is almost never liked by all, few can deny American filmmaker bravery when choosing the topics of his feature films. Although on this occasion with World Trade Center Stone seems unwilling to move away from the political plots: "my film is not of the motives of terrorists, who were, or the policy of the 11-S in any sense;" "it is the story of two types trapped inside, and their families abroad".It should not be forgotten that the production is in charge of the Paramount Studio that has marked the film between conservatism and Christianity, have had well in mind that Stone has never been the ojito to the American right and has always positioned itself in his films. It seems that with this film Stone wanted to re-establish his career through the "flag". No mention of policy at World Trade Center, the police trapped under the rubble not damned, all Americans are honorable and very humanitarian; a few authentic heroes. Remarkable film, see a new vision of our most recent history, a vision more humane, more closely what happened in that damn date. The movie filmed by the great director of photography Seamus McGarvey (hours) we are pleased with a camera movement as part of the debris until the skyline of Manhattan, and it continues to rise up to a satellite which broadcasts the news that shook the world. Spectacular. However, it is in the smaller moments where the movie shines.Stone aims to show us the intensity of human nature in extreme moments. The Fellowship of two policemen who trapped, malheridos, by its instinct to comply with the call of duty.NY port station is named after the first impact on the torre1, all flock led by Sgt. McLoughlin, a policeman with more than twenty years of experience in the body and the savviest by having lived through the bombing of 1993 at WTC. But this time? not ready. No one can be prepared for an attack of this dimension. He and his team of four volunteers, including Jimeno (Michael Peña?) (Crash) are there to help. But how? The question becomes moot when both trapped under an avalanche of cement and steel, barely able to move in confined and bad space injured.</body>
</review>
