<review author="Caruco" title="Donnie Brasco" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Does purpose of "Infiltrators", Martin Scorsese... one of the greatest successes of?Did Donnie Brasco? was offer the daily activities of each? gangsters? do devoid of everything? glamour?.</summary>
	<body>With regard to "Infiltrators" by Martin Scorsese. When it seemed that had already said the last word on the mafia, in titles such as "The godfather", "One of ours", "Death among the flowers" or "The funeral", appeared in 1997 a piece performed by Johnny Depp and Al Pacino. Its title: "Donnie Brasco".It was based on real experiences of an FBI agent, Joe Pistone infiltrated a mafia clan of New York in order to gather evidence for the detention of offenders for six years.Gray and ordinary men that could very well described as authentic currantes of the craft. They had to earn a living day to day trafficking or stealing whatever, from jewelry to a simple parking meter revenue.Joe Pistone (Johnny Depp) will not reveal the secret nor his wife. And develop a paterno-filial sincere friendship with Lefty Ruggiero (to Al Pacino), a mafioso of minor and a born loser who padrinará the young Joe in a scene, located at the other side of the law, which is not without appeal.So the protagonist end up debating between loyalty to her partner and mentor (and with the possibility that he already is also "one of their own"), and the obligation to fulfil its duty as police. A particularly important dilemma in an environment where treachery is considered a crime worse than murder.Of course, it is a delight to see together to Johnny Depp and Al Pacino, or Michael Madsen as secondary. The script must be and the intimate music composed by Patrick Doyle, perfectly defines friendship.Directed by Mike Newell (four weddings and a funeral") has a leisurely, but fast-paced rhythm and a commendable strength in some images. For example, in the initial credit titles, and with the foreground in black and white of the eyes of Joe / Johnny Depp, suggests to us that this will become an observer cold and ambiguous.And the photography, off tones, not spread from monotony sinó that helps the history to be consistent with grey characters, which can be both mediocre as unsung heroes.(Note: only as dato, in reality, Lefty, author of a score of murders, could only be accused of blackmail!, but the film book you another "final").</body>
</review>
