<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Casanova" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Light film, without more pretensions than the entertain</summary>
	<body>The seductive legendary stars in this comedy of manners set in Venice in the 18th century, true to his reputation for compulsive flirt.Don't expect much of this premiere makes matters more shady and loving a real character around which was installed a curious mythology due to its reputation of inconstant and cynical vividor, too realistic for the time that he lived at the palestra.Giacomo Casanova began at an early age his flirtatious and adventures with various women, becoming popular over time as the prototype of lover and adventurer. The man gives way to the myth and that is where his relationship with Francesca Bruni, a liberal woman who publishes pamphlets on women's Liberation. But far from being a critique to religion or machismo, this light film, without more pretensions than the entertain and help us to spend the afternoon of Saturday, raises the entanglements that sustain the plot without making us think of them too.Francesca, the only woman who managed to resist his charms and shunning it articulates the entire plot of this go and come from costumes, duels, deception and racing with the serene background, if you press me, the best of this film in the line of "Shakespeare in love", although closer to the story somewhat anodina something to talk about. This title is precisely the same Director, which in turn has certain pearls in a filmography that is moving parallel to the the last film Hollywood, although something more elaborate: "The cider House rules" and "Chocolat" tape are the strangest of all the filmed by Lasse Hallström Swedish, but we must stick to Casanovadevoid of dramatic excitement and historical value.Arrivals up to this point we recommend adaptation of the book of autobiographical memories took place in 1976 Federico Fellini, with Donald Sutherland in the role of the seductive that felt the need to pursue at least one conquers women's day. Has this Casanova, that Yes, some points in its favor: a cast consisting of those always correct Lena Olin, Oliver Platt and Jeremy Irons, who surround to Heath Ledger in a performance flat but able to conquer to the female audience (after deal with Brokeback mountain), certain real images of the unusual Venice and a distant reflection from moral fringes, the logical vindication of women's intellectual equal. To highlight something.</body>
</review>
