<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There is no other than applaud, rejoice and enjoy this film orgasm called 'Infiltrators'.</summary>
	<body>Impressive. Shocking. Really great. Scorsese has gone. But calm, not as in 'The Aviator'. This time has given us not one, but many lessons of cinema, all within the same movie. Much else you applaud, rejoice and enjoy this film orgasm called 'Infiltrators' had expected this movie and there is no.There is a long list on Mafia films, and although I must admit that I am not the most staunch follower of these films, 'Infiltrated' well he could become a classic. current movies. The drama of the double life that carried out the infiltrators on both sides, their concerns and fears make the extensive (which not excessive) duration of footage not only located without eyes the clock or yawning, but rather the desire to know the outcome of the story grow while enjoying the excellent translation of frames, intelligently confusing.The development of the story does not only increase all the virtues that contains this Ribbon, to reach an end to rise to the occasion (although it can sin, typical in Scorsese's eternal). The truth is that one is left with the feeling that, even ending at any moment of the last fifteen minutes, it is a great finishing touch for excellent film. And it has all the elements to become the film of the year (with permission of 'Children of men'): it is not only the plot (what script!), it is the atmosphere, tension, the hectic pace, the rawness, the dureza.y, the performances, magnificent interpretations. A meeting of quality in the direction and acting work in bringing a complex story.It is time to recognize the merits of Leonardo DiCaprio, which does an excellent job, and who are thus definitely falls from the list of idols of quinceañeras. Jack Nicholson is as pez en el agua doing what he likes: be a perfect bastard, to their anchas.y in their efforts. Matt Damon shows all his skills (once again) and confirms why is someone to take into account. And or if it were, the Pleiad of side is splendid: from Mark Wahlberg to Martin Sheen, all make this film (or at least should) be remembered to gather so much waste of talent.Perhaps this the Scorsese expected the Academy to give it one (his first) estatuilla.y whether finally cannot thus be committed one of the greatest injustices in the world of cinema.This is yours, Martin.</body>
</review>
