<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great idea embodied in a grayish and sadder movie. Interesting, but all exciting or compelling.</summary>
	<body>The starting point of "Children of men" is absolutely fascinating. Instead of pointing to the end of the world in the traditional manner, by the melting of the polar ice caps, a nuclear war or a devastating plague that threatens to brushing your baby's gender human, part of a premise more simple and, precisely for this reason, more disturbing, more uneasy: simply, women stop having children. They begin to have abortions and to not become pregnant and, suddenly, humanity is doomed to an inevitable end for revocation.In fact, the film starts with the death of the person the world youngest, a boy of 18 years. The funny thing is that, true to its ancient history and when approaching the end of the world, human beings are especially prone to violence, blood, confrontation and war. Britain is plunged into chaos, with caged immigrants, in the purest style of Guantánamo. Everything is grey and looks dirty, neglected and abandoned.And in that world, a girl of color, a Fugi (tiva), becomes pregnant. And the various factions that compete for power in England want to flag of the child, which found its best champion and protector in an enigmatic and individualistic losing that endorses the mission to mother and child safe, taking them to a ship that would lead them to an unknown destination in has been launched a project between utopian and hopefuldo: the bad Humano.Lo project is that with so good mimbres and an exceptional cast of actors? Would Clive Owen, Michael Caine, Julianne Moore? the film is not so interesting as it should have been. Although the approach is fine and is formally shot with accurate dryness, there is too much salad shots, too hasty escape, too much action in a film which should rather have sucked and appealed to the reflection.Because, above, the action is not to be a prodigy of pace, precisely. I like the last battle, shot almost in the manner of a video game, with the documentary aesthetic of the news on TV. I like this kind of miracle, as everything that has to do with men, only lasts a few minutes. I like the end, without excessive forced dramatismos.However, throughout the central part of the film, the command of the fish and other I was boring and dreary, without claw, as fulfilling a mere formality between the approach of the story and its outcome. Incidentally, the infamous dubbings of the main actors is not contributing to make this part of the narration more attractive.In short, a great idea embodied in a grayish and sadder movie. Interesting, but all exciting or compelling.</body>
</review>
