<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Maleficio" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We are already tired of American charms, which seems out of Tennessee, Nebraska, Nevada or Wichita Falls there Poltergeist or possessed. It is what happens to them for having a very small story.</summary>
	<body>As one is innocent and is believed to foot juntillas everything what you have, I am assuming that this film is based on real events. Otherwise, deleted the innocence, annulled the sentimental goodness that everyone tells the truth, imagines what they have done is copy and paste scenes of the exorcists who there are loose and some other bad tape series B with curses and girls are shaking up in the bed, dams of some invisible form of the topical Mal.El haunted house dresses here of nineteenth-century haunted housea Gothic point. Nor have been careful in excess in adapt the era (19th century) with the history tells us. Predictable too, gives a nervous camera sweeps the screen and puts the nerves the patient spectator that at no time has been really pushed to show a minimum interest. At times I thought a premieres tv with a loose budget and two actors of posh (Sissy Spacek and Donald Sutherland), but none gives the story dramatic support because the writers have most enjoyed in Concatenate impact scenes which, in many cases, we are too familiar, instead of spinning the episode of spirits with amenity going and coming as I am pleased by the 19th century stairs.It has not been the such Solomon delete movie fan collective memory that grain which was dragons and dungeons, although the épila lose the brains by going to the cinema to its ration of petition fantasy. The badly burned resource of the startle thick: welcomes the idea of the horror film works based on noise and crackles of staircase, girls that appear and disappear in a swing or shots in black and white so we advise (is that we are idiots) who is the ghost or spirit or the sobresaltador of turn which looks and we, silly, really, look for their terrifying eyes. Everything already on the Asian.Tobe Hopper is more truculenta, but knows the subject better. Up a commanded as Sidney j. Furie made a significant entity, which is to say more or less the same, but without setting. Is that we are already fed up with American charms, which seems out of Tennessee, Nebraska, Nevada or Wichita Falls there Poltergeist or possessed. It is what happens to them for having a very small story: who must pull anecdotes and become national episode that outside its borders is absolute bullshit.We hope, anxious, Clint Eastwood and its flags of our fathers. This story is at least stronger: affects most everyone. I already do not want more fantasmadas.</body>
</review>
