<review author="Marta" title="El diablo viste de Prada" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The history is absurd, and the characters are completely unrealistic. Neither writer nor director had very clear what they wanted to tell.</summary>
	<body>I don't know why, I don't do more to do reviews that aim to convince me that "the Devil Wears Prada" is a good movie, funny, with good characters and an interesting critique towards the world of fashion, when it is not anything like that. At all. For starters, the history is absurd, and the characters are completely unrealistic. Screenwriter Aline Brosh McKenna has tried to adapt the novel by Lauren Weisberger removing important aspects and adding others that have no feet or head. Just to give an example: say your co-worker is a nasty being that you insult and you despise continuously. Let's say that you want you a lot to make a trip of company, which at last moment gets sick and your boss ordered you to go in his place. Someone would feel guilty? But what kind of 'moral dilemma' is that? Come on, man. Do not you learn anything in your work? The solution is simple: Ponte brand clothing and everything will be much better. Soon you will begin to respond to the phone safely and you can even look at your teammates, hitherto despised you, over the shoulder. The truth not I saw very clear that alleged 'criticism' of the film. And nor is it just the opposite; rather, it appears that neither writer nor director had very clear what they wanted to tell. Obviously I do not think that anyone thought this was going to be something inteligentísimo, but it is not especially fun. Many other comedies this style give thousand turns. Really, I fail to understand all those views that they praise.I agree. For some reason, seeing on the screen 'transformations in Swan' always they are entertaining, and Meryl Streep and Stanley Tucci quite raise the bar, but that fails to save the final result of "the Devil Wears Prada", which is flat, predictable and simplistic. Better to spend the money on the book, which, without being a masterpiece, is, at least, much more coherent.</body>
</review>
