<review author="Caruco" title="Las partículas elementales" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It cannot escape the long shadow of this novel of worship which serves as a source. It has eliminated many issues complicated treat or move in images; and it has sweetened the end.</summary>
	<body>Why not are we capable of being happy? Perhaps why not can meet all our desires, sometimes even contradictory. And in a world where we are exposed to the constant bombardment of stimuli, new products and experiences that "desire".The novel by Michel Houellebecq, become a bestseller, and an author already so loved and hated in France, pondered about it, on the morality of Western civilisation, sex, racism, and much more, in his work. All a punch straight to the stomach, difficult to digest, and practically inadaptable to the big screen.For this reason, "Elementary particles", directed by the German Oskar Roehler, cannot escape the lengthened shadow of this novel of worship which serves as a source. It has eliminated many issues complicated treat or move in images; and it has sweetened the end. This has made him swallow criticism (negative) readers of Houellebecq.En his pursuit of "reasoned knowledge" to put order to the chaos, it is Michael (Christian Ulmer), a scientist who tries to find "indivisible" and "impresindible" of existence. For your profession, and being a cold mind sumergida formulas and theories, sacrificed her love of children, Annabelle (Franka Potente), who will return to find with the passage of the years.The reverse of the coin is his half-brother, Bruno (Mortiz Bleibtreu), Professor of literature fully immersed in the crisis of the 40: "unique developments I have left to live are the enfernedades!". Do not "want" to his wife nor has developed its vocation of father.On the contrary, Bruno does have developed to maximize their sexual stimuli, continues with its practical onanistas, and never ceases to put face of enbobado before the details of the young and numerous female presences around him. Not hidden its racist tendencies, which will be translated in a book project where insults blacks ("one of the dominant sexual races"), led by the bitterness of his frustration.As aggravating, the past of Bruno is conditioned by different traumas, as the Oedipus complex for his mother, Jane (Nina Hoss), one? neohippie? that he chose to live in freedom without worrying about their children. On the particular trip to find if same, stops include a psychiatric centre as a nudist camp. But their destiny, if you make something, it seems madness.And trying to decipher the irrational equations of love and sex, Bruno, such as contrast and example, and Michael, as a biologist, will be precursors of a do progress? inspired by the utopian novel "Brave new world" by Aldous Huxley, which would bring us a "rational" society where love and sex have been indoles by cloning and artificial reproduction. Eliminating the evil we have the remedy. As well as these worrisome chemical and biological reactions of human relationships, but excitement and pleasure produce trouble and other more severe pathologies.This is, of course, a part of the irony of the novel conveys Oskar Roehler who however prefers to lead his film to a ground more recognizable and bearable for the audience as it is conventional melodrama, focusing on two love stories.It contains a correct narrative, as this sequence of the attempted seduction of Bruno to one of his students. And holds very good performances of Moritz Bleibtreu, which is able to keep a few first flat full of pain, distress and solitude; and Martina Gedeck as Christiane, the nymphomaniac who knows in the camp nudist and destined to become, so to speak, the love of his life for Bruno. And although its protagonists succeed in "happiness", it is probably not as her would have "liked". And this leaves us with one of those frozen smiles.</body>
</review>
