<review author="Caruco" title="Gracias por fumar" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An apology for the freedom and the right to choose, with an excuse, tobacco, which could be interchangeable by others.</summary>
	<body>Nick Naylor (Aaron Ekhart) is a man of angelical face and wide smile. However, it is also the most hated man in North America. Reason: is the public relations and defender of the (economic) interests of the tobacco industry. A habit, this the smoking, very, very badly seen by public opinion.In addition, Nick meets with a couple of friends with similar works: Polly (Maria Bello), Publisher of the sector of alcohol, and Jack ((Adam Brody), its counterpart in the spread of firearms among the young.) Themselves whether themselves as "the death Squadron" and are aware that their professions make them some rare bugs in the eyes of the people.To complete this fauna of characters is the staunch enemy of Nick, a Senator (William H. Macy) obsessed with his crusade anti-smoking. His new proposal is the force that totdas the cacetillas of cigars bearing printed a drawing with a skull and the letters "poison". And as a CODA, Nick nor can be considered a model of family guy. "He is divorced, although her son Joey (Cameron bright), sensitive and gifted, admired.""Thank you for smoking" is the promising debut of Jason Reitman, son of Ivan Reitman ("Ghostbusters"), adapting a novel by Christopher Buckley. Do their satirical content against Yankee society point a little against everything, and almost everyone: a double standard that dictates what is good and evil, radical politicians, media (double-edged weapon), tobacco employers only interested in selling their product?First and foremost is an apology for the freedom and the right to choose, with an excuse, tobacco, which could be interchangeable by others; In addition to advocating the need to educate more than to ban. Yes, tobacco kills, but you can also do cholesterol, pollution or cell phones.Thank you for smoking is a film absolutely recommended, but it is also harmless. The bullets fired, although accurate, do not contain enough lead. Too complacent and Nice, especially in its outcome. With the addition that is already weary this to hear that the protagonist does what he does because he is "which is better". Also reminded it us Yuri Orlov / Nicolas Cage as dealer of armament in the recent "Lord of war".It is of course a much smarter comedy that average American comedies and his argument traps with a twist included that leads us in the fall and public defenestration of the protagonist until its rebirth from the ashes.It exhibits good dialogues, replicas and ingenious situations. And there are notable secondary characters of those that leave footprint as the Marlboro man (Sam Elliott) whom her been diagnosed with lung cancer; or a recovered Rob Lowe as the Executive of Hollywood fascinated by the new fashion, i.e., anything that has an Asian design, and one of the exponents of this Hollywood dominated not by the artists but also businessmen.Do do some of the funniest moments come from winks to the? star system? as a divertídisimo mounting of photographs in black and white with classic and immortal stars (such as Marlene Dietricht and Cary Cooper) where smoking is has been replaced by other elements, such as treats or mugs! "" And interestingly enough I refuse not also to highlight an almost subliminal mounting: in one scene, the protagonist sitting on a plane is tempted by a sinuous stewardess offering you its services "for what you want" and then shows us a plane with the Obelisk of Washington. Phallic symbol indicating the State that will have been Nick after the offer.</body>
</review>
