<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Shines for his handling of the time: the boot platonically with Gimme Shelter, the Rolling Stones principia already where you going to go the abundant shots, brioso movies, movies with text, hypnotic film.</summary>
	<body>More than a film, is a return, a refund of the retirement trust. Gangs of New York was a spectacle as bombastic as ersatz on the beginnings of a city and the birth of their clans. The Aviator was a tour de force of dramatic, a biopic, skimmed hagiography of the glamour of an era and a character. Infiltrators is a tape sewn with the remnants of all the previous films of the Italian-American master, but the remnants are yours and this time he has made exquisite wastebasket with delivery, with very high flights and the result is amazing.Are not dealing with the masterpiece that was one of our own, which talked about the same thing, but it is the best tape, to my mind, this boring and weakling film year. Shines for his handling of the time: the boot platonically with Gimme Shelter, the Rolling Stones principia already where you going to go the abundant shots, brioso movies, movies with text, hypnotic film. Also shines because Scorsese is a fabulous stories counter: it has always been. What matters is that the events that make up the literary text are explained more clearly to the viewer and it is not thrown to a roller coaster of side stories who bring nothing to the story itself, a trilogy hongkonesa on gangs swept Asia.Para this shine, Scorsese not abused the soundtrack: confined to go dropping songs while they are subordinate in excess images as it had in Casino or the already mentioned one of our or as masterfully does Tarantino. Attention powerfully an Irish theme attacked by a band of hardcore metal that sounds like two or three times in the central part of the film. The primary attention of the director is starting from a ground zero of the feelings, thus referred you in press conferences that we saw on television. That ground zero emotion allows an epic metaphysics, a bewildering exercise of absolute resignation to any religious reference. God does not exist. It is not. Left at all and now look them from above, extremely attentive to the disagreements of all these types his whimsical hand threw them into the world.Scorsese is obsessed by violence in the human condition. Physical violence and also the most complex level of semantic violence. All of his films (this one in a very high level) are configured as vehicles for research of that obsession. The end (which not is here revealed) makes everything in place and takes the phrase with which opens this fantastic guignol of truth and the deception. "Before", it has a voiceover at the beginning of the film, "had the Church, which was a way for us to us". And now only campa rampant at the Mafia with their household God, with its tiny demiurge, who is a Jack Nicholson made a cabronazo perfect, histrionic, supercharged ego, hyperbolic, but compelling and daunting. The perfect father.Do not close this opinion without mentioning Leonardo di Caprio, a great actor that has been already recognized by directors such as Spielberg and Scorsese, that require constantly. You ache to see onwards these folders glued to the chest of the adolescents of Institute exhibited, flirty and Ladino, the face of Leonardo when he was the King of the world. Now have to Orlando Bloom.</body>
</review>
