<review author="Victor Omar" title="The Descent" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A true gem filmed with intelligence and passion</summary>
	<body>The film focuses on a practice that increasingly has largest number of followers: the escalation and, more specifically, caving. Inside a cave, safe and familiar environment for fans to this activity, becomes a claustrophobic microuniverso for those who are not: canyons, tunnels, underground caverns of twisted layout that must be overcome with effort and skill to reach the other side and see the light of day again.Not to mention all kinds of animals, insects and vermin living in the dark, non-action human. "The descent" follows a group of six women using their free time in a unconventional way, to add excitement to their normal and pleasant lives.His previous expedition went to the rapids of a river, which ended in tragedy for one of them. And now, a year later, they become reunited, this time to explore a cave system little known under the Appalachian mountains, in the Unidos.Pero States things start to go wrong when a landslide blocks the only way of input/output. They will then have to dominate your panic, and their personal conflicts, to find another route. Which won't be so easy when they discover may not be alone in the dark cave.There are two distinct in the film parts. In the first half we know the city girls who are looking for adventures in the caves of the Appalachian mountains and accompany them in a relaxed first decline, which allows to better know each character; in the second part, the events become in tragedy, the tension gives way to a rapid and violent survival horror in which "something" mortally stalks women.The great skill of the filmmaker is trying each section of the footage a radically different way, perfectly maintaining the pace from beginning to end and used the upheavals and the violence with success. The director and screenwriter Neil Marshall ("Dog Soldiers", a notable unpublished Opera prima by these directions), has done an excellent job in both fields.Its libretto is composed of interesting characters and dynamic relationships, the actresses transmitted without any effort, showing facets of their personalities without excessive dialogues. Now, however, no mistake, the film is far from original.In fact, it is not hard to find traces of other jewels of the celluloid of terror, from the design of the creatures, inspired in equal parts in Murnau Nosferatu and the Gollum in Peter Jackson, in his bowels (and never better), until all the spectacle of carnage directly imported from the 70s of the great masters gore: Romero, Wes Craven or even Tobe Hopper.Lo that occurs is that Neil Marshall orders and stimulates the batidillo ideasconcepts and tributes, so compactly that the result, far from the postmodern aesthetic to which we are unfortunately so accustomed, approaching its creation the shores of the classicism of gender.An atmosphere of genuine heart, a creepy makeup which demonstrates the physical convinces more than digital when it comes to scaring the Viewer, a disturbing as few sound treatment, and even some timid but convincing Conatus to grant some psychological depth to the characters, complete the litany of virtues of "The Descent", a film that, if enjoy horror moviesthey are not caused by donating blood and are tolerant with dilated starts in excess, they should see by Decree of law.We have one of the best films of terror for many years, with surprises, shocks, characters very well defined and an unforgettable final. Visually powerful and frightening, is vision must-have for all fans of horror B movies made with quality. A true gem filmed with intelligence and passion.</body>
</review>
