<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Yo soy la juani" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Urban drama of a generation of young people who are very lost in life. You have not found me a wonder, but I liked.</summary>
	<body>Instead of the usual nonsense of beginning, I will tell you that the film has a soundtrack that I loved. It gives a rhythm to the movie without it this would lose a lot. Do you both cost the rest of directors give with soundtracks? To highlight, as a curiosity, which includes a song by Juan Manuel Payo, none as know, than that is very funny. Then much hip hop and dance for everyone.The film is about the Juani, a girl of about 20 years who lives wanting to be an actress, but burdened by life in his small town. He has a boyfriend lover of tuning, macho and possessive, which restricts him part of their freedoms, which she did not finish see. His parents are prototypical and an example of how she will be in the future. Her friends live obsessed with worldly problems, as to not remove them the groom, if her suck or not or if you want to put tits. And this trafficking, a girl which seeks to escape his future.The truth that not found me wonderful, I liked, but I think a movie introduction. I.e. actually happens nothing at throughout the film, we have a character and when it seems that something may happen, the movie ends and us calls for a supposed sequel. Then had weird things, as that it made me very long, not be if I got bored or because they are too much data for my battered brain. One thing that I was shocked much, in youth reflecting Bigas Luna is that neither drink nor take drugs. Spend the day fucking (I was unfortunately was not the case) and with the tuning, but they drink or smoke or anything at all. And this has seemed bad, very far from reality. Then, the actors I liked, even the Canto del loco, which comes very well the role.In short, an urban drama of a generation of young people who are very lost in life. It may seem that the film is the spirit of a girl, but that is only in the synopsis, then the thing is derived in other topics. But I liked. This Spanish film if I like.Besitos.P.D: One for the young girls in balls, one for the soundtrack and one for the movie, right?Pd2: do really today's youth spent the whole day with sex? To it return me adolescence right now.</body>
</review>
