<review author="Vsancha" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film friendly, sincere and fun but at the same time hard, macabre capable of moving from a smile to a laugh easily, a story of a few losers winners.</summary>
	<body>Its simplicity is its beauty, many will say that it is one film about dysfunctional family seen thousand times, but little Miss Sunshine has something else that makes it special, something difficult to explain, but you catch the end of film. I insist on that little Miss Sunshine after seeing her leave you a certain sense of let-vu and that may it seem to many films we have seen previously, but has something special that makes during the entire duration of the film so you spend really well, a rather nice time that with the passage of the minutes and the end is a feeling which increases and after seeing her I firmly believe that it is due to his peculiar characters that conform the family Hoover, a mother struggling because everything is perfect within the family nucleus, a father that is dedicated to selling methods of self-help being a total loser, the uncle who tried suicide, teen asqueado by what surrounds it, which has the largest Idol Nietzsche and does not speak to achieve its goal, the grandfather that gives you heroin and maintains a peculiar and enchanting relationship with his granddaughterwhich is the to be presented to the beauty contest on a crazy journey will be involved all members of the family. The film is very appealing aesthetically, with a very colorful picture and an elegant address in the debut of the couple of novice directors Jonathan Dayton and Valerie Faris. The actors that give life to all and each of the members of the family are great, stressing over the role of the small Abigail Breslin and a brilliant Steve Carrell. It's a film friendly, sincere and fun but at the same time hard, macabre capable of moving from a smile to a laugh easily, a story of a few losers winners. A kick in the mouth to the American dream, to the desire for victory and the cult of beauty, an ode to normalcy and a film that reminds us what subjective is something like the success or triumph.</body>
</review>
