<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film hard, very hard. Prodigious fable. Accurate portrait of a time and the nature of the military who, through a coup d ' état, dictatorially ruled the country for nearly forty years.</summary>
	<body>It is curious to see how, for very trite and exhausted that it seems to be a theme, just always getting someone with the talent necessary to give a new and innovative approach. That is, precisely, what did Guillermo del Toro with the Spanish civil war in "El Laberinto de el Fauno".The film is a tale with two parts well differentiated, a realistic and another fantastic cutting, better integrated for what at first glance appears. I say it because the most obvious problem of the film would be little integration between the imaginary world of the protagonist and the real world. I could not help feeling that problem to see the movie, but like I said, after thinking calmly I have come to the conclusion that it is not as serious as it may seem. An example: the adventure of the protagonist with the banquet which cannot touch (magnificent tribute to "Alice's adventures in Wonderland") takes place just when she is punished without dinner by Captain Vidal (a Sergi López who would represent the monster come-hadas in the real world). I think a second and attentive viewing so that it may be necessary to do justice to the film, but for now, we continue talking about it.The work of direction of Guillermo del Toro is brilliant. Its way to introduce the themes, characters and details (the knife, medicines, keys) integrating them perfectly in the story placed you in the Group of elected globally in terms of narrative capacity.If those virtues were not sufficient, del Toro appears to be a wonderful director of actors that extract a few outstanding performances of all of them. Although Ariadna Gil and Ivana Baquero are fine, I would highlight a few magnificent Álex Angulo and Maribel Verdú in two endearing characters of those with which it is very easy to identify. And, above all, Sergi López spread its shadow throughout the film and composing an anthological character. Nothing in the film is more scary than his gaze, his movements, his obsession with the clock of his father or the coldness with which it is able to perform the most cruel and barbaric acts imaginable.In a movie with a fantastic component so marked, it is always important to the work of the team of special effects, art direction, sound, makeup, etc. Even more so in a tape of this kind which, to the fantastic slope, we add a realistic component. As well, this film demonstrates, once again, that in Spain can check movies with a finish so perfect as any Hollywood superproduccion.Film hard, very hard. Prodigious fable. Accurate portrait of a time and the nature of the military who, through a coup d ' état, dictatorially ruled the country for nearly forty years. All this and more is "El Laberinto de el Fauno". For me, so far, the best film of Guillermo del Toro.</body>
</review>
