<review author="Hartigan" title="Yo soy la juani" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is probably one of the least personal films of Bigas Luna, more commercial, and why declarademente because it is, so far, which I liked most of this author.</summary>
	<body>After a good season retired from the world of 100, Bigas Luna returns with Yo soy Juani, what we might call a "generational portrait" of suburban kids (and if I entrecomillo it is because things are very relative). Juani is a bold, decisive and talkative girl who lives in a neighborhood in the suburbs of Spain somewhere together, her panda and her boyfriend Jonah. Curra Juani from cashier while waiting the opportunity of becoming an actress, while the possessive Jonah does not want to let her go to Madrid to make a casting. Between, they entertain with tuning and the route of the cod (or what Bigas Luna seems to understand why). The sudden break with Jonah carried Juani to revolt and try to get if I sleep in the capital, where you will discover that not everything is as easy as expected.If something surprises of this film is that it has two clearly differentiated parts that look like two completely different universes. The first is which is based on young people in the suburb and its "culture": tunnig, racing, bakalao, hip-hop, graffiti, tattoos, sequins? A so exploited batiburillo today which seems provide anything new. It seems as if the producers would have seen The Fast and The Furious and had said: "why not make a Rodeo version they like young people?". Without further encouragement to me classist, there is only a class of young people who can feel identified with showing the film. They are often recognized in the film: they come late and by torbe's couples, sit in the background and engaged throughout the film and make stupid comments aloud and addressed with who tries to make them shut up. If Bigas Luna aims to fill the rooms of these boys, who adhere to lose the rest of spectators. Still, does not assure that our Jonathans and Jessicas are entirely satisfied, because the action is not much (there is a surreal race of brides with their boyfriends handcuffed to the hood of the car, but the actual images are replaced by a video game) and the music does not stand out (hip hop is decent but Moon strives to resurrect the cod of Chimo Bayo everytime you can)(, his authentic fetish from ham, ham). That Yes, there is sex and "beautiful" people (do though how bad you feel the close-up Dani Martín?)The second part of the film, in which the Juani and her friend the Vane reach Madrid, completely changes of tone. After giving a consumer binge pretty woman style, Juani is put hands to work to try to fulfill his dream. And here comes the surprise: the film isn't badass fairy tale which seemed from the outset. After the rush of adrenaline reaches realism: the Juani has it difficult. Discover the tail of unemployment, garbage work, asked English, meet pretentious managers, chuleador Publisher, the whoremonger footballer. And it is at this time that reveals the true Juani, already stripped of all his bravucona and vulgar aggressiveness: in his determination to get until the end but also in their principles and their dignity in that it is not prepared to anything and that, unlike the Vane that he only wanted to please you boobs and take advantageIt is better that the world around him, is someone that you may feel tenderness and sympathy.Veronica Échegui is a discovery. It has a special beauty that reminds, opportunistically, Natalie Portman. Like several other characters in the film, however, suffers from syndrome out of class: and it seems that the writers have gotten with a tape recorder in a nightclub and then it have remixed everything so you try to sound juvenile and desparpajo. So when you drop pearls as: "you do not I eat the head, you to my me eat pussy", sounds like the impostado that you can imagine. It is only in the second part, stripped of the artificiality that demanded the first Juani, which is really touching. Dani Martín plays surprisingly well as the cocoon of Jonah, a real big kid bobalicón. It is true that his physique not accompanies (your supplicant air gives you the look of a beaten dog) but well could become an icon of the youth of neighborhood, as Juan José Ballesta, if it is that we need more of truth. The rest of the actors stand out or have an opportunity to do so.This is probably one of the least personal films of Bigas Luna, more commercial, and why declarademente because it is, so far, which I liked most of this author. However, let me say in conclusion that the telepromoción that makes this film is truly shameful. Not only of the film itself (the Juani dreams in their epileptic delusions movie website.) (Literal) but to all kinds of brands and even a Madrid department store which are practically part of the film. Attention to the pot of Cologne using the Jonah: it is the case of "product placement" plus scandalous has ever seen in cinema, not because it is blatant but by the place in which the "product", in an erotic outburst, is "placed". The Juani not it makes him laugh. Who writes, either.</body>
</review>
