<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Infiltrados" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It tough, dry, vibrant and intense, very intense. A lesson in cinema from a master that many retired prematurely.</summary>
	<body>The outcry is unanimous: Scorsese has become. I dare to correct this clamor: the great Scorsese has become. The other, the very good Scorsese was not gone. The Scorsese who has returned is the big occasions. Which is able to count in the first fifteen minutes, merced to a frenetic montage that lapses do not at any time, a history which would give to another movie and that defines us a few characters in accurate way, with the precision of a surgeon which we were accustomed. It has become the great Scorsese and that is something that deserves to be celebrated.Remember that the film is a remake of "Infernal Affairs" (entitled on dvd in Spain "play dirty") and on its synopsis only say that it is the story of two infiltrators, in the police and the Irish mafia of South Boston. As you can see it's a police thriller and as such the film is a marvel in which everything works: the tension, the impressive pace, how to shoot the shocking scenes of action. All. "But I have said that it has become the great Scorsese and implies something else.""Infiltrators" is a reflection on the truth and the destructive power of the lie, the loyalty and the paths we must confront to keep. Scorsese offers us a Treaty on the sense of duty through the history of some young people become police officers. Some simply to carry pistol and others by the authentic meaning of the plate.Addressing the great screenplay by William Monahan, Scorsese exhibits all his talent and with him his entire team. Special attention on relentless Thelma Schoonmaker mounting and the soundtrack of Howard Shore.Punto and apart to talk about the actors because they are all Oscar. What happens is that effective veterans such as Martin Sheen and Alec Baldwin are eclipsed by a Jack Nicholson who is more Nicholson than ever and that, for those we love, i.e.. His voice, his look, his ability to know when exceeding and when not, has made him a legend of Hollywood.A his side some of the best young actors of today: Mark Wahlberg, Matt Damon and Leonardo DiCaprio. Although all (especially the latter two) are they leave, I'm going to emphasize in a DiCaprio that a gap between the large, thanks to performances as immense as it is gaining little by little. We must bow to the talent of this actor able to tell with your eyes an entire universe of inner anger, containment, hatred, love or fragility. A more than deserved nomination for an Oscar for this role could be waiting for him. What more to say? I strongly recommend you to see this film. It is hard, dry, vibrant and intense, very intense. A lesson in cinema from a master that many retired prematurely.</body>
</review>
