<review author="Hombre Lobo" title="La matanza de Texas: el origen" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is one of the worst films of terror that we had this year, from its memez of script up to the obvious shortcomings of talent of a director to know the reasons for which this saga has worked completely.</summary>
	<body>There is a whole range of options when choosing the arguments of why the Texas Chainsaw Massacre: origin (2006) is one of the worst films of terror that we had this year, from its memez of script (that adds absolutely nothing to the universe created by the original Tobe Hooper) until the obvious shortcomings of talent of a director to know fully the reasons for which this saga has worked for more than thirty years, to say nothing of shameful greed of a producer (Michael Bay, who more?) that seems willing to milking this cow until the last drop. However, the most overwhelming reason to discard this film is its unrestrained arrogance in trying to explain the origin of something that did not need to be explained in the first place. The tape of Jonathan Liebesman (prequel to the remake of the 2003) solves this with a couple of empty phrases which allude to the child Rodeo in the hope of giving birth "icon of terror" self-conscious and blatant.And worst of all is that, as in the as it was the case with his previous film, Darkness Falls (2003), the first minutes of Liebesman are not at all bad: a dirty and uncomfortable sequence in which we see a woman giving birth in the middle of a slaughterhouse to a deformed child. The child is obviously our friend Thomas Hewitt, who will later grow to become the architect Leatherface. Thirty years later, when the closure of the slaughterhouse has ordered economic death of the people and our friend and his family are left without their main source of income, he began the massacre itself. These first minutes, in which the character of r. Lee Ermey (no doubt the best of the film) "becomes" sheriff Hoyt and does his declaration of intent family never go hungry, it is the highest point of all the footage, just before the tape is released into a tailspin to the slasher territory and shamelessly go through each of the clichés normally attributed to him. However, in this case such self-consciousness is even more pathetic, that as this one prequel (occurred three years before the release of Marcus Nispel) is known from the first frame how is going to end. Hence any emotional investment one can make the victims characters is, entry, wasted. The film then becomes a festival of excesses of free design but with pasta, conceived and executed as a vulgar geek-show prefabricated for the average subscriber of Fangoria and anyone wishing to basically completely banalized offal.At first you might think that the original Tobe Hooper was little more than that, but nothing is further from the truth. Apart from the fact that its excesses were genuinely original beyond by 1974, the original film based his horror not so much blood (which wasn't much) but the portrait of the America people refused to see: one of a backyard full of ignorance, poverty and excessive violence. And still, nothing of what was in that movie was free. This prequel remake throws all of that. An example makes it more clear that none: the scene in which the protagonist is tied to a Chair and forced to witness the Hewitt family dinner scene that will no doubt know all is a direct reference to the original film. As well, in the original scene that made sense and raison d ' être, while here it has none, is merely a pop reference first, and secondly of a sample of free sadism by the characters. I could give many reasons most of the repetitive, predictable and unlikely that is each of the sequences of the film. It violent? Certainly, but that is no longer any merit in a genre where Rob Zombie, Alexandre Aja and Eli Roth have become names known to all. The Texas Chainsaw Massacre: the origin is totally bobalicona, superfluous and useless. Pass it without any remorse.</body>
</review>
