<review author="José Córdoba" title="Infiltrados" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Catch from the first minute, it flows like no, with a direction and mounting vigorous and effective, fleeing downtime and unnecessary scenes. Martin once again shows that nowadays you can see good movies in Hollywood.</summary>
	<body>Lately I am getting tired of reading the mantra that creativity in Hollywood, there is running out multitude of sequels and remakes, etc. The trouble is that many times this comes from the feathers of the most famous critics of the country, who seems to be that they do not remember that practically since its inception film has nourished second parts and remakes. To cite only a few examples: King Kong met several sequels, including the son of Kong, as well as Frankenstein and many others. Ben Hur of Wyler and the ten commandments of De Mille, are two remakes of films of the silent era. And would continue because examples there are thousands. Not worth the remake Asian movies Hollywood-style, because in the early days of talkies also made similar things, and shoot the same movie with other actors to sell in other markets in their language. What the current situation is not anything new.Also I noticed one thing, is that the same people that Miss the remakes pests silent their reasoning if they are signed by directors of their liking, such as Martin Scorsese. All this comes in the wake of infiltrators, the new film by American director. It is a remake of the Asian film internationally known as Infernal Affairs, thing indicated in all the criticisms and comments, often stating things like that surely the remake is superior to the original, without having seen the latter. I can not make such a statement because I have not been able to enjoy this film, well actually is a trilogy, but I can say one thing and the Scorsese film is an excellent film, one of the best I've seen this year, if not the best.The story of two infiltrated the mafia and the Boston police, catches from the first minute, due to his devilish pace. The movie flows as any in a long time, with a direction and mounting vigorous and effective, fleeing downtime and unnecessary scenes and that despite a duration close to two hours and a half.The cast also magnificent both the protagonists and secondary. Special mention for Jack Nicholson to even become threads and histrionic as always gives us with an indelible scene that shows all your Oceanside experience cameras. It is the scene in which accuses the character played by Di Caprio to the topo of the police. In addition the Scorsese wise, who had lost to the film cause for several years, known stay in second place in that scene giving Court both Jack and di Caprio, very well maintained by the type.The script maintains interest throughout the film, the characters are well drawn, and side including, understand their feelings, their motivations, not being redundant or sobreexplicativo, an evil of many American thrillers. Perhaps the plot of the love triangle is a little blurred, but I guessed that it is because many scenes have fallen in the editing room, along with the high sexual burden of the character of Nicholson, which finally is more intuida than shown. As usual in Scorsese music in the film is dominated by pre-existing songs, some well known, giving little pitch for the original score of Howard Shore, on the other hand, nor knows to find the tone and is even annoying in some scenes, something that was already happening in his score for the previous film, the Aviator. just saying Gangsters and Scorsese would be enough to make everyone run en masse to see the film. If that isn't enough, then I would add strong leadership, a precise script and actors in State of grace. This film returns to prove that nowadays you can see good cinema in Hollywood, even being a remake.</body>
</review>
