<review author="José A. Peig" title="Un buen año" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Here is heard, from beginning to end, gnashing of predictable, trite, rehash, topical, schematic, plumbous. A very simple story with some very simple resources.</summary>
	<body>The truth is that it is irritating - but that irritating muuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuy - spend two hours watching as harmless as this product. I say harmless because implicit and explicit you intend to claim certain things and wants to communicate a well-intentioned message, and hence put the stop by Mannerist of the matter. Often smell. Or often pile of shit, should I write with knife fingers instead of the calm tapping with which I am about to comment on the last film by Ridley Scott (I think is the same that made the incredible "Alien", the very interesting "the Duelists" or the "Blade Runner" classic, but I'm no longer sure of anything). Let the truisms and move on to something else, butterfly, it looks that has milk the affair.Story about a materialistic banker (man, clear). History on a child cuatro-ojos with an air of gilipollas integral (because what are educating the sacred rules of competitiveness, will not take all the blame and leave a margin for its pristine innocence) that it reaches adult and turns into a consolidated comprehensive asshole (I do not mean with bad faith, I simplifico a little things to go more quickly). They spend a few quarters of an hour, will occur a few graciosillas things, a little league, takes any reprimand, relive his childhood, has a moment of doubt, just the movie and integral asshole remains asshole integral but not so much. Gets a bit of the fold with risk to stay out forever (because the good aunt that has been caught not for less, go) and see the other girl taking a bath of grapes.Sometimes, in cinema it is possible to make a good movie with a script or a schema of ideas is summarized in three sentences, but here is heard, from beginning to end, gnashing of predictable, trite, rehash, topical, schematic, plumbous. A very simple story with some very simple resources. We have a character that goes from a point A to a point B, but apart from that the Viewer already knows the end (because it is a story that have told us the million times), the character not runs on its own, but that he is trapped in his predictable cliché. There is no progression, there is the more minimal ability to make credible the character played by Russell Crowe can choose the other option. Because it is a character, as I have said, without life, without this dimension of the human real. This doesn't cause both a bad script, but the same idea which part: Mannerist, giving and predictable. And if level script not to throw rockets, because there is no where cogerla.¿Hay subtlety?. No there is dramatic force in the "transition" from the central character?. No (or not many). Is a comedy of manners with "bodacious" which exercise aperspectivista from a pattern of crystalline and smooth realism? No. (I hear chuckle) photography, staging, the music, they provide some enjoyable time (and the assholes that salen.brrrrrrrrwww). There who want to save her attending these technical aspects (and testosterónicos), as they have done with the futuristic truño of Alfonso Cuarón, but where no there, there. It is sad that even large makers are falling into the same garbage. Or will they were right that, already for quite some time, say that Ridley Scott is and has always been a bluff. What desire I have revise Blade Runner.</body>
</review>
