<review author="Caty" title="La tierra de los muertos vivientes" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More than a horror film is a sign of warning to the society</summary>
	<body>After many years, George a. Romero (who revolutionized horror with his film "The night of the living dead"), again with a new twist to his idea of the creatures than the rose to stardom: the zombies, and this time, taking on their side all the technological advances that the never had and helped quite this new delivery. Its protagonists the zombies are still slow, but so wild and butchers as always were in the hands of this director. Unlike the current films of the genre, Romero films are much more visceral and violent death is something more painful and more frightening, and that is one of the greatest merits of the director.In this installment, the Earth continues ever more dominated by zombies, and few humans who still resist, are confined in cities, which have become major fiefs markets by walls electrified and defended by armies. In the Centre of the city, in a luxurious Tower, are the rich, living isolated from the poor, who live close to the walls. Supply for these cities (food, clothing, etc.) is carried out by highly trained and militia armed, in surrounding cities dominated by the dead. but things start to get complicated when one of the undead begins to reason, and initiates a kind of "revolution". What has changed with regard to previous films of the director is the degree of maturity of Romero, their dead are not just a few wild human flesh eaters, they begin to unite as a social class, who decides to fight, leaving advance only by issues of instinct, moving forward objectives. They learn to use weapons in their killings, making them more dangerous than they already were.Within the militias, have the person concerned Cholo (John Leguizamo) and the honest Riley (Simon Baker), which have completely different conceptions of how treat the zombies and about his own life in the city: while that Cholo dreams of moving to an apartment with the elite, Riley thought to flee to the North, where the man lived not ever and therefore free of undead. but on two of them, the character more interesting is developed by Dennis Hopper, of Kaufmann, owner of the tower where the rich live and which controls everything. This character represents the role of the economic elites and rich in contrast to the gross and severe reality of poverty and the misery that the vast majority of the world has to live. Phrases like "your will never be one of us" (this Cholo when he tells her that he wants to buy an apartment in the Tower) are perfect examples of how companies and countries try to mainly to the most poor.My conclusion on the works of Romero is that the man is not destroyed by the zombies, but by situations that originates the same human being: the deaths of the film are the result of acts performed by the same man and that happens in all films of the director. The proportion of four zombies portrayed in the film by humans is a sign that men are having an absolute success in his intentions of self-destruction. The main message is that we are immersed in a constant "bestialización", in a process of individualization ever more absurd, where on the other hand, the zombies become one, going to live in society.The land of the living dead is more than a horror film, is also a highly politicized speech and a sign of warning to the society and the directions it is taking.</body>
</review>
