<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="Un buen año" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>There true classicism in?Do a good time?, the speed with which moves history, the simplicity with which everything is displayed, how effective their dialogues, its more than good performances.</summary>
	<body>2006 Is coming to an end and there are many bad movies that have been released this year, and I have no doubt that was even released some more. We have also seen some great movies and I have not doubt that we will still see some more. Already I will speak at the time, as I did last year, the best and the worst that brought us the 2006. ?A good year? It will not be in either of the two lists, but if we did one in which only we appoint welcome films that convey the feeling as be happening a short holiday, you can film Ridley Scott headed the list, and even may have been the only one.For which this endorses Scott is simply one of the best directors of the past 25 years. Since that he started directing, in each decade has left us at least one masterpiece. Is also true that it had blunders and leg fat, because things like?The O´Neill Lieutenant? they have no name. Lately we are accustomed to see him directing blockbuster mastodónticas result of the huge success of?Gladiator?. Still, from time to time is has taken a breather for directing "smaller" as in the case of the maja films?The impostors?. Do now, after failing Orlando Bloom would be able to convey emotion, and before embarking on the most ambitious?Do American Gangster?, Scott is taken as a minivacaciones in every way to give us a piece of small good cinema without more pretensions than the make us feel good. And it succeeds.History the have seen a thousand times, or maybe more. An important London Executive hated by all due to his financial successes, receives the news that his uncle has died. As it is the most direct heir becomes the owner of everything that his uncle had: a large house in the French Provence, surrounded by vineyards. A place that is not going from years ago when as a child Summering there while he learned valuable things with his uncle. There is something more but already you the you know, and do not want to be the culprit of gutting you the predictable end. That Yes, no hagais case of the trailer, because if there is one thing that doesn't ever have a trailer that is the way in which a director addresses a particular story, its way to direct it.Scott realizes that not counting the greatest story ever told, something that other directors not taken into account. Even aspires to be a great movie regardless of the argument, and is in the absolute lack of claims where the film exits completely victorious, aided also by the impeccable style of a director to known chemical meaning the word cinema. Already one of the characters says: what is the most important thing to make a comedy work?, the pace. Scott met with more than, the pace of the movie is perfect, and to us we know in advance what is going to happen not get bored ever and continue with some interest until the end.An interest not found in the history that are telling us, but in the form of filmmaking by Scott, who performed here her most unusual film, and this is the strangest thing of all: the more atypical film of Scott is a completely typical romantic comedy. But we maticemos, we must always be qualified. The film is not a comedy in any rule, that make us laugh out loud. In fact, as much we outlined a smile and nothing more. Romanticism Yes there is, but not too load the inks or becomes ñoño, although that will depend on much of what they consider the Viewer as a geek (does there are beings who believe that?)The bridges of Madison? (is ñoña). And what does get the film is infect of joy that give off their images, although without reaching exceed us of course. That record again that we are not talking of a great movie. And it is this joy and the form of address of Scott so that we leave the room satisfied, especially if we have entered thinking that we were going to see a truño of three pairs of noses.Somehow and bridging the gap, this film reminded me some classic films today already forgotten by 99% of humanity and that saves some similar, although not precisely plot. There true classicism in?A good year?, the speed with which moves history, the simplicity with which everything is displayed, how effective their dialogues, its more than good performances. And that makes someone that makes the difference between this film and another of similar characteristics: Ridley Scott.Como have said it is not a great film, its lack of pretensions will benefit but also harms him, to which must be added one history rather than manida, and something really important: the absence of comical moments of truth. Suggests a few but never end develop completely, and that rather disconcerting. It is as if Scott not wanted that the spectator riera, that he does not remember this film as one of those where you've not stopped laughing and then you forget. I think that he has partly succeeded, but on the other hand we are left with the feeling that perhaps a couple of good jokes not him would have been bad, and even the film he would have won it.With regard to the actors say they are all magnificent and incredibly natural, as if they carry portraying their characters throughout his life. Russell Crowe is a simply amazing actor, and the fact that only has an Oscar seems unfair. Here a little crush see him in a role not dramatic, but there is no doubt that knows to move through the film like a fish in water. Albert Finney leaves less than one would like, and it is clear that the veteran helps you achieve a great interpretation, his character is charming. As is that of female potagonista, Marion Cotillard, a francesita that can stop with the mouth open to anyone. Also leaves Freddie Highmore demonstrating that it is one of the best child actors of today, their moments with Finney are the best in the film.A good film can draw a smile from ear to ear and achieve that we want to go to holiday France even if it is only a weekend. This for me is enough. Paraphrasing the singer Luis Moro in one of his multiple cinematic references, I don't have great stories, me is enough to make me feel good. Scott's is not a great story (its default), but makes you feel good (its success).</body>
</review>
