<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Scoop" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not the masterpiece of Allen, but that does not matter so that the result is a fresh, fun, comedy that fulfills its duties and that makes us to stress that we we have one of the best directors of the current panorama.</summary>
	<body>Returns the great Woody Allen, as every year, following its successful "Match Point". On this occasion occurs under the arm with "Scoop", a comedy that is a mix between "Manhattan murder mystery" and "The curse of the Jade Scorpion".The argument is quite simple: in a magic show, the great Splendini (Woody Allen) choose Sondra Pransky (Scarlett Johansson) to do a trick. During the same, the young Pransky (which is a student of journalism) appears a famous journalist, who has just died, and gives it a world first: the murderer of the tarot is Peter Lyman (Hugh Jackman).From this point Allen and Johansson become nail and meat when it comes to investigate the alleged serial killer. The director of "banana" is an expert in the comedy, and us here makes it clear that their situations, dialogues and other events we are more fun. It is appreciated that have chosen himself to embody the great Splendini, as it is a privilege to be able to see him on screen, and unfortunately in his previous films not we had been able to delight us with their presence.Again it embodies a kind of endearing with which we are identified and that you take affection in the first moments of the film. His connection with Johansson is almost perfect, and this time can enjoy the great work of the actress, very beleaguered after "The Black Dahlia", and that in these areas, and/or under the tutelage of Allen is fine and shows that apart from being pretty is good actress. "The third protagonist is Hugh Jackman, who more than anything is limited to portraying the son of one of the best English families, with the consequent game of glances and smiles of a handsome, rich and strong, type something that is not difficult to achieve.""Scoop" is not the masterpiece of Allen, but that does not matter so that the result is a fresh, fun, comedy that fulfills its duties and that makes us to stress that we we have one of the best directors of the current scene and of all time.</body>
</review>
