<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Yo soy la juani" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The best of the film undoubtedly Verónica Echegui and Dani Martín, as well as the aesthetic that presents us, including scenes at discos, overprints of sms are sent the protagonists, tuning meetings, and the discovery of Madrid by the two friends.</summary>
	<body>Bigas Luna returned to the screen with "Yo soy la Juani". History of neighborhood in which the protagonist has craving for overcoming, there comes a time in your life that needs take a radical turn and change everything that surrounds. Their environment, marked by the marginalization, with a father who want to expropriate the House, which usually drunkard is and mount at Jamborees, as being a mother who decided to take care of her husband and start a family rather than luck as a singer, a boyfriend (Dani Martín) that despite desvivir by it, does not mean that it is a Gulf and put the horns have tried naturally contributes to this. To all this we must add that Juani (Verónica Echegui) works in a supermarket and that what he wants is really becoming an actress, and unless you do something with his life is going to become a reflection of his mother, wasting few opportunities he had, and with the consequent remorse for not having tried. After deciding together with his best friend and leave his neighborhood to move to the capital, Juani will realize that achieve their dreams will not be as easy as she believed. This is what presents has Bigas Luna, that Yes, supported in an aesthetic characteristic of the world of tuning, and the most junior, where often the protagonists can be confused with prostitutes, because of their outfits, and where the boys are having fun making races with their highly modified cars. Then it presents a world away from all this, where reality becomes harder, and show us the difficulties to achieve our goals.The best of the film undoubtedly Verónica Echegui and Dani Martín, as well as the aesthetic that presents us, including scenes at discos, overprints of sms are sent the protagonists, tuning meetings, and the discovery of Madrid by the two friends among other things.</body>
</review>
