<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Scoop" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The argument is not interesting, actors are outlandish and not think, or make you laugh and already known jokes like Woody Allen since starting to smell like the wagons of the Madrid metro in rush hour.</summary>
	<body>When one you have always said that he is a genius, it should come a time in which one believes. And when one is believed to be a genius, the arrogance and high-handedness be obscured by the objective view of the quality of a work. Something similar occurs much with the so-called liberal professions and, specifically, with particular virulence in the world of cinema. How many actors know that his major contribution to the camera is the teach bait? And how many directors, forgetting that your product will be distributed in a film and not in the Hall of his house, room are left embelesar by the compliments made by pseudointelectuales vassals?This preface is a case in an attempt to explain how a course director of the quality of Woody Allen may have done so excessively boring movie as a Scoop. Honestly, isn't this one of my favorite directors, but the fudge I witnessed a few days ago in the film is of considerable dimensions.To start the base is not very good that the plot isn't interesting (a student of journalism receives from the more beyond the tip-off about the identity of a serial killer), this idea is taken with too much linearity, so much that half of the movie you know what will be the end.The actors are outlandish and not think, or make you laugh (in fact, is something that has always done Woody Allen; let us not forget that in addition to believe a good director also believes a good actor, because presumably see a man so ugly with a so deadpan face going to cause a lot of laughter).All this is accompanied by well-known jokes like Woody Allen already start to smell like the wagons of the Madrid metro in rush hour. If we mix all these elements in a Shaker we will obtain a result poor, boring and of dubious quality, or what is the same, Scoop.</body>
</review>
