<review author="Calaf" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Very notable film, which critics elevated to the altars, and I am sure that like much to the public in general, even if only to see the impressive performance of Jack Nicholson and above all to Di Caprio is immense.</summary>
	<body>It seems that movies are encouraged and is full of interesting proposals. The Black Dahlia, children of men, El Laberinto del Fauno, Scoop, Copying Beethoven, or which took me, the last of Martin Scorsese, who after his fiasco with the Aviator returns to sonar for the Oscars this year. And it would not be surprising because it is a very notable film, which critics elevated to the altars, and I am sure that like much to the public in general, even if only to see the impressive performance of Jack Nicholson and above all to Di Caprio is immense.A small synopsis, to know what is going, which reveals nothing of the plot (but is good to read it), because it is what we have nothing more to start: a young policeman, Billy Costigan (Leonardo DiCaprio) in the city of Boston is infiltrated a criminal organization with the intention of ending the head of the local mafia, Frank Costello (Jack Nicholson). At the same time, another policeman, Colin Sullivan (Matt Damon), is part of the unit that aims to put an end to the mafia group. The police not suspect that Sullivan is a mole of the own Costello.Yo compare this Scorcese's Casino. If you liked the style of Casino, you will like this without remedy, but if one did not convince you, can the script you end paying. With the style I am referring to dialogues, transitions, the way raise the scenes, pace, characters, the level of violence, etc. what liked me? Leonardo Di Caprio. Spends the entire film with a face of crazy that it reflects the anguish of their situation. And above all, not let it eat at levels with Nicholson, who is also immense, although that is less surprise. In fact, like all actions except Matt Damon that I do not just believe. I also like how the plot is closing slowly, as if it were a funnel which ends with the expected duel. The use of mobile phones, history key is also very intelligent as well as songs that will sonando.¿Y why not I liked? Violence, verbal and visual. I went with the aforementioned Casino, who arrived at a saturation point that bothers me. It is clear that the gánsters are killed, and speak by saying many tacos, but I do not know, also found me it noisy, and a tad long. Total, which is worth seeing, even if only by actions, and a clever plot, although it still does not convince me at all Scorcese. A. 8</body>
</review>
