<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Yo soy la juani" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps his anticipated absence of solemnity render it more dignified: perhaps. Rayana in the tacky, I am the Juani will like (and much) to teenage audience that identifies with the Rosary of relating kitsch.</summary>
	<body>Long Spanish Cinema left the brush and dandruff, brutal uncover and extruding of disco to win international recognition. That the post-war film was a tiny amusement that played the hunger and forgot the rigors of the Franco regime. As always generalize it is counterproductive, not him we stole some masterpiece (Bardem, Berlanga, Neville) or we take at face nothing. Our glorious transition brought other sketches and produced tapes where most happily campaban the epidermis that we never saw. And little else. Bigas Luna, which fits in the verismo Italian style of a Ferrari or customs of the early tapes of Tinto Brass box, although a little less accelerated provocative born in that section of our cinematography.Moon cinema contains the seed of the stale neo heritage and, at the time, a dramatic content more thick, deeper: his characters are always clearly identifiable, they have their house label. From the thuggish Javier Bardem gold eggs or ham, ham to this decisive and meteoric Juani to his particular stardom, Verónica Echegui recreates with impressive naturalness. Everything for a dream, might say. The Juani leave their neighborhood, their marginality and choked in Madrid. Here is the best part of the film: that dive in the malls in the easy life to the Pretty woman in the Archetypes of the city and the Juani lumpen stumbles, of face to face, dramatically, with the ilk more meanest. Bigas Luna is able to photograph this world of the outskirts; He always did and always did so with passion. Cod (excessive, in my opinion) is missing and the new icons of modernity: tuning, mobile phones. This salad of vicissitudes of urban clans are puts an aesthetic of MTV music video and we guarantee a more ample box-office because Bigas Luna did, reluctantly, his best impersonal film: which is more hence its plastic universe. And in the background one sees Bigas Luna as a plastic artist, rather than as a storyteller. Images shape the text: rather than the reverse. The absolute evidence of this artistic consciousness makes that, occasionally, not worry of what tells runs out (huge) opportunities that expand to each frame. A director of long length, usually stay in a shorter distance, but distance from others that less amazed with the colorful and icons of the Mediterranean and castiza-total Spain, give the size in a thing nor give in the other.We can not expect Bigas Luna of the total film: never has been given, except for the ages of Lulu. Does with dedication and with impeccable style their trade, which is to make us see their dreams, their rarities, their vices. Once complete male Hammerer (Bardem is his alter ego), has now agreed to dump its imagery in the female domestic, painting a perfect, priceless Juani. Out of this portrait, which borda, the film is short, easily forgettable.Perhaps his anticipated absence of solemnity render it more dignified: perhaps. Rayana in the tacky, I am the Juani will like (and much) to teenage audience that identifies with the Rosary of relating kitsch that decorated luxuriously footage. As to the tenor of the producer, if the thing goes well second party (Juani Hollywood), we will have to go making us the idea that for summer we will have a Juani New Yorker, hocicando its provincialism in the Windows of Tiffany's or looking for gigs in a pizzeria in the Bronx. Everything for a dream.The best, their amounts receivable graffiti and this complete, anonymous, Juani emerging new discovery of this polisher promises amateurs. Oh, and the surreptitious idea that creativity is born in the outskirts and is then transported to the Center, that copy their models and sells them as theirs. This idea is not new: you only have to see current advertising or how the language we use comes from Street, the suburbs, they are imposing to acquire status of habitual use, blessed by the SAR, but that's another story and this is a page of film, and not of semiotics.</body>
</review>
