<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="La prueba del crimen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fast-paced film, full of action and dialogues that engancharán to the public in his armchair, making that they enjoy so far in which Kramer and theirs out of the top hat the latest tricks.</summary>
	<body>Attracted as many others by Quentin Tarantino in the poster advertising, I started to see "The proof of the crime" without having almost information or news about the film.The truth is that the new work of Wayne Kramer is irregular. When you go to see you have the feeling that you have cheated, because the script is very fake, liar and made for the Viewer. The truth is that it is a great mistake, because if once seen the movie you get to thinking about her and turns that has, the truth is that it breaks down enough, let alone completely, and is a shame because until then history hooks you, and above all leave you surprised with a sequence that is simply brutal, and not by what comes to see, but it is itself and for showing us what is able to make someone (in this case a pair of unbalanced mentally, that they deserve other descriptions that I am going to omit).Paul Walker leads the cast and will be who has to be behind this proof of the crime. And it is none other than a gun with which have been killed by a corrupt police officer. But let's go by parts. Joey Gazelle (Walker) is a gangster, Member of the Perello family, and while they are in a shady, they are surprised by members of the police. With this similar scene to the climax of "True romance love" starts the hectic day of Gazelle, after killing Tommy Perello to one of the policemen, he gives the gun and asks it to dispose of it. As it has to be, but there would be no movie, the character Walker ignored the order, so coincidentally the best friend of her son is the gun and flees after using it, endangering the rest of characters, that it is essential to recover the weapon for various reasons.Cameron Bright interprets the frightened girl, and with an amazing cold blood, in a remarkable way, Vera Farmiga (who can see in "Infiltrators") plays the wife of Walker, Karel Roden as the stepfather of the boy and Chazz Palminteri as one of the corrupt policemen, they are some of the protagonists of this fast-paced film.In some respects the proposal of Kramer is too far-fetched and reloaded visually, while others relax and shows us more quiet and classic situations that have to live actors, being the latter the most successful. In short "The proof of the crime" is a fast-paced film, full of action and dialogues that engancharán to the public in his armchair, making that they enjoy so far in which Kramer and theirs out of the top hat the latest tricks.</body>
</review>
