<review author="Bloody Will" title="La matanza de Texas: el origen" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bad, very bad. Puzzling and engañabobos. Almost two hours of blood without any explanation, although he never needed, and with a few ways to mascadas and manidas to finish the characters. Hopefully that it is the end of a saga.</summary>
	<body>I do not remember very well how was called the documentary, but for many years issued it in TVE and was a kind of collection of the best scenes of the cinema of fear of the 1970s and 1980s. Appeared in "Halloween", "Nightmare", "Thing" and a host of more films. The image that struck me most of all was that of Leatherface behind a blonde that bellowing like a pig at a slaughterhouse, in the original "Texas Chainsaw Massacre". What is far left already that, and what they have done with the saga, God mine. does "the origin" of what?. Stupid argument trying to equip a research into the origins of the murderer of the saw for a film which tells the same story than its predecessors. Do not fool, the birth of Leatherface lasts 30 seconds. Its origin, vague explanation. Its development was seen in the remake, but with different girls.A road, a sheriff who preys to the kids and a succession of races and short breaks on the outskirts and interiors of the House that is unmistakable. That is not the origin, but the same mechanics used to kill 70 and peak people, and which can make 30 sequels more, to the rhythm of the dead we have. Not have I heard why Leatherface killed, what led him to have the disfigured face, nor their obesión by cutting the carne.¿Por what it was butcher?. How, it's easy, what scam. I assume that the mask that accompanies the psychotic is the face of the first youngster dead, played by Matt Bomer. This must be, because it is not you see it clear. Gentlemen, this is not a film of origins, is a film franchise that continues needlessly, and which we can expect no surprise, that, to its prequel, won't die caracuero, obvious.The girl, Jordana Brewster, very cute, seen in "A todo Gas". The boy, Matt Bomer, seen in "True Calling". Their roles, flat encephalogram, with the sole purpose of stay alive the greater possible footage online. The other two co-stars better forget them.The best two: one, r. Lee Ermey as sheriff Hoyt, of which we know his way to ascend in the Police Corps; and the other, the sound of the mechanical, brutal sierra until the end. Perhaps it is that the end, the only thing remarkable for a film that already not scary to anyone, and where blood, in abundance, is not giving much disgust.Bad, very bad. Puzzling and engañabobos. Almost two hours of blood without any explanation, although he never needed, and with a few ways to mascadas and manidas to finish the characters. Hopefully that it is the end of a saga, although I doubt very much that, not being dead caracuero, carnage continue?</body>
</review>
