<review author="Silvia" title="La casa del lago" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The most romantic will perhaps be people enjoy more of this story, which although it no longer predictable, is no exaggeration have handkerchiefs from paper to the side if it comes to overwhelm the emotion contained.</summary>
	<body>A man and a woman maintain correspondence, with the peculiarity that are separated in time by two years. He lives in the year 2004 and it in 2006, but thanks to a magic mailbox they can keep an epistolary relationship in real time. Both are (or become) alone in life and begin a relationship by letter as a result of having lived in the same House. The Lake House mailbox is as a nexus of Union between the two times, two times. Love distance will emerge between the couple but think that they will never manage to see. But the fact that live in different times will not be an impediment for can be found in some moments.As protagonists, the first work of the Argentine Alejandro Agresti has interpretations of Sandra Bullock and Keanu Reeves, the mythical pair of Speed which returns here to be so. The Lake House is the American remake of a film released in the year 2000 South (Il Mare) Korea. Hence the pace of the tape is so leisurely, and perhaps lower the tension of the film towards the middle.But to enjoy the film must be prejudice and logic on one side by the unreal of the situation. The film invites us to be ourselves for a moment and imagine a better life. Invites us to let us go by dreams, to not settle for a comfortable life when we can have another better.The protagonist, Kate Foster (Sandra Bullock), maintains a formal relationship that seems the ideal companion but are not satisfied with his life. Paradoxically, despite being separated in time, along with Alex (Keanu Reeves), Kate manages to enjoy a full love.The protagonist asks: what if you live a lifetime and nobody is waiting for you? The film teaches us that worth waiting for love, for a genuine love and presents the dilemma between giving up true love for a life with fewer complications or do everything to keep it. The eternal dilemma between resign or fight for true love, difficult to be.The story is pretty well built, the two times of the narrative are well intertwined and it seems justified the moments in which the couple manages to coincide in time due to chance or fate. Another noteworthy aspect is the careful photography of the film, the aesthetics of the images is impeccable. But perhaps the most romantic people enjoy more of this story, which although it no longer predictable, is no exaggeration have handkerchiefs from paper to the side if it comes to overwhelm the emotion contained.</body>
</review>
