<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Infiltrados" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>What I'm saying is that a film director not can kill one of his creatures in any way the same as a master can not kill one of their pets.</summary>
	<body>What I'm saying is that a film director not can kill one of his creatures in any way the same as a master can not kill one of their pets. Long listening at a Conference to José Luis Sanpedro have their characters charged its own life, which he as a creator at most that arrived was to portray them. I found a beautiful exercise in humility confess unless a creator, a chronicler. When you create a character being in front of the audience to a human being with all that that entails. When the film zarandea and punished without mercy one innocent man is because the director he has reserved a happy ending. No vulgarity is not shoot thousand times the same thing, it is a Covenant. Viewers we are honest to a burning nail losers. If a famous director wants to break you molds then put the camera in an ashtray or make a traveling overhead from a spit, but dispatch to who pleases is not of Knights."Infiltrated" also it has a good of those who make history, he has a good of truth. One knows that it is good. It doesn't matter in that side of the law is, could be gangster, or not to be. The girl knows it. The director can make mistakes with their balance, I can be wrong, but if Vera Farmiga will lie with a type, it is because such is good, it does not return spreadsheet.The good and the bad are murmurs with mobile, nothing of secret keys. A RAID planned to the millimetre collapses because the mafia tópo know write sms's with the phone into his pocket. The police mole hangs from another phone. Called with a dead mobile, moles are not known, but they have direct line. The film there on a mobile phone.The film is two moles. The mole of the Irish mob in Boston is a lackey of his head that rises in the Police Corps without stopping. We know that a body of officials the most incompetent is that scale higher. The police mole infiltrates the mafia and the boss knows that he has a mole, but does not know who is. In the midst of a string of murders and a matter of traffic of microchips for future Chinese arms industry, bad Mole conspires with his mobile to rid the mafia of the police, while good Mole is played the skin so the police reuna tests.</body>
</review>
