<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Un buen año" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Gladiator sometimes puts eyes feeling so deep and profound one is passed the function hoping that appear about his position Centurions and kill you the woman and the child.</summary>
	<body>I know that those who write film seem a bunch of embittered, we always see the glass half empty, and when everyone you pass it well feel obliged to draw the feet of the dish and find three feet to the cat. I do what I can by talk about cinema as a spectator of the street, as one of those who asked the Council as a friend. I try to set aside, above all, the nonsense of verismo, the film is fiction. Even so, there are products that I can with them as much as I strive. "A good year" is an example.A London broker without scruples, which collects the insults that send you as triumphs, inherits a vineyard of his uncle in Provence, and has to travel there to sell it. The House and the plantation are filled with memories for him, but are two other reasons that retain. Appears an illegitimate daughter in search of his identity that could claim their rights, and secondly, meets a woman of the place that it falls in love with at first sight.The contrast stressed urban life? rural life is nice if not because they have thrashed it hundreds of films before, and with much more content. The character of the soulless broker did many more observers directors delight, Scott helps to release a couple of phrases rough without the most remote relationship with grace. The future that awaits the protagonist in his bag Agency is represented by the Chief alarmed and obsessed with his Van Gogh which cannot see by security measures. The head of "Intolerable cruelty" of the Coens, was much more graphic full of cables and casing. There are side very useful to have clear which is the best choice you can do the protatonista.Illegitimate daughter is in the film so let's look at a feature of the heart of the broker, while it is an unnecessary feature, or worse still, disjointed.One of the characters in the film, the uncle, says who knows the trick of the comedy "the trick is in the rhythm". It can be that the guy knows, but the director certainly not. What prints more than an agility, is a species of spasmodic rhythm.Although I won't to the cinema to see what they do the actors, I usually thank them that they do not spoil me the story with their faces. They should not have hired Russell Crowe for a comedy, the Gladiator sometimes puts eyes feeling so deep and profound one is passed the function hoping that appear about his position Centurions and kill you the woman and the child.</body>
</review>
