<review author="Jose Luis" title="Manderlay" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tape is not for everyone, but quite interesting for those who, at the end, may be the subject of a long discussion.</summary>
	<body>Toward the year of 1865 abolished slavery in United States, freeing thousands, if not millions, of African-Americans on its soil. Was undoubtedly just as more human? But were ready to be free? Manderlay, Lars von Trier's new tape, begins with that question, then do many others and thus raise once again his criticism towards United States, country which by the way, has never visited.The tape is part of a trilogy that began with Dogville, starring Nicole Kidman, whose character now takes Bryce Dallas Howard, with a fine and accurate performance by the way. Trilogy which will give end next year with the von tape (thus without h.). This new misadventure of Grace, the main character, begins with to find travel with her father and his followers of gangsters arrive to a cotton plantation in the middle of nowhere, where slavery continues 70 years after be abolished.In a matter of minutes Grace with the help of his cronies, frees the slaves, but as this about to continue with his trip, discover new freemen need something more.I'm afraid of what will happen now. -It confesses one of them. ? I don't know if we're ready for a new way of life. When we were slaves we cenábamos every day at 7. What hours dine freemen?So Grace decides to stay in Manderlay and help the community learn to live in freedom, striving to install equality between men, healthy coexistence and democracy, almost by Decree.And so chapter by chapter, we see as von Trier happens by weapons the american way of life, slaves soon cease to be slaves to sign contracts and be workers, who will have to work forcibly to cover their debts, suddenly Grace has the same interventionist attitude of his country, trying to convince everyone that the best is to be as she and her country. But soon their new society plays background and made other "American thank you" hand as justice and the death penalty, that Grace will suffer firsthand.Again, Lars von Trier, made hand in hand with the concept of Dogville, to roll the tape in a huge black study, with some lines on the ground showing the Division of the different places and just some scenic elements, i.e. as if it will be a play of Bertolt Brecht, which is not well received by many, but which in my view adds several degrees to its already if dense atmosphere.And although, as dictates it the Dogma begun by the director himself, the lighting is quite elementary, will create a beautiful and rather appropriate picture for tape and helps to faithfully recreate the atmosphere of a plantation of the 1930s.This is a perhaps more palatable tape the first, at least not so bloody, but step by step, the tension grows up to resemble the dramatic limits of Dogville, with a couple of surprising turns of nut as well as grace, we will stop with the mouth open.A tape is not for everyone, but quite interesting for those who, at the end, may be the subject of a long discussion.</body>
</review>
