<review author="Ana" title="Scoop" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Match Point last year was a Summit of his mastery to make movies with a resonant philosophical message. Scoop in sorties, is an entertaining comedy that transcends not.</summary>
	<body>Woody Allen is very productive, 37 films in his long career. Most as director, writer and actor. Its hiper-creatividad reveals his genius and his discipline, but the results are uneven. Match Point last year was a Summit of his mastery to make movies with a resonant philosophical message. Scoop in sorties, is an entertaining comedy that transcends not. Although the fun should not have to apologize for anything. Offering more than other films here, says more and makes laugh.An American journalism student on vacation in London, appears to him a journalist from the world of the dead while in a "desmoleculizadora" box to disappear as part of a magic show. Volunteer for the public just involving the magician in his research and falling in love with the object.Born Hebrew but he converted to narcissism. Allen's best recent films are those in which missing him as an actor and best even if you don't have a young actor imitating his character. This was Match Point and agreements and disagreements. But both things happen here.The problem is that his character alter-ego is already too old to be seductive. It is a relief that Scoop does not try to be him and accompanies Scarlet Johansson pretending to be his father and out of proportion. But in this version the character is very ironic his public personality: a disillusioned wizard who is sold as "Splendini" and repeats his bad jokes without much conviction. Attacks if same without compassion on a character that narrow-mindedness and adaptability have just destroy. Without mercy this character works, in addition to being funny and even seems less old than the last time. An immense value is needed to poke fun of oneself and of the perception held by the others of you, but there is where the good comedy. What makes laugh while he destripa.But not by him appeared in the movie leaves out the young actor in role impersonator. This time it is up to Johansson. Everything else did Jason Briggs. In Melinda and Melinda, Will Ferrel. Both end up look like cartoons which blurs their characters. The interpretation of Scarlet Johansson is worse, because it ends up splintering is and to des-moleculizandose, perhaps. I.e. disappears, has no substance and if it were not so pretty maybe would be better if it disappeared really.Still have tricks up the sleeve. The magic is the art that complicated tricks seem simple. Hide what makes them work, the idea is that look easy. The affection which has Allen magic is seen in many of his films, for example, shadows and fog. Here also note that he started his career writing jokes and gags, because they are not missing at any time.Also his interest in the narrative of mystery. In fact Annie Hall originally was going to have a mystery plot, but I stayed in romantic comedy and one of his best films. That ruled out plot is what I supposedly use later in Manhattan murder mystery. At least that tells the legend. What is clear is that the roads of creativity are tortuous. The comedy, as the magic, also usually hides a look on world and society, you can say many things without fear that anyone take too seriously.Another wonderful thing in this movie is the use of classical, call somehow fantasy the echo that appears the Dante boat that leads to the world of the dead. What also Allen knew before use in powerful Aphrodite with a Greek chorus with answering machine.In the end, is film is highly recommended, if you like to laugh and mysterious romantic comedies. If appreciate cinema and humor of Woody Allen, say a no-brainer. The picture of this film is wonderful and Hugh Jackman is great; others say.</body>
</review>
