<review author="José A. Peig" title="Scoop" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The friend Woody returns to accommodate composing one minor works, without more ambition than the personal entertainment and of delight their fans with a bunch of tics and hoses the House brand.</summary>
	<body>After the notable "Match Point," the friend Woody again (as in other occasions) to accommodate composing one minor works, without more ambition than the (bravo he recorded) personal entertainment and of delight their fans with a bunch of "tics" and "hose" the House brand, cemented in a story not devoid of the usual turn ironic and burlesque, which works with modesty, especially thanks to the ease gained during decades of film and almost always moving in a same area. This is for the benefit of the accommodative side bet of a cult author, but rocket positions against innovative betting as his previous work, confirming the stagnation of a filmmaker who will always be welcome to billboards and watched with pleasure by a server, but their recent stories would pass unnoticed if your name and surname does not appear under the "written and directed by".Set tics and phases you are configuring the story hides the usual philosophical ínfula disertada through a small group of characters, to see which of all is relamido and tasteless: student pavita seeking a getaway to his journalistic and research ambition, the amiga confidante who always supports him, the shy son of Dad that hides a secret, the funny character out of a theatre of magic and a plot sustained in the typical serial killer that "nobody knows who is but we all know who will (or won't) be ultimately". I.e., a set of characters without any notion of originality and freshness is added a very predictable plot scheme (and brought too schematic).It is not a bad film, Allen has great moments in some witty dialogues (could not be less) and at some point in the story that manages to coagulate altogether, but there are very specific things. Very little happens in most of the footage and jokes are not of a sarcastic and ironic intelligence surprised. It is the style and charisma of Woody Allen saving function, the text and representation, by themselves, are too insubstantial. And that, obviously, is very little.</body>
</review>
