<review author="Marta" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not a masterpiece not invented anything new. However, even so, it is an interesting and entertaining film which is worth seeing.</summary>
	<body>A pleasant surprise. I had read that "Children of men" promised more than what gave and, frankly, was expecting something rather disappointing - admit that the posters influence me. However, I found myself with a well made, exciting movie and had a very interesting history, although it was not the most original of the world. By 2027, in a future that suffers the consequences of pollution and violence, Britain has become an extremely repressive and totalitarian State in which all immigrants are deported. 18 Years ago that took place the last birth of the world, and the entire population attends helplessly at the end of humanity. In these circumstances, a pregnant woman will be a treasure that everyone will want to get. As well, from this approach, "Children of men" chronicles the journey of this woman to the place in which may be his son safe and become the last hope of the human beings. The film has a futuristic aesthetic or a completely happy ending. On the contrary, it is eerily close and familiar. Unfortunately, stays a little lame in the portrait of the "bad", that leaves no clear why they are so bad and are typical stereotypes who seek this woman could be persiguendo the secret documents from the Pentagon or the microchip of the mysterious company on duty. To counter, featuring two spectacular scenes. On the one hand, a Chase filmed in impressive manner (who would say that something as common as this would come to the attention?) and, on the other, a few minutes, somehow, summarizing all the film: the passage of the protagonist with his newborn baby among a crowd of people who stop shooting to hear crying to contemplatemute, the creature, and that continue killing immediately after. "Children of men" is not a masterpiece not invented anything new. However, it is still an interesting and entertaining film which is worth seeing.</body>
</review>
