<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I liked the end result of the work, and pretty, but would have to give a good slap to the director Milos Forman for not having documented correctly in various aspects on the life of Goya.</summary>
	<body>I heard the other day on the street, while waiting to enter the press pass of the documentary "The great silence", (which I, personally, would have entitled "The great pestiño") to a group of prestigious media film critics commenting on his impressions of the film "Goya's ghosts": "What horror! - read one - if Goya painted 'Saturno devouring his son' on a wall and not on a canvas." And how bad that war is represented. The worst, a pure garbage. "And Goya seems an artisan than a genius--said another - go film horror!, I think Bardem does not want nor do interviews with embarrassed that is."It is true that we should give a good slap to the director Milos Forman have not been properly documented in various aspects on the life of Francisco de Goya (is true that Goya was known as black paintings on the walls of the fifth of the deaf and later moved to the oil (producing deteriorations in the paintings).) Also, the vision that is done on the Spanish war of independence is very incomplete (seems we won thanks to the English and while it is true that, together with other countries, England helped US quite as not interested in France had more power, the real weapon that won was the so-called "war of guerrilas").Having said all that, the logical thing is that you think that I did not like the film, however, in contrast to what most of the criticism is saying, I have to tell you that the end result of the work I liked, and also pretty.This is not a biography of Goya, or it tries to be: the painter is a character rather than live a given historical time but agrees that he left us in his legacy the vision of what I thought. That is why, so Goya is important to the film. First of all, Francisco de Goya y Lucientes was a condemn champion of ignorance. And when this ignorance is exercised from power, also has another denominator in common: the abuse.The protagonist, Ines Bilbatua, is a fictional character that Goya is just an acquaintance. And the narrative lies in what happens to it and not in the life of Goya. This makes that the historical mistakes that has the movie can be forgiven, but not forgotten, (hope that the Magi you bring to the Lord are a book on the life and work of the great painter as well as one on the history of Spain in the 18th and 19th centuries).Bardem is impressive and Natalie Portman almost reaches him. The setting is quite correct and the end leaves a good impression. Worst, the errors of which we have spoken and the white actress Portillo that unconvincing in her role of María Luisa Parma.Como curiosity indicate you that the movie is based in her novar the eponymous written by the director himself and writer Jean-Claude Carrière and, curiously, it has gone on sale sharing with the movie premiere.Incidentally, for those critics who are connoisseurs of art created not just them say that Goya did his black works on the walls of his house (we already know all), if they want to be more pedants quibble I would recommend warn another error of the film, which by the way, not I heard nothing during the conversation of the Council of wise men: the greater plundering of pictorial works undertaken by the French army does not fall on Velázquez but Murillo.</body>
</review>
