<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="Transamerica" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Masterful performance by Felicity Huffman</summary>
	<body>Since that saw the trailer of?Transamerica? do already I can't see equal?Desperate women?. The makeup of Felicity Huffman in the film helps it seems someone who previously was man, but their own factions are somewhat masculine and especially when you make some gestures, it is difficult to see Lynette as a woman. Probably, her husband in real life, William H. Macy, protagonist of?Do murder?, are not the same. To finish the mixture, the character of Huffman in?Transamerica? do is called Bree, as another of the?Desperate housewives?, to which gives life Marcia Cross. Despite the title of the film and that your advertising has focused on this aspect, the central argument of?Transamerica? It is not transsexuality, but the encounter between a person and the son who did not know he had. Difficult encounter by the secrets both have been saved and the revelations of truths that are disappointing. But these secrets and lies could be others and the movie would have exactly the same pattern. Do occurs as in?Do Brokeback Mountain?, where the central argument is not homosexuality, although trafficking at least more than here transsexuality but the story of an impossible love for social issues. The word?Transamerica? not only tells us the change of sex, but also a side trip to one from a country that is changing according to Bree and Toby are proceeding on his journey. Due to this treatment of road movie, and the sentimental plot of p/mother and child reunion, the film reminds a TV movie. The end happy, slightly sweetened and too reconciliatory also brings closer it to this format, which does not end of fall thanks to the quality of its realization and interpretations. The doubly transform Felicity Huffman, as well as achieve a masterful performance, get a gesture, a profile that seems to be a transsexual. Paradoxically, when it takes less makeup and you can not take hormones, it is when it shows that it is a woman. For this reason, perhaps it might arise if it would not have been wiser to that paper embody it a true transsexual, it is less common to have characters for them and this movie could have been a great opportunity for an actress that a change of sex has been practiced. Like in the movie?The hours?, be could have given a chance for a little gracious actress, because they usually have less chance of being movie stars, rather than makeup and afear Nicole Kidman. However, it seems that the "harder still" is one of the preferences of the industry American and, especially, Oscar (see it?)Do Forrest Gump??Does rain Man?,?(Do girl, interrupted?, etc.). Is therefore quite likely that we see Huffman climb the stairs and pick up a new trophy to join his Emmy for?Women desperate?.</body>
</review>
