<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The jumps that are produced, together with a somewhat forced development left the feeling that something is wrong. It can at best be seen.</summary>
	<body>Director Milos Forman is considered by many a ' cult' director. 'Amadeus', 'One flew over the cuckoo's nest' or the controversial (by its equal number of lovers and detractors) ' Man on the Moon', they are probably his most outstanding films, and as you can see, are quite disparate in terms of gender. Or not? Perhaps the human psyche predominates in some extent.The beginning of the movie we are in the Madrid of the 18th and 19th century: the burden of the Inquisition and the monarchical absolutism still stands, and the echoes of the revolution reach Spain. In this panorama lives the great Spanish painter Francisco de Goya. Do and in this sense, the film makes a different reflection (successful or not) of the Madrid then and the life of the artista.pero with a noticeable lack of hook, or can last throughout the film or it can be improved, irregularly, with the possible minutos.¿Es that the script has some guilt? Definitely, Yes. The jumps that are produced, together with a somewhat forced development left the feeling that something is wrong. While going through the perhaps somewhat excessive footage (or insurance unless it is could have used better), the viewer missing know more of the why of the changes in the works of the painter, because this is progressively relegated to the background. Wouldn't be more appropriate title as 'The ghosts of Agnes', the Muse of artist, excellently played by Natalie Portman? Or perhaps something referring to father Lorenzo (a correct Javier Bardem), that it almost becomes the protagonist of the film, especially in the initial part and end?May be one of the strong points details, merit special attention the vision of belonging to the Inquisition dungeons, and the portrait of the sick (incredible artistic aspect, to the point of leaving unrecognizable Portman); and also others, such as the production of a work process, or on the relations between the painter and the royalty (what great choice for the role of Charles IV: similar physique between Randy Quaid and the monarch is so real that it becomes comic), or even the soundtrack, which does not stand out, but has brilliant moments. But it is more than likely that vacuum that can leave (and leaves) the film despite more than any of its virtues.In short, 'The ghosts of Goya' is a film that, without Excel, be seen. But no more: as much would stress the interpretation of its main actors and a somewhat different at the time reflection. But it is unforgivable to submit to the great painter Spanish, and not get to deepen in him especially if we consider the title of the film.</body>
</review>
