<review author="Vsancha" title="La matanza de Texas: el origen" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Nonsense would be the word to describe this exercise of ineptitude in the form of video clip whose realization only makes sense if it is not so that Mr Michael Bay fills the pockets.</summary>
	<body>Nonsense would be the word to describe this exercise of ineptitude in the form of video clip whose conduct only makes sense if it isn't so that Mr Michael Bay fills their pockets by exploiting a series does not give for more ideal. The great mistake of this film is its very existence, i.e., this film is totally unnecessary, adds nothing new, teaches nothing we have not seen before and attempting to explain the origin of the family, maniacs and Leatherface is a serious mistake, as one of the great successes of La Matanza was exactly not know because these people were acting that way. And also later, once you finish watching the film, you realize account there a few minutes of single origin and most of the footage is repeated over and over again the same formula that we of course already know of memory. The film is boring from beginning to end and that which takes least time and a half, but is so repetitive and predictable that all get boot staff are a few yawns far their claims something provocative of viscera and blood that nowadays is the least you can ask to a tape of terror of these features. But the thing is getting worse as boredom takes over the Viewer, starting with the futility of the Lord which is behind the camera, not is that demons will have wanted to make this film Mr Liebesman, but it is very harmful to the view the continuous level/contraplano and dizzying camera movements and if that join the darkness that invades every scene of the filmhardly we can identify the figure of Leatherface. A caracuero that, like his entire family of disruptors and sickly murderers, in is film loses all the charisma that had as a symbol of the horror movies &amp; mythical figure of the slashers movies becoming a ridiculous character. I won't delve into the stupid couple of bikers that just show the narrative awkwardness of a script makes no sense. Or in the bland gang of young victims. The origin is just pure guts prefabricated, a commonplace innards show that distorts the true spirit and origin of the massacre of Texas.</body>
</review>
