<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the most overwhelming beautiful films of the year. A touching futuristic fable, lasts, shocking at times, and which can continue talking for hours out of the film.</summary>
	<body>If only a few days ago I spoke of the great fable about our past made by Guillermo del Toro, now it is the turn to another Mexican director who in turn created a brilliant fable of our future.Based on the novel by P.D. James, "Sons of the men" (Children of Men) immerses us in the world of 2027, where wars and terrorism are only part of the problem. The greatest tragedy of humanity is that women have lost their ability to have children. 18 Years ago that does not originate any human being and, therefore, the species is endangered?One of the main virtues of the tape is that when I say that it immerses us in the world of the future I mean exactly that. During the almost two hours that the film lasts, and that by the way they spend in a sigh, the spectator lives in this world. He is fully aware of the tragedy of the lack of babies on the planet and the importance that born one. In this way, fully understands the hopeless nihilism of Theo (a magnificent Clive Owen), the desperate struggle of Julian (the always brilliant Julianne Moore) and the descreída hope to change the world of Jasper (Michael Caine that already nobody doubts it, is one of the great).Several are the elements used by Alfonso Cuarón to put us both in the history. The first of these is a brilliant address artistic, credible and very realistic, retains many similarities with today's world but clearly outlines the differences to help the Viewer to imagine better what has happened between now and the future.Another important element is the special way of filming the movie, with a predilection for the camera in hand and the plano-secuencia that give some moments a semi-documentary tone that provides an exciting and frightening verism. Obviously this would not be possible without the imposing work of Emmanuel Lubezki, cinematographer who already you will must an oscarAñádase to what a beautiful soundtrack, fitted like a glove to every moment of the film, and that goes from the "Bring on the Lucie" of John Lennon to the brilliantly appropriate "Kindertotenlieder" of Gustav Mahler.El result: one of the most overwhelming beautiful films of the year. A touching futuristic fable, lasts, shocking at times, and which can continue talking for hours out of the film.</body>
</review>
