<review author="Jose Luis" title="Volver" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of the best films of Almodóvar, very close to all about my mother, perhaps with time receiving the recognition it deserves.</summary>
	<body>There is who is receiving the new film by Pedro Almodóvar with enough lukewarm, perhaps that she does not appear Gael García dressed women, do not have scenes explicit sex, or talks about a rough topic and morbidly in vogue. On the contrary, Almodóvar, in a pure State, removes all excesses to which we are accustomed in their cinema and focuses on tell us a strong and touching story about the strength of women, the family and women's loyalty.The tape begins when Raimunda, his sister solitude and his daughter visit the grave of his parents and to his sick aunt in his hometown. There is the legend that the dead are returning to life to help his family and meet some outstanding in that picturesque town. Soon solitude and Raimunda will have to decipher if this is actually true or if they are just old tales? that there are some issues in requiring help.The tape goes straight to the point, the script is drained with energy and strength, revealing little by little, revealing his true nature? This is a story of black humor, it is drama, melodrama, surreal is? Perhaps is a bit of everything, less surreal, that perhaps this is the tape more attached to reality, at least the most likely of all the varied filmography manchego Director.The solid group of actresses, all of them are fairly accurate, form an unbeatable team on the screen than the same pass without much effort from the fun to touching, all commanded by a memorable character, in charge of Penelope Cruz, as a strong woman, determined, "heavy" as her would describe his sister, a beautiful woman, who instead of sitting down to cry face of difficultyput hands to work and solve any problem with wisdom and speed with which a housewife orderliness in his kitchen.The colorful picture shows a Spain different from the rest of the films of Almodóvar, a modern, globalized and diverse Spain, where young women are coupled to your cell phone, and Latino immigrants give a new flavour, a Spain where they appear suddenly in a single shot men of color. And all this combined with the rural environment of the manchega Earth saw birth Almodóvar, and that no doubt influenced cinematically speaking, to date. A barren land, where the wind blows hard all the time governed mainly by women.And there is in this town where occurs a very memorable scene, where dozens of women in black, try to listen to the legends, presenting his condolences to the mourners and pray at the same time.In summary, and in my very particular point of view, one of the best films of Almodóvar, very close to all about my mother, perhaps eventually receive the recognition it deserves.</body>
</review>
