<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film's are condede few joys and will, I suspect, little audience. Missing heroes. There are only victims and executioners, and a painter that notes with an uncompromising eye.</summary>
	<body>Watching "The ghosts of Goya" one learns that a portrait cost three thousand real more if they were painted a hand and four thousand if the two were painted. Also learn how made Goya one of his engravings, from the manufacture of the paper until the pressing; details about the Inquisition trials, executions to bludgeon, the costume of the time. Milos Forman has put curiosity and attention. I leave it to others who are looking for the mistake with his sagacity; I'll stick with this Spain. the first part of the film seems a set of variations on the same theme: Goya paints the Queen is very ugly and does not know if beautify her or speak the truth with his brush; one of their models, Agnes is required by the Inquisition and asked the truth, but she prefers to sign whatever to avoid the pain. The father of Inés makes sign to the Inquisitor is a monkey to demonstrate that the Inquisition has no method. The Inquisitor suffers by his signature. Everything seems to lead us to a sick society where the truth seems madness and the madness of truth. And where the humor there.The second part takes the characters after an ellipsis of fifteen years. The madness of the former regime we come to the madness of the French troops who invade Spain. The same intransigent of the Church have become intransigent of the revolution. They remain the same with another necklace. The same change could have shot with the excuse of the civil war. If someone finds improbable it is because you are too used to the novel it always discerned logic.The film's are condede few joys and will, I suspect, little audience. Missing heroes. There are only victims and executioners, and a painter that notes with an uncompromising eye. It should perhaps be in the role of hero the father of Agnes, the only that rebels, powerless against the nonsense.</body>
</review>
