<review author="Beatriz Perez" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The character of Goya is non-existent, i.e. does not look anything. It is an excuse to give a title with packing adventures story.</summary>
	<body>Doing a couple of games of words we can say that Milos is not shaped and Goya does not look anything. Seven years after the appreciable, even pretentious, though?Do man on the Moon?, and decades after?Amadeus? and?Does one flew over the cuckoo's nest?, the Czech director returns with a nonsense of such dimensions that it is difficult to decide where to start to bring Manus to head:?The Goya's ghosts? (?(Do do Goya? s Ghosts?, 2006). Yesterday premiered in Madrid cinemas and tomorrow reaches the general Billboard. Perhaps the errors begin with the character of Goya is non-existent, i.e. it does not look anything. It is an excuse to give a title with packing adventures history which could be located in any other time. If only it was that and at a secondary level, very well, but is that above dare to show him as a buffoon that presence, without getting involved, the time that live you. His character is not that it lacks depth or motivation: simply does not exist, and you can do little Stellan Skarsgård (do the two new versions of?)The Exorcist?,?(Do the Caribbean Pirates: dead man's chest?) to fix it. Before well, convert to the temperamental Aragonese in a funny pintamonas and temperament. In addition, its clearly Scandinavian physicist achieved only provide more improbability for their anemic performance. But the fundamental problem, once again, is the script. The treated story is the classic 19th century Feuilleton of Fourth Division. Ya are us classics of the 19th century stultifying today in day?The Goya's ghosts? It is one even greater simplicity. The twist of script with which the conflict of the film arises is the most absurd that has seen in years and, as if that outside, the interpretation of Portman still leaves it more ridiculous. The thing is as follows: willing to "clean up Spain" according to the teachings of brother Lawrence (Javier Bardem), the henchmen of the Inquisition will a Madrid tavern where repaired in the curious behavior of Inés (Natalie Portman). This behavior is that, when they provide a succulent segovian suckling pig for dinner, she refuses with a grimace of posh girl that is neither credible nor is well performed. If foreign, it could react this way, but being Spanish, we would have seen this dish sometimes. A grimace that would make even Lindsey Lohan in?I want to be superfamosa?. So, seeing the inquisitors that she refuses to eat pork, come to the conclusion that it is a heretic who practiced rites judaizers. Or that is what he wants to make us believe the script. In fact stop her for being such a bad actress: when, seconds later in the same scene, want to do the "place" kissing the feet of a dwarf, the improbability is greater than if seriously Pamela Anderson to collect the prize Nobel. How Natalie Portman, who only knows a role has credibility as an actress, is something that goes beyond me. While still need to explain why Keira Knightley is superb in?Pride and prejudice? Leaving aside the bad acting, the problem lies in that it makes no sense that her stop why, is a twist of forzadísimo script.But the worst of the script is not mental simplicity of the story or its thick outline. The worst thing is that, for having "importance", also is take hand in hand with the history of Spain during the fifteen years covering the film. Obviously a stupid and simplistic story needs a historical context to simplify the history of Spain far as the insulting folklore.The first insult begins to focus the story on the Inquisition. While it is true that it is a relevant part of the history of Spain that does not feel particularly proud, it is also true that perpetuates the topic Anglo-Saxon Spain = Inqusición, so successful as to say that the history of England is summarized in the extramarital adventures of Charles and Diana. Secondly, simplify all the reforms that brought the invasion by Napoleon to leave them reduced to "a group of Lords very, very, but very bad, firing to the priests at mass". Thirdly, the expulsion of the French and the coronation of Ferdinand VII is sold as an instantaneous process that allowed the Spaniards to return to its authentic be: scream "Live the caenas!" and reinstate the Inquisition which we liked so much. If you want to ignore me, try to support which is probably the worst movie of the year and alucinen with the following number of things: the dual role of Natalie Portman, making crazy and disfigured mother and prostitute daughter it. Another trick of cheap script that makes that Natalie Portman will be found, a conveniently abandoned baby. How bad is the portrait that Goya painted by Javier Bardem. Pathetic "montage scenes" that are using paintings of Goya. One thing is that, as a Convention, we accept that English speak when in theory they are talking about Spanish or French, but then, why do we suddenly hear screaming in these languages?Only the work of the "dialogue coaches" saves: all Spanish players have a more than decent English accent. Do otherwise, things like?The Goya's ghosts? and?Alatriste? only give more greatness to which, against all odds, has risen as the best mega (co) production Spanish historical and adventures of the year:?The Borgia?. Do always assuming that?The labyrinth of the Faun? is in a different category.Should it have been titled?The daughter of the chaquetero?, in honor of the character played by Javier Bardem, true protagonist of the film and almost only thing salvageable from it.</body>
</review>
