<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Saw 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Saw 3 is more of the same. Blood, suspense, more blood... and final tension (already feature). But it does not disappoint at all.</summary>
	<body>Two years ago, premiered in theaters a film budget, that virtually no one knew and whose fue.excelente result. He not only raised much more of what it cost, but that we returned (finally!) the 'horror' film lovers a genre that many had by unrecoverable. 'The massacre of Texas', 'I know what you did last summer'. and other stupid American movies, without any script, suspense and only with topicazos everywhere, to scare us or try us.The franchise went forward, and in what way: an end to the most original and a well achieved plot constituted a few real good strengths of a tape that even hoped so successful. 'Word of mouth' helped a lot in attracting followers, it was more than likely a second part. That Yes, had not seen very rewarded by critics, although in reality, it seems to be film critic implies you like deep films, not know or to assess aspects of those that are not intended to but entertain, keep you in suspense and teach what others don't is atreven.¿Y what we have now? Saw 3 is basically more of the same. Blood, suspense, more sangre.y final tension (already feature). Is it bad to be repetitive? In this case not: the vast majority of viewers again looking for what they liked the original and its sequel, they do not want peace and harmony. want gore scenes, desagradables.y enjoy the desired outcome. And in this sense, Saw 3 does not disappoint you: is no better that the first part, but a worthy sequel, which I doubt will cease to delight lovers of the saga.It is possible that on this occasion the plot is not so original as in the past, although it is probably more complex than those. There are fewer participants, but further explanation (pay attention to various details). There are less genius, but am not disappointed. At all. Even knowing that this kind of movies can be more unlikely, no one has said that the film has to be so. That Yes, if there is something that I finished convincing is the mareante (and pointless) camera movement, which aims to achieve tension but does but lose to the Viewer. He spent in the first part, in the second, and now not going to be less. Perhaps if not outside, so we'd in falta.pues everything is so particularly characteristic in this trilogy, predictability is unpredictable.For this reason, and despite that it is not so cool, so original and possibly somewhat more predictable, the truth is that, once again, the end returns to surprise, perhaps not with much astonishment, but with enough as to leave us the feeling that, in the fourth part, there will be one spectator.</body>
</review>
