<review author="Joseba" title="Las colinas tienen ojos" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Of course that is superior to the original, but only from the point of view of a brain contaminated by al gore as the mio. Because the movie is stuck to the original.</summary>
	<body>Not bad, but not bad this remake of a child film by Wes Craven classic for now almost 30 years old...30? A moment, have almost 30 years passed since that film than the only thing salvageable today are their sorted covers of classic VHS? Then I start again.Not bad, but bad East remake, but. either we move on. Of course that is superior to the original, but only from the point of view of a brain contaminated by al gore as the mio. Because the movie is stuck to the original. Flags side baked heads? If. Empalamientos wild and fun? Of course! Do lot of tension, at times almost unbearable, especially with babies infants of medium? I can not deny it. But. 12 hours after having seen the movie, I wonder if that is for both. I mean, if a group of music that this fashion, with good pull among young people and a fucking great production, makes a version of some classic of the Ramones. I am sure that many stun you will say that is better than the original only because it is more sugarcane, but slut and more punky, but. Is this remake more punk than the original? If you hear more high, has better production, and much of the good in the carabana gore, but. I guess that 30 years ago thought that the movie was the rehostia, and I guess that Wes not pin flags yanks in the hollow head of the nazi cowboy turn because purportedly even had much to say in the film industry. and so it was clear. Do not want to dwell much more on the same subject, so I can only conclude by saying that you see the movie, which do not need to I tortureis seeing the original, but I guess that that the you have seen, entendereis what I mean. Or not!Despite my misgivings, prota gafoso improves at times until it makes a hole in your heart, the young gunman is unbearable, just like the screams of the sister Dante onstage of the caravan (very jevy!), me much happy when the old is carbonised and a few things that stand out, above all for his regustillo life Gore made with styleIf that is possible.I give a well-deserved 7.5. High tension, the previous film Alexandre Aja, was far better than this, in my humble opinion.And finally, to say that I am a great admirer of the Ang Lee Hulk, and both nuclear mushroom in the prologue of the movie, do not you had a good nuclear bomb molao green sweeping Texas and a charming green coming out from the wreckage bug saying Hulk crushes? Surely if!</body>
</review>
