<review author="José A. Peig" title="Palindromos" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Above all, a lyrical, atosigador story of our consciences and often a fun elegy to any lost soul, despite the burden of a somewhat irregular set.</summary>
	<body>"Palindromes", the metaphor of our tragedy as alleged instigators of change and evolution if you don't find departures to a universe of emptiness and disorientation. Gives the same how you named and what your physical appearance: you are all, all are the same, there is no change, only the pain that comes from a misunderstanding.Analytical film, immersion in disturbing thoughts and dark States of being. But there are also pretensions of taste and hope by innocence, as well as fear of children, stage of maximum disorientation in this continuum of solitary beings fleeing to other prisons emerged in a social fabric unstructured, a bitterness of dreams that are shades of cherished and lost forever.Todd Solondz has woven a bitter poem on love and fear to life brilliantly. Perhaps there is no greater cruelty than the do birth. But without the perpetuation of life we lose all hope in love and that the need to love and be loved may bring us something more than desire and the poetic enjoyment of vulnerable souls. Aviva may be the entire society or the lost sheep who us shouts to consciousness from its moorland. The structure of the poem in the same essential profile that takes different faces is quite accomplished and reaches the proper metaphorical significance. The cinema has no why be a toy for moviegoers pedants quibble, Solonzd, bold and honest, shows us that pieces so small and unusual as they discover the uniqueness of an idea or a few thoughts that do not belong in the cinema of masses. Just why his last work deserves to be enjoyed by all types of public, although cinemas which is planned upon arrival in Spain with two years of delay can count on the fingers of the hand.However, cinema not necessarily entails the guarantee of high quality cinema. Despite its stimulant and correct film work, "Palíndromos" does not go beyond a few profiles and a story that just proving too megalomaniacal, and sins of a too explicit Mannerism in a speech deterministic and doomed to the mere effect in the mind of the Viewer, without leaving sufficient margin of decision against a work which had aimed at displaying a sour image of fate and life, but not manipulate and in response to the alleged complexity of discourse. On the other hand, the grotesque characterization of some characters not always effect functionally speaking (in some sequences nothing be a capricious of dubious taste extravaganza, while in other scenes, sections or places seems to conform to a texture of circus poem around the world Freak with pretty packaging).Above all, a lyrical, atosigador story of our consciences and often a fun elegy to any lost soul, despite the burden of a somewhat irregular set.</body>
</review>
