<review author="Reinderdot" title="Truman Capote" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Hoffman will accomplish with this film the respect it deserves</summary>
	<body>A major portion of the blogosphere, is strongly seduced by what is called "New journalism". So when a film about Truman Capote starring jumps into the ring by the? so far, I think - underestimated Philip Seymour Hoffman, the least can do you is a short post.I think that Hoffman will succeed with this film the respect it deserves. "Capote" is not a comprehensive and historical biography of the intelligent, sarcastic and effeminate journalist, but an intense approach to a key moment in his life: the development of "In Cold Blood", last book of Capote (and subsequent film with Robert Blake's protagonist) and first piece framed in the genre "not fictional novel" that opened the door to the "new journalism" and/or "Gonzo journalism".This film is entirely of Philip Seymour Hoffman. Achieve what Nicholson in "About Schmidt", a total retinal detachment of your "real" image of actor and a total embodiment in the character. Not only the acute voice makes credible and the characteristic gestures, basic and key aspects of the character, but through their looks, gestures, reactions and intonations, manages to condense in less than two hours that the script could not do voluntarily. He did lack to see map of Capote's childhood, when he tells them in one of the most intimate moments of the film. If the film wanted to show to Capote, it has achieved, without specifically show all aspects of his life. Bennett Miller (director), Dan Futterman (script) based on the book by Gerald Clark have achieved, through Hoffman, outline its personality, life and work.Hoffman is also supported in other good and sober performances (Catherine Keener as writer Harper Lee, Clifton Collins Jr. as the convict Perry Smith and Chris Cooper as the detective Alvin Dewey, among others) "Capote" makes us make us the same question that has not been able to be answered in reality: were the events around the development of "In Cold Blood" which led the writer to its self-destruction through alcoholism? Considering that the writer in question is Truman Capote, this question makes this film an interesting audio-visual option. This option of the type that they reverberate and conclude in the search for other books, articles, reviews and film, to extend the original film beyond its footage.</body>
</review>
