<review author="Mario" title="Gojira (Godzilla)" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A classic of the fantasy film that has generated countless sequels and which should be recommended with contraindications. Need a good predisposition to seedy entertainment and fun without complexes.</summary>
	<body>August 1945: the most dramatic war episode the planet Earth has ever known is about to conclude. In the West, Germany had capitulated to the thrust of Soviets and allies, but in the East, the Empire of the rising sun was reluctant to sign the surrender. Emperor Hirohito still aspired to a treaty that does not deshonrara his people against the all-powerful American war machine. On the other hand, the United States of America were not willing to grant nor a day effort more than war. On August 6, 1945 drops the first atomic bomb on Hiroshima, three days later another artifact does in Nagasaki. At that time, the world learned to where can human perfidy, and which is the power of destruction that it possesses. Japan would be marked by these events forever, and Godzilla is a good proof of that.Almost a decade later, director Ishirō Honda wore to the big screen the story of a Jurassic creature awakened in the 20th century, by the virulence of nuclear testing. The huge reptile (then not be spent about dinosaurs were precursors of birds) radioactivity it emanated through all the pores and, even, had developed a nuclear breath with immense destructive power. The monster, angered by the belligerent human activity, step on firm ground sweeping everything he gets ahead. While the human protagonists of the film discussed which would be the most appropriate course of action.On the one hand eminent paleontologist Dr. Yamane is opposed to the destruction of the shabby, arguing that its scientific study would be more useful to humanity. The rest of the country who, horrified, sees no way of destroying the grotesque animal would be opposed to it. Even his daughter will end up asking for help to the young Dr. Serizawa, creator of a new deadly weapon.The message of the tape is clear. Dr. Serizawa has discovered the desoxigenador of water, a tool which, through a completely implausible chemical process in which cut off the oxygen from the water do?, is capable of ending lifetime bathed in aqueous fluid where is immersed. Despite pressure from his friends the doctor refuses in resounding using the artifact against Godzilla, eventually ceding to the terrible disaster generated by the creature. His regret for having discovered a weapon of mass destruction in the hands of men could lead to unimaginable misfortunes, takes you to burn all evidence of his research and, ultimately, to ending the last container of such knowledge.Thus the film opts on one side, to the historical question of whether scientists who discovered nuclear fission had or not responsibility for the genocide of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. According to this version every man is responsible for his actions and should be required to amend them, even if the life in this.The destruction of Tokyo to paw, teeth, tail and radioactive breath by Godzilla is also very significant. In a time of war, in which Japan trying to escape from the crisis caused by the World War II, the razed city conjured up the miseries of the conflict and the nonsense about the misfortunes that it generated.Transferred to the screen with an excellent commissioning scene at frenetic pace (even from the current point of view) and with spectacular special effects for the time. The festival of fire models and toy car that burst, is delusional. The scenes of disaster do not have to envy nothing to which we currently see in our cinemas. Is notable the sequence in which Godzilla topples a tower from which several journalists taking pictures, as the bug approached, one of them live tells what is happening?The monster is directed towards us? Do not have escape? It's horrible, increasingly is closer? We are going to die! He is shaking the tower this is the end! Farewell to everyone? Good bye!?The film is a continuous reference to the classic King Kong (1933) Hollywood, despite the fact that on this occasion the stop-motion should be replaced by a simple costume and, apparently, it is also influenced by other American productions of the time. It's funny as, despite the implicit criticism of the USA, along the footage we see strong foreign influence in the post-war Japan, either in the clothing of the characters, in vehicles that used or directly, in the way of making films, which set his gaze at their old enemies.Ultimately, Godzilla is already a classic of fantasy films that has generated countless sequels to each more pajera, and which should be recommended with contraindications. Need a good predisposition to seedy entertainment and fun without complexes; from there, perhaps beyond of the Fireworks, you can glimpse an extraordinary movie.</body>
</review>
