<review author="Albert Puyuelo" title="The Queen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Drama on the situation of decadence through which pass all the monarchs today. Frears plays with delicate issues that tend to be abused by the yellow press.</summary>
	<body>Get to our screens The Queen, a production of United Kingdom with a very British flavour. So much so that it focuses on a small stage which passed their monarchs. Specifically, this film tells us what happened after the death of Lady Di, when the pedia English population to his Queen to make a public display of pain. One of the key characters in this short historical period was the newly elected Tony Blair, who here plays magnificently Michael Sheen. Its role is compelling from start to finish, something which is absolutely essential, because he is the connection of all the characters. Although it is only really a puppet and it seems babear kiss the hand of the Queen, his figure lets air where there. For this reason, with another actor who had not been able to reach the level of Sheen, it is possible that the fabulous interpretation of the Queen of England does Helen Mirren, had not served anything.What tells us here Stephen Frears hardly will be of interest to the general public. The relationship between the Queen and members of their families, or with his chamberlán and other lackeys, becomes a bit repetitive. Of agreement that the life of a monarch outsole to be very monotonous, but it did not lack that laid out in the film. If the history of Lady Di and his relationship with the Royal family does not interest us, or we know it very well, might not hook us the plot of The Queen. But there are enough elements added for taste. The monarchy is represented intelligently, with very subtle ironies, but without never falling into the realm of comedy. It is a drama about the situation of decadence through which pass all the monarchs today and that, in this respect, it will please any Democrat. Stephen Frears touches gently topics that tend to be abused by the yellow press, and even sandwiched images of actual recordings with fictitious videos to explain the key moments.</body>
</review>
