<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film isn't at the height. The screenplay by Milos Forman and Jean-Claude Carrière is quite weak and bland, unfortunately scratching into vulgarity.</summary>
	<body>The year 2006 will be remembered in Spanish film, above anything else, as the year of the great historical productions. On the big screen have been portrayed the century 15th, 16th, 17TH, 18th and 19th, the rise and decline of the largest empire in history, and the final sunset of another of the great empires has been humanity. Returning to the film field, this year also has been shown Spanish cinema can seduce a Director such as Milos Forman (one of the few filmmakers alive with two Academy Award for the best direction) and a star of worldwide as Natalie Portman.Los ghosts of Goya us dips at times turbulent and turbulent, while in Europe the new ideas and thoughts opened step at any price and under the protection of armsin Spain there was the ancien régime and the Inquisition still retained the old ideologies, frightening the people. Inés (Natalie Portman) is the daughter of a wealthy merchant, who poses as a model for Francisco de Goya (Stellan Skarsagard). Due to the fanaticism of the Inquisition, Agnes is arrested and falsely accused of heresy. Brother Lorenzo (Javier Bardem), Member of the Inquisicón, which he paints Goya, tries to intercede in favour of Agnes, falling for her. With so many expectations as it has generated Goya's ghosts, fulfil them all would be an effort really Titanic, and in honor of the truth, it must be said that the film is not the height. The screenplay by Milos Forman and Jean-Claude Carrière is quite weak and bland, unfortunately scratching into vulgarity. All the strength that could boast the film, taking into account such as Milos Forman as a filmmaker and the greatness of the figure to portray, is conspicuous by its absence.Despite failed plot, Goya's ghosts is a brilliant technical Bill that stand out especially Javier Aguirresarobe photography and the artistic direction of Edward Hidalgo. Above all, stand out interpretations of a superlative Javier Bardem, a solid and convincing Stellan Skarsgard, and one suffered and human Natalie Portman, capable of transmitting all the suffering of his character in Goya's ghosts. Although comparisons are odious, it is also inevitable that you come one to head this superb work by Carlos Saura (especially in the visual aspect) is Goya in Bordeaux. Goya's ghosts is a film that visually is a delight for the public, but which it fails the primary livelihood of any cinematographic work: a good story behind it.</body>
</review>
