<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Scoop" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The ingenuity of Allen is evident from the foreground of the film until the last, causing real attacks of laughter and uncontrollable laughter. Scoop is a new genius of one of the greatest masters of comedy and cinema.</summary>
	<body>True to its annual event, with the first cold of winter comes to Spanish screens new film of one of the most loved and recognized in our country foreign filmmakers: Woody Allen. His last works, especially Match Point though without forgetting everything else and Melinda and Melinda, away from the more recognizable Allen, ironic and sarcastic. Four years after A Final Made in Hollywood, Woody Allen returns in its purest form, with a comedy which will delight any good amateur to the seventh art.Sondra Pransky (Scarlett Johansson) is a young journalism student that passes the holidays in London. There, a night will attend the spectacle of Sid Waterman, "Splendini" (Woody Allen), who will choose it for one of their numbers, the "dematerializer". While Sondra expected, appears the spirit of Joe Strombel (Ian McShane), journalist of recently deceased prestige, who informs him of a great exclusive. There are few things more fun in this world who see a genuine and inimitable film of Woody Allen, and Scoop is part of the standard. If you need to compare ' Scoop ' with other tapes of Allen, it slightly reminds this jewel that is Manhattan murder mystery. The ingenuity of Allen is evident from the foreground of the film until the last, causing real attacks of laughter and uncontrollable laughter. If the script is full of subtlety and fine irony marks House, the work of direction that develops Allen is as always impeccable, carrying the story at its own pace precise, without slowness and crashes, something which often suffer the current comedies.And as also comes standard in his films, Allen brings out the best of its performers, including himself, with his mere presence already it takes one smile. Scarlett Johansson, the new Muse of filmmaker, shows that in the comedy it unfolds as well as in the more dramatic role, although Hugh Jackman him nor lags behind, to the positive surprise of many. In short, Scoop is a new genius of one of the greatest masters of comedy and cinema.</body>
</review>
