<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Yo soy la juani" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>More than a fiction film should be considered only as an exemplary testimony to the reality of a good part of the youth Spanish current, and as such it is worth seeing her.</summary>
	<body>There are some filmmakers that for one reason or another, by the talent they have, the themes, or a mixture of both, never leave anyone indifferent. There are many makers that fit this description in Spanish film, and Catalan Bigas Luna is without doubt a clear example. Films such as the ages of Lulu, ham, ham or eggs of gold are already part of the mythology of the cinematography Spanish (not only for having discovered and consecrated to Javier Bardem and Penelope Cruz), and assumed a new way of understanding the narration in the film. Now, five years after Son of sea, Bigas Luna presenting to the public its vision of the icon of Spanish modern women, Juani.Con this new film, Bigas Luna was looking also for the discovery of a new actress, and this was dedicated six months looking for the perfect interpreter to give life to this new icon. Juani (Verónica Echegui) is a young woman who dreams of becoming an actress and be a great Star, despite his ailing father and the neighborhood where he lives, a backwater of the peripheries of a big city. Her boyfriend Jonah (Dani Martin) are passionate about the tuning, to the point of live dedicated to body and soul. The Juanita and her best friend Vane (Laya Martí) decide to go to Madrid to succeed, but once there they discover that success doesn't conquer so easily. The best quality of Bigas Luna in the film is the portray a social reality that a good part of the population is unknown or facing another part. The characters, their character, their environment, the way in which expressed their dreams and ambitions, through tuning, are reflected to perfection. However, admittedly fiction that stands on such recreation is quite weak, without force or excitement. The script is simple and predictable, the characters neither move nor evolve, and the plot is unable to or engage the viewer more predisposed to do so; that Yes, sometimes is seen submerged in a visual and musical binge without apparent end. Note to the League intended to make a sequel, if accompanied by the blessing of the ever-changing public. For its part, the actors are in general in a tone of medium-high, although without fanfare by none of them.I am the Juani, rather than a fiction film should be considered only as an exemplary testimony of the reality of a good part of today's Spanish Youth, and as such worth seeing her.</body>
</review>
