<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Ficción" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Movies like?Do fiction?, however, are to remain in the memory of viewers. A film that leaves poso.</summary>
	<body>"In the city" by Cesc Gay. I don't know that demons have stuck this litany in the head, those six words which, as cyclical as continuous, come me to mind. I know that they refer to a film, very lauded and annotated; and a Director, young and greatly valued. But nothing more. I've seen, nor I know what will be the movie or its author. If is it something.The case is that it has just been released "Fiction", the last movie of Gay, which has also attracted applause from critics. And I went to see her, to a session slut, thinking if not should have seen before that happy "in the city". Come on, that he did not know if Cesc is one of those self-referring authors who, to catch them the item, you must have followed since the beginning of his career.But not. At all. Although by the issues raised in "Fiction"? the relationship of two hardened urbanites that coincide in a kind of creativo-espiritual retirement in the Catalan Pyrenees? It may seem that we are before the bucolic reverse of a film entitled "in the city", that is, can be enjoyed and savored with true delectation, even without knowing anything about the previous work by the author.And is that we we have one of those movies small and intimate, seemingly simple, they talk about banalities such as life, art, creation, faithfulness, love, betrayal, friendship, commitment and a long etcetera as long are the various possibilities offered by relationships of humans in a society as complex and contradictory as the Spanish from the beginning of twenty-first century.And, best of all, the major success, talent and ability of Gay resides in talking about all these far-reaching issues, which in other hands would have tended towards the bombast and the engolamiento of a pristine, crystal clear, simple form and without pretensions, without rhetoric or estentóreas proclamations, without empty rhetoric, paraphernalia without free ornaments.Throughout the film, obviously, things happen. But they are things of every day. For example, the four protagonists leave the mountain, distance themselves and the two more inexperienced are lost. What could have given rise to an Odyssey of suffering, overcoming, drama and others; Gay solves with an astonishing naturalness: lost both quietly descend and the fall of night reach a signposted path that leads them towards a mountain refuge and a village. As it has started to rain, staying at the shelter where, still uncomfortable, spend the night good.Naturalness. These is the key to the story. A naturally in abundance, in characters, in his dialogues, in their relations with their reactions. Characters of flesh and blood, taken from a reality that Gay, screenwriter and director, knows how to capture and describe perfectly. And is there a fact in the history and lived by the author: the sentimental failure of friends and acquaintances who, being young parents, throw down the drain their relationships.It does not have the realistic film of great predicament, today. However, films such as "Fiction", paradoxical title, you reconcile with these morsels of reality with these natural notes that persist over time. Where the spectacular special effects today, tomorrow are child's play, esas-mega productions which now command a huge media interest will be grass of oblivion. Films such as "Fiction", however, are to stay in the memory of the spectators, to be part of the sentimental and cultural heritage of this our society, and as it is the case, for example, with moral tales of Rohmer, who both reminded me this "fiction" that, with the passing of the hours, it is gaining in strength. A film that leaves poso.</body>
</review>
