<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="Ficción" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A devastating orgasm, a very powerful however so modestly erotic bomb: a quiet beauty, a delicatessen for film buffs, a pristine piece of art.</summary>
	<body>CESC Gay continues to grow: with "Hotel Room" was unveiled, a small, almost "underground" film, who discovered a talent in the making; with "Nico and Dani" confirmed its ability to tell stories related to love and sex, with a sensibility certainly striking; with "In the city" demonstrated its ability to discuss everyday issues to various bands, always interested, fascinated frequently. Now, seeing this little gem of recent Spanish cinema which is "Fiction", one recalls inevitably that beautiful love story East titled around the world "In the mood for love", and in Spain was distributed as "Looking forward to love" (see criticism in CRITICALIA), the Chinese filmmaker Wong Kar-wai. "Fiction" runs that same space, albeit in a completely different way; arguably the Chinese film is the inspiration, but the Spanish story has his own way: two human beings, man and woman, both reasonably happy in their respective relations, he with his wife, she with her partner, will live a few days of coexistence in the beautiful landscape of the Catalan Pyrenees; in this relationship, theorists friends, is brewing, no wait, a love that desasosiega. But both do not dare to take the first step, fearful of breaking their daily life, the gentle routine of their days with their respective partners. When both are on screen, which is almost always sutilísima tension is palpable, transcends from the screen in a way infinitely more disturbing than if the couple (who does not dare to be so) give rein to his unbridled passion. The only physical contact, the last farewell Kiss, will be like a devastating orgasm, a very powerful however so modestly erotic bomb: a quiet beauty, a delicatessen for film buffs, a pristine piece of art. Chapeau for the actors, all splendid.</body>
</review>
