<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="El corral" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fun and recommended beef story of overcoming. Films for children like this that does not insult their intelligence with jokes facilones are appreciated.</summary>
	<body>Films for children like this that does not insult their intelligence with jokes facilones that dot boring frames are appreciated. Get to know them, Aesop and safe Iriarte who would have dedicated them many of his fables. Moreover, if they lived and to have audiovisual culture, each animal of this curious farm would star at least one short film. With pace, used the surprises and playing with regarding film that among children they can pass unnoticed, this film connects with others such as Chicken Run (evasion on the farm), although more by that theme by the way already in this respect it reminds Jimmy Neutron, the same Director.After a recurring title hides a world that can not accessible to humans. Stevie Wonder composed the tracks on the album the secret life of plants, suggestive phrase which undersigned provokes images of flowers and shrubs with personality, such as which discovers Alice in her wandering around the country of wonders. Something so with this portrait of usos y costumbres bestial is not more than a vision of the most hidden life of animals. Having children as a target group, there are archetypal patterns, although it is not the most outstanding point of this fun beef story of overcoming. Policymakers seem to not care that cows with their udders and all, are male. This can confuse especially small. Inconsistency, but at the end and the place is one license more like them that have allowed the dubbers Spanish in its decision to impose a Galician accent to an unusual trio formed by three cows (males) mad.At times it becomes something excessive for its mellow ravings. History oozes moralina, not many, but enough to check which is the Lion King harvest. Here isn't Simba seeking the comfort and support of his father, lost in the firmament, but Otis resembles much the leoncito of the Disney in certain sequences. We know that references the current film lives and this work is full of them, although they also abound the hilarious moments provided by a ferret eager to sink the teeth to a pessimistic chicken. Fun and recommended.</body>
</review>
