<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Gal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Too based on real facts and get us it all done. Even they repeat a couple of times if we have not heard. And that the Viewer is not stupid, bored him.</summary>
	<body>The exaggerated histrionics stain this thriller which, however, can function in the same way that the Wolf, although only if one forgets to historical accuracy.After that story about the infiltrator Mikel Lejarza, had another episode related to the terrorist group ETA which should deal with their corresponding frames. An approximation in GAL that does not meet expectations.The case of the known anti-terrorism liberation groups arrives sifted by the look of Miguel Courtois who works the world of evidence. Possible realities assumed as certainties and corrupted by the torn apart at the same time commitment staff of Melchor Miralles, head of world fiction and one of the architects of the journalistic investigation of 12 years that brought to the fore the GAL case. Too often, a good writer (Antonio Onetti) does miracles.Watching the film one has the feeling that it is not fair, but at this point we know that there is no objectivity and less on film, a field open to all sorts of subjectivities to abide by the principle of creativity. Without entering the substantial historical matter? you will see as cuesta-, GAL delves into the journalistic profession: which is independent, the are trying to manipulate, which has interests. No one is free from sin.Plot starring gunmen, hardened reporters, confidants and victims are also executioners comes to rhythm of video clip as a sequence that squeaking above the others to be treated in parallel murders and luxuries funded card coup. We leave behind the characters stereotyped to the maximum. At this point we are not fulfilling promised and fall into the similarities with the story: an example, always convincing Jordi Mollá who here gives life to a being that Jose Amedo, recalls the Superintendent with the effrontery to torrent and José María Aznar.Es stop the most caricatured a hilarious cast: Abel Folk gets into the body of Pedro j. Ramírez; José Ángel Egido works a character half way between the former Ministers of Interior Corcuera and Barrionuevo; the? man of the tonic? do gives life to the parody of Felipe González - that accent, please - and relates the? wrong abduction? of second Marey. Most achieved are secondary to those who give life Ana Álvarez, Mercé Llorens, and Mar Regueras. But the couple protagonist weakens: not you think manual released claims the character of Verbeke and ridiculous are the winks of the enamoradizo played by García. anyone miss that behind this film is much of the people who rode the world of the 21st century but are so clear the references not being left via free the imagination and much less interpretation. It is too based on real facts and get us it all done. Even they repeat a couple of times if we have not heard. And that the Viewer is not stupid, bored him.</body>
</review>
