<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Ficción" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Is the film attractive? internal chat? that intends to Cesc Gay. Narrated from the rest, giving priority to the flow of conversations with oneself that we not hear, his fiction not uncomfortable and that it shows something so sad as a story about refrenadas passions.</summary>
	<body>This Alchemist working with sensitive material, emotions and relationships, dislike of great excitement. Supported in the family climate accomplice in which situates the story (promoted by the real links between actors and himself), Cesc Gay explores new territory, more restful than the before: leaving the city to take refuge in the rural environment, passes from the ensemble cast to intimate work... Load your backpack with close-ups of actors that have many things but without saying a Word, with the exception of camera, so vigorous and skillful as ever.Complete a trilogy about the problems facing us at every stage of our lives. Nico and Dani, in the city and fiction are very different among themselves, but is curious to cover stage: adolescence, the thirty and the maturity associated with the crisis of the 39, a veteran who comes naked and hopeless. The idea of the film is seen as an affectionate farewell hour and a half in keeping with the reflective look of a filmmaker who is doing with your site within the European landscape.With the permission of Eduard Fernández? there is to remember to remember a bad job-, subtlety is the main protagonist in a story that revolves around the feeling of resignation and responsibility. The search for inspiration is a plain excuse to abandon the life that you hastía for some time. and even there we can count.Gives just the end of the journey seem predictable, what matters is the journey, the trip to the other side of the world with pace leisurely, almost stopped and nothing artificial. Fernández is in Montse Germán to their ideal partner: he holds your gaze and balances the balance. The other three characters buzz limited to observing without altering nature. Away from apparently pretentious Gay poured into his paintings of life grateful and multiple references, musical and cinematographic, without going into metaphorical of the title and the character alter ego of the director.As a point we can say that filming took place chronologically, doing the work of the actors more credible. A liveliness that, like so many other aspects, comes in a subtle manner through a simple and beautiful love story that everyone is entitled to live. Because no lives who does not suffer, but only be a little bit.</body>
</review>
