<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Jackass 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This excessive mixing between laughter, embarrassment and disgust is not more than a surrealist and insulting, blows, testing wild and bloody tinker Carnival that does not deserve to reach the charts.</summary>
	<body>Grace is there, but it is so apparent that it not supported a feature film made by pieces engarzadas with the unique storyline of unconsciousness. Do more hard is that its proponents are not: know very well that the people retorcerá in the armchair at the time that ask for more and more, which gives idea of comparison with the? bread and circuses? of our ancient Romans so the populace saw no further from what their leaders are interested in to see.The leaders are a few thugs producers of MTV, television channel which has seen rises the audience with a group of Stooges able to do whatever. It is their religion, which leads them to put a leech on his eye that chupe blood, tear out teeth and vomit after. Vomiting, in short, that already gives quite disgusting!They smeared money to their foolish guinea pigs and leave them at home: what are you able to overcome with more wild proof? Well here. They have no any appreciation for your skin, your body. Something that comes from long ago: I thought that he would be lost not having seen the first part, but not. That Yes, an unknown force seizes us once inside the room, that they snagged the crap, each more absurd than the previous one. Do one of the graces may be in the dubbing into Spanish: professionals strive to provide their voices of that tontorrón tone that is sure have the possible original.¿Es version a spectator mimics the nonsense that hour and half occur on screen? We assume no, but we will not be any form of stupid life censors. Yes recommend us spending a single euro in this dubious work shot camera in hand, with close-ups and the signing of types such as Spike Jonze, as if this would constitute any warranty.</body>
</review>
