<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Milos Forman have a rather biased look at the complex Spain of late 18th century. It does so through a film also troubled and quite irregular.</summary>
	<body>You can be accused of lacking reliable reality but he defends argued that told a story, not the history with capital letters. Not going to see a portrait of the artist as he did Carlos Saura Goya in Bordeaux or, saving discrepancies, Bigas Luna in Volaverunt. Francisco de Goya takes second place: is not the protagonist but the witness of a few facts that during the first few minutes get hooked to then lose interest and consistency, for unnecessary dalliances.Da same be Javier Aguirresarobe behind photography, costumes have been designed by Yvonne Blake costume (with Oscar and 4 Goyas) or that it rodase in locations where the past comes alive. The libretto, the spinal column, weakens by an excess of Manichaeism: have good ones, which are until they cease to be so; the bad, the inquisitors, come to recognize the ineffectiveness of its methods.It has two distinct parts. On the second half flies the bird of the folletín, not without some burlesque tone, logically without trying it: the transformation of the character of Bardem hard to believe; Portman has good moments, by repetitive, are heavy. It appears that the protagonists are encorsetados in their characters, more concerned about not disappoint his followers with one film. Those who give life to historical portraits - Stellan Skarsgard as Goya - Swedish are delimited by the sight of the more literate; the rest, rather, José Luis Gómez is the one who walks with ease, despite incredible testing. Milos Forman (Amadeus, Valmont) is recreating past drawing parallels with the present. Here has tried to condense many aspects, too many and not very well yarn, a stage in our history which we were unable to capitalize. Challenge for a foreign director that passes a priori to be more critical and be more interested in the story than the patriotic. After the thrill is the impertinence by contextualizing the plot with topics in the style of Hollywood, emerging Spain that want to see, as well as Memoirs of a Geisha showed Japan through Western eyes. After the drubbing comes the defense because we must not be attributed to a filmmaker roles that do not correspond, as Professor of history.As product can work with luxurious sequences as containing an engraving process. And we are sure that we were not wrong in saying that you like more outside our borders that inside, where more than one is has been imagining the movie that could have been so juicy human material. We are still eager to enter through the cinema in a pictorial universe as varied, but you will have to agree with the purists: the paintings in the Museum.</body>
</review>
