<review author="Hartigan" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Agile and dynamic, but in its claim to cover everything becomes sharp.</summary>
	<body>The figure of Goya and his vital career, above the other artists, has attracted the eye of important authors. In the theater Buero Vallejo spent the sleep of reason and Carlos Saura made Goya in Bordeaux in 1999. To them they were joined by the Czech Milos Forman, director of legendary titles as someone flew over the nest of the cuckoo and Amadeus and whose last two movies, the scandal of Larry Flint and Man on the Moon, used the biopic genre to bring into play the social controversy environment issues as individual freedom from the provocation. So, the first thing that surprises of Goya's ghosts is Biographical paragraph is relegated to the background: it is not the person of Goya, their conflicts as man and artist, which focused the film, but that is a character only tangentially involved in the events. Which is not to say that Goya does not paint anything in this film: pint, and much. In fact paints it all. Your look is which gives sense to the story, which reveals their flashes of beauty and its depths of horror. His eyes and his brush, the only thing that keeps you tied to the world after suffering a deafness which has paradoxical biblical punishment dyes. It is the witness that puts voice to the innocent, "the flowers crushed by the chariot of reason" which spoke of Hegel in his fight against obscurantism. Another thing is that the value of this look is lost in the abstruse adventures of the main plot and the sometimes hasty pace of the film. The young Agnes, daughter of a wealthy merchant and Muse of Goya, striking a night of the Holy Office to not wanting to eat suckling pig in a tavern. He confesses under torture be judaizante and his father, in an attempt to free her, get Goya make an appointment with the brother Lawrence, with whom Goya is painting the picture and is responsible for the resurgence of the activity of the Inquisition. During that night, the family of INES used their own weapons against Lorenzo from which derive an absurd signed confession to him blackmail so intercede for his daughter. The "intercession" by Lorenzo just resulting in pregnancy of Agnes and the ruin of this that must go into exile. Twelve years later French troops occupy Spain, eliminate the Inquisition and Goya is reunited with a shattered Inés physical and mentally by his confinement and a Lorenzo converted into champion of the revolutionary and rational principles imposed by Napoleon to blood and fire.The thesis of the film is clear: both obscurantism and why drag his step innocent victims that nobody remembers. Power games are simple permutations of the same elements. The sleep of reason produces monsters. There is a real love for the work of Goya plastically reflected in this film, in the scenic reproduction of their whims. Something similar to what we saw in Alatriste, escenas-cuadro: in this film, however, are inserted with a much better sense of the opportunity. Do not be límitan to see: mean. However, something which "sings" greatly is the adultearación of original paintings so that they have the face of the actors. For example, the equestrian portrait of Queen María Luisa with the face of Blanca Portillo (magnificent on the other hand in their short speeches) is a blunder that stripping the film integrity. It seems that the director has become enmeshed in the mechanisms of the transition from reality to fiction, and in its intention to show Goya as a painter who makes works "too real" has ended up doing things that are directly false, both inside and outside the film. A Goya paints false works of Goya is a false Goya.Lo same is true for the rest of the film language. The film is agile and dynamic, but in its claim to cover everything becomes sharp. Twelve years pass from one scene to another. The characters appear and disappear without just transitions. This lack of subtlety gives the main plot the pretext of vaudeville who both have criticized you, with mothers, fathers and daughters that appear and disappear. In the height of clumsiness, Natalie Portman plays simultaneously the mother and daughter. Despite transformations truly impressive physical suffering actress, the parallel is blatant, even more when the good of Natalie does not have a variety of records. Outside these exits of tone, sharing works in an exemplary fashion and we must praise the roundness of the characters. Bardem, another guy that also stands out for its versatility, manages to give the entire extent of the vileness, while Michael Lonsdale as Grand Inquisitor is the perfection of the perversity without histrionics. Randy Quaid as Charles IV appears to leave the original brushstrokes of Goya to give them life in four exactísimos strokes. Finally - there will be have on this point, as it usually happens with the heads of cast - Stellan Skarsgård makes a great Goya. Not only by his physique that seizes the scenes by its intensity but to establish the dualism of the character, a Goya at first surprised by his debonair character and clumsy, but just leading to the bleak tragic sense of the author of the vagaries. It is not enough, however, to make a round film Goya's ghosts. The confusing pace and the tone that passes from melodrama to comedy in such a way that it seems sometimes accidental (particularly in the case of the interpreter of Goya, whose gestures move laughter even in the most dramatic scenes) tarnished its bright color.</body>
</review>
