<review author="Yul B." title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A movie to pass the time, without excessive enthusiasm. At least the original version may be more appreciated.</summary>
	<body>It is frightening to feel so visibly how the Spanish Inquisition raged in the lives of many innocent people.Scary see impotent used how heinous tricks and unfounded allegations and esperpéticas to stop torturing, accuse (after the confession to avoid the pain), and, finally, in the majority of cases, sentencing to death at the stake or the garrote vil supposed heretical enemies of Catholic orthodoxy.Such miserable work of evangelization and their consequences, incomprehensible today, is what shows mostly in this film.Moreover, it is the engine of history: a story that takes place through the eyes of the master Francisco Goya (Stellan Skarsgard) from the last years of the Spanish Inquisition in 1.792, through the invasion of Napoleon's army and ending with the defeat of the French and the restoration of the King of Spain by the British of Wellington.No army is more than the sad episode in the life of Inés (Natalie Portman)a teenager musa of the famous Spanish painter who is accused of heretic by the Episcopal inquisitors led by father Lorenzo (Javier Bardem), and imprisoned for 15 years without absolution.Milos Forman has managed to make a film of Goya where the painter is the least important of the history. He is the character as a mere observer, and at some times, like an unsuccessful mediator.Do do you would think that by this premise, the film disappointed immediately, taking into account that the title mentioned you with appearance of being its? leitmotif?. However, the tape fails entirely to the Viewer for other reasons very different from the explained, and which are outside the scope of the address.There are several strengths; among all the setting of the film. Do magnificent locations, majestic decorated and care clothing and props make of?The Goya's ghosts? a movie time visually believable, especially with regard to the scourge of the Inquisition. Historical accuracy in the rest of the details, including the figure of the artist, is another story.On the other hand, the script works very well for the first three quarters of the film, managing to keep a plot continuity entertains.And, finally, the interpretation that makes the character of Agnes Portman after being imprisoned for 15 years, is very successful and it is really emotional, especially in the final scene of the film. The incredible characterization of the actress helps quite.The weak points are also several; among all the auto-doblaje of Javier Bardem, mainly of the first part of the film (in its stage of Inquisitor). This actorazo has a port, an exceptional presence, which is reflected on screen, but his great touch is the naturalness with which represents their characters, so it is too artificial to see him portraying the father Lawrence with a voice dubbed by himself with an overly leisurely tone and suavón, that clears the cartoonish in English. In the second part of the tape, for plot reasons, his voice has to be different, more strong and secure, so then start to fit his image; but you are not going head which is a dubbing. The dilemma of doubled himself or leave the job to a professional has opted, in my opinion, for a misguided choice.If to this we add the appearance throughout the known Spanish actors film (is a UK-Spain) whose usual medium is television, along with characters from the gossip (Cayetano Martínez de Irujo y his Holy wife!) attention to the plot is lost. All this causes big ups and downs in the credibility of the story.Also the script at the end of the film becomes precipitate. The Napoleonic invasion and the restoration of the monarchy by Wellington spend in a sigh without giving time to assimilate the changes.With regard to the interpretation of Portman as Alice, the daughter of Agnes, is not excessively bright (divinely to hairpieces teeth more exaggerated have given) and his character slightly disturbs joining him temporarily with the same Agnes, much to say that the resemblance is amazing.Of Stellan Skarsgard can say little. It passes through the film as his character, making little noise.If we all commented in a balance, the result, in my opinion, would be a movie to pass the time, without excessive enthusiasm. At least the original version may be more appreciated.</body>
</review>
