<review author="Robgordon" title="Melissa P" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Except in the script, the rest seems removed from a middling telefilm</summary>
	<body>"The 100 hits", is the name of the controversial and successful book that autobiograficamente wrote Melissa Panarello, a young Italian woman now around the age of 19. This book brought the scandal to recount the sexual life of this girl when he was only 15 and 16 years old. And is that this is not a story of sexual awakening to the "Summer of 42", is a mirror of today's society in which sex is no longer a game of adults to be a game of children, with the risks psiquicos and physicists that this could lead.This is what it tries to convey in the film version of "Melissa p.", where sex with all its variations is discovered by Melissa young, when his innocence and his naivety still are skin-deep.This Lolita of the 21st century, the Italians have been imported to the Spanish Lolita, Maria Valverde, actress who became known and won a Goya for that great Manuel Martín Cuenca movie entitled "The weakness of the Bolshevik", in which knew how to give his character needed the sweetness and shamelessness. A discovery in that film, where only had 16, Valverde has become one of the most promising actresses of our cinema. Let us hope that his face añiñado and innocent isn't one day flower and which over the years know face roles other than the provocative girl. That you can attach to adult roles.On this occasion, his role again to require children's gestures with mature attitudes. Valverde convinces in its innocence, but not so much in its contact with the adult characters. There to wait for Valverde to comply 18 so he could shoot the scenes of nudity and the truth is that they have spared in such sequences, on the other hand, to tell a story, which is not necessary, but a sexual diary with all its consequences. In addition the dubbing of the own Maria Valverde, makes him a disservice in its Spanish version.The truly interesting thing of this "Melissa p.", although nothing new on the other hand, is something that already contained the novel. This mirror, as we say, in that a large part of the earliest youth can look. Sex and its consequences in a child that still uses backpacks and just stop playing with toys. The mental disorder that may ensue in the person. To reaffirm the fragility of the girl, the film introduces two characters and one ghost around Melissa. A mother who believes that gives everything to his daughter, but that in reality hardly known, a grandmother who understands the girl, but not live at home to advise her and a non-existent parent with which Melissa, only communicate by SMS.Therefore a portrait where we see a quinceañera, without patenal or maternal, help without the basic family environment which is needed for proper socialization of a human being. A house where solitude abounds. And with regard to the scope of the Institute, good and bad influences are shown on the tape. The choice of one or other part of Melissa, her lead to an uncontrolled sex hell or the straight path that corresponds to their age.The strictly film of "Melissa p.", little we save or highlight. What interesting and previously cited, was the basis of the book, and how could it be otherwise, remains on the tape. But the rest seems removed from a telefilm of middling, as or more likely chains to the telefilm seleccionarian for your grill.An address without touch, without taste. A bad montage and a terrible use of music.Luca Guadagnino, the director of the function, is halfway between the poetic tone and tone sordido. Enter characters that forgets easily to then introduce them again on screen without prior notice. In addition some sexual sequences are shot without the slightest talent. And what is most worrying, sometimes gives the feeling that we are before an announcement of compresses.There is nothing with a minimal relevance in "Melissa P.". A story nothing scandalous, (perhaps a few years ago if it were) sometimes free, with claim of offender, an unfortunate story, almost two boring hours of footage and a terrible direction. Isn't exactly with the recommendation of the week, although there will be many who were enamored with María Valverde in "The weakness of the Bolshevik" who want to see how it goes this girl with two years more.</body>
</review>
