<review author="Yul B." title="Gal" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do a documentary of short duration very? light?, overly artificial and hastily told.</summary>
	<body>It is usually more difficult to do a film based on real events in fictional facts. Especially because there is an implicit obligation to be as faithful as possible to the same. But it is that if these facts above are somewhat complex, the difficulty increases.In most of these cases it is necessary to do important work of synthesis to to sum up to the maximum account of events which in reality have lasted years (which we are discussing, 15). So it is logical and normal, that any tape of this genus is tell us the inspiring story of a rapid, almost frenetic form.And that is precisely what has happened with?GAL?. Throughout the entire film, one has the feeling that every moment of the plot there are fast and running, without allowing breaks, to give this time to treat the data immediately after and not leave nothing forgotten at the end. Part of the blame has it the length of the tape: only 100 minutes. Surprisingly little.There are, however, to recognize that the material on which this film is based is delicate: a sad episode in the recent history of Spain on the anti-terrorism liberation groups during the 1980s did the dirty war against the terrorist organization ETA. They were welcomed by the Ministry of Interior at the time, and were responsible for numerous killings and kidnappings, in some cases even against persons who did not belong to the terrorist organization.However, as it's a complicated structure, it would have been preferable to deal with it in a more partial way, without globalidades. Thus is had been able to enter deeper more highlights of this episode, even to argue, in the most rugged; as well as the personality of its main protagonists.The conclusion that is removed at the end of the tape is that a documentary of short duration, has been very? light?, overly artificial and hastily told. To Miguel Courtois, its director, he has fallen short work.What of? artificial? is an adjective addressed directly to the performances of the cast of the film.It must be borne in mind that none of the real people of the history has been literally depicted in?GAL?. All are more or less free versions of the characters directly involved in the case.But is that despite such freedom, no actor cast is saved from this lack of naturalness or credibility, not even the star Jordi Mollá. both José Garcia as Natalia Verbeke, which they give life to the journalists who uncovered the plot of the GAL, are caricatures of these pens.I do not know what is happening with Garcia, but his performance is really mediocre. Perhaps the dubbing post-production which is usually done in a few films (if any) which does not do justice, but does not give the likes of protagonist. In almost all scenes in which it has a text, he recites it as if had memorized it a few minutes earlier, and with very little naturalness.As for Natalia Verbeke, its shareholding in Spanish comedies make losing authenticity in a dramatic role. Put you effort, but fails to convince. It would be missing you encadenase several works of this same court, even more heartbreaking, to become credible in that row.And that I left half cold is Jordi Mollá, in his role as Ariza. In my opinion, sobreactúa. Or at least that is the impression given.Is not for their attitude or by its characterization, because that Yes has dominated it; It is your voice, too forced and unnatural wanting to give a tone so serious, hard and torn. This detail makes losing authenticity to the character in almost the majority of the scenes. Even sometimes it is comical. It is certainly not his best performance.The only strong point of the film is its technical aspect, called photography, editing, sound, soundtrack, etc. Everything together (except the flashbacks that sometimes baffle) builds a scenario very faithful to reality and ideal to clothe a very sinister plot.No wonder why as it was moving the film wishing with all my strength that no character opened mouth. What for?; to spoil her?. Do I still being with?The Wolf?.</body>
</review>
