<review author="José A. Peig" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In any case, this film is a good example to be able to distinguish the narration of the Fund alive, ambiguous and subtle envelope which should sustain. And it does not.</summary>
	<body>The arrogance of the human being and the inquisitorial intransigence are placed in the center of all the historical framework that shows compressed and polished for a rapid consumption in this new film by Milos Forman, another of the great filmmakers who us is now unrecognizable.You can give many hypotheses to try to clarify the reason why Goya was chosen as an excuse to shoot a very trite story about the Spanish Inquisition and the consequences of the Napoleonic invasion. In any case, this film is a good example to be able to distinguish the narration of the Fund alive, ambiguous and subtle envelope which should sustain.And it does not.The story itself, could offer more of what has been, and no doubt the story flows with enough sense of rhythm and progression of events, almost without respite to the Viewer, is moving at breakneck speed. Many are things narrated in 100 minutes, but the content is so hieratic, thick, rugged and devoid of life beyond a few characters that parlotean and go from one side to another, ending by deflate it and become another folletín to use, plagadito of platitudes and shamefully exempted from any hint of subtlety dramatic situations. I.e., this film is a product so flat, so inert, so obvious, so mechanical, that one cannot understand how it is possible to be sponsored by a filmmaker as form and, on top, allowing the luxury of starting its pathetic journey with an evocative musical band that accompanies the suggestive images of the paintings of Goya. It is not narrated history is "dense" or too complicated, it is rather the emptiness generated in the treatment of each of the thematic elements, profiles psychological or ineffective structure aimed at articulating the whole: from the individual drama depicted the characters played by Bardem and Natalie Portman to collective drama, and Goya as liaison and neutral perspective between the two. Disjointed and schematic, the narrative flows into a superfluous and shameful "sampling" of a time and facts represented with such simplicity, both in the text and Visual, that better be saving the time and money it costs to a film entry.</body>
</review>
