<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Ficción" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film about feelings that the only thing that made me feel was a considerable drowsiness.</summary>
	<body>Have you ever thought of being unfaithful to your partner? Do has been playing to be the almost-loving someone? Does he decided to finally do nothing? Therefore if you are married and with children, in addition to being a complete cocoon, might be the protagonist of the last film of director Cesc Gay.Jugando to be Isabel Coixet and trying to make a good movie about deep feelings, the Catalan director has concluded a mediocre folletín about the romance of a few snobs who are dedicated to the art world, he directs films and her playing the violin.The film tries to show how the feelings that do not pass, that frustrated so we keep for ourselves, have the same importance as those we expose ourselves to others. The problem is when these feelings stem from characters in addition to not have very clear what they want in this life surrounding the selfishness. Fruit of this interpretation the Viewer may feel rejection by what feel the protagonists.Much more rich and interesting is the intense relationship of friendship that we see in the characters played by Javier Chamber and Carme Pla and of which the director just shows a few scraps.Apart from the minor that gave me the beautiful alleged love relationship, other components of the film also helped me to digest her. Slow, too slow (only the character of Santi lighten some scenes), a little working script (when one falls in love with someone I understand that the communication flow between the two is of vital importance and the dialogues that keeps the couple recall a little to the "mythical" series out of class) and, as a final auction, a desperate and unnecessary morreo (more than love what seemed the jacuzzi of big brother).In short, a film about feelings that the only thing that made me feel was a considerable drowsiness.</body>
</review>
