<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Gojira (Godzilla)" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Sympathetic and endearing film that has perhaps lost strength over the years but remains entertaining and very dignified.</summary>
	<body>One of my old outstanding accounts with the cinema of entertainment that I both defend was the mythical "Japan under the terror of the monster" of Ishirô Honda, better known today as "Godzilla" or "Gojira", the film that created one of the most enduring myths of Japanese and universal film.It is not necessary to tell anyone that the tape is the fight in Japan against a radioactive monster that emerges from the depths of the sea because of the nuclear tests. It is not of more is that let us consider for a moment what he had assumed this film in its time.If it is not too early to make films about the attacks of September 11, 2001 in New York we are proposing in this 2006 in which we still live. Well, "Godzilla" is a film made in 1954, only 9 years after the massacres of Hiroshima and Nagasaki, which killed some 200,000 people (according to the most optimistic versions) and a few months after the nuclear accident of Castle Bravo/Daigo Fukuryū Maru. It very difficult to not think about the emotional impact that due presumably to the Japanese see again its cities destroyed and radioactive, even if in a monster film. The impact that the Atomic trauma brought the art of Japan abroad, particularly in his later film is also logical.Leaving aside those issues, I have to admit that the beginning of the tape, in the opening credits appear on an austere black background while it sounds the magnificent soundtrack of Akira Ifukube, the steps and the roar of Godzilla's Fund, get me the willies (view the trailer to check it). In fact the first half-hour film I quite like, has great rhythm and presents the story in a very effective way.The second half an hour for me is the failure of the film, since it deviates a bit from his way into minor characters is not that they pantry but should have been engaging differently in history. Thus, the pace is a little broken and interest lapses with regard to the beginning of the movie. Fortunately, it revived again under the exciting final climax. It is at the time when the anti-nuclear allegation becomes more evident and retains all its current.Ultimately a sympathetic and endearing film that has perhaps lost strength over the years but remains entertaining and very dignified.</body>
</review>
