<review author="Lara Croft" title="El ilusionista" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not enough me, hence my sense of guilt. Edward Norton with that stark and concentrated look reminds me more an astigmático than to an exalted illusionist.</summary>
	<body>How long have to turn a blind eye by no sin of arrogance? It is true that in this blog I have tried poorly to several films because I were comic to a superlative degree when its initial mission was not just the comedy (as proof of this just take a stroll through the category not see). But the goal of any visit to the cinema is usually the mission accomplished satisfaction and pleasure that generates a good movie, sensations that for one reason or another I am not from makes enough (at least with regard to the reviews on this blog). When I published my opinion about the great trick a few weeks ago I did it with the same ideas floating around in my head, but at that time, perhaps only be the first of two similar achievements, wasn't so strong sense of mission not accomplished. With the magician I cannot but feel some guilt to declare that I did not like. Because there are many factors that usually carry a movie to the rating of "Good" or "Very good" in some cases, factors which in this opportunity for me there have been sufficient.Music composed by Philip Glass, rarely so consistent and subtly dosed, photography Dick Pope (the secret of Vera Drake) with delicate cuttlefish who do more than immerse ourselves deeply in the Vienna of 1900 wonderfully set with the design of production of Czech Ondrej Nekvasil.Como always a pleasure seeing Paul Giamatti and can fit not only any shoe that reach you but also clothing (elegant not flashy) Ngila Dickson (the saga of the Lord of) (the rings). so? Then not reached me, hence my fault. Eduard Norton with that stark and concentrated look reminds me more an astigmático that to an exalted illusionist, Jessica Biel little lacks to earn the nickname of Miss gall. If your character is madly in love with the main character, is a well kept secret because there is no chemistry with Norton.Y finally Rufus Sewell as Prince Leopold has so many details of tyrant and dictator as the same great and surprising film illusion.</body>
</review>
