<review author="Alvaro Oliva" title="Gal" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Presented as an interesting proposal, but unfortunately we found a completely different product that film leaves much to be desired. .</summary>
	<body>Well could replace G by a M, the new proposal by Miguel Courtois leaves much to be desired, and has no point of comparison with its previous proposal. "The Wolf" was presented as a very successful, well interpreted thriller and a very interesting topic, as opposed to this, "GAL" is presented as a film rather boring, poorly performed and with a theme that is could have gotten much more party. Home hits the protagonist Carlos García, though French, in Bend could have been careful over in interpretation, intonation, and other vocal features, insofar as it seems badly bent on purpose, so start not we can believe this character. The same applies to Jordi Mollá, tried to imitate to Amedo, made him put the most serious voice, which has become a mixture of torrent and Carmen de Mairena, subtracting all the credibility to the character. I do not understand this decision, already that if what they characterize us as well that have done so and put us his natural voice, or if you want a little more "masculine", you would us the character in every way, without having to resort to something as false as it is that voice. Total than with the pearls released and this way of saying them, just doing you enough grace the character.Natalia Verbeke cannot pass. Unlike other films as "The method", here is not with the character but part of the blame also has the script, which has stuck with shoehorn phrases and I don't know very well to come. A clear example is when the duo of journalists go in search of a hideout of the GAL, and in the middle of the road type pearls are heard? We should already be close, that should be the tree with the brand. ? It may here not sound bad, but on screen is really regrettable, and more when they take place on a general level that could well have been left with the sound environment, in addition to dubbing and deepening more in this example, seems to read without the minimum interpretative intention.Once touched upon these points, we continue to find us some "jewels" continued to make incredible history. The best side as Merçè Llorens, Mar Regueras and Miguel Hermoso. In the case of Ana Álvarez should say it is irregular, as in some sequences is very well and others fail to believe us. Final "GAL" presented as an interesting proposal, and even more so on the basis of the experience of the previous film proposal of responsible for this, but unfortunately we found a completely different product that film leaves much to be desired.</body>
</review>
