<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Las uvas de la ira" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Chronic descarnada of the qualified injustice as demagogic by more rancid sectors of criticism, the film resists all destructive analysis with its sober treated social x-ray of an era.</summary>
	<body>1. The birth of a naciónAhora film has passed its first century, will be good (to complete this urgency of grilling recent make balance sheets and compose loas) remember the two trends which forged its matrix and its subsequent propaganda apparatus. On the one hand, cinema of nature documentary filmmaker, univocal, sober, naturalist, who filmed the departure of workers of a factory, put on the case, and the film creation, instrument valid of literature, visual entertainment (audio came later) to decimate the pockets of the proletarian and greedy worker of these new busy that just came out of the factory before recorded.The art should come after this first vocation of invention to entertain the masses and pursue them, between newly parido century so much misery, a distraimiento, a powerful stimulus to renew capacity of astonishment of the citizen.This statement of principles is important for putting the grapes of wrath in precise context. The film is born in a splendid Hollywood that is beginning to be considered what has later been: dreams factory, industry of epics larger than the life of the style that the wind.The new public debate between the great depression to survive and cope with the glamour of the new times, undeniable crucible of opulence and luxury. This is why what the film could not be born: not having been designed, produced and invoiced during a fragile temperament as they were the late thirties and principle of the forty States founding premise windsurfing from the novel by Steinbeck on which it is based (and in addition the Ford film) is the criticism of social injusticemanifested in the Joad, a family of Oklahoma who emigrated to California Golden in search of work once the mechanization of the field esquilme them all hope of progress and that a company they will expropriate their land, ancestral symbols of its roots in the world.Ruin and famine push them westward, the land of promise idealized by the new batch of rumors that draw a paradise to be discovered for the brave that hug. In this, Ford feels comfortable because, ultimately, what we are talking about is transfigured, metamorfoseada presence, of the classic western with his useless heroes they sacrifice to see birth a country and be they part of this mythical Foundation. This stench to Americanism novice is still noticeable in XXI century, but we not leave the argumentativa.2 line. The grapes of wrath baldíoLas trip is, as we have said, a rarity. Does not seem to be easy to make a very contemporary film, shackled in a so little margin of chronological difference: that portrayed the miseries of a country and its precarious work with such a degree of verismo.It is a film-mirror: a chronic descarnada of the injustice, that is, in the absence of laws to govern a country. Rated as demagogic by more rancid sectors of American criticism, reduced to easy tear melodrama, the film resists all destructive analysis with his sober treatise of social x-ray of an era.Describes a period of history from the same story: John Ford carried term in the middle of an economic depression excruciating so the film acquires, in its genesis, in its context, a patrilineal testimonial character, documentalist, truffled of a truth the reality not discussed because it was, at times, more raw, more atrocious than this fiction of a family that seeks its place in the world after having been dispossessed of whichin truth, it belonged.These dispossessed, these desclasados, these outcasts of the Earth are the film Joad. Archetypal characters that assume others compassion, that have nothing and they not want much, but lampan to find a site on which to build their new existence.Tom Joad (a sublime Henry Fonda who did not win a well-deserved Oscar) acquires a up Trade Union, social and political and civic awareness in their journey to the promised land. There is an epic of the working class exciting, heartfelt.John Ford opts for a realistic point of view: suits the plot dispossess of any artifice. What will narrate the director is an eviction, an exodus, so it has to adopt the technique of road-movie, which did not then exist either as a concept.The narrative discourse of the film (hence the Steinbeck novel) is an ode to the human. No Joad or the troubled Tom, so tight in his tormented complexity of failed, seeks a benefit that is not love, tenderness, the terroir (more closely). John Ford being a Catholic militancy and a declared Republican there is another view of the matter. Also fixed nor a guilty of this misery. The culprit (it has a character) it is a bank in Tulsa, but there is only an administrator that does what say you. To that (add) we cannot put him a shotgun before. It is a term. A worker. Otro.El travel, finally, abrupt climatólogicas inconveniences and transportation (this truck rickety where it is worth everything and where stirred an intense microcosm!), is vacant. The voyage to nowhere, that I would say our Fernán-Gómez. A trip that progresses to a destination that already intuímos: corruption, deceit, racism.California is Oklahoma, but two hundred humiliation beyond.I read does not much to the grapes of wrath disturbs, shocked. This is the perfect definition which I endorse. Especially shakes the sweep of faces that the Ford House (with very precise photography Gregg Toland, then collaborated with Welles on Citizen Kane) ago in the camp of illegal, its simple misery and without deception of the infamous barracks.Ma Joad, at the end, said: "We are the people". "Always exist". His son, Tom, the ghost (there are up to a disk of Springsteen that takes this idea: from the espectralidad of the failed and anonymous hero of Tom Joad) wanders a changing, utopian, lyrical and brutal country is clearly in the figure of the disenchanted preacher, which hangs the habits and grabs new faith, labor activism then it became what today we understand as unions. The acclaimed reception of the film in the Oscars that year (best director for Ford and best supporting actress for Jane Darwell in the role of the tender mother) infer that times were changing and that America (that part of America, more properly) condescendía to the navel-gazing and declared unstable, corrupt, but also hopeful and exciting. It was a country by train, stuck in a war and a devastating economic disaster renanciendo.The Joad were there to raise the flag of his homeland. John Ford, not forget, was a Patriot mind-sets. No adversity they would bother too much. Why are heroes and that is why one attends this formidable show with the shrunken heart and with the secret idea that the world, despite their frivolities, their here and his penalty (both punish to die for one, said our Miguel Hernández) worth and in the journey, in transit, is the joy of life. The story that we see is the story of man: its achievements and its penalties. Universal, enduring film.</body>
</review>
