<review author="Dragon negro" title="Saw 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It accuses the lack of surprise. Well thought out and successful, although the final surprise is rather weak in comparison with the previous installments.</summary>
	<body>New installment of the serial killer known as Puzzle that follows where we stayed in the second part. Puzzle is bedridden in a dying bed and his assistant which is responsible for preparing the tests whose first victims will be among others the police that in part II pursued the murderer. Puzzle hours are few, but still have time for a last game while it kidnapped a doctor to keep it alive during this.The third part of Saw accused the lack of surprise and impress the Viewer, that tests are nothing more than the same has already seen with slight modifications and some failures of imagination this time. The film runs between two lines argued them, the man caught and faced various tests, and the murderer about to die in bed and the care that carry you out the doctor, under threat of death clear. Thus this second line is the most interesting and which arouses more curiosity to know if Puzzle will survive or not.Large doses of blood and violence back to be present and are already the House brand, but I said, that already they do not impress both and have lost this capacity surprise and cause the bad feeling that they gave in the first and second part of which still hurts if I remember the hole full of syringes. All the pieces of the film just fitting in a puzzle, the murderer does not leave any loose, nothing is the result of random, it is all part of a grand master plan that has just developed as he laid down. As such the film is well intended and achieved, although the final surprise is rather weak in comparison with the previous installments. But, in spite of its many flaws, the film entertains and appeal to all who enjoyed other deliveries. In addition, his great collection at the box office has assured a fourth installment in the face of next year, we Saw for a while.</body>
</review>
