<review author="Sara Rodriguez" title="La fiera de mi niña" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Work very thorough and aesthetic who inherited many things of the silent film era, a few gags incredibly disparatados, entanglements absurd, misunderstandings and confusions, reinforced by a few as well elaborate dialogues that is difficult to forget them.</summary>
	<body>Shot in 1938 and starring two major film, Katharine Hepburn and Cary Grant, "The beast of my girl" (Bringing up Baby), was not a box-office hit. In fact, Howard Hawks was fired by RKO and Hepburn, which at the time was considered "box office poison", after having invested in the film and renounced charge for this film (the conditions placed by the producer when they agreed to make the movie), was forced to buy his contract. Although in the end not he went so badly that the tape was reporting him benefits until the day of his death.With "The beast of my girl" they were already two times that Grant and Hepburn were working together. They had already agreed on "La gran aventura de Silvia" of George Cukor and would recur together with other fun comedies as "Live to enjoy" and "Philadelphia stories" of the same director. But this time, the two would be part of another example of films go unnoticed, even to fail at the box office, but that eventually become cornerstones in the history of the cinema. This course is one of the most famous of the time in its genre.Okay, is a comedy (or to be more exact, a "screwball comedy", name given to the crazed comedies of the 1930s), a quite undervalued genre today, and Yes, is white and black, which will cause more than one an allergic reaction and a sudden attack of drowsiness, but this is not one comedy any. For me, it is humor with capital letters.Tells the story of David Huxley (Grant), a paleontologist that luck smiles: just found the last bone that was missing to rebuild a Brontosaurus and a spinster millionaire is willing to donate a million dollars to his Foundation. In addition he is about to marry his Secretary Alice Swallow. But suddenly appears Susan Vance (Hepburn), a crazy girl that puts his life upside down (with the help of a Leopard named Baby) and that will prove to be the niece of his possible patron.Apparently history has nothing out of this world and still we have not forgotten that is in black and white xD, but is that Howard Hawks really knew how to make movies and to check just need to take a look at his filmography with great titles in genres as diverse as comedy, westerns, war moviesscience fiction, film noir or musicals. All of them are characterized by the unmistakable personal touch of Hawks, who used to say things like:-"I have ten commandments to make a movie." The first nine are: do not get bored!.-"A good movie is based on three good scenes and no bad".All this makes it's not hard to imagine what we will find in this film, after its simple appearance hides a very thorough job, an aesthetic which inherited many things of the silent film era, a few gags incredibly disparatados, entanglements absurd, misunderstandings and confusions, reinforced by a few as well elaborate dialogues that is difficult to forget them.Not in vain Hawks had worked as a screenwriter and knew who surround themselves. Another reason why is considered an exceptional director is the unbridled pace of his films. He himself used to say that they unfolded 20% faster than the other productions of the time, something that we see in "Bringing up baby".Finally, we must not forget master interpretations has the film, which is by far one of their strengths. Katharine Hepburn, after testing it was one of the best dramatic actresses of his time, register and shows that it was also a comic actress of the first order. In addition, combines perfectly with the charismatic Cary Grant, who despite having gone bad considering having some scene close to the Leopard (in fact refused to appear with him), he used no double coming to perform some that other acrobatics in the final minutes of the tape and stars in unforgettable moments with Hepburn. Surely anyone who has seen recalls the song that you sing to the Leopard: "Everything you can give it less love you babyyyyy."Maybe that one can put some but to the "special effects" or the filming some scenes with a stuffed Leopard, but come on, there is nothing that can not forgive taking into account that it is a film of the 1930s.</body>
</review>
