<review author="Iñigo" title="Flores rotas" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>He relates the concerns of the contemporary man, with abundant metaphors and unforgettable moments</summary>
	<body>The life of Don, a Don Juan gone in years, has become a kind of stagnation, in a purely innocuous wait. A man who has been (and is being) how his life and opportunities escape, while he remains static and parsimonious in his sofa. His life is going. but he is simply able to see it pass without even analyzing situations, assess them or think a minimum of them.Don is alone. Don feels alone. He feels that his life is not anything that can be fact you. But do not feel (forgive the double meaning) to think about it, to find the reason for his condition.It is a totally empty and lost, man that can not get to see any notion of vitality or feeling. But he that seems to not care. Actually, at the moment not known the meaning of importance.It is part of your sofa. The closest thing to a static object simply was let go by weather, by chance or by the cobwebs that the wheel of your life can bring you.Bill Murray, our particular and bland Don Juan last thread, fashion and everything that happens to him the most avid Viewer is immersed in one of those roles that only he could make culminating with a convincing result. The character of Don him goes like ring finger, that I do not think that nobody dude. And after other similar jewelry jewels as "Lost in Translation" (especially the movie Sofia, with which "Broken flowers" saved certain parallels) or "Life Aquatic", has seen how the celluloid has managed to discover the perfect hollow of the actor between so many unexplored aspects.For many is now even dated, but it is absolutely true that there is no actor (at least in Active) able to do its job without doing absolutely nothing. Bill good is unique in making its inexpressiveness gala, but giving it at the same time of an impressive expressiveness, however much that contradict both cases. That is, our "Ghostbusters" in particular, a time to here (as many think), just to earn a salary is walking ahead of the camera wearing her deadpan facies and its position static (almost to the cadaverous stiffness) to any corner, situation or moment, requires it or not the sentiment reflected in the script. No heckling of any kind. And the funny thing is that he achieved much more than other "academic" actors who use such hackneyed technique books and/or workshops.And I think that there lies one of the weak points of his detractors. They see him, without doing anything remarkable, produces unexplained results. And that can certainly be frustrating.With a single face (which, I might add, nor is any expression standard bearer), a simple opening of the mouth beyond than usual in his person or a simple turn of the head, comes to communicate in a brutal way. Maybe a similar feeling always communicates (vacuum, vital distaste, irony, apathy or pasotismo), but is something really complex.Comes me to mind one of the eyes of Zissou in "Life Aquiatic", replete with an innocence and depth anthology, which I doubt that any actor (with all the gestures and words of the world) could match, much to do. Bill Murray comes without barely raise it. It is his way of acting.Maybe for some, that could undermine her merits. But his talent is there. To convert ordinary and banal into extraordinary and profound. And, although be aware of many things that I have argued, to me, personally, I love it. Yes. I love Bill Murray. I adore your inexpressiveness. It is so. expressive.Thus in "Broken flowers" see a Bill/Don has stopped being human ago time. Its vital carelessness has already reached a point of no return, a time in which, much to do, nothing can be achieved. And the problem is that he does not want to do anything that turbe his banal and boring life. Gives you fear the mere fact of thinking about it. What search sense things? It is better than the time pass, the present Act, the past is left behind and the future. simply come.Jarmusch, braid, a seemingly simple story, can watch with great ease, but that is fraught with great sense of many of those issues that occasionally we set, but sometimes not dare to analyze them. What will happen is fearsome.Among so much simplicity and apparent banality, Don can glimpse a small hole in which look and reconsider their own existence. And, although their desire to live and feel sometimes lead you to madness or absurd imaginations, you can rediscover himself. Maybe realizes that his life has been ridiculous, is an indomitable asshole or that it has been wasting time, but at least not fail that things come as is."Kafkaesque" search of his supposed son is just an excuse to look for himself, give meaning to a life that is lost and without direction. Imagination, the power of inventiveness, the desire to make sense of things and search are things that give strength to the spirit before such zafiedad and carelessness of a past. Therefore, no matter if the kid is really his son, what will matter is the journey made. Although end resembling an abnormal, an idiot who returns to observe (unperturbed) how his life is absurd. But, again, it will give you all the same. Or maybe not.Film director as "Coffee and Cigarettes", carried out in that way, which is his best work. Her it garnished with their logical touches of personality, with those elements that differentiate a director with talent and full of ideas. Therefore, we again see that mixture between surreal/absurd and ironic humor and sobriety of a calibre close to exhaustion. It is, in appearance, a very serious film, but at the same time full of situations which will result in the laugh, even though it it also from a point of view serene, parsimonious and acid.We can also see other classic elements of the film from the director of "Permanent Vacation". Their accurate drawings, their continuing breaks, its scarcity of dialogues (often unnecessary), the image apparently empty or banal, and that it is actually loaded with nostalgia. As an example, we have these repeated scenes of travel by car from Don, in which show us the elements that pass or the spots through mirrors, as throwing the look back, looking for a pleasure lost in nostalgia. That same, to cite something, gives us to understand the sad past of a man who was Don Juan par excellence and is today a Don Nadie. These elements her almost approaching a "road-movie", with gear that could articulate her as a work of cult and, no doubt, as the best film of Jim Jarmusch. His earlier works are discussed between the genius and the irregularity, but none reached the level of formal perfection of "Broken flowers". A luxury and an example of how to make a different and sincere film.All this sprinkled with a great touch on the picture, in charge of a David Lynch classic: Frederick Elmes. And not forgetting the excellent musical choice, worthy of a nearly masterful success.As regards interpretations, one could say that the rest of the cast is really good, but is completely overshadowed by the presence of Bill Murray.En final, we have a very relaxed pace work, with a serene, flow without potholes, which manages you goals fully in the history and see her as something natural, sincere and very credible. It's something real and close, despite the apparent extravagance of his characters.It is a very common theme in our time as the loss of vital sense of a man who thinks that it no longer has anything to offer, after being all in earlier times.Relates the concerns of the contemporary man, with abundant metaphors and unforgettable moments: the rediscovery of the new life (not very stable or happy, so to somehow) his past relationships, touching occasionally extravagance in his travels, or, for example, the terribly scathing wink with the appearance of the particular "lolita" of Jarmusch. For all types of palates.</body>
</review>
