<review author="Silvia Giner" title="El camino de los ingleses" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is very well directed, that is undeniable, but despite the good things that I have told you, I did not like.</summary>
	<body>Well, last night I was passing for scholars of "camino de los Ingleses". This is my verdict. This is without a doubt one of the criticisms that more work has cost me perform, not is whether this will be significant. This film is based on the famous novel by Antonio Soler, awarded the Nadal in 2004 and that Antonio Banderas as director, adapted for the cinema in a rather peculiar way.Seemed notable the way that you have chosen Antonio to tell us this story which in my opinion is quite vulgar. In this case I'm more with how to with what.This story than a principle (what said of the way of telling things), may seem a real mental, tells straw with the deep voice of Fran Perea (congratulations Fran) the crossroads of teenage lives that meet at a point of the way of life in which decisions away from the fate that had fixed, in order to escape their sad reality and achieve their dreams, the camino de los ingleses, shown as allegory in the materialization of a street of Málaga excess of sex that I got to be even grotesque in some scenes. An ode of Andalusian, with the rescue of the best actors that has given this land, as Juan Diego, a native of Bormujos (Sevilla).To highlight the direction of actors, which found me very good, it shows the involvement of Antonio at this point and the picture beautiful on many occasions. As a lover of the flat burned, I have to admit that fascinated me one final sequences with Victoria Abril (great by the way) and Alberto Amarilla FACE to FACE. Albert, I mean I liked his performance, the expressiveness of his eyes, this is an actor that communicates that comes to you, although you have to improve some techniques. Without a doubt the worst of this distribution is María Ruiz, excessively higher in camera, for the role (bags, Crow's feet and lines of expression included) this actress that we have previously seen in "The amazing world of Borjamari and Pocholo", not just convince me, its performance is mediocre and transducer? big mistake its presence in this film, eye, this does not mean it is bad actress, simply that are not adequate either your profile or your interpretation. Absolutely all the supporting actors, seem greater for the role that interpret, all, except one as the grandfather, the body (great Maria Nieto) and some more, in particular referring to adolescents, we continue insulting the audience putting actors in 28 years to play the role of a boy of 19? regrettable, little credibility and total nightmare giving wanting to flee with dread of the room.I liked this incursion of flags as director that the film is very well directed, this is undeniable, but despite the good things I have cash, not liked. Those who do not like the cinema that will not see, because this is no doubt a tape of author. Band sound, curious and evocative.</body>
</review>
