<review author="Caruco" title="The Queen" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will serve to revive the debate on the need of the monarchy, and the personalities of Elizabeth II and Lady Di.</summary>
	<body>Stephen Frears, once fierce chronicler of wild capitalism that fostered the first Minister Margareth Thatcher during the 1980s in England, with titles such as "My beautiful laundrette" or "Samy and Rose make it up", returns with this telefilm of luxury that is "The Queen".A chronicle of the Black week, the six days that made wobble to the British royalty, which broke with the death of the popular Princess Diana, on August 31, 1997. And Stephen Frears, as Prime Minister Tony Blair (Michael Sheen), labour, submitted in the first instance as reformer and modernizer of the English Government, almost just converiéndose the fan number, not Lady Di, but also of this superior, elegant and stately Queen Elizabeth II, who plays so well Helen Mirren. discretion and dignity.However, more than an admirer of the monarchical, and despite showing with sympathy, and somehow endearing creatures that made up as Prince Charles (Alex Jennings), Prince Philip, the Queen's husband (James Cromwell) or the Queen Mother (Sylvia Syms), Stephen Frears seems to enjoy nice in this recreation of a historical fact that put in check, before his own people, to the royalty.With an Elizabeth II educated in forms already deciduous and away completely from the feeling and the ways of thinking of its people. That you want to act with "discretion and dignity, without publicly express or mourning at the death was his daughter-in-law, and without disguise, in privacy and with"discretion", the hatred that had for him. "But that won't have little choice but to requests from citizens, the pressures of the media and the advice of the Prime Minister Tony Blair, to show his, no sense, mourning the death of Diana in public."This fool Blair! "And in addition, your tea will has enfríado", he exclaims her husband back to reality, with all the kindred, a refugee in the summer residence of Balmoral, dedicating himself to hunting and take tea. Example of one of the pillars of an ancient almost ancient institution, or a symbol still necessary to the capacity of a nation, according as you look at it.Duel's popularity.At the funeral of the mourned Di Lady being called two million people and, on the first line, names such as Elton John, Tom Hanks, Steven Spielberg, Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman. And the ceremony was followed, in a spontaneous reaction by millions and millions of viewers around the world. A convening power and popularity, unimaginable to the Royal family.Before what is approaching, even the Queen come to identify with an elegant stag with a Horn of 14 antlers as majestic as unique in its kind, perhaps destined to extingirse soon. While the members of the new reformed Labor Party to power the calls "gorrones" that cost millions of pounds taxpayers.Priceless scenes with Cherie Blair, the wife of the Prime Minister, scathing and radical antimonárquica (Helen McCrory), for example, during the visit to the Queen, with poses of reverence and respect looks so forced and ironic, as patosas, while Queen Elizabeth II provides with some contempt but yes, keeping the "dignity".Moreover, the realization of Stephen Frears is absolutely flat, relying on the script and the good work of its actors. "The Queen" will serve to revive the debate on the need of the monarchy, and the personalities of Elizabeth II, Queen "dignified and discreet" in their stale hierarchy; and Lady Di, the "Princess of the people" with hook for a world in need of idols.</body>
</review>
