<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bond is played the skin much more and is less predictable. Even the love story have few drops of truth that one is not expected of this immaculate dandy.</summary>
	<body>Casino Royale begins with a declaration of intent. 007 discovers the traitor of the Organization and while the villain him lecturing on how difficult it is to kill a man, 007 flies him head. Bond is not, in this installment, the blameless man who only returned blows without dirtying the tuxedo. In this installment, it seems that it competes with Ethan Hunt, and nearly beats hard. This is the Bond you never had commissioned from Roger Moore.Se called "Casino Royale" because Bond plays a Fortune with a criminal who handles the money of the terrorists, Le Chiffre in a casino of Montenegro. Le Chiffre is a bad much more real than the previous series. Not build huge fortresses useless to make Bond the pieces. Just much more easy to understand and to believe, and to foster criminals money is it played in the bag and the tiles. If it loses the game knows will make it mince.Bond chases a small criminal in Madagascar in a retrospective collection of acrobatics and pull thread up to discover a conspiracy in an airport, also anthology. Thus arrives at Le Chiffre.Cuando Bond persecutions had fallen into a rut, one you know before it will lose its Aston Martin in a ravine, this installment makers have decided that they could still surprise us. Bond is played the skin much more and is less predictable. Even the love story have few drops of truth that one is not expected of this immaculate dandy, dipsomaniac lover of the martinis. The scene of the girl under the shower by the weight of his conscience the had signed Truffaut.Hay a rule script that says that the second act can not end well. If it ends well, it is that it will happen something terrible. In reality did not lack the rule. When the protagonist has achieved what he wants and does not fall the iron curtain, one already prepares for the Gale.</body>
</review>
