<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Storm" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The stridency of modernity in three acts entirely dispensable Garners however, condescension, even if it is only about the risk involved in this Europe with so much need of film that combines box office and critical.</summary>
	<body>Storm is a Swedish film that not directs Bergman which is so to say a pop group other than Abba and Roxette. Moreover, well it could have been Namibian or Belgian. Now the film has these things: that his arguments happen in a country abstract, decontextualized. As well (guess) any viewer can identify better with what it has.In Storm this (lawful) reflection marra: the couple protagonist embarks on a crusade which at times seems a Treaty of psychoanalysis and by others we see a metaphysical thriller deep Kantian principles. Or is. That the directors (two perpetrators of the event) will have bundled more than enough and, in the end, they have delivered a mass entertainment with pedigree of art and essay not enters through the eyes and that escapes (is my case, let's see, going over the years losing mental fortitude and can not stand three jets followed) by some brain gap that we not well closed.To me I was whole. It also took little. It could be the afternoon or mood or a symbiosis of both with a plus of prior labour fatigue. Storm is a disconcerting film, which does not mean bad altogether. Not it admits to clear any gender and dive without enthusiasm complex sea the abundant mini-géneros will be presenting by way of sophisticated fashion show. It is not concerned at any time by calling stylistic or narrativamente in any. Perhaps (for its deliberate lack of serious pretensions) do you not need.Storm is a creaking Mystic: maybe Swedish cinema post-Bergman is everything and the Nordic public is already tired of pastors that persuasions on faith and Sin in a farmhouse lost in a forest. Master Bergman, which to me bores me a lot, was the case. The fascination exerted by some of his portentous images (the dark streets, the camera dives, twisted on the pavement) does not save the film, but not they drag it to total oblivion. There are moments of cinema care: there are no two bunglers, but also shines the pulse of a steady hand who knows at all times what and in what order. This lack of clarity exhibition is, in my view, previsa the very succinct script.Interested in the hodgepodge between the naïve and the hardcore, this deadpan limbo of its complex (and abobada) plot. The style of Storm is his no-estilo. And that has a merit is the Swedish film or, as I say, Mozambique. We have the belief that history is not the fundamental attraction but there are other possibilities: we are more aware of not losing that reach port. Is that a symptom of a bad film? I have not clear at all. Do not rest you a charm, a picturesqueness, a certain artistic direction, a simple composition of the scene that brush a plot with a vocation for science fiction or modern thriller or horror, but some dialogue disarm my patience and produce me a huge intellectual anxiety that disturbs me hours later of seeing it.The stridency of modernity in three acts entirely dispensable Garners however, condescension, even if it is only because of the risk that is, in Sweden, in this Europe with so much need of film that combines box office and critical, making this film. Let us not, then, hard in excess, but in what to me it regarding promise not lie with viewing except that oblivion disturbs me or me again soft like a croissant at eight in the morning. Oh, and if someone sees and has more wisdom than I am to see if it explains me the storms that come and go and the ultimate meaning of the box of yore. I just need a psychoanalyst. Argentine, if possible.</body>
</review>
