<review author="Otis B. Driftwood" title="Scoop" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Allen again, nothing, to delight us with a good invoice job, it is not bad bearing in mind that it is going to pace of film per year.</summary>
	<body>This is a film of Woody "normalità", which in my own scale of values means that it is worth the price of admission. Without being even remotely of the good of the director of Brooklyn, the fact is that tells the story works, is simple, unpretentious, fun without falling into the grotesque and adds the speck of intrigue that came so well in "Mysterious murder in Manhattan", adding more suspense with unequal fortune.But it is also a romantic comedy, field in which Allen isn't safe specialist of collateral form, or if you like inherent to most of his film, in the sense that there is always a story of love kicking during the footage and that serves to especiar the plot. Here is part main of what counts, both or more than the history of research, and this allows to become more involved with the characters that if had been limited to tell the story of this aspiring journalist, Sondra (Scarlett Johansson) who, in the most unusual way, stumbles upon what may be the pitch information of his life. Determined to get the exclusive of the unmasking of a serial killer, just falling for the main suspect, Peter (Hugh Jackman) and is submerged in a dilemma between their feelings and the ability to be getting into the bed of a dangerous criminal.Woody Allen here again in front of the cameras, reserving a small but juicy role as Splendini, an unlikely conjurer that malvive of the cheaper tricks of the genre. As you can see, a mattress perfect to bounce the neuro to which we are accustomed. In his eagerness to help Sondra despite the Funk feel, you will have the opportunity to be ducks on countless occasions, while also getting unexpected success. Provides, therefore the indissoluble comic note of his productions of what you give to call its "third stage" (see the summary on "Mysterious murder in Manhattan") and when it is not Allen onstage (this time leaves little, we suspect that did not tiring), appears his roster of carefully chosen actors to fill the screen. More or less: on the one hand we have Hugh Jackman, who seems to have been paid to the role of Heartthrob when it does not grip of steel and that makes sovereign efforts so not notice you that it is Australian; It is correctito. On the other is Ian McShane as the spirit of the Reporter Joe Strombel, miserable, vile, creeping and effective even after his death, i.e., McShane in its purest form (what a shame to not see him in more movies). A classic, Charles Dance, also appears in a rather testimonial role. And, carrying the weight of history, we have Scarlett, on which I can never be objective but whose freshness and latent sexuality are capable as myself I could watch at the movies, get a murmullante room to stay completely in silence (men and women) when you remove the bathrobe in the pool. I do not deny that the comical vis what is perhaps needed in this kind of films, particularly when your opponent is Woody Allen lacks, but let's be serious. I doubt very much that the viewer wait that it is she who round off the jokes.Allen returns, therefore, to delight us with a good invoice job, it is not nothing wrong taking into account that it is going to pace of film per year (I think that the next is already in Assembly phase) and that also, because of this, can leave you authentic brick type "Celebrity". Moves much better in their histories of ninety minutes and it shows. He repeats his scheme and again, but you have taken so far that it is difficult to it goes you wrong. I will not say that "a masterpiece each year" that tend to drop the phrase enthusiasts, but I do believe that it is fair to recognize that, at least for who this writes, Woody Allen is reason enough to go into the cinema without a shadow of doubt.</body>
</review>
