<review author="Otis B. Driftwood" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Craig transmits many nuances to the character, as many as the new approach requires, and for my taste - I'm sorry girls - it makes it infinitely better than Brosnan, whose greatest merit was put face of palo embittered during the footage.</summary>
	<body>This James Bond is different. It had to be different, by force, for many reasons: the key, the character needed an "emerging", one updated to preserve its essence and gain a new audience that was beyond us, nostalgic fans who grew up with Sean Connery and Roger Moore. From the point of view of producers, that reason implies a strong economic, undoubtedly, vital to the survival of the franchise that has been able to extend for more than forty years, but ran the risk of anquilosar is. And opted for the more risky bet, actually: preserve the character more "conneryano", but humanizing it, i.e., Bond continues to be indestructible, but that status is not obtained for free, but through a hard process of forging character. and how to do that? Since bringing the character to its origins, this is, the novels of Ian Fleming that gave him life and containing a rather less limpid than the films Bond. The trick is to make "Casino Royale", first of these novels, the first adventure of the British agent as a double zero, licensed to kill. Thus the 007 incarnate by Daniel Craig is younger, more impulsive, more trusted, more arrogant and, paradoxically, less certain of himself. All these faults will be polishing disappointments and sticks, especially many clubs, as in "Casino Royale" see how James him shake as nice on several occasions. Yes, dear readers, James Bond bleeds, shouts, gut pain, physical and moral. He has no fear, because to reach double zero has had to remove it long before, but he looks much more fledgling and vulnerable.This approach, along with the election of Daniel Craig as an actor that would embody the get smart, planted of controversy this film much earlier, even start shooting. However, I like both the approach and the interpreter, although I admit that I was of them that they hesitated with the election. With regard to the physical, it is clear that this Bond is precisely the opposite Pierce Brosnan, but it already happened at the time when Moore replaced Connery in 1972. In this case I believe that change is even better, since Craig provides much more tough guy image. On the character and his interpretation, I think a very novel way to portray to the actor to evolve with it, giving the impression that in forthcoming films grow and mature at the time that makes Bond (or vice versa). Craig passes many nuances, as many as the new approach requires, and for my taste - I'm sorry girls - it makes it infinitely better than Brosnan, whose greatest merit in the four films made as 007 was put face of palo embittered during the footage, without showing even a pinch of humor that this always leads get.Moreover, the film is quite entertaining. Without being the best in the series, it outstrips its recent predecessors (except, perhaps, "The world is not enough"), and since then, reconciles with those who almost vomitamos with such bad taste joke called "Die another day". "Casino Royale" largely meets all the elements that make the Bond franchise which has always been, with scenes and spectacular scenery, action vibrating when it is (and give thanks to Martin Campbell, the director, learned the lesson of "Goldeneye" and already not extends persecution to infinity), a perhaps unusual hardness to which we were accustomed andvery important, return to the rounded bellezones with languid anorexia that seemed imposed in the last decade. Eva Green as Catherina murine illuminate the screen while falling drawn to the charms of our hero. A couple of bugs that I find and that are fairly obvious: one, the footage again excessive by the ballast of wanting to explain too much that could be explained alone; the other is that the villains, although they come equipped with all the Repertoire of tics and own iconography bondiana physical defects, appear somewhat diluted in its conception and never seem to be at the height of 007, do not give that feeling of omnipotence that no doubt appeared in almost all the previous films. Maybe that he has wanted also "humanize" the villain as they do with Bond, but if so the effectiveness in this case is much lower. Also squeaking some blunders of continuity that, while not influencing the history, fans of life may seem annoying; for example, the fact that "M" remains the "new" head interprets Judi Dench from "Goldeneye" (and also in this film before, indeed, as successor to Admiral Miles messervy ever besides) and yet here appears as his original head. That and the disappearance of the characters of Q and miss Moneypenny, but if I have to be sincere, I no missed them less.As I try, quite risky, revitalize the franchise, would put you a significant effort. Certainly needed polishing many things and that, certainly we will have to get used to see a more mundane James Bond although it remains invincible and irresistible in equal parts. The survival of the brand and the character much depend on how the public reacts to this new (or perhaps not so new?) visions of Mr. Bond. That Yes, the writers should take into account that this 007 will be much harder and aceradamente cold in the next films, and that the caprices that come here excused by history not be allow you so blithely later, when you suppose that Bond has managed to eliminate them. I'm not saying no nonsense of fan obtuse with this, put that in the same "Casino Royale" that is already pointing in a way nothing evening towards the end of the tape. And if producers are consistent with this, I have the feeling that we will still have James Bond / Daniel Craig for a while.</body>
</review>
