<review author="Bloody Will" title="El ilusionista" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>"The illusionist" is an impressive film that lacks the three deadly sins of the current Hollywood: pretentiousness, scripts made in the fourth bathroom and divos as only solid part of the film.</summary>
	<body>"That crude copy" I said to myself when I saw the poster for "The illusionist" a few days of launching the first pics of "The Prestige". Edward Norton, Jessica Biel and Paul Giamatti. "That so strange distribution", ask me again. Total, my entire predisposition to not pass a as revenge of advance premiere with a theme that my beloved Nolan due embroidery. "Do result: sometimes I am asshole?""The illusionist" is a stunning film. Perhaps you equipareis to name such an "excellent" but that is not what I mean. The way in which the story in the film is flawless. It does flow, and as such, keeps you in constant attention to what happens on screen. It's like one of those books that will cost you leave them despite having the eyes as brótolas. Nothing seems misplaced, and will find her how and why rather than leaving the end credits, something that is very complicated in the current film.Directed by Neil Burger, whose first film "Interview with the Assassin" I have read, the film is the adaptation of a Steven Millhauser story about a magician in the Vienna of the Victorian era. Shot entirely in the Czech Republic, "The illusionist" has managed to finish the consistency of your script with a few fabulous foreign. All the recreations, included the theatre where the wizard protagonist acts every night, are unbeatable. What I mean by all this corny litany is the atmosphere that has managed to recreate the director you wraps both or more as the story that counts. Of such history better know right and necessary. Fear gives me mention some scenes of the film, simply wonderful, that you agradeceréis keep you in the dark to see it, because every step and every event is as unexpected as the previous. A magician, (Edward Norton), a lady (Jessica Biel), and a somewhat neurotic police (Paul Giamatti). Their lives are interlinked to an unconventional ending.Sorpresón gives me Paul Giamatti. After having wanted to give two you born in "La Joven water", a Victorian aupa Grissom gives me. His performance as a policeman who is torn between licking ass or serve the law is as simple as genial, and they should make a spin-off for him only.Edward Norton does not surprise me, because this guy is good wherever you are. Tell me a single film is not where more than right. Jessica Biel just there to say that his interpretation is not visibly below their partners, and that there is much in a film where the duel Norton-Giamatti is anthological.The villain is Rufus Sewell? if not. One of the actors most villains has incarnated, and that makes in specialist. His drawing of a King without ethics or moral adds more attuned to the main chorus and that is why, as I have said, the result is rounded over not being able to.You already vendréis to tell me some which is shit, but "The illusionist" lacks the three deadly sins of the current Hollywood: pretentiousness, scripts made in the fourth bathroom and divos as only solid part of the film. Is a romantic tale (abstain "A todo Gas" fan), with good very good and bad very bad, and as says its motto: "Nothing is what it seems"?</body>
</review>
