<review author="Dragon negro" title="La fuente de la vida" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am sure that it will have its detractors and admirers, be those movies that either you love or you hate, but it will not leave indifferent anybody.</summary>
	<body>The film, in the projection of this morning has finished receiving, after a cold and timid start, quite a few applause. To begin we must say that it is not an easy film or that you understand first, indeed nor do I believe that it is necessary, and than a bad serious criticism the easy option, tar it mental straw for Aronofsky so panchos and incomprehensible. But the film deserves to be reviewed and revisionado to appreciate it in its entirety.It must be noted that the film is of impeccable beauty, from the more everyday scene to the futuristic images that are really beautiful. The storyline takes as its basis the present history and is taking us to the past and future turn. The fight of the doctor to find the experimental cure to save his wife terminal of a tumor shows us two options against the death, acceptance and denial. Accepting death in a natural way and as a symbol of humanity or clinging to life and fight to the end with all media. The man, in all his seasons, will be who find that eternal life with the woman, the polar opposite, which will be who attempts to convince him to stop something that is unfinished and may only terminate accepting the final truth.All this already commented when I made the review of the graphic novel, the film shortens in the stories of the past and future, perhaps by not having more time or not have a larger budget, but major points are virtually identical.What he wants us to show Aronofsky is death as way to create life, death is not a nothing but a whole, that as stated in religion, dust you are and powder you convertirás, and that the fact of eternal life does but anything other than the final acceptance of the cycle which means life. And all accompanied by the hypnotic and beautiful music by Clint Mansell returns to fill life images of the director, as did it in his previous films, this time adhering to a more intimate and delicate style as requested by the film.We could give rise to many interpretations and debates on the film, but I do not gutting too before that you see, and perhaps that is why this criticism sounds something cryptic. I am sure that it will have its detractors and admirers, be those movies that either you love or you hate, but it will not leave indifferent anybody.</body>
</review>
