<review author="Jose Luis" title="El ilusionista" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mixture of fantasy and romance you are about to leave speechless even the viewers more skeptical.</summary>
	<body>Can a man achieve the impossible through the magic? Can you create in a circus act action that misled our pupils and our reason in order to surprise us? Can man change his destiny with the help of the magic? These questions are that obsessed director Neil Burger, director of the illusionist, who jump to fame in 2002, with its tape interview with the assassin, which could create the illusion of be watching a documentary and not a tape of fiction.And this time, magic also is on their side, to create a tape round, smooth and with a mixture of fantasy and romance that is preparing to leave speechless even the spectators more skeptics...Eisenheim, is a man of magic, a magician, who after crossing the world looking for mysteries, returns to his native Vienna, from where he fled many years ago, escaping a tormented childhood romance with Countess Sophie, who is now the fiance of Prince Leopold. But? They will have forgotten the young lovers? Magic could this time avoid that the destination separate them once more?A script to direct and accurate, based on a story by Steven Millhauser, directly the story, keeping the attentive Viewer, using the narrative in charge of Giamatti and flashbacks, focusing on the points of view of two characters in appearance opposing but in the end are complementary, a script that prevents that romance is the only flavorIf not that garnished it with a fine thriller, framed in an excellent work of photography and the unmistakable musical touch of Philip Glass.Pero perhaps the best magical pass is the pair of action between an ambiguous Edward Norton, which at times becomes fear and Paul Giamatti, stealing the tape with the cynical character of Inspector Uhl, who created a good chemical antagonist. Though Rufus Sewell, also make theirs with the Stoic Prince (bad?) of the story.More arduous detractors of the film discussed that the end may not be the best that you could have, but should be considered that, unfortunately, often only there is place for the magic on the screen.</body>
</review>
