<review author="Sara Rodriguez" title="Casablanca" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Never happens fashion and still falling in love with anyone who sees.</summary>
	<body>The time: the second world war. Place: Casablanca, a city of easy access but almost impossible to leave, especially if your name is on the list of the most persecuted by the nazis. As it is the case of Victor Laszlo (Paul Henreid), who comes to Casablanca hoping that Rick Blaine (Humphrey Bogart), the owner of the "Rick's Cafe" help, a man who is not at risk by nadie.salvo by Ilsa (Ingrid Bergman).Almost all know what is Casablanca, some, even her they have seen several times and you know some of the memorable phrases that shines the immense Bogart in the film (excluding that of "play it again, Sam" made famous by a Woody Allen film xD). It has been described as a legend of Hollywood, a jewel, whose value increases as time passes.But why us Casablanca both like?It is a love story that has a historical context thousand times brought to the screen in the history of the cinema and we will have seen in more recent productions, best special effects, a spectacular photography (clear that the filming in black-and-white insurance that limits a bit xD) and incredible locations outside studies. However, Casablanca was filmed entirely in the Warner studios in 1941, with a total budget of $870,000 (which today would not give nor to pay the second Assistant of any superstar self-respecting.), in an era in which addition, actors not chose their roles, they signed contracts with producers to make a certain number of films and were those that chose for them, although most them was worth the actors not put stick if they wanted to see legs in the street.On the other hand, none of those involved in Casablanca was too confident in it, they thought that it was only a film study more.In fact, George Craft (chosen by Michael Curtiz after rejecting other applicants for not giving the carving to embody a tough guy), rejected the role of Rick Blaine that he had no interest in participating in a production of this type with the unknown (until then) Swedish actress Ingrid Bergman. It was a big mistake for Craft and a great success for Bogart (the seventh candidate of casting), which led him to play the role which would give the film "Eternity". Apart from the casting, there were many more problems that even make jeopardized the nearly million dollars which cost the film as bad English of Michael Curtiz and the complicated relationship of the Epstein brothers, responsible for the adaptation of the screenplay based on the play theatrical "Everybody comes to Rick's" or the question that actors often came to the set without knowing what dialogue played them that day.And, although it may not be the prototype of modern sex symbol Humphrey Bogart (also moved away enough of the canons of beauty of the era) or that I had to shoot the scenes with Bergman uploaded to a platform of 23 cm. compesar the portentous 20 cm. that it happened, but it is with the rough voice of Bogarthis eyes deep, almost abysmal and his overwhelming presence did not take much more. Also maybe the modest Ingrid Bergman, in this film is away from the typical "femme fatale", but it is undeniable that there is a palpable chemistry in each one of their scenes together and acting power of this production is one of its strengths.Therefore, Casablanca is a film that never happens fashion and that still falling to anyone who sees.</body>
</review>
