<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Scoop" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One of those small movies that Allen likes to do from time to time; light, entertaining and fun. Adjectives that are, to be honest, the best that can be said to a comedy.</summary>
	<body>After the enormous satisfaction produced by "Match Point" (link to critique in Moonfleet), expected eager the next film of Woody Allen to see if it was still in the same line of the previous or changed record.Outside expectations, Allen has decided by a light comedy of those he does with your eyes closed and may be a part of the public unfairly, leave disappointed. The film features the research that, based on a peculiar tip-off, performs a student of journalism (Scarlett Johansson) to discover if the known aristocrat Peter Lyman (Hugh Jackman) is the murderer of the tarot. The rookie journalist will have the help of a Wizard of second row (Woody Allen).With size argument not to expect anything other than a light comedy of entanglements in which Woody Allen offers the best of himself and shows that he has not lost an iota of his comic vis. Each one of his appearances on stage is a gift for the Viewer. To me, just to see how it moves already gives me laughter. At his side, Scarlett, ducks and fun without losing a bit of its appeal. The other characters, let alone worked in other Allen films, exercising of mere comparsas although they are equal (especially Ian McShane).As I say the script works as a clock of intrigue both his comic part although, as in all good comedy, what we least import the identity of the murderer. If we add this to the pace at which Allen knows to give to his films and the facility that has to tell a good story in an hour and a half, we will have a slide show that is passed in a sigh. It is clear that comparison with films such as "Manhattan murder mystery" would be quite uneven and unfair because it seems clear to seeing it, that Allen did not intend to make a film as well. Instead, we have one of those small movies that Allen likes to do from time to time; light, entertaining and fun. Adjectives that are, to be honest, the best that can be said to a comedy.</body>
</review>
