<review author="José A. Peig" title="Alien, el octavo pasajero" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The major achievement of?Alien? It is a superb combination between human characters and physical environment, the pervasive sense of horror and the unusual and the aesthetics of the graphic design.</summary>
	<body>Even at the end of the 1970s, the idea of which part this absolute masterpiece of the genre of science fiction is very unoriginal: story of suspense and terror on "bug that pursues and eats humans". Novelty occurred with a new location of the monster: the abyss in the framework of the futuristic vision of space travel and space. It is not enough to carry an old idea to a new space and time. I.e., the Ridley Scott film could be rather mediocre and, on paper, little or nothing would glimpse.But the great achievement of "Alien" is a superb combination between human characters and physical environment, the pervasive sense of horror and the unusual and the aesthetics of the graphic design. Conjunctions in the service of an eerie account for his sense of suspense, but also by its power of metaphorical, reaching an overwhelming operatic texture of claustrophobic in the depths of outer space. In fact, the real star of the film are not human profiles, but the physical and symbolic wrapper that acuna: the gigantic ship Nostromo. The design of the great commercial ship alludes to a huge mechanical monster that haunts in the interstellar void, or a large Castle or Gothic fortress that imprisons its inhabitants. The struggle between the human and the mechanical is present in their various strata. See the beginning of the film: the dark vacuum of the cosmos gives way to the mechanical monstrosity. Then the camera of Scott recreates in - through slow and contemplative close-ups - visualization of the passageways, wires, gossip, depths and computer devices which mean the Robotics soul of the ship. In this way, the environment is configured in real protagonist of visual representation. Then, a door opens and leads us to the room in which the human inhabitants are about to end their hibernation within the fortress: is no coincidence that the computer brain that governs the spacecraft and directs the human Entourage carrying the name of "Mother". From that point, enter to know the human life in the interior of the nave with a drawing of characters as simple as effective and, above all, diverse and rich in perspective: from the cold introversion of Kane, sarcasm and irony of Bred and his pupil, the extreme and Machiavellian scientism of Ash, the anguish of Lange or honest but hesitation authority of Dallasthat whole human provides an excellent chemistry of decisions and ways to cope with the danger. I.e. the physical packaging is added a highly human, depending on the needs of an argument which does not require characters excessively complex, but yes they must be significant in the confrontation with the situation and psychological context. And it succeeds.Beyond human it, the design of the alien and of each of the interiors, brimming with an aesthetic to horse of the Gothic and psychedelic, the abrupt and ghostly, configured a dreamlike atmosphere which adds to a sense of the horror experienced by the human characters at all times. The claustrophobic emulsion caused by suffocating architecture of the nave and the subtle presence of the alien is reinforced in different frames in which Scott cares well placed human profiles in a closed space doors, passageways, gases, sounds, and ghostly silhouettes insinuadas in every corner of the visual field (see the sequence of Dallas in the search for the bug through the ventilation tunnels): a simple frame of Dallas profile violently cut and suppressed by the closure of one of the hatches, a single resource but of great expressive force used in this context, which reinforces the stinging claustrophobic dimension of the story. (Or the wise does not show the entire body of the Alien, accentuating its physical ambiguity on par with their presence subtly drawn in the reliefs of doors, walls, ceilings or walls) very intelligently, the own silhouette and physical texture of the alien resembles and is confused with the tubes that run along walls and passageways, making the human environment to form a unit with the mechanical environment of the nave and the biological of the alien. This perfect and stimulating combination of elements is which gives it its great singularity.In the metaphorical, the physical dimension of the ship, the "Mother" (its counterpart "psychic") computer, Ash and the alien are mechanical parts of attenuated cold rationality faced sharper humanity of Ripley and his. The story gains a rough and deeply dramatic background when we discovered that real conspiracy puppets are not human but machines: the death of Ash, so gesticulante with these violently truncated cables, white coming to GLUGs and grotesque cybernetic noise blood, transmits with a great sense of dreams the chilling discovery of inhumanity that hid under a guise of responsible for rationality. In the words of the same Ash, the alien is the biological body par excellence, for its destructive action without remorse and "without moral fantasies" that could suppress them. I.e., the perfect machine that frightens and pursues those who already are prisoners of the ship Nostromo. so because its enormous metaphorical power leads us to a consideration as important as its excellent realization at the script level, structure, tonality and aesthetic in the narrative field as in the plastic sense; "Alien", apart from a tale of terror, is also an allegory about the objectification in the technological age, man lost in a cosmic vastness of findings in the form of travel and technological creations, but helpless against the machinery of power and the unconsciousness of many.In a sense, the solitude and anguish of Ripley running through the interior of the bowels of the ship Nostromo, through the passages saturated of technology, fumes and industrial fumes, sounds shrill and threatening, in a ghostly setting in which you do not know the danger that lurks to turn the corner in each fork, his solitude reflected the loneliness of modern manmore human than ever but increasingly more prisoner of the mechanical. And what better environment than the empty abyss of space to place this modern nightmare.</body>
</review>
