<review author="JohnTrent" title="Saw 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Its creators have been allowed to carry by the merely conformist, possibly to knowing that you do not have to do much to bring the film back to be a considerable success at the box office.</summary>
	<body>Do if in recent years there has been a series of terror that has managed to unite to the general public? both fans to the genre as those who are not interested in too - with the box-office success and the opinion of some sectors of criticism, this has been the start by "Saw". And is that, now that the third installment hits theaters we can see how the expectation has not decreased and that, far from threatening to leave hit the fans, their scores in certain pages are not negligible (IMDB: 6.6;) Film affinity: 6.1), although there are admittedly in decline with respect to the two previous installments. It is not for less, since this third installment is the weaker of the three, as well as demonstrate a lack of ideas is charged even in the pace of the plot. Despite this, the film does path of the $ 80 million in United States? and its budget has been a 10.Los background of the psychopath.In 2004, with a budget of only $ 1.2 million, the young director James Wan won with his second film, "Saw", one of the "sleeper" of the season and one of the most profitable movies in a long time. Is that, their 102 million dollars collected around the world gave good proof that the public was increasingly accepting truculenta terror? although, to tell the truth, this first installment was rather little explicit - after the somewhat bland Decade of the nineties. "The film also became a big hit in DVD market and was quickly created a considerable Legion of fans to his around, impatiently awaiting the new torture than Jigsaw (the murderer of the puzzle) had designed for the new victims of their game."Saw "a few months later get"Saw 2"(spectacular) example of shooting at high speed." Change to the director, James Wan, by (the also little known) Darren Lynn Bousman and the budget, despite being somewhat larger, continued to be negligible; 5 million dollars. The success of this sequel was even greater to that of the first delivery, calculating its fundraising world in $ 152 million. The film, for its part, eliminated the factor surprise of its precedent for entering roads purely gore (always within certain trading patterns). Augmented the torture, the cruelty of the same and the number of characters that are inflingidas, its makers left the cards on the table for the next installment.And became the third.Thus, one year after the second installment, already have in theaters the new continuation of the series, to be sure, again directed by Darren Lynn Bousman and in which he has also participated as an executive producer, also having something to do with in the script, James Wan, which has not helped too to save the downturn in quality with respect to the two previous ones that happened to comment below. And it is that, if the sequel worked well by accumulation, without presenting news especially interesting, in this third comes them, in part, the shot backfires. In his eagerness to loop the loop the plot in both the visual, perpetrators? emphasizing the writers, i.e. the same Darryl Lynn Bousman and James Wan - propose us a game more unhealthy if it should be that in the second, even with some component hallucinatory, more dirty than expected, but far from functioning as it should ends becoming, by lack of ideas certainly in an artifact partly hollow and wrong tack, which definitely is too a notorious neglect to advance the series with some work.So is the feeling, as it advances the plot, that the script is not going nowhere, that the characters do not stop having one greater than a monigote personality of fair and that presumably dynamic rhythm that you want to give not this extensive plot holes and therefore interest slippages.It is likely that they read my (somewhat) enthusiast criticizes close of "the Texas Chainsaw Massacre: the origin" a few days ago do not well understand my position before a film, "Saw 3", which is not far too much of what we proposed in the visual and narrative, among other things, the new proposal of the psychopath headed by leather face family.The case is that, since to give explanations, "the Texas Chainsaw Massacre: the origin", although not more than an entertainment without more work by its makers add more gore to one plot thousandfold told previously, it has an overwhelming pace at almost all times and, above all, a few characters that, at least for which this writes? I am referring to the psychopaths, not girls victims - have a malevolent charisma and effectiveness on screen that, although manages to be so settled, be effective at all times, unlike the little interesting character of Amanda, aprendiza the murderer of the puzzle, that not trasfiere far the madness and the well made histrionics of the psychopaths of worship has given the genre. Jigsaw? Well, as the second part returns to be very interesting. Several torture.If there is something that really will resist the passage of deliveries of this saga, that are torture. In the film we are dealing with are more twisted, bloody and unhealthy that so far, with the difference that are worse dosificadas in the plot. Likewise, no longer exists a real interest in the person which you happen, they simply serve as macabre divertimento for al gore addicted. And here is where I want to go, because with this new installment the saga begins to have some aroma to the unhealthy and dirty gore of the eighties. They are moments such as the cranial operation, filmed in close-up and with some fairly explicit moments, which I took directly to "Re animator" and his bad baba to show, without having to provide explanations of any kind, gruesomeness everywhere, but the most obvious case would be the mini classic entitled "Maniac" (without lead to mistakes, because that only the final climax of the unhealthy work produced more bad feeling that the saga of "Saw" Board).The visual style used to display the atrocities is once again the same. The "look" videoclipero is added to a fast-paced montage which always leads us from one side to another of the victim. So, and without losing detail, can go? in few seconds, that if - as an arm is being fractured, like a hand this being Circumstellar in a pot containing acid or as a type of his body starts several "piercing" of considerable size. All this with the unique and clear intention of seeing where the public expects another "Saw" each passing year can achieve.When we got to the end, the typical and expected plot twist makes more clear if what said above; its creators have been allowed to carry by the merely conformist, possibly to knowing that you do not have to do much to bring the film back to be a considerable success at the box office. Said twist without being surplus if it is lengthened in excess in a succession of "flash back" that tell us something that was already understood from the outset.A never-ending saga.Today, and if there were doubts, confirmed that we can speak of "Saw" as the saga of terror that picks up the relay to the once very successful "Nightmare on Elm Street" or "Friday the 13th". Is the new series which, when it begins to fail at the box office, will continue his tour of the video club or more distributions limited within the cinemas, but always giving benefits for very badly that go things, because if something has a saga "Saw" as a developer is that with two hard can be very profitable things (learn a little those who carry the Spanish film) and that there is nothing like creating an icon do pop within the genre?Jigsaw - so the Legion of fans of the character, as well as with Freddy or Jason - beyond the viewing."Do so far, and as already announced a few days ago in criticism of"Them", this French horror film makers are already confirmed to be after the cameras"Saw 4"and?"Saw 5 ".</body>
</review>
