<review author="Marta" title="Scoop" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You are not among the best films of Woody Allen, but outperforms many of its most recent comedies and part, without doubt, the best film of humor that can be seen today.</summary>
	<body>The downside of having a career as Woody Allen is that you've put yourself the bar very high. It is difficult to please everyone after peliculones as "Annie Hall" or the more recent "Match Point". That being said, it is clear that a work which exit losing in this comparison, can perfectly overcome many of the films competing against it on the Bulletin Board. That is exactly what happens to "Scoop". Despite not being among the best films of the director New York, it beats many of his most recent comedies, such as "Everything else" or "Desmontando a Harry", and part, without doubt, the best film of humor that can be seen today.In "Scoop" Allen repeated London backdrop and returns to join intrigue and comedy as it already did in "Manhattan murder mystery". Although he fails to reach the level of the latter - which is, in my opinion, among his best works, returns to tell an interesting story form fun and ingenious, with witty dialogues and the rest of elements typical of his films. Scarlett Johansson is a young student of journalism that investigates a possible murderer from the information giving you a ghost. Yes, a ghost. Well, it is not the first time that this man plays with the absurd, nor much less, right? And the truth is that we would appreciate seeing her in a role other than bellezón, while not one of his best performances. For its part, Woody Allen returns to put in front of the camera to accompany it in its investigations and interpret, course, curious kind of always the same role. Those who hate the Woody Allen movies because it leaves Woody Allen hate also, clear. The rest will enjoy her, provided that they do not intend to director capable of beating itself everytime it launches something new. And those who still do not know - if it is someone - can have a good time in cinema with a comedy different from what is often seen regularly. The truth is that I am already expecting the next.</body>
</review>
