<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Borat" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Maybe that the film gave the stroke, but it should not be taken as a novelty. The rednecks crowd screens since the film is film, and this is not the sharpest.</summary>
	<body>Americans love the rednecks. American cinema is full of rednecks. ET, for example is a space both. Elliot and his sister passed it pipe showing the American roll. Also, taught it to Terminator, Crocodile Dundee, Johnny 5, thousands of robots, aliens, elves, Martians, clones, beings fallen from a nest. There is nothing that an American Viewer likes more than see an ignorant learning the customs of America La version espanola of the both is that of rogue. Cinema Spanish, especially the 1960s, preferred to the rogue. It is the same story, but told from another point of view. The has the both and the account to other rednecks. LeBlanc, Landa, feigned to be fools to fleece rich abroad. Traveling to other countries I discovered that they have the same mythology that we in the 1960s. In Cuba, many films now laugh at naive tourists, of us, who we now are like the Yankees.Borat is a mixture of the two points of view. Borat makes a tour of America inviting us to laugh their ignorance of his inferiority in the developed world: does not distinguish a cup of a lavavo toilet, masturbating on the street and makes their needs in the gardens. The rich can laugh here. But on the other hand it is a false naive. We know that it is taking the hair to each of the Americans that interview, we know that it is not the fool pretending to be: an American Senator offers a piece of cheese and then explains that it is made with milk of his wife, in a society dinner asks if he can bring a friend and invites an ordinary prostitute. Those who live in poor countries may laugh here.Maybe that the film gave the stroke, but it should not be taken as a novelty. The rednecks crowd screens since the film is film, and this is not the sharpest. He has saved funds of production using only to ordinary people and has not squandered neurons filling meters of film with scenes of coarse humor, or looking for the scandal in the vulgar like our domestic both, Santiago Segura.La blend of reality and fiction (respondents don't know that camera that focuses on them is a stupid patochada), resembles the interviewers "Who fall fall". If this film wanted to be something else that rubbish would have to have entered the game so well handled by this television program engage in complicity with respondents, rather than grossly mistreat them. Borat has only complicity with the audience, which, it seems, is on track to achieve a handsome box office.</body>
</review>
