<review author="Caruco" title="El ilusionista" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Echo less more capacity of disturbance, claw more film. But it is not call pears at del olmo, and Yes to make us spend almost two hours entertaining.</summary>
	<body>Mystery, magic and romance wrapped in a supernatural halo is that promises "The illusionist". Its cast is also very attractive: Edward Norton, Jessica Biel and Paul Giamatti. Ummmm!The era in which it is set, that Vienna from entresiglos in 1900, is still some fascination. And more as the setting for a story (another more this year, following "The girl in the water", "Palindromes", "El laberinto del fauno"?), inspired by the pen or computer of a Pulitzer Prize, Steven Millhauser keyboard. More ummmmm!Our charming Prince is not of such rank sinó of humble and rather solo status and booked. It is known as the magician Eisenheim (Edward Norton) and his tricks are so spectacular that it seems that he has allied himself with the same supernatural forces. Now use all their tricks to get to the woman he loves, a lady prohida (Jessica Biel) that belongs to a higher class. And make it rivaled, this Yes, all a Prince (Rufus Sewell). it seems all great! But I'm still hoping something of intrigue that is worth remembering, and footage that is based on a too stretched idea. Film and characters move in a functional manner and on many occasions, why Yes, why it says the script. Or the final outcome is surprising, because it hinted at with ease.Norton and Giamatti what great are!Do it is then when one falls in the mind that the true vocation of the film directed by Neil Burger, forged in the realization of? spots?, is only the entertain and point. Either try to make history in cinema.And "The illusionist" meets its goal, being grateful that no character is actually as good or as bad as it seems, even the OGRE in the form of Prince who plays best Sewell.Lo of the function, without doubt, are actors, especially Edward Norton and Paul Giamatti as the inspector of the police Uhl, a representative of the law who is torn between two duties: the entertain to established power and maintain full in his tenure.Moreover, the romantic plot between the aristocratic Sophie and the plebeian prestigidador continues to follow the more well-trodden outline of "boy meets girl;" "boy loses girl and, already know, waiting boy recovers again the girl." Optical illusions.And I put into question some of the magic tricks that Eisenheim staged were really possible with the verismo, for the time, but in 1900 they were beginning to develop optical illusions which rise the film.Do do the same movie uses the technique of the? autocrhome?, created by the Lumière brothers at the end of the 19th century, whose colouring is smoother, less contrasted and therefore closer to black and white, allowing to provide the photography and the production design of a certain layer of unreality in accordance with the spirit of the film and its setting.Interesting, and further taking into account the story creates expectations with time as the (alleged) occurrences of the hereafter or an exhibition in charge of Eisenheim reminiscent of the legend of Arturo.Pero the staging of Neil Burger continues to be very discreet. Echo less more capacity of disturbance, claw more film. Does but is not call pears at del olmo, and Yes to make us spend almost two hours entertaining, give her for valid, but?</body>
</review>
