<review author="Uruloki" title="El ilusionista" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It manages to be entretenidísima and surprising. If anyone had doubts that go to see her, you will enjoy.</summary>
	<body>Yesterday afternoon we are encouraged to see the illusionist (2006), film directed by Neil Burger and based on a short Steven Millhauser, an American writer winning story of a Pulitzer Prize to the best work of fiction in 1997 and whose work often reflects these temporary phases where the evolution of a system marks a turning point in history. The work "Eisenheim the Illusionist" offers this detail showing us the change of the ancient magicians full of paraphernalia to the current, a world where mechanics is of vital importance in order to create the most incredible tricks and where the little theater, in mode actor that embauca, and minimalism make the illusion still much more amazing. Starring an underutilized Edward Norton, mira which is good actor and not noted for great films for starring roles, a growing Paul Giamatti, Rufus Sewell and the very interesting Jessica Biel, puts US in the Austria at the end of the 19th century. Eisenheim (Norton) is a young magician who, after falling in love Sofia (Biel), a young woman of a status well above its potential, disappears for many years to return, and using his tricks of magician, free girl with their social obligations with the Leopold Austria Prince (Sewell) regardless of the consequences that this will entail for theShe and the future of the country.The film has no pretensions and therefore manages to surprise and provide a result far superior to many of the films that have been seen in recent weeks. both De Palma and Scorsese so much so that in the end the adaptation of a short fiction story be the very best that you can see by the cinemas. With a curious picture of old film with true gradient on the edge, a fairly currado script, a musical composition by Philip Glass, the sea of interesting and a sincere atmosphere, achieved that it is entretenidísima and surprising. If anyone had doubts that go to see her, you will enjoy.</body>
</review>
