<review author="Dragon negro" title="Dead or alive" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The movie is simple, stupid jokes, the relationships between the characters superfluous, struggles past thread and exaggerated, the script is predictable, but you do not see as well that I've been seeing this movie.</summary>
	<body>DOA, Dead or Alive, is a wrestling tournament where participate the best in their specialty and that takes place in a complex on an island. There they were invited to participate our protagonists, Christie, a thief were chased by the police, Tina, an expert in wrestling with a rather peculiar father, Kasumi, a princess who leaves his Kingdom in search of his brother, and Helena, daughter of the late Organizer and that attempted to show what it is worth. Tournaments randomly facing the opponents and any time and stage is good for a fight. But this year the tournament is not clear water and its current organizer has hidden intentions. And already, there is no longer just it nothing more than chicha in this film, or what expected, great philosophical conversations, characters that evolve with the plot, social criticism, interpretations of Oscar. Will not find anything like that here, just a plot and a simple script and even senseless times, spectacular fights, some more successful than others, and girls in bikini, and already is, well, not, and volleyball, of course, not me forget volleyball in a bikini.Fans of the game will have their tribute in the early fighting, with the positions taken at the end of each one and even energy level markers. The villain is not Eric Roberts, which makes time not seen in the film and actor in series B and everything that throw you it that should leave be more. The rest are grips guys and girls who spend half of the tape in a bikini and the other half with tight clothing.They are three scenes where displayed their skills and their bodies, bikini and underwear, clear already from the outset DOA leaves clear of that is going to go, the presentation of the protagonists. The film does not leave a moment of respite, there are fights either or there are showcasing bodies in bikini, or both. There are zillions blows, espadazos, and much violence, but at no time we will see a drop of blood or any wound, no face marked, like great aunt in a bikini but little else, a real shame.The main virtue of the film, and here lies its charm (and not in the girls in bikini) is that you are not taken seriously at any time, knows that they cannot offer much more than what they offer and are not intended to anything else than be pure entertainment last thread. I'm already sick of shit movies ranging from serious and profound film when they are not. Here at least not they stubbornly give a depth to the film and a background when it is not, nor desire. They are playing their cards and play them well, fights and aunts in bikini and point.The movie is simple, stupid jokes, relations between the characters superfluous, struggles past thread and exaggerated, the motivations of the characters little defined, the script is predictable and often inconsistent, but you do not see what good that I've been seeing this movie. By the way, did I say since there aunts in bikini all the time?</body>
</review>
