<review author="José Córdoba" title="El ilusionista" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The most topical and predictable movie I've seen in a long time, a complete disappointment, although ideal for a little loving and demanding public to reverse serials.</summary>
	<body>As it already happened previously two similar themed movies they premiere in a short space of time. After cases of Deep Impact and Armageddon, bugs and Antz or the dangerous liaisons and Valmont, arrive the illusionist and The Prestige, both set in the world of magic. The second, directed by Christopher Nolan (Memento director) and starring Scartlett Johansson, Hugh Jackman and Christian Bale, Michael Caine, will not arrive until January, but the first is already among us.As in the detailed examples above, when agree two similar films one usually being the younger sister of the other, the duckling ugly a priori, trying, in addition, advance in its premiere to his older sister. The illusionist falls into this category. With a limited budget (for American cinema) of $ 16 million and with a cast full of familiar faces (Edward Norton, Paul Giamatti, Rufus Sewell and Jessica Biel), solvent, the film is made by the unknown on these lares Neil Burger and tells the story of impossible love between the fiancée of the future emperor of Austria and a mysterious magician newcomer to Vienna. Hacía time had no feeling that I had nothing more start the film. On the quarter hour or so, already not me was liking. In those fifteen minutes the shortcomings of the film were already patent: clichés and platitudes everywhere and a realization flat, unable to provide rate or visual innovation to the flashback of the children of the wizard, which is all foreseeable that one can imagine. Unfortunately the film was not clear of that feeling during the footage.Already during the film also leaves out the lack of means which has been filmed. Filming took place in Prague, pretending to be Vienna, but, and this reminded me to Alatriste, just a couple of foreign enclaves, showing the budgetary shortcomings of the film. Something which is not negative per know, if the rest of the elements might make up for it, but this is not the case.By structure, the film refers to the usual suspects: two characters, one of them narrates the events that have taken place up to that point, to which we return at the end of the film, and from which continues the narrative with included final twist to flashback mode. In addition the film's story refers to Casablanca, including triangle and with a corrupt representative of the law but of good heart, as Captain Renault played by Claude Rains, and that in this film is played by Paul Giamatti.El script is riddled with clichés: young lovers separated by their difference of classes, their reunion years later still she promised and he under another identity which gives much success, the jealousy of the powerful and future husband, etc, etc. This series of elements would add the magical element of the matter, as an original element, to the nor is it takes party. It is a dispassionate script, there is no great tragedies, there are no edges, there is conflict, little everything is shades of gray. The characters are barely drawn, do not evolve, and you know little more of them apart from its generic description. And is also predictable, including final surprise.Neil Burger is flat, worthy of TV, unable to give some life to the subject, and clumsy directly at the trigger time of the entire fabric to be shot so typical and obvious, prevents that you enter in the game because you know what has happened and what will follow. Also the realization of the tricks of magic, something that should be surprising or disturbing, is artificial and incredible, then opt for a solution via computer, that it is entirely impossible already not for his time but for the current also, because if something makes clear in the film, is that the magician is a magician, not a be with special powers.The cast is correct, little more can be asked actors with papers that have, although maybe Giamatti is a little past thread on the final stretch.Photography, costumes, art direction are very appropriate, referring back to old cinema, even with tones and mounts solutions specific to the time of the film silent. Music on the other hand, composed by Philipp Glass, nor help, due to the style of the composer, perhaps not the most appropriate for a project as well. Glass a prestigious and innovative composer of the minimalist genre has a very distinctive style based on the repetition of patterns that achieved wonders in a movie like the hours, whose soundtrack is prodigious, but this pattern is here wrong due to the absence of the film life. So the music rather than enhance the images power weary rhythm, constant, gray throughout the film.In summary, the most topical and predictable movie I've seen in a long time, a complete disappointment, although ideal for a little loving and demanding public to reverse serials.</body>
</review>
