<review author="José Córdoba" title="The Queen" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The Queen is a surprise, a small well narrated film, well written and miraculously starring Helen Mirren.</summary>
	<body>I cannot with the biographical films. They tend to be hagiographies which, although showing the dark side of a real person, always appears anti-aliasing, smoothing the edges and possible rough edges. They also tend to want to tell too many things, to cover periods of time far and, as the saying goes, who covers very little press. Thus most successful are those biopics that tell us a brief period of a person's life than those who try to reflect her life on screen. The Queen of Stephen Frears was in the latter group.The film narrates the reactions of Queen Elizabeth II of England and newly appointed Prime Minister Tony Blair in the seven days following the death of Diana of Wales. A priori it is an issue that no attention too, and that did not interest me too and, however, Frears, its screenwriter and, above all, an ACTRESS Madam named Helen Mirren get interest not decay and you involucres in history.The film told in quasi documentary tone, in fact is punctuated by images of the news of the moment, begins with the presentation of Tony Blair to the Queen, having won the elections. Already from the beginning see paths to the characters with the marriage Blair, dismissive, mocking with the monarchy and the derogatory Queen, superior with respect to the commoner. During the film, attitudes will evolve, being very striking that of Blair. And is that, unlike the illusionist, the characters reflect the events, the time, and, although between the beginning and the end of the film barely two months have passed, the characters have changed mirror suffered developments, have a background.The film's interesting because of how different characters used Diana's death: Blair takes advantage of the indifference of the monarchy to monopolize the role initially; Prince Charles undertakes that its image doesn't come out damaged, approaching Blair, at the expense of damaging the image of his mother; the husband of the Queen and her mother prefer to act as if nothing had happened, unable to give his arm to twist, to go against tradition. And in the middle is the one hand insensitive to events, but on the other Queen seeing that you can lose the affection of the people. All the characters are very careful, we understand their motivations and goals, we can understand them despite away who are of us.Special mention deserves Helen Mirren among all stakeholders. His performance is brilliant, contained, without fanfare, meticulous in detail, splendid. Master tempo, the gestures, the column, the breathing. Create a character with its own entity, not mimicry with the real model but creation from the actress. The rest of the cast is also very good, but the work of this woman is in another League. Moments as his emotion to the beauty of a deer and its subsequent dead or when receiving a bouquet of flowers from a girl, are unforgettable, especially, in contrast to the coldness to it before everything with Diana.La Frears realization is simple and efficient, providing a good rhythm for the film preventing decay interest. Photography is realistic, approaching the documentary tone and clearly distinguishing aspects deprived of public characters. On the other hand, Desplat music is original and very elaborate in this style of productions, although remember to work somewhat for Birth (reincarnation).The Queen is a surprise, a small well narrated film, well written and miraculously starring Helen Mirren.</body>
</review>
