<review author="Juan Nadie" title="El ilusionista" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Good film of love, revenge and deceit. Especially if one takes into account it boasts an unbeatable scenario, that the novel is set in Vienna.</summary>
	<body>Magic and love are two impossible to separate closely linked concepts. They say that when the magic ends love becomes affection, but this is subject for another film. Which we are discussing, the illusionist, plays the two sticks but with a reasonable distance. Do the protagonist is a magician, a magician, living of? trick? to those who pay to see him. It entertains them and makes them see things that are not on stage through tricks that we've all seen once and we have tried in vain to decipher. But not only this illusion is that feeds the film directed by Neil Burger, that taps into which arises from love. A beautiful story of adolescent love between a peasant fond of tricks (Eisenheim) and a noblewoman who wants to escape his fate (Sophie). However, the cruel fate oblige them take their separate ways until return to stumble on a stage. He, as Wizard Professional and recognized prestige and she, as the fiancée of the malevolent Prince (Leopold, an alluring Rufus Sewell, who the most friáis remember for Dark City). From there arise a number of encounters and disagreements with inclusive love triangle that lead the old love that is reborn, the defiance of the horned and the fear of what is to come later.The magician, whose argument is that is has the blessed in the title role with Edward Norton, one of those actors who only with his presence fills the screen and capture the attention of the Viewer. At this point in his career (already has 37 spring despite his face of youngster), Norton has little to show after movies like American History X, fight club and the last hour. Although it is true that the paper isn't too complicated, because you need only put face of mystery left in the dressing room secrets which no one must discover, while one of the emissaries of the feared Prince Leopold, which gives life a deception Paul Giamatti fan, try. A success full in the cast as part of two of them, the evil Prince comes round to Sewell, who will simply with his usual look to frighten us into the body. And then there is the girl, Jessica Biel, which we have seen in several television series and is on the road of becoming one of the most desirable, when the whole world is account of his talent. The illusionist is a good film of love, revenge and deceit. Especially if one takes into account it boasts an unbeatable scenario, that the novel is set in Vienna, a city which contributes to mystery that surrounds all the history which dominated by Browns and blacks of the time. The magician enjoys an aesthetic cared to the maximum in which the viewer can accept the invitation to a journey through time that be fooled by a skilled make-up artist of reality as Eisenheim. A wonderful invitation which should not be rehusada by the usual strange thing and Norton. But perhaps, best of all is the regustillo which fits one after seeing. Somewhat similar to experienced after seeing the coup (this wonderful work of public art) or The Score (not so good, but almost). Those who attend the cinema to see will understand it.</body>
</review>
