<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Dead or alive" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another more, another video that comes and crashes into the screen. Those responsible for this production are at least aware that are playing in a lower League.</summary>
	<body>Not noted by adolescent which is destined, consumption but by the homage to all those tapes that have its own entity and here leave remnants, Matrix and Tiger and dragon head.In the tradition of the adaptations of adventure games, this title is far away even those that have all the lose in the oblivion of time, as the irregular Alone in the dark and Silent Hill. With an argument that to be in front of the computer is more than enough, on their way to the cinema not offers some consistency. He has more than 30 movies behind him, only a previous shot outside Hong Kong (Transporter) and by what they have seen thanks to this, all dispensable. Corey Yuen is the director of an orchestra where instruments desafinan and the musicians laugh at themselves. The sense of humor that doesn't lack in this parody with bikinis, girls and much muscle that at times seems a vulgar copy of the House of flying daggers and Los Angeles of Charlie, forgiveness, wanted to say tribute.Bland and without any sense, DOA (thus, in confidence) shows that its leaders lack imagination but enjoy of a wonderful mechanism to make bearable infumable footage. It seems impossible that the history is not boring, but another thing is to have the little things positive to highlight, few truth: the argument calls for a flexible mounting to print pace to the action scenes. Do do the only thing that attracts our attention, both runnig pace in the end positions us to an unbalanced conglomerate of? peleítas? and struggles, shot with unwillingness to constituted the bulk of the script. A script, by the way, full of jokes facilones, sexist clichés and a mild attempt to turn the woman protagonist and not for its beauty or their wonder in the field of martial arts. You don't have the slightest interest.</body>
</review>
