<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Beyond the sea" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>For almost two hours, we will return to live the magic of the orchestras of the 1950s, American social change in the 1960s but, above all, the desire to live a child who believed could not exceed fifteen years of age.</summary>
	<body>It is possible that many of those present not us it sounds for anything the name of Bobby Darin. Also, it is very possible that it cost us to put songs like "Beyond the sea" or "Mack the Knife". Do but, we perhaps something more familiar the following stanza: by the corner of the old quarter saw him pass, with the? tumbao? do they have the handsome walking, hands always in the pocket of his overcoat? pa? they do not know in which one takes the dagger.Do do do do use a medium wide-brimmed hat? Lao people? and slippers if there is a problem out? volao?.As well, this letter belongs to one of the multiple versions that exist in Spanish one of the greatest successes of the popular singer Bobby Darin, teen idol during the 1950s and 1960s and whose lyrics can still hear in the category of Robbie Williams.La interpreters mouth biography that has played and directed Kevin Spacey (and which in United States premiered in 2004) not only about millimeter form to the life real multi-faceted artist (also an actor) but that, in addition, conveys extraordinarily of the same quality; and that has its merit, especially when the soundtrack is performed by the same Spacey (and I assure you that it has no waste, in fact, the role earned him a Golden Globe nomination for best actor in a musical or comedy).The film is exquisite not only sound but also sets and costumes, masterfully recreating the atmosphere of local legendary as the Copacabana in New York. For almost two hours, we will return to live the magic of the orchestras of the 1950s, American social change in the 1960s but, above all, the desire to live a child who believed could not exceed fifteen years of age.</body>
</review>
