<review author="Iñigo" title="Crash" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Despite his mistakes, so it manages and represents is a very notable film</summary>
	<body>"Crash" is a controversial film. But it seems that face a criticism of it is even more controversial. Let's go by parts. The film has enough in their favor. It is a work, above all, very overwhelming, with abundant amount of good cinema and know-how.It was writer of the drama "Million Dollar Baby" demonstrates that he knows something more to write. Their film knowledge are large, of that there is no doubt, as evidenced in this his first film to the address. Flat sequence are wonderful moments crucial are directed with a mastery of worthy of mention, emotional music is bound at the exact moment and cast raya at a great level.Between so good interpretation (an exceptional Dillon, a large Cheadle, a Newton and Howard incredible. come on, all of the cast) and many characters of Sandra Bullock goes totally unnoticed.But. Yes, the movie has several buts. Greater or lesser importance (according to the degree of emotional impact that has led to the film in one) can be given, but what can not is to deny them aseptic perspective.It is obvious that Paul Haggis is controversial, and therefore must be borne in mind that any resolution could cause collateral damage. Thus, the best in these cases (only if you want to avoid the controversy), usually treat the film with the greater possible ambiguity. And it is clear the director knows, is to disguise its ideological positioning, but succumbs in several attempts.Firstly, it must be said that, in a global sense, "Crash" is such a sensitive subject as racism and solitary confinement due to culture shock with sum intelligence, without excessive stereotype and entering land trivial and manichaeans. But there are too close to the cartoon characters and that they tend to exaggerate, without being able to avoid, thus falling into the clichés as feared.And it is also true that the decisive moment for the characters may seem somewhat manipulative and easy to emotionally speaking, pulling towards to the sensationalism that ultra-lenta camera with heavenly music as background. As if Paul Haggis was to provoke the Viewer.But those moments and film quality, also raise the film. Reach levels close to the daunting. And it moves.The script is very good, no doubt, but (in addition to the subjective feeling of irrigating some level of hate) characters do not end of frame at all. It concludes with the impression of not having given the necessary game to the inner spiritual and life of the protagonists. It seems a sort of incomplete description to, it is true, does not affect the general appearance of the film, but that it could have raised more the complexity and quality of the final product. Therefore, this kind of bastard son of "Lives Crusades" Robert Altman or "Magnolia" by Paul Thomas Anderson, does not reach the greatness of the same level. It even gets to the depth (especially relating to the characters and their quest for vital sense), complexity and epic level of "Magnolia".Maybe with more footage the error could be corrected. Maybe.It is true that what is most valued in a director and his intelligence is showing aseptic and know to bring that feeling to the Viewer, without seeking to make judgments or justify, leaving us to us the role of the decision. Thus, proves that he really understands and is able to delve into what he is talking about, giving the opportunity of redemption to any positioning. That is what Kieslowski defined as "craftsman".But we are going to give more opportunities, because that is his first foray into this world. And it is a huge first step. Few begin as well as Paul Haggis. And I think he deserves further progress and correcting errors. It will grow as well. Then, we'll see. For now, as a tribute to "Magnolia" (which reached to remember much at times), we will preach with forgiveness.That Yes, it is not morally acceptable nor sense is that we complain of the obviousness of the anti-racist message of the film (which is true it's partly) when we bother by the ambiguity arising other films to deal with such complicated issues. This is called contradiction.I am not going to be me who deny it, the film is very exaggerated and difficult. But he also has a strange, abstract, delightful and almost poetic beauty. And he makes it clear, once and for all, that racism, prejudice and intolerance are not things of a single race. Not based on who invented, but on the basis of who practices it. And, in essence, it's something more dangerous, dehumanized and globalized.Therefore, ultimately, despite their mistakes, so it manages and represents is a very notable film, as it impacts, does reflect much and, in a way, risk. Note landing on the screens of this type of films, and that does not happen very often. "It is certainly a fact very much in his favour"."Brokeback Mountain" is too tough to "Crash", both from a qualitative point of view and from the simple and likely positioning of the votes. However, cannot be said to not keep the type. It is a very worthy film.There is a phrase in the film which is probably the most significant: "." "We long so much this contact that we collide against each other just to feel something."</body>
</review>
