<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El apartamento" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>His script has a mixture rich of genera that make an unclassifiable film, but who has desire to classify the pleasure?</summary>
	<body>The maximum of not bore you never had Wilder. His proverbial weapon was the intelligence: his films squander it, without exception. Her advise in the monumental serious work (the crespúsculo of the gods, days without trace, downfall, witness for the prosecution) and the fascinating comic work (with skirts and crazy, one, two, three, the temptation to live a above).The apartment is located between the laughter and the tears. Installs easily in the most hilarious comedy and to following drops with arguments of classical tragedy with all of the law. His script has a mixture rich of genera that make an unclassifiable film, but who wants to classify the pleasure. The talents of Billy Wilder as screenwriter wallows in acquire narrative provisioning in any of these genres and engarza them with such precision and with both technical aplomb that we attended (as he does not want the thing) the closest thing we have that, forth, might be called pure films, this is life. The apartment portrays the restoration of dignity in a bland man who, for love, for love always, gets invaded by others: can they ninguneen, that they manipulated to taste such not be noted and perhaps with the secret purpose of doing good, without looking at whether such an exercise of goodness will put him in a difficult territory, in a limbo of idiots.The visual style of the film receiving a black-and-white prodigious, the work of Alexandre Trauner, usual Wilder and artistic director superb, able to imagine and realize the enormous Office that illustrates the mediocrity and mechanical life of Buddy Baxter, our endearing bobo.This Chronicle of bitter feeds some performances seamless where Lemmon shines at a great height and Shirley MacLaine, new after his meritorious first great role but who killed Harry, of the master Hitchcock, outlines with astonishing naturalness.What gets Wilder with the apartment is to introduce the lyricism, beauty, tenderness in a plot of measured extravagance, in a recital of absolute pessimism (he himself was a consummate pessimist who believed, above all and in spite of that recidivism belief in the moral high ground of the individual.)Buddy Baxter, our endearing protagonist, has a huge moral high ground. He is a good-natured. A man without cynicism (so unlike his creator). A perfect character of humanity of the best times of Frank Capra comedy. One sees Lemmon and warns that James Stewart could also have completed the greedy role of the play.Satire sweet, bitter, sad, cheerful, romantic even. There is a point of pleasant surfeit in the treatment of the events. Occasionally, we came to irritate us by the goodness of Buddy. In others, we hope to change. Get Wilder get so in its history we are Buddy Baxter and identification occurs at a level absolutely intimate, irrevocable. The love he feels is the love that once all we have felt. Connivance with the cunning and the double standards of his boss is the feeling that we have had, at some point, when we have witnessed any injustice in this society our so bizarre, hypocritical, false in which Wilder, if I now lived, enjoy because it contains all the ingredients which he introduced in his narrative corpus and that raised to very high levels of clarividiente master in superlative mode.It is said that Shakespeare is all over the map of the human feeling. Also in Wilder. In the apartment are many. Just being carried away by his tender story of late love and fairy in concrete blocks which are, between the plant once and the twelve, pongo by case, her Prince, to know its blue and vague nature corridors, pensive, desasistido of charm, dreaming of a world (who is going to deny) best: cleaner, fairer.</body>
</review>
