<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Blade runner" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Say once they have seen things no one has seen, that beyond of Orion ships on fire fall like tears of gods on the scorched earth of despair. Or something like that.</summary>
	<body>1. A brief review of the film géneroEl came to birth with Julio Verne, Mélies header reading. Science fiction, at least the more powerfully rooted in popular taste, came to birth with cinema, although fantasy literature had given noble deliveries of space adventure and epic beyond where our eyes are.The trip to the Moon, founding film, real exercise of film sleight to tenor of the rudiments in use and technical logistics precarious tenure, became a brief, but imaginative miracle that revolutionized a way look that he had not suffered any transformation and had the painting as almost only valid reference element.This science fiction arming of pure series (b) chewy and frivolous to engolosinar a virginal audience that embebecía with the magical showcase of fiction. Few more subscribers for narrative imagination and terrain for the showcasing of the technique that this science fiction.Celluloid was of documentalism: invested in news images. Film, as entertainment, due to the fantastic narrative almost all their primitive ingenuity. The shortage of mounting a film show of height, that appeared not ridiculous and restituyese in images the huge potential of the written arguments of pure literature, slowed in dry a boom of the genre.From the founding movie until 2001, an Odyssey in space, the Kubrick master, there is a sci-fi truly colossal, with one greater height of view, when other genres (comedy, adventure, horror, thriller...) had delivered indisputable masterpieces from well early open unstoppable career of what we have become known as the seventh art.George Lucas gadgets lowered gender to divertimento with popcorn: we entered the new era of the film franchise squarely and money, for the first time, became the basic parameter on which the success or failure of one film all time science fiction itself required that magnificence to demonstrate absolute Vertigo of its literature with sharpness and likelihood pivotaría.Ridley Scott had become the Duelists and the vigorous and warmness Alien, the eighth passenger, which revived fabulous effectively the pulse of science fiction.In 1982 he makes Blade Runner.2. Electric sheep, divine pastors.Blade Runner is the adaptation of the Philip k. Dick story "Do Androids Dream electric sheep?", written in 1968. . Dick, Bradbury and Haxley are the triad of worship in futuristic literature authors.Metaphysical reflections and the visual poetry of the film is melancholic, almost bucolic tone heritage, history of Dick.Blade Runner is a unblemished mixture of science fiction and pure noir.The action takes place in Los Angeles, a city ravaged by acid rain that a lead neon illuminates with laziness.Detective Rick Deckard (Harrison Ford) seeks to Replicants, mutinous droids who want to become human. Which modern Prometheus, Dick (and Scott in the prodigious translation of the tale in images) we refer to the history of Shelley, to his Frankenstein emerged from the hand of the man, who wants to emulate God. Dekcard falls in love with a replicant (Sean Young, in the role of atypical and disappointing career).The company of Deckard, withdraw (remove) the roids in absentia, whose desire is to find Tyrell, the demiurge, its fantastic creator, the father in the shadow, his Doctor Frankenstein locked in his secret Castle. One of his works most singular is Roy Batty, that proverbially recreates an inspired Rutger Hauer, whose subsequent career has not had any worthy continuation.All amateur film (and gives equal what age who has always had the pleasure huge having seen Blade Runner) recalls the monologue of Batty. "I have seen things that you have not." Attack ships on fire beyond of Orion. I've seen C rays shine in the darkness near the door of Tanhäuser. All those moments will be lost in time like tears in the rain. It's time to die "." Remember his sacrifice, his redeeming flight, the recitative of the English visionary poet William Blake. The Dutch actor brings a physical immeasurable: somehow, Blade Runner is his face under the lluvia.3. The Blade Runner universe: Mystic cyberpunk. The thematic complexity of the film lastró his commercial career. The almost thirty million dollars that it took drawing the future and rewriting the fantasy of Dick, devastated his city, his particular obsession by the ethics of robotics, did not have an immediate consideration. The film was vapuleado in the criticism of the time. It was hoped that the newly encumbrado director Scott printing a quicker pace, more in line with a play action, but Blade Runner is an inquiry of first order on the nature of the human soul and religion as an engine of the existence. The Android Batty looking for their God, which sacrificed because not provides the metaphysical answers calls. This thick consideration not within (or with latest shoehorn) the book of style of action films. Eventually, Blade Runner earned a well-deserved fame. He knew how to present a series of moral questions which are now, two long decades after its premiere, reflection on the cultural forums to use.The image of the death of the replicant Roy leaving escape a symbolic Dove is a contemporary film icons par excellence, in my very humble opinion of the film like that have passed ESA collective memory the scenes of Bogart and Rains in the airport of Casablanca, Cary Grant, fleeing from an airplane in a desert wasteland or Vivien Leigh vowing to never again go to hunger.The voiceover of Deckart refers directly to Raymond Chandler, to film noir of the 1940s. The raincoats with long necks and blades fans in the detective Office create the illusion that we are witnessing a film by John Huston and Bogart may appear at any time, disenchanted of life and disgusted to see so much horror. Either lack the femme that is the aforementioned replicant Young.La possibility that own detective is a replicant, expressed on occasion by Ridley Scott, fatal, delivers one object of worship. Apocalyptic and dystopian, Blade Runner resists multiple viewings. Moviegoers Pro agree that there are films with letterhead of classics that hardly manage to overcome the test be seen continuously by the Viewer. I have a good friend who swears to having seen Blade Runner four times in a row and have found a reason for different joy in each pass. I have I declared fan. I've seen enough times to hate her, but it has gained in stature, height artistic. 4. Newslists Legion of fans of Blade runner are in luck: it was announced by the end of November, a limited version of the disc with a sound restitution more according to these times of digital sophistication.In 2007, Ridley Scott himself will take care of the design and the contents of a Final Cut edition, which promises to be a landmark in the marketing of DVDs of classic cinema. We hope that the review of Scott is not so farrullera and little attractive as that made Alien.El price will not be abusive. I read that it will be around the fifteen euros and not contain (for this future revision in 2007) of any bonus disc with additional exclusive content. Either way, there to celebrate it in style. Make therefore tail, come to the nearest video store, save a rainy night to reverse in the promised restoration noise and chromatic.Say once they have seen things no one has seen, that beyond of Orion ships on fire fall like tears of gods on the scorched earth of despair. Or something like that.</body>
</review>
