<review author="Matías Cobo" title="The Queen" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film is, above all, an acute reflection on a basic attribute for those who wield power: popularity.</summary>
	<body>A large number of titles of 'tv-movies' desktop, of dubious quality and repetitive invoice, usually attend the "based on true facts". For certain kinds of audiences, this is an incentive to sit on the couch during the nearly three hours that you can extend the viewing of the film, along with their respective advertising breaks. For others, myself included, it tends to be a mitigating circumstance to the tape that uses such claim. The magnificent film by Stephen Frears does not require the tagline of yore by the obvious that would be it. The Queen focuses its story in the days of May 1997 mediated between the first electoral victorial of Tony Blair and Lady Di died in a car accident in Paris. Interesting thing about its history is the dissection of how you lived those directly affected by the events of those days of questioning the monarchy and acclamation of the newcomer to Downing Street. So the film is, above all, an acute reflection on a basic attribute for those who wield power: popularity. A whimsical quality that not always smiles to those concerned with the record that they like and that leaves them suddenly and without prior explanation, with the same ease that one day arrived them.A third key character in the film, Lady Di is not interpreted by any actor: his presence is recreated through the enormous amount of available file images from it (something similar to what's done by Clooney in good night, and good luck with Senator McCarthy). Its long shadow will be agigantada by the mitómanas properties of his early death unfortunately for the Royal family. Queen Elizabeth II will live with displeasure the unanimous acclamation taxed his people someone to who she no longer considered as part of his family. Charles, Prince of Wales and ex-husband of Diana, is portrayed as a fragile man, afraid and unable to stand up to his mother. In view of the acclaim that the British fired his ex-wife, Carlos ventajista medrará so that their family report to all the possible honors a woman whom he tricked and whom he had divorced six months before his death. To make reason her mother will go to Blair, who will try to convenver the monarch of the convenience to dismiss Diana with the honors of "the Princess of the people" (adjective coined by Blair in his posthumous speech at the request of one of his aides earned him applause from the press).It goes without saying that a tape of these features, the importance of the interpretations is key and goes beyond the mere physical asemejación. The work of Helen Mirren as Queen Elizabeth II is so exemplary that it could well be in a master class for students of interpretation. Because the dificutad to face a living character of much relevance, is added the stumbling block that this is an educated woman to millimeter dosed the display of feelings. So his performance achieved through subtle details, denote the State of mind of the monarch and, at the same time, the eagerness of this autocontrolarse and avoid that they arise those feelings that has autoprohibido show in public. In addition, the rest of the cast the clothes with great solvency London actress: from a model Michael Sheen as Tony Blair, until an effective James Cromwell as Prince Philip or a scathing Sylvia Syms in her role as Queen Mother.But it would be unfair if not also valorase the excellent screenplay Peter Morgan, witty and subtle in darts that launches a few and other characters. Because the easy would have been playing for work and have drawn up a profile osco and grumpy an envious of the fame of Diana Isabella II, and not try to make a weighted assessment, as in the film, from the points of view of other characters involved in the hehcos. Morgan succeeds and the director of Les Liaisons dangereuses moves like a fish in water in this portrait of alcove of nobles and rulers.</body>
</review>
