<review author="Ivan Sainz-Pardo" title="Borat" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Borat works perfectly as a mockumentary where we see the protagonist causing certainly excessive, eschatological and hilarious situations.</summary>
	<body>Must see this film in English with subtitles. My subtitles were in German because agreed me that I saw in Munich. The cinema was crowded. And the public, to five minutes, totally delivered. Word of mouth on this comedy this running as never before. I guess that word of mouth advertising is something that bewilders in greatly to the large film studios. Always so unpredictable and little controllable.The main virtue of this film is that they present as a comedy and it really is. It is very, very funny and complies with what promises, it is already much more than most of the films that reach the Billboard to say. In fact, I not remember laugh both a cinema and the projection of Borat.El Borat mood is a mood quite cabronazo. It is the humor of me River of you and not with you. But also, at the same time works as reflection on the true nature of our modern societies and the current clash of civilizations. Consumerism, fashions, double morality, prejudice, materialism, there are many items that are very cleverly us slapped between laughter and laughter.Sacha Baron Cohen plays a reporter of Turkmenia marching to the United States together with his producer and a faithful camera operator to make a documentary about American customs. It will soon be transformed into a documentary Roadmovie irreverent, satirical, and the Antipodes of being politically correct, where the destination to pursue will be neither more nor less to find and marry Pamela Anderson, from whom our Borat falls in love watching an episode of "The watchmen from the beach" in a room of hotel.¿Con this premise can make a film?Well Borat works perfectly as a mockumentary where we see the protagonist causing certainly excessive, eschatological and hilarious situations. The improvised parts and more documentaries work brilliantly as a kind of mixture between Michael Moore and Jackass. And it is precisely that Cohen is spinning a plot and is forced to stage, when the tape loses some strength. However, the creator of "Ali G", is a smart, daring and talented showman and get to do that throughout the film stays in place thanks to this.This Borat breaking all world box office expectations and will no doubt be the phenomenon of the year. Deserved. Do not miss and enjoy the humor acid and relentless of Borat.</body>
</review>
