<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Saw 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If the first two deliveries were pleasantly disconcerting this third was disappointing, by repeated.</summary>
	<body>Saw III is a franchise with viscera and heart attack signs: is fast food organic and twisted for restless souls already back from almost everything and beyond (or indifferent) the routine program of serious film with love that break and sentimental brushstrokes of families in crisis.Saw III is very B movies with a stench to chicken with consciousness that eggs that are gold. The reasons of the Prodigy at the box office and the undeniable pull in the dvd market come from his witty, intelligent, sometimes approach although burns the formula by sobada himself soon and no longer the truth, much.Hybridization between commercial cinema and film gore gives the phenomenon lasts ten years longer. New generations are refocilarán with the exploits of the Jigsaw, which will become the new Freddy Krueger willing to cut the morale of the viewer more benevolent, cautious and timorous.There is a very light, very brief reference to Seven, while in the narrative field and in Crassus stylistic field was shining at a height infinitely greater, giving the genre a new packaging, a dignity which lacked for the sake of this flood of adolescents ranging to the cinema to see how shift bastard disgorging to the blonde with silicone and botox in the brain.The long dozen films in this style between the apocalyptic and the Venereum puebla with intention of perennial residence more briosas racks of the video neighborhood shops, which are my downfall when the screens do not provide golosinaje of posh or the time, anyway, what we say, do not get to go to the big room with all the frequency that one would like to, but not us deviate from the fundamental purpose of these letters. Saw, I repeat, is complicit in this mortar perverse and requests, each delivery, another more extreme: more overload to the received atropellamiento of murders.And if the first two deliveries were pleasantly disconcerting (I even had my moment of reconciliation with the genre in the first, the best, certainly), this third was disappointing, by repeated. Would not wish to the gentle reader think that the film is bad: isn't that. It doesn't matter here make it clear whether it is good or bad in the eyes of this spontaneous chronicler. Noticiable truly is the phenomenon Saw going forward: triumphs, sweeps, gives the curious diana of the sensitivity of this new modern, strong sensations, Avid audience eager to get out of the room with a point of trepidation of nerve crazy spinning like a top in the same pit of the stomach.I guess I do that the writer, whose name I do not know, has already tired: has pulled previous vices, also of any acceptable virtue, and has produced, without effort, not disposable, although unnecessary continuation. Money, in this case, is the claim, the dog of Pavlov, the icing that makes color cocktail.In this installment the screenwriter has escaped with the daughter of the producer and now I have no doubt that a daikiri in any Hilton of the Caribbean away from the tumult of Hollywood, well breastfed of alien lust walk taking in our name. In this issue of the account, Jigsaw, hereinafter the psychopath in continuing problem with the world, dies, although we know that it takes dying two films. You die, I say, but is hoeing a henchman with identical degree of disturbance that perpetrated, in its own way, not more, desvelemos the go plan for revenge of his mentor in the crime.Series runs of shocks and already not afraid: the number ten slicing concerned not the slightest. The first, to deny what this evidence, yes that brought us the soul in a tris desbocar is and give of face to face with the Knight of the row in front, that seemed, in the distance, at the rear, a mannequin, a subject completely disarmed by eloquence rogue of the images. Come Saw IV this summer: they wait and see. Come Jigsaw, the Spanish Puzzle, with new tricks, with a renewed nasty and avid for progress public queues.I saw last night at my video store header to two mozalbetes that explained, his way, forms and the funds of the previous Saws. One defended her with burning. The other, more wise, heaped them the swampy store films of rapid consumption. Fast food, I say, but let's not fake: cinema is plagadito of jumbles of this ilk, and more would like many reach her to a crystal clear height, because although he ranting against angry adjectives and sweetened vitriol, I admit that I have entered and have endured, without excessive blushing, with dignity, the stretch long of writhing (that is the more accurate Word) mental. And who knows, like I'm in row seven, in August, when want to give another session of burnt flesh and GLUGs of marketing. In addition the surprise at the end, on this occasion, less strain: or anything. So another of torture for the mass.</body>
</review>
