<review author="Robgordon" title="El ilusionista" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The illusionist is a pleasant surprise, very well structured, mysterious and beautiful. A small production within the current Billboard, without artifice, big budgets or turgid ambitions.</summary>
	<body>The magic back fashion film. Gone are those beginning of this art, in which Melies played a fundamental role supported in conjuring tricks, contributed to that cinema as we know it today, possible already. This year, magic, as in the early years of the seventh art, again starring in various productions.On the one hand we had Woody Allen as a shabby Wizard of Splendini name at the service of a story eminently comic in "Scoop". Allen already had shown years ago his taste for the prestidigitadores and magicians, playing with that element in "The curse of the Scorpion of Jade". After "Batman Begins" and the excellent "Memento" and "Insomnia", Christopher Notan has also pointed to the magic. "The Prestige" we speak of two magicians in continuous struggle for being the best magician in the world, Hugh Jackman and Christian Bale, which not hesitate to steal tricks in his eagerness to achieve this distinction."And now, comes"The illusionist", a film based on a short entitled Steven Millhauser story" Eisenheim the Illusionist "and under the direction of Neil Burger (responsible for the mockumentary" Interview with the Assassin ").""The illusionist" is one of those small and modest productions Hollywood which emit tremendous respect for history that have been proposed to count. One of these films under his guise of low-budget film, caring for the maximum setting, resulting collected and more successful than many of the tapes with dollars and dollars invested in them.We can say that "The illusionist" is a small great filmic achievement. A drama of time simple but very effective, able to hypnotize the viewer with their images in order that this not take-off eye of the screen.The tape puts us in the imperial Vienna, where a mysterious magician's name "Eisenheim the illusionist" (Edward Norton) will come to surprise its citizens. "There you will find Sophie (Jessica Biel), his childhood sweetheart and now promised the Crown Prince Leopold (Rufus Sewell).""The illusionist" has the necessary elements to achieve the interests of the audience as Eisenheim the illusionist succeeds with his amazing magic tricks. Imperial Vienna, magnificent and beautiful, political and cultural, is very well recreated (and with a laudable economy of means), the careful setting and sober decorations, the music of Phillip Glass (who reminds that the composer made for "The hours") very in tune with the images and a photograph of the British Dick Pope that perfectly evokes the beginnings of the 20th century in which is situated the plot, as well as the still tender cinema of those years.Moreover, "The illusionist" has an added incentive of the magic tricks carried out Edward Norton, as sober and elegant as the set of the film, and that make the audience to the room to see a double show; film and magical.The direction of Neil Burger is commendable. With an own script and adapting a short story which lengthens while the script will suffer, Burger has created a romantic narrative that takes classic elements, such as the love between people of different class or a corrupt power. Burger manages and executes all technical and narrative elements to perfection and leave that in the raised wrapper, Edward Norton, the secondary luxury, Paul Giamatti, Jessica Biel and the eternal villain Rufus Sewell (bad very bad in "The legend of zorro" or "Fate of Knight") enforce their talent and veterania in their roles. The ongoing duel between Giamatti and Norton is high-flying and their meetings are one of the many strengths of this film has it."The illusionist" is certainly a pleasant surprise, very well structured, mysterious and beautiful. A small production within the current Billboard that without artifice, big budgets or inflated ambitions, offers 110 minutes of good cinema, with a well orchestrated elements for the enjoyment of all attendees to the room. A film you must see with the same eyes that see a magic trick, without asking too many explanations before the end of the trick.</body>
</review>
