<review author="Caruco" title="Lola Montes" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Your images look us now maybe obsolete, old-fashioned, but also we climb in his time because?Lola Montes? It contains a very special essence. It would not escape its viewing.</summary>
	<body>Prior to the critique of "Borat", a recommendation im-pres-cin-di-ble. Sure we have all heard talk about a hundred thousand times of masterpieces such as "Psycho", "2.0001, an Odyssey of the space", "Casablanca", "what the wind", "Citizen Kane", "Skirts with crazy", "at the end of the escape"? and we could continue to include hundreds, thousands of titles.But few have been one of the largest and most forgotten films of the history of the cinema, that "Lola Montes" than the German Max Ophüls, most remembered for undisputed classics of romanticism as "Letter from an unknown woman" (1948), "The round" (1950) or "do Madame of?" (1953), filmed posthumously.Precisely yesterday, Tuesday 21st, reissued on DVD "Lola Montes", that was during its premiere in 1955, the most expensive production of European cinema, and also a famous failure at the box office.It recreates the life of a famous courtesan of the 19th century, of Cuban origin, endowed with a beauty and irresistible sensuality. Desengañada love decided to live freely, defying the rules of his time. It became a celebrity due to her multiple lovers, which included sultans, tsars or Kings, and his life ended up being exhibited in a show of circus where she is the main star.Love and power in a trapeze.With Lola Montes (1820? 1861) erected in circus phenomenon begins the film Max Ophüls. Do narrated so little conventional, Baroque, exquisite, elegant, full-color and that? never reached attract too much public. However, if they are looking for any other comments also read wonders of this film. and is not for less! Ophüls traces a parallel of grotesque proportions between the spectacle of the life of Lola and which takes place under a tent full of dwarves, funambulistas, Trapeze artists, dancers, horses, theatrical scenes or shadows projected trás curtains. It's the circus of life!Legend and reality intertwine in the troubled history of a unique female that even shake Governments. And as the master of ceremonies (do Peter Ustinov,? unrecognizable!) will telling lovemaking acrobatics and the social and political rise of the heroine (Martine Carol, priceless!), more steps will rise Lola in the number of its role Trapeze.Humor is always subtle and with taste. For example, when King Ludwig I of Bavaria (Anton Walbrook) must choose the painter of portrait of Lola makes it according to the criterion of "slowness" of the artist's work, and achieve in this way hold more time in your country.The 12 perfections.Or to reflect fun sway, the chain of command and the movement, which can trigger the simple order of an influential character among his vassals. For example, in "does Madame of?" was a Pearl Necklace lost in a theater of Opera, and in "Lola Montes" is the order of Louis I to his servants to bring him, as soon as possible, thread and needle to sew the dress of the Lady.And I said, Martine Carol and Peter Ustinov are both absolutely memorable.Also highlights the lyrics of the song the master of ceremonies dedicated to the whore and that says something as well as: "Lola has 12 perfections." 3 dolcezze: heart, fists and hands. 3 Follies: eyes, hair and feet. 3 brevedades: arms, ears, and nose. 3 curves: figure, mouth and breasts. The men are condemned to offer fortunes. "And you offer your body, but the soul you reservations."Your images look us now maybe obsolete, old-fashioned, but also us climb at the time why "Lola Montes" contains a very special essence. It would not escape its viewing. Don't believe me? They will be surprised.</body>
</review>
