<review author="David" title="Truman Capote" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I am an alcoholic. A drug addict. A homosexual. I am a genius</summary>
	<body>Fortunately I could attend an avant premiere of Capote on Tuesday, February 28. I went with a little scary because as I said above still not I finished reading "A cold blood" and knew that it was going to be present. Of course, the film rebelled me parts that still I did not, however far from doing that my enthusiasm esfumara rather catapulted him which hopefully is capable of generating that discipline in the reading still I can't.Yes I will recommend before seeing the movie what the reading of "Music for chameleons", mainly the preface and "Turns night". In the preface Capote is a synthesis of his life up to that point where you can find the following paragraph: "I started writing at the age of eight, unexpectedly, without the inspiration of a model." Did not know anyone to write. In fact, barely knew someone who read. The fact was that only four things interested me: reading, going to the cinema, zapatear and draw. Then, one day, started to write, without knowing that I was chained from lifetime to a noble but ruthless master. "When God gives us a gift, at the same time it gives us a whip, and it is only intended to the self-flagellation".The movie might be on the performance of the whip after the manifestation of the don. And the whip has no mercy, acts with a contrary energy and intensity equal to that used in the exploitation of the don. In "Turns night", it is a dialogue between Capote and Capote, confesses "I'm an alcoholic." A drug addict. A homosexual. "I'm a genius".His alcoholism is present in the film, might be this. Or maybe the main theme of the film is his homosexuality. It is here where the development of the character in charge of Philip Seymour Hoffman stands. Not for having achieved its Capote is more effeminate man who has ever seen, but for that look.Almost at the beginning of the film Capote makes mention of the way in which they saw and treated him given their modes. Also about helpless which is always felt. And his desire to leave a mark on the world as he knew that the descendent was not in the plans. This look was all that and was present at all times.Regard to ".." "I'm a genius", also, the film this could be about his self-centeredness that was not neglected in no time. Except in the first scene, Capote was present at absolutamtente all the remaining. Nothing was happening behind him. And if it was happening it didn't matter.The time was even managed by Capote, no matter how forthcoming death row was and is there when Capote loses control. When time ceases to depend on him. The film might be this.There is very little presence of music except at parties and on some occasions where the leading role was taken by some trees without leaves, where a shy piano appeared. After execution is when the film accelerates overly leaving that feeling of "was too short"</body>
</review>
