<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Borat" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Borat is a mediocre film, to be objective, but necessary. Viewing is essential as a useful exercise to document on aspects of American culture that we do not know.</summary>
	<body>Every little goes a louver that seduces everyone with a different, alien to orthodoxy, film based on original parameters, thinly based on a sublime irreverence. Reminded me Woody Allen's Zelig or Reservoir dogs of Tarantino.Ambas, in its own way, created a way of making films has given noble products and infamous for the greater glory of the greedy box office new formulas that make box. Borat I don't see a finding as outstanding as many want to see. There is a glimpse of these signs of genius in their eighty minutes long. Borat is a grandiose and bombastic guignol of today's American society and escrute with a crude and nothing complacent look of both with knowledge, the way of life yankee and gives us a little rigorous, but accurate, analysis in his casposa derision of the times that we have had to live.The miseries of these sons of Bush, which voted you and which not, explicit admirably in this film. Look vitriólica, politically incorrect, disarms all caring idea of American culture that we can possess: it forces us to consider that the world is unfortunately ruled by such subjects and the such Borat, impeccably played by the British comedian Sacha Baron Cohen, stays, in fact, halfway, because he could have gone (if possible) further still and teach the shames of a country more viciously, with more contempt.Borat is a mediocre film, to be objective, but necessary. Viewing is imposed as a useful exercise to document on aspects of American culture that we do not know and that Michael Moore, that came to mind in several sections of the film, is not to expose as much sharpness, do coarse Humor? With all safety. Vast. Up untold heights. Worst dirty have seen, and at least on this occasion the mock object is fully supported as a subject mofable. PS: refrain souls of blush on the cheeks and little desire to see an ugly film, that not bad. Ugly. Ugly.</body>
</review>
