<review author="Kiko de España" title="El truco final (The Prestige)" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If not for a few drops of pace too obvious, it was for masterpiece, but stays in a notable high.</summary>
	<body>Difficult, very difficult to talk about the successes and failures of the new proposal Christopher Nolan without gutting over the account. Adapting a wonderful novel by Christopher Priest, Nolan makes suyacon an exemplary boot: the foreground of the film is beautiful, but as I say at the beginning that it will be very difficult to talk about the film without gutting it, above all of the part (supposed to be) clarification. The first hour of footage (reaches the 130´) it is simply masterful, with great characters that begin to differentiate themselves little by little then end up being equal, and is that the obsession of a man, and especially if this is magician, can be very dangerous. Both Jackman as Bale shine with their own light in his performance, staying Scarlett with a role secondary and more straitened than ever, something that my life grateful to Mr Nolan (Encorsetar: put corset, especially when it sticks much), leaving Michael Caine with a role somewhat confusing (especially in the final part of the film) and Sir David Bowie with the /visionario inventor Nikola Teslaa man (very, but very) ahead of his time.It should be noted the use of the camera on his shoulder, which is shocking in a product of this kind, where elaborate and artisanal levels (that is, of course), and also the atmosphere that surrounds the film, a kind of "movie of Scorsese with magicians instead of mobsters" is expected and precisely these wizards keep you in suspense as to a small child that presence a function. What happens is that we are no longer so children and know that the wizards are always saved an ACE in the sleeve.And the main fault of the film lies in this. And it is not for the classic (and abused already in demasía regardless of gender) Super giro final, because the viewer knows something is going to happen (on all the viewer who has read the novel), but because what happens is not, in my opinion, very well explained, and one leaves the film with a feeling similar to that which took at the end of Mementothat you understand the story "half", although there may be someone whom the end of the tape seems the last trick Nolan, make us feel like one of the characters in the film.In short, it is a highly recommended film, directed by one of the greatest talents the current American film starring two great actors that despite being superheroes (and will remain so) every time they are shown more effective and more records, backed by a great cast and a couple or three splendid moments of pure magic. If not for a few drops of pace too obvious, it was for masterpiece, but stays in a notable high.Note: The Prestige will be released with the title of the final trick. It takes longer.</body>
</review>
