<review author="Silvia" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It takes place in constant tension of not knowing what bring the future to Owen and its protected. Luckily I Michael Caine it deals offer the humorous note.</summary>
	<body>Imagine that we are in the year 2027 and humanity is doomed to destruction because they are not born more children worldwide. Alfonso Cuaron returns to surprise us and change log (remember that MOM led titles as diverse as one of the installments of Harry Potter and the exciting and you also) with a history of science fiction which has sufficient elements of reality and so that the viewer touches before the catastrophe which tells.Children of men is an adaptation of a novel by P.D. James that recreates an apocalyptic and bleak future where the human race is doomed to disappear because due to a strange epidemic - which is not very well defined - the men and women are not able to have decentralized-Baghdad. A barren, infertile, world in constant state of war and conflict, with an incompetent Government, inexplicably, for facilitating the suicide of the people managing them a kind of relief to suicide kits. It is frightening to see how bombed them with the idea through TV spots, as if it were any other product.A Government which does not know to deal with the problem of mass immigration, which ignores and despises. The streets of the world appear full of cages in which foreigners, in the style of the concentration camps are imprisoned. It may seem paradoxical, but under the passive gaze of the Government, terrorist groups seem to be the only ones concerned about the progress of humanity. And is that the movie teaches us there is no good or bad, only people trying to survive in the best way they can.The environment of destruction is perfectly profiled in the film: streets populated waste where the smell of destruction is almost able to penetrate the screen, human mountains of immigrants crowded in cages which dangerous animals, traffic chaos, widespread disorder, the living image of the chaos and the decline of the human race. But the chaos that reflects the film is not the kind of chaos that usually us show science fiction (with alien invasions of the war of the worlds-style) but one much more appalling because it seems a warning that if the world continues along the same path, the situation shows that we can become a reality.The anguish and despair of knowing the proximity of the end of the universe permeates every scene of the film, but are you miss a little over emotional involvement by the protagonists face catastrophe, especially the character that plays Clive Owen. Example of what you are talking about is the serene, hieratic, attitude which shows the character when his father, uncommon attitude to a fact of such emotional magnitude died. Although perhaps it is understandable in the situation of resignation before the catastrophe living.But not everything is hopelessness is a pregnant woman last may be the salvation of humanity and the character of Clive Owen will be responsible of protect and accompany her in his search for what he called human project, a set of intellectuals working on an initiative in the hope of building a better world. It is precisely a woman immigrant than carrying in her womb the hope for humanity, while the Government does not want to open our eyes to the immigration.The film takes place in constant tension of not knowing what bring the future to Owen and its protected. Luckily I Michael Caine it deals offer the humorous note, with its role of hippie father of the protagonist, the only one that seems to have not lost the illusion for life.The end, but you can guess, manages to excite and open a small glimmer of hope in the midst of a story in which the resignation to the human tragedy flies over a world broken by pain. Recommended for those who believe that the end of the world is just around the corner.</body>
</review>
