<review author="Yul B." title="Un buen año" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Scott is a newbie in the romantic films: there is no depth of characters and situations, not even a fairly consistent and original argument.</summary>
	<body>When learned me that Ridley Scott was preparing a film? pastry?, I thought was quite rare. Is not a director that prodigue in that genre (to say practically nothing), so he had several previous opinions, clearly contraditorias, ranging from the sceptical? do it may be a daring twist to recover from the stick of?The Kingdom of heaven?, until the rotunda?is this man going descabezao?.What made me doubt for Scott was the presence of Russell Crowe, because after his masterful performance in?A beautiful mind? and its prominent role in?Do Cinderella Man?, both from Ron Howard, made me think that he would repeat the feat. But, of course, we are not talking of the same director nor of scripts of a similar level.After this experience, shows that Scott is a newbie in the romantic films. In?A good year? There is no depth of characters and situations, not even a fairly consistent and original argument: an expert in bag, addicted to the work and the city, Max Skinner (Crowe), receives in inheritance a country house with a small vineyard in France, specifically in Provence, of a deceased Uncle his call Henry (Albert Fenney) which sees not long ago. Initially decides to sell it, but as will spending more time in it, you will get to know the people of the place, especially a girl (Archie Panjabi), and are happening various recent which is logical it unveils not by not definitively destroy the film, comes more strongly the idea of keep her.The story you sound already known, right?. Because that is precisely what happens to?A good year?; It has one the feeling of seeing before, apart from lacking the depth of which I have spoken before. Everything is very predictable and even some details are inconsistent; and must not make much effort to guess what will happen in the next scene, almost to the first, what is even going to be the end. The only two moments that work very well for the film are the uncertainty facing the Viewer, for about 30 minutes of footage, to know which of the two girls made to shot of the protagonist is going to be which will fall into his arms. Do and bucolic past years by small Max with his extravagant Uncle Henry, lover of wine, in the casa de campo, are remembered by? flash-backs?.As for the first time, the uncertainty is resolved quickly. And entered in the typical relationship in which the girl goes from hatred and initial indifference to Max, to a minimum interest for him but without going over, until you reach the passionate love. Can you see more of the same. The second time does not last many minutes. Would have been a success spend more time the tape this past because Fenney chemistry with the actor who plays Max's small, Freddie Highmore (?)(Charlie and the chocolate factory?), it is magical and hooks. I was wanting more.With regard to interpretations, everything revolves around the star, Russell Crowe. The carries the weight of the film, which is a success if the actor in question did a papelón, but as it is not the case the tape loses bellows in many minutes. Its interpretation is not mediocre, but required more commitment.The rest include Fenney and Highmore, as I have said before, building two characters married to perfection and which transmit the feeling of love and admiration between the two wanted to Scott. In summary?A good year? It is a film that could have reached more, despite its sobado argument, but who has become a dominguero movie that can be seen. With this criticism I meet a request from Eva, a companion of work.Do do certainly Crowe does honor to the title of the film, because the man is seen of? good year?.</body>
</review>
