<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Once home, we reflecting from the aftershocks visual that we have experienced.</summary>
	<body>Grinding and continuous balance between hope and agony, this intense work warns us that heralded tomorrow is already here.The beginning, vibrant and concise, gives us the keys to what you see: a London of 2027 similar to the current one. a priori. The skilled Alfonso Cuarón introduces us to the overwhelming history with few planes and no unnecessary digital devices. Don't have more than a few fast, accurate panoramic and some other informative document which could well airing on current TV.Shot with intensity and tone looking for real at all times, the film strikes us a blow to us who placidly sitting in an armchair and what we see seems distant. The end of humanity is no longer in the hands of aliens or robots thing. Can we not die by a major earthquake or the impact of a meteorite; We will be the culprits and how terrible is the comfort with which we see.The V for Vendetta and 28 days later, the disturbing children of men is set in London, a Western capital where it is not surprising that the phenomenon of immigration takes bestial consequences, in a step beyond the given by Michael Winterbottom also essential code 46. We don't forget the winks to terrorism and the handling of citizens as puppets in the hands of the rulers. This fable it enlarges everything but is told so credibly that scared. What is more, until we can imagine the end, because we do not need answers to the questions raised.Camera in hand does not stop shooting during minutes made eternal. They are the so-called planos-secuencia, supported by the thunderous sound, it helps that I have the sensation of being inside a terrible simulated adventure. Clive Owen (Closer, Sin City, hidden Plan) and the convincing Clare-Hope Ashitey are our guides by this world sometimes poetic and always tremendous photographed so sad and expressive, with shades of gray and blue. The color is given by measures interpretations of Michael Caine and Julianne Moore. They provide the necessary point of comical tragedy to have more value.Not the eponymous book by P.D. James went through my hands, but I have commented that any resemblance to him was pure coincidence. It confirms our idea that we are two different forms of expression. As regards the substance, it is not that the text had more philosophical and humanistic content, but that Cuarón opted for suspense and action, filmic weapons which contribute for the message to arrive almost without warning and the slap is most famous. Once home, we reflecting from the aftershocks visual that we have experienced.</body>
</review>
