<review author="Caruco" title="Borat" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In this orgy of the offense and the insult?Borat? do just for making a mess, pointing in all directions and unclear what is? open to criticism? or not.</summary>
	<body>Is matter of taste, but the type of cinema as "Borat" (with the addition on its title in Spanish: "the country of Kazakhstan second best reporter travels to America"), is at the Antipodes of which interests me. The humor thick "caca", "vaginas", "straws" and "ass"; the trompazos and blows; cause by cause, splitting the loop of bad taste, it is neither original nor attracts me. Even if, as it is the case of "Borat", it is a sociological phenomenon by its éxitazo (surprise) at the box office nortemaricana (one more example of the "terrible" impact of Bush's policy, make a film like this a taquillazo).And not attracts me even though he defends with the alibi evidence to the difficulties of the fraternization between cultures or be a reflection (which it is, as faithful as pathetic) "more civilised" society today. Do have in fact, Kazakhstan, in Central Asia, is used as a distorting mirror of the worst of the culture, society and belief? Yankees? and? in the Western world.Jokes that spreads like poisoned darts Sacha Baron Cohen, aka "Ali G", alias "Borat", a raised to the maximum power, both seems to not escape nor handicapped physical, mentally deficient, collective gay, feminist, senators, preachers, black, wealthy people, ordinary people in the street, bienpensantes, malpensantes, citizens of the deep America, of the city of New York or Jews.Irony according to?Borat?It is understood that in many cases Borat sceptical about prejudices very, dangerously, rooted. Thus, the excuse for his documentary in the U.S. is taking ideas to modernise and find solutions to the "major problems" of Kazakhstan, who are, literally: "economic, social and Jews".Do one more (allegedly) funny sequences shows us this macho reporter, retrógada, vain and anti-Semite housed in a home of? horror! Jews. The sequence is treated as if it were of a horror film, with nod included one of the most remembered scenes of "The Blair Witch Project".But do not put the cry in the sky. I have blown the British Sacha Baron Cohen is Jewish, and also convinced and practitioner. So he will know better than anyone what the feeling many times, being Jewish to others.However, in this orgy of the offense and insult, "Borat" just becoming a mess, pointing in all directions and unclear what is "open to criticism" or not. What is not its intention to separate one of the other, and that everyone decides? Do do that, that is not understood or the same Borat Sagdiyev.Genial Borat, regrettable Borat.Para therefore more confuse the viewer travels to a format of? road movie? in plan "mockumentary" with deliberate aesthetic feista (and entails no default, on the contrary, the form fits the content), and where it is supposed that there is a bit of everything. People who know that type of film are intervening, others that smell it and others that catches them completely by surprise.Mixing between them, Borat makes his tour, rather than to get "ideas" to modernize his country, to meet their own and selfish sexual desires, and basically expressed in meats and forms of Pamela Anderson.El home in Kazakhstan is great. Do also hilarious the? gag? at the hotel, where this Kazakh journalist confuses the elevator to your room, and refuses to leave because the space already feels fucking great and think that your room will be smaller.But the half an hour was wishing that Borat was quiet, and in projection waiting and hoping that the peliculilla ended, for heavy, crude and unconscionable. Do do even a sequence as "Anthology" as "grotesque" fighting to the? agree?, with Borat and orondo producer naked in free competition of wrestling caused by the audacity of the second to masturbate to a picture of his beloved Pamela Anderson, served to brighten me function. Nor the fact that the sequence has one of the most hilarious and clever of the film details the place an elongated black spot decrying the penis (supposedly long) of the protagonist.Borat at the Museum.And while instead of surrender and enjoy this feast of laughter, one asked things like: why Borat not listening to their partners after ask them? Why he meddles in any site and insulting everyone? Why is does constantly fool if you know very well what their intentions? Of course! It will be because speaks of incommunicado detention and the need to cause as a means of transgression.Art, of course, is transgression. It must also have a sense of humor and know take things to banter. But "Borat" is like planting a cagarro in half of the Guggenheim Museum. Each shock, others laugh, others numberless his daring, others would break kicked if they could. It would also be the option to take it with indifference.But I do not remember any "shit"-shaped this, "shit", that has done nothing for art or culture. In the same way that few times a film with humor (who not comedy) Intelligent has triumphed at the box office American. Bueno! At least now a lot of people, myself included, will know that there is also Kazakhstan.</body>
</review>
