<review author="Mario" title="Saw 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps these productions does not contribute much to our beloved genre, but it is likely that in the era of the pay per view we can not aspire to much more.</summary>
	<body>On 11 November saw the light in our country the last, though certainly not definitive, delivery of the franchise more successful slasher of our times: Saw. Do for the third time in others many years (a record worthy of himself Woody Allen) have the opportunity to delight with the? games? Jigsaw proposed its not as helpless victims, with only the altruistic purpose of trying to teach them to correctly estimate the most precious: life itself.What started as a modest production, without many pretensions and indebted explicit films as Seven, has become, after his unexpected and enormous initial success, in a blockbuster of the genus, with huge advertising campaigns to their backs and unsolicited honour flag to the cinematic psychopaths of the twenty-first century.If we refer to the beginning, it is obvious that the inaugural impact of the virados arguments of the series (must take into account that the writers were well tanned in the glorious series of X-files cult) was becoming was the total alienation in its second installment. The argument of Saw II spit changes direction without ton or are pretending and getting artificial surprise the Viewer, in a way, that Yes, quite committed. If the plot mess became increasingly Baroque (and more fun in my opinion) the new approach given by the director of the sequel, Darren Lynn Bousman, not stayed behind. Doses of offal and viscera were multiplied, and the complex torture away increasingly from reality, giving it a more appealing, excessive film character in my opiniónPues well, if the episode progressed by a tricky way of excess, bypassing the first length of James Wan, this third time the bizarre escalation not only doesn't stop, if that gets to rise to unexpected extremes.The plot turns into a fascinating flurry, with absolutely cheats twists, evoking earlier episodes with shoehorn, but which do not stop being irrationally funny. From the perspective of the viewer the story returns to the starting point, with less involved characters and a plot more controllable, but, even so, no longer quite implausible. Bousman is exceeded not leaving caught up in the intricacies of the script and get to do more cash if possible. Focusing on this occasion in horror situations generated by the puerile moral dilemmas of the protagonist, in deciding who lives and who dies.If in each new installment the style of the movie becomes more and more excessive, as it could not be otherwise, you have already deducted the most admirable virtue of Saw III. In this version the violence evolves until a few scenes gore's most ferocious, producing uncontrollable downloads of adrenaline in the pass that I attended. Uncomfortable them sequences wouldn't let anyone, indifferent from the forced smile, until the vomiting that preceded the abandonment of the cinema (weak minds, not scared that you there is for both) to personally say that my proto-wife wanted to kill me by forcing her to contemplate such savagery (this if that is a martyrdom and not the Jigsaw, should think).The first 25 minutes of the roll overwhelm us with three consecutive torture to each which more gore and awful. The autofractura of a foot, the man crossed by chains, the container of acid? extreme situations that lead to our brain over a thorny road that ends in a State of insensibility feromonal, which protects it from what is to come later.Even taking into account the disposable motivations of the characters and the delusional attempt to marry this installment with the previous two, cannot be denied (at least I can't) the continuous enjoyment during the nearly two hours of footage, mixture of horror and recreation. If you are you looking for subtle psychological horror, or intelligent approaches, it is certainly not your movie. The impression that caused me personally is that the crew accepts definitely are doing pure rock´n roll and let themselves be carried away by the spectacle without asking questions.Saw III belongs to a generation of tapes that virtually since they could constitute a new subgenre of the horror film. With films such as Hostel or final destination (purée, and with unequal amount of success in each case) Saw stands as the flagship of stories where consistency is unimportant, and rejoicing and excess main thing. Perhaps these productions does not contribute much to our beloved genre, but it is likely that in the era of the pay per view we can not aspire to much more.</body>
</review>
