<review author="Dragon negro" title="El ilusionista" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film as his best virtue has an effective atmosphere and above all an actorazo is Paul Giamatti which fails to nobody overshadow him. Entertaining proposed and recommended seeing.</summary>
	<body>The custom in Hollywood for films with similar themes in pairs, such as donuts or the petitsuise is known, the topic in question this time is that of the Magi of the 19th century. The first news that were were the film The Prestige, that done Christopher Nolan, but before this the magician of Neil Burger.El has reached us film recreates the life of Eisenheim, child fond of magic that small was forced to flee due to his impossible friendship and love with Princess Sophie. But Eisenheim again years later become already an exceptional Mage and a master of illusion with a show that quickly become one of the bless of the city, a 19th century Vienna, and will run the voice over the supernatural talent of the magician. Both called the attention until the heir, Leopold, attend one of his duties accompanied by his fiancée, the Princess Sophie. After meeting the wizard and the Princess will resurface this latent love between the two.The film has an effective atmosphere as your best virtue and above all an actorazo is Paul Giamatti which fails to nobody overshadow him portraying the police on the side of the burguesia investigated to clarify the dirt of the magician and his interest by the Princess. Edwar Norton, despite being one of the best young actors today, you note tense and not stand against a Giamatti in State of grace, as almost everything what makes this man lately. The magician tricks surprised by being an overwhelming simplicity at the same time that incredible and show that it doesn't show a great magic show to be convincing as a wizard, in that the film is a success.But the movie fails in a script that tries to surprise and that really don't get, is there are things that are already very views and we are already very tanned in this film. Despite this it is an entertaining proposed and recommended to see, but certainly will be back as soon as we can see The Prestige and compare both.</body>
</review>
