<review author="Torbe" title="Una verdad incómoda" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do do after seeing that movie, the saying I always say of? fuck, fuck, that the world is going to end? charged sense.</summary>
	<body>After seeing this movie, the saying I always say "fuck, fuck, that the world is going to end" sense. In this movie that I had that being President of the United States, you speak with a harshness without Paragon, and more or less tell you that we're going to take by ass.I saw the movie in original version and leave me the eyes of both read all the talk of the good of Al Gore. The movie isn't a movie or a documentary, is a guy giving his students a class. Sometimes photos are videoclipes but the bulk of the movie is the guy giving an eternal charleta. As the bastard talking about fast, did not give time to read anything of what said.Warning: who does not know geography, or a little bit of Economics, to not see this movie will not know anything. The girl that I went to see the movie I wanted to kill because does not understand anything. And is that he must have them well large to make a movie with a guy giving a class in plan rally.Certainly go chalkboard that had Al Gore piece, I imagine the classes in the University with something? All the stats and what you so great so please? It would be amazing, but that is dreaming too, we are in Spain and has not yet come here or the motosilla. I am already imagining some badass joke how to put the picture of goatse in giant size rather than come el profe, hahaha, what we were going to laugh.Finally an acojonante movie from the verb acojonar. A scary of the good movie, because the argument is as follows. The site where we live will become unbreathable in a few years. This is like the movie SAW, where the doll is this descojonando and us is saying, in a few years there will be an arricharrante heat, more tornadoes than ever and hurricanes, water will cover the Earth and there will be millions of displaced persons. Live on Earth as today will be a utopia and will become a nightmare.Global warming of the planet is a reality and Al Gore is going to all sides to communicate that the data of scientists warn us where we're going a tomar por culo. The only that seems to be that they did not hear are the politicians who spend to do nothing and remain locked in their wars stupid that if I said this or another, believing that so going to scratch a few votes to fools.I have always said that this system of politicians only serves to let some hyped at the expense of others. Still living as of yore, where Kings and bourgeois looted the village. And above when we have a real problem that affects everyone, the world does nothing. I don't even think as we're going to organize before a possible alien attack.The human race is a quirk of nature, and I think that what us happening is that we are about to die from success. We are so many that it is difficult to agree. Anyway, I'm still saying the same thing, fuck, fuck, that the world will end.</body>
</review>
