<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El castillo en el cielo" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We do not have large doses of violence and it has a heavy burden of moralina that does not hurt in these times. And possibly to the kids they love.</summary>
	<body>I cannot overlook the fact the original name of the film "The castle of Laputa". Not is if they should change the name to the Spanish version, given that they could have edited two, exactly equal, and it had double the profits. These so deep names have much commercial tug. Well, I misled before you start.The film is about a young girl found on board a type of airship. This is addressed and the girl falls into the void. When it is about to esmorrarse against soil, a necklace that bears wakes up making it float. Below, a kid with some resemblance to Peter (of Heidi, no Almodovar) picked up and aid. And I will not tell more, that for a worthwhile not I her I destripo.We have a recording with an aftertaste of total "The journey of spirited away", although a little bit worse. The introduction is incredibly beautiful, with machines that seem drawn from the imagination of Leonardo Da Vinci. Although truth be told, then they do not have much to do with the movie, but it is interesting. The pictures remind us much framework and Heidi (I was waiting to see if he left the monkey Amelio, but in the end does not appear). The argument is not incredible, as the spirited away, although it is not wrong. And what still find me amazing is the imagination that these people to make unlikely cities and unworkable junk. It is impressive. As a point against, which is a bit long, but to me I care not.In short, that you paseis by the video store to rent right now, which is one of those that like to see. We do not have large doses of violence and it has a heavy burden of moralina that does not hurt in these times. And possibly to the kids they love (although remind you that girls do not fly, by many necklaces with).</body>
</review>
