<review author="José A. Peig" title="El perfume" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great work poetic, so much fun as dramatic, so direct in their aesthetic intentions as ambiguous and multifaceted in its ultimate meaning. Film that is part of a hidden reality and dream.</summary>
	<body>The perfume is the essence of everything, since there is nothing that is so early as the smell, located in the fragrance that transcends the purely physical beauty and raises her to the altar of poetic and sensual. The perfume upsets because it is a subtle mystery, a carnality so evident that it symbolizes her in his mesmerising Ethereal smoke. There was a boy born of crap every day, which soared above the filthy Plebs who could never rocked with the due motherly aroma. The same social stench becomes reason and weapon to return evil for goodness or kindness despite such evil. If you find your perfume, you find yourself. When the circle closes, you return to the origin, the dirty origin which takes you the final debt. Great story of a Savior resulting in victim of his own humanity.European production directed by German Tom Tykwer, inspired by a known bestseller, we are faced with a purely symbolic film. Their beauty lies - as in a lyric poem or epic - represented history under the fertile look of the metaphorical. It is a unusual fable that gravitates argues in a varied assortment of aesthetic resources that dress with the proper dress of the so-called "poetic function". Once again, substance and form live in harmony with the claims made by their authors.Let us look: the story begins with a birth so terrible that it seems not real; There is no rawness, the way of giving birth it resembles a deposition of feces on top of a garbage dump of rotten fish (located in a physical and social environment of dirt and violence); It is rather a dreamlike nightmare. The creature, always at the Centre of the gaze, survives a first sensory hell, which her heading towards a future of search of the sensual fragrance. Their isolation and social rejection geared their steps toward love that no one can ever give. From that starting point, defined with millimeter precision and an enormous sense of the visual, the central character is defined in his tragedy and their gestures in conflict and need an environment of aromas.Chromatic resources are as important as the development and scenic changes: silver, dark, ochre and Brown in line with the experiential State of the protagonist, and smell always symbolizing their emotional connection with the environment in the first steps of his initiatory journey. The colour scheme is transformed when meets his first love, the first fragrance, the first victim of his need to find identity and meaning to his deprivation. The fragrance turns into obsession, must hold, because it is what lingers after the death of the beloved object. They are the essences, unscented there is life, there is no identity. From this point of the story, predominate more vivid colours, in line with a new State of being. It has found a meaning to his life and travels in search of the essence. Solo on the heights of a monte, discovers its interior when they go away the interference of the obsessive sensory world that enslaves it from abroad. Parable, in any case, the immeasurable interior journey that transcends the external noise. Just find the master fragrance that allows you to control the unconscious and the banality of her fragrant Plebs, hungry of cruelty.Words, just words. Their metaphorical power opens a window of meanings, not because it is so grave as alleged, but yes for being so increadibly playful; under its dramatic and disturbing tone, flutters a laudable sarcastic laugh (see the death of the seller of perfumes portrayed by Dustin Hoffman or the speech of the cardinal against the fearful mob) that often turns into a fierce satire with Kafkianos dyes. In a first leg, we believe to be attending a surreal parable about a social outcast, then we are entering a stage worthy of thriller about a psicokiller. The mixture of genres and textures give the metaphorical game rules. We are before a turbulent allegory that is watching us with very bad milk, but at the time, seems unwilling to take very seriously itself.A toy poetic and rich in flavors, physical and spiritual.All this should add the remarkable setting and historical reenactment, the commissioning scene arrogance, the sober but elegant and precise direction at a time requiring lyrical meaning, and a montage that emphasizes - in a very appropriate way - the obsessive action of his central character around the remaining cast. With regard to the narrative, is appreciated the subtlety that emerges from a crucial omission: never come to know whether the latest victim (which will provide the final drops for the composition of the spellbinding perfume) has been forced or has ceded voluntarily to a necessary sacrifice; the decline in the gesture of violence and subsequent exchange of glances between the beautiful girl and the young collector of fragrances accentuate the ambiguity to open a channel of possible meanings and interpretations, in perfect conjunction with the poetic vein that reinforces the proposed game. However, he sometimes suffers when it comes to combining all the thematic elements and does not have the depth that aims to: may have some confusion in its mixture between the explicit and the implicit metaphorical. What is, ultimately, "The perfume"? Parable of an outcast? Metaphor of a hypocritical society? Ode to an innocent person who is born and dies eaten in a world of wild beasts?. The use of planes slowed at the scene of the massive spell is also questionable, although in this case it seems to be justified by reference to the oneiric. Or, simply, the work than the understanding that now can be a server giving. This has overtones of future masterpiece, applying a more quiet look.Today, regardless of tastes, what cannot be denied is "The perfume" a masterpiece of poetic, so much fun as dramatic, so direct in their aesthetic intentions as ambiguous and multifaceted in its ultimate meaning. Film that is part of a hidden reality and dream.</body>
</review>
