<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Mi vecino Totoro" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The drawings are charming, the musiquilla of chord and the characters are wonderful.</summary>
	<body>Well, we are back to the load with another film of Mr Miyazaki, which should be already signing the monthly check that sends me for the praise and praise him I am. I believe that it is the only foreign film director which I are name and sure of which more films I've seen.The film is a family of two girls and a father that move to the rural Japan. MOM is sick, in a nearby sanatorium, and girls want to with all his forces this gets good. Arriving at the House, they discover that it is inhabited by spirits of the forest, so they have to expel. They then discover a giant and furry, Doll has more mouth than body, and that when he shouts the wind is born. The breast then catches a cold and girls cry. And suddenly get a gato-autobús and all laugh and appear a few titulitos in Japanese and stops the recording. I don't even imagine that the film why certain critics drink winds can be summarized in this, it must be the prologue.Therefore, the film is not that. Luckily, it is short. Come with the good news, it is precious. The drawings are charming, the musiquilla of chord and the characters are wonderful. The strength and vitality of the girls is intoxicating, and messing with Totoro is cane. The parents of girls want to much and everything is the ideal world that which we love to take to fill factory and progress. The trouble is that nothing happens throughout the film. There is a central story, but that Miyazaki is telling us their stuff, but nothing that we hook. The thread in the countless ads could throw by Telecinco and not perderiamos.In short, if you're a fan of Miyazaki or child (for example, that you've swallowed of raccoons) is highly recommended. If you liked spirited away and you think that it is more of the same, you ass. I personally recommend with reservations, that it is a little defraudante you finish and it has been nothing.Miyazaki, are what give me thief?Besitos.P.D: I think that it is the kind we should see many times to delight with the images and characters.Pd2: The inclusion of soot balls (converted in not is what forest) is nice.P.D.3: The scene in which the girl chases invisible stuffed animals are very funny.P.D.4: to eat Totoro? Because with this mouth I don't think that you eat little. And imagine the cacas lie, that horror.</body>
</review>
