<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Separados" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Surprisingly recommended, for all those we see in these movies, again and again, as always.</summary>
	<body>I must admit that I am a suffering from this kind of film, and that when yesterday, "my santa" suggested me to see this movie, I I revolví, almost in pain, before again 2 hours wasted in a script planned to the millimetre and which passes through all the possible States of this type of film, and yet my opinion cannot be more successful, that this tape, begins just where the others end up, come on, the next step to "and were happy and ate partridges." (and we gave us, with the dish in the noses), because well, here, those who stick (and that way) with the dish in the noses are a Jennifer Aniston in her role as always, and Vince Vaughn, in his role as always also. And is that the plot we all know; boy meets girl, blah blah blah, quickly entered during the opening credits (accompanied by a Queen song "do You? re best Friend") and along with photos showing brief pieces of their relationship, and in a moment, we get "the mess" (or plot), where both Aniston and Vaughn throw junk at the head, over and over againhonestly, I felt identified with the role of Vaughn in hundred of times, put that here, server, also often getting home and ignite as a soul that leads the devil, the XBOX, for killing Martians, getting goals, or triple, forget for a few minutes of his painful work routine.As I have already said, Jennifer and Vince are normal, accustomed to this kind of film, they move like fish in the water, and nothing of them emphasize, or outline, correct, certainly they cannot be more, however, that if they manage to take the cat to the water are secondary, in particular, already, director Jon Favreau film, face, never better said, Cole Hauser, and a nice Justin Long that begin to see regularly in the Vince Vaughn movies, here as Secretary, gay, Jennifer Aniston.Tal, the only note negative that I see in the film is that covered under the blessing of the "romantic comedy", fails never beside him more correct, and is that, when it is intended to be dramatic, it is funny, when pretends laugh too, sorry, and when he tries to be morally correct, ends up being mortally voracious, so, Peyton Reed (and I thought that this name was a pseudonym), turns to go again, as happened in "Down with love", the shot backfires.Surprisingly recommended for all those we see in these movies, again and again, as always; also useful for not believing that our House is the navel of the world, unfortunately, all (without exception) are equal.</body>
</review>
