<review author="Caro" title="Transamerica" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Great performance by Felicity Huffman</summary>
	<body>I have no words to describe this film is simply great. Felicity does a great job and shows the great actress that is and why has taken all these awards (the Oscar it has to win), I had only seen in desperate housewives and the change of registration I loved and if you see the film in VO can be seen much more. Plus: the same as the bends in the series has been commissioned to put the voice in the film, not puts serious enough, at first a little bit her, but then you forget. The first half hour is a bit slow, but once they gradually develop the stories of the characters stay hooked in this world. Say also that I like more the American tagline that have been Spain; Life is more than the sum of its parts.Bree, before Stan, is about to get the authorization to undergo sex change operation, but receives the call from a guy who claims to be his son. Her psychiatrist tells him that he must know the boy before signing the authorization. Bree reluctantly agrees to go to New York to get the kid in jail, although bail is $ 1, Toby is not No Angel, with 17 years trapichea with drugs and he has been arrested for prostitution. The kid convinces him to take him to Los Angeles, where will be porn actor, and buy a car. The journey is full of incidents and lies. Bree has not told that it is his true father and less is actually a man (he said that it is the Church of the potential father) and Toby just discovering his secret. Although initially he reacts badly, ends by accepting to Bree. A hippie steals the car and leaves them stranded on the road without more clothes than carrying it implementation. In a bar, Bree League with a man that leaves them in Phoenix, in Bree.La parents house mother fatal reacts to see her daughter, but the rest of the family does not seem to have any problem (especially the sister). When he confesses to them that Toby is her son, the mother begins to treat him superbly, and even wants to stay to live with them as a condition to pay the airfare to Bree that he arrives late for his operation. Bree finally tells it to Toby who is actually and fatal, reacts to give him a punch in the eye. Already in Los Angeles, Bree is operated, but that day is not the happiest of his life, Miss less Toby.Lo better without a doubt is the great performance by Felicity Huffman. Many of the phrases "my body may be still in process, but there is nothing wrong with my soul". The transsexual blonde and friends. The mother of Bree</body>
</review>
