<review author="Jose Contreras" title="El perfume" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The joke, hard to laugh because it lasts two hours, and because it is also a bit philosophical, is that love, that thing that we both like, is a lie. Nobody is going to love ever, because what else can perceive, experience, wish or love of us is our perfume.</summary>
	<body>When someone talks about a book that has not liked tells you that it is well written. Always to oígo someone say that a book is well written I think that has finished it the force. The books that my I like are not well written, simply are great. "The perfume" I thought it was a great book, why I hated to hear that it was well-written. I hated when someone said that Süskind knew a lot of aromas. "The perfume" is not a manual of smells. If I were a manual of odors would not be a great book.For Süskind odors are an exercise in Synesthesia, something like talk about colors to describe a music. In fact, the film uses music that we understand the emotion of the protagonist. The smell is that indefinable thing that makes some people like us and others we are indifferent or unbearable. The perfume is what everyone seeks when he undergoes cosmetic surgery, buy expensive clothes, gets involved in workshops of speaking well, good manners, or read books on how to appeal to the people. Wonderful perfume, like everyone is what everyone wanted to find, but the only person in the world who know how to manufacture it is Jean-Baptiste Grenouille.De Tykwer film I like reading that has made Süskind. If someone does not like you can not say that it is well written, but we can talk about photography. What Süskin was proposed, in the background, was launching an absolutely wicked sarcasm. Once achieved the sublime, all characters gives them equal justice. Probably, also, to all spectators. The joke, hard to laugh because it lasts two hours, and because it is also a bit philosophical, is that love, that thing that we both like, is a lie. Nobody is going to love ever, because what else can perceive, experience, wish or love of us is our perfume.</body>
</review>
