<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="Dead or alive" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Like all those that have peeled the thumbs, giving the command at home, playing the game in which the film is based.</summary>
	<body>Umpteenth adaptation to the big screen of a video game and is that Hollywood, yesteryear, dream factory has become a kind of sponge or funnel through which passes any item to be taken to the big screen, this step see adaptations of "Tetris" or "Pac-man" film format, but time to time.This leads, is the adaptation of a fighting game, where are feminists that "divided the Cod" somehow so what happens on screen, where all the narrative power take it 4 females, and is the only potential is admire (and also babear) its more than desirable good physical, as it is hard to convey the vulgar expression to literary format "are more good than the bread with Pate the herd".Corey Yuen, author of tapes of action as "Transporter 2", "the monk" or the Eastern "So Close" (which I strongly recommend), signed the film, to the delight of the fans of the game, and action cinema lovers and fight. Where this roster of faces, from Devon Aoki ("To all gas 2" view), Jaime Pressly, view in "the dirty history of dirty Joe, Sarah Carter (who many remember the series"Smallville"as the perfidious Alice), and Eric Roberts in a few hours so extremely low, to see him fight in the few fight scenes where causes the largest of laughternot because the man fought badly, that commitment puts, but because it is already higher for similar atrocities.In short, the film will like all those that have peeled the thumbs, giving the command at home, playing the game on which is based the film at home (I have understood that movements of the actresses are quite well inspired in their virtual models on screen), the rest will therefore like see meat (fresh) and little elseforgettable, if it were not for females.(*) Peel, giving and House in the same paragraph uy uy uy.</body>
</review>
