<review author="Mala Besta" title="El perfume" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A rather boring movie that will probably like the stalwarts of the book and three people more. Recommended that burrow the nose.</summary>
	<body>With "perfume: story of a murderer" comes to our screens a new hero: Jean-Baptiste Grenouille and his alter ego, the pituitary man, which is not steel as Superman, but also lacks, because with its marvelous nose can smell the bullets to the wind and avoid them. And if you don't believe me, go see the movie, go.Based on the known Patrick Süskind bestseller, "the perfume: story of a murderer" tells the story of Jean-Baptiste Grenouille (Ben Whishaw), from his imprisonment and sentenced to death, point that begins the film, back to the presidio to their rough birth. A Parisian and miserable orphan who was born with a marvelous nose, Grenouille can be distinguished with her all kinds of smells, uncluido the patchouli and vegetables people throws. After numerous misadventures get starting his career as a perfumer under the protection of Baldini (Dustin Hoffman), and with it he discovers the existence of a perfect perfume that nobody has been able to synthesize. No one except him, of course. And so embarks on journey to Grasse, city in which attempt to obtain the essence from its basic ingredients: the smell of damsels that Grenouille acogota previously. Of course, the disappearance of these women does laugh to Antoine Richis (Alan Rickman), one of the Councillors. Of itself, the script is not necessarily boring, to make abusive and use quite annoying voice in off of a sexagenarian Narrator, whose main objective is the explain the feelings of the protagonist, since if they had to be adivinados through the performance of Ben Wishaw, the film need subtitles. One of the fundamental components of the story also the world of smells, as well as in the original book. But while in this the use of the word allowed some slack to the writer when you try to transmit the olfactory sensations of its protagonist, in the film Tykwer is do the same visually, but what Súskind was a slack, here becomes handshake. All these moments are reduced to one or more players with the face of Ecstasy while Fund can happen the most outlandish things and/or what, from pigeons arrullando among the flowers of spring mass orgies.Tykwer also has other problems, which it much descompensa the pace of the film. While at certain times it entertains offering recurring plans of Grenouille dedicated to the more mundane tasks while background sounds like a Symphony, in others the story advances treméndamente fast, as if suddenly someone had noticed that there were already two hours and there not passing anything. And in one of these apurones, the film ends towards the great final climax, moment in which takes up the timeline of the first minutes. At this time, "the perfume: story of a murderer" offers the viewer a finale in my opinion contains two of the three worst shot and most ridiculous in the history of the cinema scenes.We have a tremendous European blockbuster, with creative German and English-speaking cast, which no doubt turn it into a candidate many Goya Spanish film. And as such blockbuster, the visual aspect and the setting are greatly cared, in line with the current historical, which usually require that everyone be very ugly and dirty. Again the white wigs and rice powder cover black nails and the filth that in "perfume: story of a murderer" covers it all. In addition, Tykwer recreates the close-up, so everyone can see the decay of all living being that looming screen.As for the cast, it is unevenly divided. While quite unable to actors such as Ben Wishaw (the protagonist) steal almost all of the footage, great professionals such as Dustin Hoffman and Alan Rickman are left with the crumbs. Despite this, and especially the latter, they get enough lift the film, especially in comparison with Wishaw. It is not that the boy has no expressiveness. It is a very expressive player. But the problem is that it has only an expression, and she has to endure the nearly two and a half hours of film, which become cuesta above the Viewer, so imagine him.Finally, a somewhat boring movie that will probably like the book unconditional and three more people. Recommended that burrow the nose.</body>
</review>
