<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Daniel Graig presents a much more human, sensitive, imperfect Bond, and why not say it, much more handsome and statuesque.</summary>
	<body>Fortunately, times have changed for up to one of the most casposos agents the film, Agent 007. That of being sexist, rude and insensitive never liked women (though foul and illegal AXE campaigns creatives still believe him).Lucky cease in his role as 007 Brosnan helped the actor show another type of facets (Matador, 2005) and producer making a 180 degree turn on the image of the secret agent who, on this occasion, we will know from their origins.Daniel Graig presents a much more human, sensitive, imperfect Bond and why not say it, much more handsome and statuesque (making silence those mouths that quickly criticized him). But not only the male protagonist has changed in this new installment, as the female protagonist (Eva Green) no longer be displays submissive and hypnotized in the presence of the "super macho" 007. She is beautiful and intelligent but does not make his body a profession and prefers to reserve for his private life.The film, based on the homonymous work of Ian Fleming, account with great action scenes, made impressive decorated underpinning a dynamic plot that, occasionally, is you could reprimand some gaps that may mislead the Viewer (do not know with certainty how many days takes the game in the casino, at the airport is not shown clearly when Bond leaves his gun so that it sounds not the metal detector)(, etc.) However, these details cloud not the intensity and quality of the film that, mostly, they do not provide vital information for the development of the plot.Worth seeing the film for several reasons: is a good history of action we will entertain, we can see the evolution that suffers from a classic film character (though curiously this was the first novel), and we also welcome sight during more than two hours. Incidentally, this time them will not be who emerge from the sea, it will be (and you did not disappoint, promised).</body>
</review>
