<review author="Caruco" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>James Bond abandoned its charming and elegant forms to become a tipejo barriobajero, thuggish and rude, but still well continuous being impressive to be brandishing a weapon or wearing Tuxedo.</summary>
	<body>Strong Agarrénse! The new Bond has a full replica, peeled and great, cry that is already film history, at least for me. I do not desvelaré anything else, but it takes place in a sequence that will also be very dolorasamente remembered, above all, by men, because it hits exactly there, where it most hurts!And now I must mention another phrase that is not mine. Belongs to the critic Paul Arendt of the BBC: "the first thing is first: Craig is not a good Bond." It's a great Bond! "Specifically, it is a 007 as conceived it Ian Fleming". I love this critic! (Good!) (Don't get me wrong).And third praise, I don't know what the writers have taken is shaken or beaten, but not only is one of the best action games ever seen on a screen but also because it is truffle of brilliant and witty dialogues. And the plot is not that it is especially complicated, but has the sufficient unnerving twists.The direction of Martin Campbell, filmmaker already hardened in the necessities of 007, is effective, and the last thing you want to a Bond product is the director, and not the character, who imposes his universe and personality. But who wait the same Bond, the same characters, the same archetypes, characteristics or the same? gadgets? as always, it will be halfway. Do for a start, one of the brands of the Bond factory, the? teaser?, avoids the typical spectacular time for hooking us and in return gives us the time in which the most famous secret agent gets the "two zeros before", the licence to kill. The images, in black and white, very harsh; strong mounting and dialogues, short. They are a foretaste of what is to come.Without forgiveness.Announcing a change in the evolution of the series, and these are specified in a darker treatment of the characters, but above all in the fact that James Bond abandoned its charming and elegant forms to become a tipejo barriobajero, thuggish and coarse, but ever as well continuous being impressive to be brandishing a weapon or wearing Tuxedo.Yes, his face is animal, primary and wild. Don't miss the answer that gives a waiter when you ask as you prefer the Martini, and is a huge nasty.For years many commented that Bond, and so he was so devised as Ian Fleming, was not a hero but also a cold and ruthless killer. And so is the composition of Daniel Craig, a rough, but with class and taste, and no trusts or of its shadow.Why to kill as he does in all his films have to be thus a devil roundly, without a place in his heart for feelings, nor his soul for the remordiento site, as evidenced by William Bill?Will Munny?, or may be, in the Clint Eastwood teacher work that is "without forgiveness" (1992). And one of the writers is Paul Higgis ("Crash"), signatory of the libretti of "Million dollar baby" or "Flags of our fathers", of Eastwood.Lo that is already more realistic is another sing. Bond is able to pass through walls or undergo one "desfibriliación" (!), in one of the most tense sequences of the film. But Bond was always the opposite of the spies of John Le Carré. As a reflection of its time, no longer of the cold war or save the world but also that the background is terrorism, one of the scourges that are of most concern, and enparanoian, the current world. And the villain role, though several appear, it is also vulnerable. His name is Le Chiffre (Mads Mikkelsen), a banker who plays cards money from their clients, terrorist. every penny!And there are two pieces of females between the Bond girls: Solange (Caterina murine), who wears what it can in the few scenes that give; and Vesper Lynd (Eva Green), in total chemistry of hatred and attraction with Daniel Craig. Bond, also arrives to discover which means the letter "M" (interpreted by the charismatic Judi Dench, jumping pass the chronological order of the superiors of the British agent). Never comes it to disclose on screen, but I swear that it means "Mother" (i.e., "mother").And he cited the principle a memorable phrase, but there are other great moments as the persecution between a building in construction of Madagascar to a saltimbanqui (Sebastian Foucam, one of the personajes-hallazgo of the film), which are pure Vertigo; or the last (of defeat and victory, and vice versa) glances between Bond and the terrorist of the airport.There is another special dialogue during the presentation, on a plane, between Bond and Vesper. She is a Treasurer of the State which must give a very high sum of money so the spy faced, before and behind a table of Poker, with Le Chiffre. "Here's the money!", breaks it. And Bond, rather than reply, exclaims, referring to it: "Every penny!". As this new Bond worth it. Is it perfect? Of course not. It is extremely flawed!.?</body>
</review>
