<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Casino Royale" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The saga of 007 returns, and makes it big, with numerous and notable changes, that may or may not be liked by everyone, but which in my view were necessary and are efficient.</summary>
	<body>They are many months already which leads talking of the new movie of the most famous British agent of the last century, the character of Ian Fleming, James Bond. There were many doubts about the suitability of Daniel Craig for the characterization of the spy, who could in part be justified 'a priori' (blond, too muscular), but which also served to give free advertising, but grateful.As well, doubts may already be dissipated. You can like, not like, much like or not like anything. And to me? To my I liked. More than others in the series: has a more interesting, less liosa plot what is customary, explains quite a lot of the character of Bond and is, as always, action, with several successful scenes (Chase across the rooftops). To give, or at least try, a blow, hired the head of one of the best films, as it was 'GoldenEye'. And to top it off, they wanted that Paul Haggis (writer of the sobrevaloradísima 'Million Dollar Baby') and Director of the great 'Crash' was in charge of the argument. And seen, the result is good. At least, better than expected. We have one of the Bonds more cold, hard, personal and serious of those seen so far: a change, no doubt. At best, at worst? At least to worst no, but we should wait for the next film to be able to have more founded opinions.That Yes, the movie is not perfect: the romance between the characters of Daniel Craig and Eva Green, is full of pretentiously intelligent dialogues, but lacking of. chemical. Sense. With 'statements' arriving to be shocking and artificial. In addition, it is possible that something be done 'long' in the last 20 minutes seems it can end without leaving a bitter taste in the mouth. But ignoring that, the product has a remarkable rating: perhaps something irregular, but focus the plot on poker, while reflected us through the 'secondary' details the rest of the story, does not come out badly. You can leave you something cold, but so are already appreciated some touches of humor, that more than one laugh (counted, but sound) will be releasing.Evaluating already separately every aspect, it is impossible not to judge what we all had already in mind to see the movie: the work of Craig. As I said before, not only meets, but gives a personal touch, endorsing the character, and making believe you that's Bond. And it was difiícil, but it does. I liked it, and I am glad that he has been. And Eva Green? Correct, but not comparable to the rest of 'Bond girls'. To my still leaving me cold, and having to assume the role that was given, I doubt that it is good. The rest of side seconded the work of actors, without either having no notable action.Thus, 007 saga returns, and makes it big, with numerous and notable changes, which may or not be liked by everyone, but which in my view were necessary and are efficient. And Craig? Then another one, please.</body>
</review>
