<review author="Iñigo" title="Cache Escondido" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When the soil of the past begins to open beneath our feet...</summary>
	<body>Haneke, one year after another, is dedicated to hitting the conscience of the spectators. Us pokes in a brutal manner, to the point of asking falter and that we not feel practically the soil that keeps us upright. With "Cache" would not be otherwise. On the basis of a formal basis apparently more classic, simple and minimalist, Haneke, away from explicit "Funny Games" but staying close to his already established personality in the same or in the brutally metaphorical "the pianist", again may trouble us with his criticism, but aseptic stories at the same time, against human morality.Although apparently the film does not contain visual violence of previous works, if we desenmascaramos the true content, discover that violence, even though contained, is much greater. We will then receive a terrible punch.Haneke, in pure and State more full of fullness that ever has been sweeping across Europe, festival by festival. As is the case in his films, has not ceased to puppet head. To lead in the delivery of the Academy Awards of 2005 European film, which did not breathe any of his opponents. Took home five awards, among which were the most important of the event (best film, best director, prize of critique,) best actor.No doubt, Haneke was tired of collect both Prize, anyway, after acknowledging the good make one of the most interesting directors of the impoverished current panorama. At this point, it goes without saying that Haneke has devoted his entire to think hard about consciousness, morals, hidden violence and the status of the human being.Such reflection probably reaches, in "Cache", its maximum expression. The Austrian director makes observer grouper, and challenges us to a game: the guessing game. Puzzles that lead us to our own nightmare, the most horrifying fear which nests in our interior, terror to know who we really are.You don't even need music to start to recreate his personal nightmare for mood torment to which subjected us, which will be reaching truly unspeakable levels of tension. It does not need theatrics to achieve the distressing development of knowing what will happen to become something almost unbearable. From the first until the last minute, Haneke does not give truce. It keeps us in a terrifying suspense that does not break. His game has caught us, and we have no chance to return back. As the Bible reads: "perhaps we have finished with the past, but he is not finished with us". Therefore, if we want to play, we must receive much. We ache it, because it is difficult to know who we really are, know us to ensure something, or say that our past is clean.Because "Cache" primarily talks about the ghosts of the past. It is true that it uses a common thread (rather, Mr McGuffin) which is nailed to the of the "Lost Highway" by David Lynch. But, despite that both deal with the subject of consciousness, they take very different paths.While Lynch was based on the psychological torment and consciousness that haunted his character by earlier acts, Haneke makes it the same way but giving a tour of the screw which opts more towards morality. Towards a moral that we believe have lost, but that really is not the case. She is there, hidden, to remove the head slowly and haunt us by our dark past. Therefore, the challenge of Haneke is based on excuses. The director wants to play with us to the impossible. The impossible from the point of view of the placement of the camera which observes to Georges (or would do so with ourselves, in the same way), that is nothing more than a non-existent trap. As impossible as it receives at home tapes that increasingly reveal more about his past. No one is really sending them. What Haneke wants is to see what is happening to us. And so let us consider ourselves. He does not want us to say who sends them simply because that is something that we have to discover ourselves. And know that the videos are actually, our memories. Something abstract, purely metaphorical, and physically non-existent. Then, by very insurance that we believe to be our Throne, we know that our most terrible acts are always waiting in the deepest.We are sure to live a completely normal life, without bumps, without past crimes to justify a present so strange and oppressive. But Haneke is responsible for calling into question and get the innermost reality of us. It deals with hitting the slap in the face to the well-to-do bourgeoisie so you wake up once and for all and is able to see what happened and no longer deny it throughout his life.Spit what in the deepest of himself knows that it actually nests, while in everyday life it not even remember.Guilt haunts us continually, and, therefore, fear (is not a terror to the use, is the fear of the simple every day) is something that accompanies us to each corner. He gets up into our dreams and takes us by the hand to perdition.With a stunning montage and a simple address (sometimes reminds us a home working) but prodigious, Haneke brings together two great actors that perform two monstrous interpretations: Juliette Binoche and Daniel Auteuil. The film exudes a nearly exhausting sobriety and an atmosphere superb and necessary to get what you really looking for: overwhelm the protagonist, and thus the same Viewer. Because, ultimately, what pursues is let into question our supposed good morals when making a difference between social classes. World of difference which causes rejection and avoids recognize him, since some stripping of all others to be able to taste its so comfortable and settled life.A manipulated life, in essence, by the distorted information offered on television. A means which only opts for the side that fits him best. It is indifferent if wars occur, suicide attacks or if the victim is really that appears. As we do with all of our decisions in pursuit of achieving a future accommodating and quiet. Bypassing who is necessary.But, sooner or later, as much as we want to deny to ourselves and preach all our kindness and life so exemplary that we have conducted, will end up turning against us. US attack to unstable most of our being: consciousness. And guilt will end harassing weaker than we have and what we sincerely want most: our children. We know it or not, so we go from generation in generation. And the ball will grow. To an extent as inevitable as frightening. Conscience, in this way, is as if he heredase. And if we do not understand, it still there, hidden, noting, as aseptic but cruel as ever, so our descendants her suffering and her suffering. Until that we realize what we have caused. Us or those who come later. If someday come to do so. Reality, very hidden that it is, is the most hard and cruel that we may never attack. More than any punch, hit or shot.Therefore it is not a visceral punch, that judges, discards, deletes, or decides. It is a punch that observes, analyses and gazes. That compels us to us to decide and to reflect, without position on any side. And it is, in essence, the kind of punch that hurts most. It's the blow of the weight of the conscience of the past that us seeks and makes us tremble to the point of not feeling the ground beneath our feet. It shows the fear to be observed and analyzed by our actions and decisions. The fear to be judged by this, to be persecuted until our destruction. To be persecuted by no one else. by ourselves.Since then, the rest of the world of cinema, especially the vaunted of United States, should kneel before the evidence that "Cache" is the best of 2005, that the work of Haneke is cinema in its purest form, and that gives hope to the rest of topical works that flooded the celluloid and make viewers seeking new concerns are plunging, increasingly, in the deepest of the disappointments.But, as usual, not everyone will be willing to play the game of Haneke. You can not cope with it. This is something that also understands the director, as also understands our human condition. Work teacher Michael Haneke.</body>
</review>
