<review author="Pablo López" title="El camino de los ingleses" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>To be a very personal project he recreates too in some passages and scenes that give a slower pace than it should to the film.</summary>
	<body>Well, I tell you. In regards to the film, let me say that I really liked, is a film something risky, courageous, but that if he gets the dot, you can enjoy a lot, with very good music and a photograph. It is very nice, very sad, very sincere, I don't know, to my personally have found me a beautiful story. I already bought the novel by Antonio Soler (which is from Malaga).Antonio flags (pro Malaga) at the address is has ported fairly well, rather than by address itself to this very correct with some very good clarity dots, because to be a very personal project yours too recreates some passages and scenes that give a slower pace than it should to the film.The actors are very well, perhaps the fact that does not see 'My Adorable neighbors' has made me convince Alberto Amarilla as Miguelito Dávila of the 78, but my it seems to me that all do very well, especially Raúl Arévalo, which already at the press conference a couple of journalists assigned Goya revelation of this year. Special mention are the already tanned Juan Diego, Victoria Abril (in a character that I completely subjugates) and one huge Lucius Romero (another Malaga) in the role of the character of Raúl Arévalo grandfather. Fran Perea is another that has a very interesting character, which I would have liked to be developed more, but with this boy playing. better as well.We start now with the two strengths of the film: Antonio Meliveo (Malaga also) has made a score for this film really nice, simple, without too much artifice that gives an air of tranquility and be that long that it did not see in a movie, at any time could imagine the film with another more appropriate music. And choose the Who to put in the soundtrack, has also joined points, lol. Xabi Giménez is another that also is has currado, the director of photography has been able to translate very well, with a lot of beauty what flags wanted to this story, because the picture is really beautiful, even in those particular moments in which requires extra effort.I think that not left me nothing more in the pipeline. Only her, I recommend that you go to the cinema to see, that if it catches you point you can enjoy much, because it is a film which has not ideally see it, but think about it days later.A hug!P.S. Note also the morning the wonderful movie press kit that I spent at the Teatro Cervantes, that happened to be from this moment the most beautiful of my collection (which is not small), no doubt. And how not, this cocktail with your drumstick, his loin sauce, its canapés of cod and vino de la tierra. You have to see how caring for the press!</body>
</review>
