<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="El perfume" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Intriguing, dramatic, evil, raw and essential history of a type without smell which extracts his fine young for "El Perfume"</summary>
	<body>Notice to Mariners, this is a film not literary criticism. I have read the book, nor was I would make references to the same. Only say that my medium peach, that if is what has been read, also liked the movie. Certainly not I forget, if you arrive ten minutes later to the film does not pass anything, unless they mentarán you to the mother craft some Viewer. It seems to me that a start did not take as well.The film is about a type who was born in Paris of a few centuries ago, with an incredible gift, their sense of smell. More amazing is, taking into account the pestulencia were in the streets of the world at that time. As you have a rough birth, ends up in an orphanage, where he sold to a Tanner (not encurtidor as they say in the movie, these sell pickled Eggplant) fur. And thus, malviviendo reaches a master decorative which takes him as an Assistant. Our protagonist has a single obsession, which is the capture the essence of things, that smell that we all have. Well, and a roll of 13 essences is very poetic. Total, pim pam, pim pam, the thing is complicated as it says the joke "if I came for bread, which I do with shorts for knees?". But he killing fine muchachas.¿Que if I liked the movie? Me ha encantado, with the exception of the first 10 minutes were not necessary nor much less. The setting I think is exceptional, and the pretty good cast, with the exception of the protagonist (not transmits me anything). The argument is conspicuous by its originality, and I have to say that the resolution found me of the strangest I've ever seen (there will be more than one to say that it was foreseeable, that oracles are not missing). Development hooks and you get caught, although he fails to get you into the mind of the murderer. And it is that it is very difficult to describe odours. Nothing more to say, that you should go to the cinema to see it.In short, intriguing, dramatic, evil, raw and essential history of a type without smell which extracts his fine young for "perfume". I dare not recommend, given that my opinion in this case is very personal, but I was delighted.</body>
</review>
