<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Casino Royale" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The tape plays a notable role as prequel and paves the way to coming deliveries starring Craig.</summary>
	<body>All successful formula needs to evolve to not stagnate in a monotonous repetition. The Bond películas-franquicia, evolution usually come hand in hand with a new actor takes over from another in the incarnation of the British agent. There are so many developments in the style of the film, their characters or in its history that the relevance of these is similar or greater in this Casino Royale the annotated, and controversy, the list of agents Bond Daniel Craig joining. Since the beginning of the movie when Bond WINS their double agent zero gallons killing implacablamente to the two objectives required for the position, a clear intention to land is perceived of by means with recent work starring Brosnan, more closely related with the usual style of the series of tapes based on the famous spy of Ian Fleming.La elegancesumptuous luxury and beautiful women are still there, but Bond, which is at the beginning of his career as 007, is more visceral, less sophisticated and, above all, more human. Violence is more explicit and Bond spends real trouble in action sequences that old solventaba without disheveled. For example, memorable is the initial persecution this Herculean Bond makes an offender by the streets of Madagascar at the beginning of the film, with a pace and a visual montage dazzling. Enemies, always key in this tape, have more mundane goals and no delusions of global destruction of their predecessors. Nor is repeated the ritual visit to deadly gadgets expert and women do not appear so profusely in other exhibition 007 testironil tapes. In fact, and despite this most hard Bond profile, this will show more vulnerable before the beautiful Vesper Lynd (a gorgeous Eva Green). With her live a love affair very different, and larger vessels to the shared with other 'Bond girls'.Therefore, if producers wanted to distance himself from previous tapes, have done well. Another great success is having placed the story of the film in the early career of Bond as Agent 007. Thus, the tape plays a notable role as prequel and paves the way to coming deliveries starring Craig (something already scheduled). The extensive length of the film (two and a half hours) and the true imbalance in the pace conducive to sequences after the Casino are perhaps questionable. Nevertheless, the work of Martin Campbell brings a breath of fresh air to the character and will meet the expectations of the public to see Casino Royale with the intention of seeing good cinema entertainment. Oh, and even if it is a superfluous detail, also know that this new Bond, ethyl than ever, little or nothing cares that their 'Martini' are stirred or mixed. Just want to be them to serve soon.</body>
</review>
