<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="La Batalla Tanuki de la Era Heisei Pom Poko" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The pelí is horny, but not is if it was the intention of the author. I think that West does not understand too well.</summary>
	<body>Takes, takes and takes, Tito Chinchan has achieved and I brought a film that you had not seen (nor you will see) in life. Nothing more and nothing less than the battle Tanuki of the Era Heisei Pom Poko, that I as believe it or not, there is truth. It is director Isao Takahata and I will tell you that it will. Before that, know that in Spain it is not published and that if the conseguis see, will be with subtitles. It is still funny.The film is about raccoons living in a forest. One day discover (arrive an excavators and expel them from the House where they lived) that humans have plans against their territories. So far almost normal. Suddenly, the raccoons fight by not be reason and it is that they aren't raccoons of truth, but rather Tanuki, so they become things to fight. Suddenly comes out one of them which I think is a female (looks like a drag queen) and tells them that they have to fight against humans. So all join forces and learn to tranformarse in human and things as well.I think that film is the most original I've seen ever, that first and foremost. It is funny but the argument makes very difficult to follow. Not is if it is because you have to go reading it or what, but it took me. It should be a criticism of human or something as well, but not so ended up catch. Then the Tanuki have many problems to not be what came, but divert the attention of his problemón with humans. I can not finish the criticism without comment a scene. During the beginning, called the antención testes have raccoons, perfectly drawn but without pilila. Well, since he is the master talking with his students about a great red carpet (fit about 25 raccoons average bears) well, it says "the transformation is an art, by ejeplo, do you see the carpet on which you are?" "They are my testicles" so it picks up and all raccoons fall to the ground. I also I cáí ass.In short, that the pelí is horny, but not is if it was the intention of the author. I think that West does not understand too well (I learned nothing, come on).</body>
</review>
