<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="La lista de Schindler" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>These times of conversion of the itself politicians require that a movie like Schindler's list exists so that life triumph.</summary>
	<body>The experience of a generation is not transmissible to no other: transmitting the details, symbols, but not the history not regenerates, full, corrected, so that the future learn from its mistakes and agrees a hope. It might be thought serve as starting point for understanding a film like this.Cinema is not silent witness to history: is history, inventory of fashions and cultures, ethnicities and religions. Schindler's list is a formidable film and is a page of a book of Historia.El Viewer is deprived of its ambiguity: requires it to take a stance and the images are from a sobriety so brutal that there is no escape.Oskar Schindler (Liam Neeson) opposes the nazis recruited Jews who thus saved his life. This is, very briefly, the plot of the movie, but there's more. It is the horror of the war portrayed as few times: with cold objectivity, with grey demolition, with absolute asepsis. Wants Spielberg did not involve his eye in what filmed: confined to frame, move the camera where the action so requires, but remains pollute by which eye he sees, which is (I insist) foolish man, fear of man, the war man interposed between your happiness and your destination.These times of conversion of the itself politicians require that a movie like Schindler's list exists so that life triumph, and this I write is not a book of phrases rimbonbantes phrase: is the most efficient way of expressing the feeling that remains in the soul after we have seen its exciting plot.Schindler's list is an ode to life from the absence of life. A poem of three and peak with rima canalla in pairs and the odd pain. Tells Oskar Schindler in a scene of bombastic tenebrism to the nazi occupation under the command of the field how power is recognized by the goodwill and flexibility of who exercises. Tells that the accused knows dead before the execution and that it recognizes to the master by the possibility for it to resuscitate or postpone his death. On this conception of the authority, in times of war, Spielberg raised a monument of tenderness and crying with a black and white (only bypassed in the flame of the beginning and the end of the film) exquisite, accurate, beautiful to the absence of words that can express it.Very genuine American, so friend life system of shift to one side or another of prudence and justice, commits the peccadillo of consent to movies like this from time to time: beacon of light that should illuminate the blindness of men prayed in an advertisement for the time of its release.Ben Kingsley and Liam Neeson, even protagonists, do not carry the weight of the film, despite its dramatic ability is at the height of the very serious circumstances representing also.There are no actors: delete the character the actor. Spielberg did their myths of childhood (the alien, the hero with whip, Peter Pan, the dinosaurs) and resulted in an account with the Historia.Su recent Munich can not see from all this perspective, while save undeniable similarities with the list of Schindler.Curiosidades in line with the película:1.-A Jewish custom is go depositing a stone on the grave of a loved one as a token of eternal gratitude. At the end of the film, it looks like a retinue of Jews is leaving stones at the tomb of Schindler. They are Jews who in real life were saved by the own Schindler.2.-Steven Spielberg could not get permission to sign within Auschwitz, so of the death camp scenes were actually filmed on a stage that was intended to be an exact copy of one 3-the screenplay for the film passed through the hands of Martin Scorsese, backed for the sake of his Jewish ancestry and not knowing if it acometería the company with enough objetividad.4.-Tom Hanks and Kevin Costner also aspired to be Oskar Schindler, but Spielberg helped the novice and less well-known Liam Neeson playing the role of his life.Do not have here the best Nazi movie or best film about the Holocaust: is one of the best films of recent years, and undoubtedly the best (in my opinion) by Steven Spielberg. And the soundtrack adapted (along with the piano by Michael Nyman) to the object that Orchestra. John Williams is, no doubt, a teacher.</body>
</review>
