<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Casino Royale" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Little action film about a secret agent that begins in this license to kill. Almost better us hopefully to his version on DVD and her enjoy a rainy day.</summary>
	<body>To my the 007 this I never ended like, but thanks to the love of my father by bondiano refinement, I I've swallowed all repeatedly. Yore, viewing of one of their tapes was all a family event because, although it will not liked much, had to recognize that the explosions, the action, the devices used, etc, were only in the movies of the time. Now the topic has changed and any film has a few special effects of scandal, so it costs more than highlight the movies with "licence to kill".The film is a secret agent in the service of the British Government which kills two gentlemen to be double zero. Then in his first mission almost creates an international conflict, so give it a vacation, take advantage to pull the thread and discover a bad taco type who cries blood by an eye. So it gets in a game company to put this man in leather and remove million to international terrorism (if it had given him a shot at the beginning of the movie, there eventually). What do that I think the film? I am glad that ask me this question, friend. The film found it me fairly loose, and that I was expecting little. They have to start (the actor and the character) catch a fairly backed bond, with little refined manners that humanizarán you, but that take away all the glamour. Perhaps is correct for the times they run, but I prefer an anachronistic character. They show the evolution of the character, as it matures during the recording, but in cinema entertainment pure and simple that needless. Then, where is the action? It has three "Hairpin" scenes, some sex and love, eternal and boring game for which we do not understand the poker, some of the humor caracterísitico and I like and little else. The tape no wasted action as expected and has a depth of script that found me not necessary. By the way, the torture scene is a little pathetic.In short, little action film about a secret agent that begins in this license to kill. Almost better us hopefully to his version on DVD and her enjoy a rainy day.</body>
</review>
