<review author="Pablo López" title="El laberinto del fauno" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film which could perhaps lead to confusion, because the sell something that is not exactly, but for me, of course, a confusion that gave me a major surprise.</summary>
	<body>On Thursday I had the pleasure of going to the cinema after a long time, and it left me very good flavor of mouth El Laberinto del Fauno, by Guillermo del Toro. A film which could perhaps lead to confusion, because the sell something that is not exactly, but for me, of course, a confusion that gave me a major surprise.Ophelia is a girl fond of fairy tales which has live times of the Spanish civil war. With her mother, Carmen, was directed to a mill located in the mountain where Captain Vidal has mounted the front of operations against the last Republican resistance. Upon arrival there discovers an ancient labyrinth located a few meters from the residence.With this first premise, del Toro composed a story tinged (few) fantastic on the imagination, survival and the horror of the war (in this case postwar). A text which although it lacks some details that consider you best, puts our film in a very good position, and that if, with a quality more than acceptable (not as Alatriste), lack of view Los Borgia (which do not draw me nothing, inter alia by the cast, history is very suggestive).The actors are all pretty well (even Maribel Verdú), highlighting of course to a huge Sergi López, which while we already knew that he was a great actor, here continues to demonstrate it, piece of character which builds and piece of interpretation. Chord music, without too much flourish, a very 'à of del Toro' address and a photograph and address of art to remove his hat, because really, the film would not be nothing out of this world without the gloomy touch that fills with images and the Curran direction of art that you immersed in a fantasy world (even when this is not the world of fantasy)of course, aesthetically a very notable work.One aspect that I found very commented in the reviews of the people (specifically in FilmAffinity) is the ideological position of the movie. It honestly seems a trivial subject, simplify this film in a history of good and bad seems somewhat too helpings to use as an argument. It is true that somewhere, but honestly, you must position to tell a story not be if by affinity, by carelessness or because it seems a topic so last lap, that I not stopped to think that detail until I came home and saw to the same jaleosos of always getting darnel. A penalty.But well, back to the issue before us. You have to go to see her! And it is already.</body>
</review>
