<review author="Pablo López" title="Piratas del Caribe 2" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Friend Verbinski, that although I have past tit seeing your film, I think that you could have a little more risky and have done things in a position.</summary>
	<body>Dear Gore: Sorry you tutee, but with a few movies to your back and other so many entries of the film to the mine, believe that confidence there is. During the viewing of your ' Pirates of the Caribbean. The dead man chest ' has assaulted me a question, the same when I saw its predecessor. Why not make one says the film adaptation of the video game the secret of Monkey Island and stop winks, copied scenes and other fruslerías? So much money does Disney say that you basáis in its attraction of fair? It is coincidence that ILM is there, being the owner of rights LucasArts? Many questions for any response. That Yes, I gonna allow a claim: film adaptation of the adventures of Guybrush Threepwood already!As regards the film, male, you've tried, very Curran special effects (courtesy of tito Lucas), decentitos actors, a story flojita but elite and an atmosphere of scandal. Although you have used easy technique, the give more of the same and in larger quantities. Nothing in there is disappointed, but lose the freshness of the first part, where everything was novel, here already you you smell things the League and if you also unes you that the movie lasts two hours and half (made larguitas) because he loses charm.Separate mention receive your writers, who have evil to make this part of the trilogy a not auto-conclusiva film, which subtracts points, but those WINS recovering to that great character will war in the third and lost in the first. Good change, in my opinion, and a strategy that my always liked. I see that Hans Zimmer has enlisted in the boat. a good choice, but, while half the world creates the first soundtrack was a pigswill of refried and plagiarism, Gore, I have to tell you a secret to me, I loved it.Final friend Verbinski, that although I've been tit watching your film, I think you could have a little more risky and have done things in conditions, have cared a little more the script and stuff, but well, you understand: bad news is the haste and that power has pasta, and much more if Mr. Bruckheimer which gets you (prisa)(, and pasta). A hug, colleague!Carefully, and waiting for the third part, Pablo.P.D. Not be if in the third pondréis scene after the credits. But if ye do just a detail: put something interesting. Thank you!</body>
</review>
