<review author="Pablo López" title="Transamerica" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A picture made with four hard, an escacharrado car and a rubber penis.</summary>
	<body>It seems that this year in Joslibul don't need Almodóvar to stir up the minds of the conservatives as regards sexual orientation refers to: we have out there to Ang Lee and on the other hand the film today responsibility us: TransAmerica, a picture made with four hard, an escacharrado car and a rubber penis.While films 'seems that it is happening this.' I like into perspective (I recently have still the master what remains of the day), think that you for issues like these that people tend to not want to listen to, should be better to show them as they are, without possibility to doubt 'this means one thing, but can also mean another'. And perhaps Ang Lee suffers a little bit of that, leave the intimacy, simplicity and self-reflection at the mercy of a subject as interesting and as important as that dealt with in Brokeback Mountain, while TransAmerica show shamelessly life of a transsexual who a week after his sex change operation discovers that he has a teenage sonwith all the problem that leads to him, together with which they had previously. It has seemed curious that while Lee sample homosexuality in jeans (in this case concrete rather cabreros, right?), this road movie presents us a personage with Indian descent. coincidence, or feature?Stands out from the film a Felicity Huffman well nominated for an Oscar and a script that moves between the more sweetened fussiness and the hijoputez more absolute, making stops at intermediate points that represent some of the best scenes of the film. Still, the script has holes a number that would not be more that had filled in, because the 100 minutes that lasts the film spend flying.In short, a short film that shows a Felicity Huffman in State of grace (continuous, since its appearance in desperate housewives) and that raises a very interesting story to learn a little more life transsexual collective in America. That Yes, although it has been stock Lee, must say that his film is quite better movie than this, because the limitations already technical, not artistic, are quite notable.</body>
</review>
