<review author="Pablo López" title="Munich" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When everything pointed to 'Munich' was going to be the new masterpiece of the already alone master Spielberg, was the date of the premiere, and was not only confirmed, but they exceeded by far the adjective</summary>
	<body>It is difficult to criticize or comment of a film when it ends out of the film, but the clothes still wet from the flood than I expected to exit I write this, because it is certainly a worthy film of this, this, and much more.When everything pointed to 'Munich' was going to be the new masterpiece of the already alone master Spielberg, came the date of the release, and not only confirmed, but exceeded by far the adjective 'masterpiece' and became something much larger. A film about the revenge is a very risky project, and a movie about revenge and that also include Israelis and Palestinians could easily be considered to be 'time bomb'. But there is nothing impossible for Steven Spielberg.Siendo sincere, none of what he says of this director will be new, and will not be comparable to what has given us with this film. Spielberg is simple and simply an immeasurable, brilliant, masterful, director which gives this film a visual force and a formidable pace, three hours glued to the seat without blinking will fail with any camera coup. The film is a slap in the face to the morale of all moderately sane human being, an ode to peace, a critique of violence without sense, and above all a touch of attention to the human being, the only animal that stumbles twice with the same stone. Indeed, the scene of Eric Bana with the father of Louis (' you can call me Pope '), is very similar to the conversation about the socks between Morgan Freeman and Clint Eastwood in 'Million Dollar Baby', a cornerstone of the narrative, that glimpse of great features two characters, and the group they represent.Janusz Kaminski acquires, with this work, the master category, showing different pictures (that can be misplaced at the beginning) depending on the environments of the film, but all, and I repeat, all, worthy of the most absolute mastery. Already demonstrated with 'The war of the worlds', show disappointing landscapes, some cities destroyed really fine, but the picture of this film narration gives an atmosphere really intriguing to the purest style of film noir and intrigue.John Williams is another true to Spielberg projects, and how it could be otherwise shows a score which, while showing discrete in the story, is very effective and really beautiful. The music appears when it needed, and collaborates to the rhythm of the film with cuts worthy of the best films of intrigue, the best thrillers and undoubtedly the best Williams. Special mention deserves Rick Carter, the artistic director of the film, Spielberg also contributor in other projects, which makes us believe that Spielberg had this film hidden 33 years and that he recorded while the events took place there by the year 1972 and later.In short, a masterpiece more master Spielberg, accompanied once again by the maestro Williams and that with the collaboration of great Janusz Kaminski and an artistic direction that make mella, bring us a movie that won't leave anyone indifferent. A mature movie, a committed film, a film valiant, and ultimately, a necessary and essential film.To leave the film I thought, and I write it here. Having seen that seem to be two clear favorite for the Academy (the Cowboys by critics) and this for me, I must tell you that if it were up for me, 'Munich' would be the big winner of the night, as in none, and Yes, I said well, none of the nominables aspects, can even 'Brokeback Mountain' make shade for a film like this. This Yes it is risky, this do is transgress the minds of American scholars, and not what the Taiwanese Ang Lee and his pair of jeans of dubious sexual identity strain as masterpiece.</body>
</review>
