<review author="Pablo López" title="Brokeback mountain" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is a western, nor this is come out of the closet. It is, on occasion, quite effects, but he delves into aspects that do not develop the main plot.</summary>
	<body>Today has played to go to the cinema to see the new work of the irregular Ang Lee. Waiting with eagerness to this film, and much more after the Golden Globes, but has not been as much as expected. I note that this comment contains spoilers for the film, so that has not seen you not to read, or read it at your own risk.Many awards, mentions and nominations preceded the name of 'Brokeback Mountain', which I took to get huge expectations on what promised to be the movie of the year. As well, come the day, and once outside the room say that the film I liked enough (not is if for the quality of the film itself, or because my subconscious tells me that you have to like me), but that has several aspects that do not make it a round film and, much less, to my sanityan Oscar.La film history, that he intended to show as 'a history of gay Cowboys' is, on occasion, some effects, but delves into aspects that do not develop the main plot (the love between them), but in a few sub-plots which aim to enrich a plot that is not at all developed and it is almost non-existent, so at the end left a movie something lame and implausible with what was intended to be the proposal as risky of Hollywood.Los actors are correctitos, in the absence of a good original version to throw me in the face, have to say that neither Heath Ledger's nomination, nor his wife in fiction, the repellent Michelle Williams 'Dawson grows', is not worthy of it, while it is the emerging talent of Jake Gyllenhaal which stands out above the others giving an interpretation very very believable (also has there 'Jarhead')(, which earned him many points), I bet because by this guy for possible nomination to the Oscar.El other elements of the film are nothing out of the ordinary that can highlight, while the music of Gustavo Santaolalla comes in handy to the story, the picture of Rodrigo Prieto is quite normal (landscapes are in the show off, but this guy has passed) and the direction of Ang Lee is quite normal, with some scenes that are really nice, that Yes. Finally, technically discretita.Anyway, the film does not all eggs in one basket, could be much more incendiary, but prefers to be diplomatic, discretita. Even so, and as I said a bit before you write this: this is a western, nor this is come out of the closet. But I liked, albeit with limitations.</body>
</review>
