<review author="Txapulin" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You do not have English elegance, yet it is not misogynistic, still do not know what is an Aston Martin or a gun with sileciador. Deconstructing bond, James Bond</summary>
	<body>The deconstruction of omelette of Ferran Adriá is to present the three basic ingredients of the Spanish omelet (egg, potatoes and onion) in liquid form in a glass in three distinct layers, and the set is taken as a soup spoon. The funny thing is that it tastes like omelette despite having a presentation and eating one is absolutely different to as grandmother taught us. But the originality of the presentation and how to eat it remains attentive to new sensations senses while we tasted classic flavors. We open our eyes to the genius of a new dish commemorating an immortal recipe.The new Bond is somewhat similar. Daniel Craig is completely unlike any of the previous entry Bonds it is blond and is much more grips is elegant, gross and to ducks, only by way of example we note it is more skillful throwing the pistol to the eye of the enemy which by shooting him, suffers and bleeds when they stick, is even enamoradizo, and many times her shit because this Bond thinks quite pocoy is a little animalonly acts, sometimes clumsily, and falls, stumbles and discover you more than once. The film itself is also somewhat different, somehow is more leisurely, but it not worthy at all the action scenes, which are excellently well shot, especially the initial persecution, which is like a gorilla chasing a clever spider monkey, or a bulldozer chasing a racing car that manages to reach it based on tear down trees or destroy the roadrespectively. The final scene in Venice is also impressive. In the middle are scenes more paused, poker game, and the romance with the Bond girl, is not one more, but that is the first, unforgettable as all first love, but perhaps is the subhistoria that more weakens in the film.In any case all Bond ingredients are there, or rather, are generated in this movie, that something is based on the first novel that Ian Fleming wrote about the character, a still undefined character and creates as it progresses the footage. Bond still does not say "My name is Bond, James Bond", still lacks English elegance, yet is not misogynistic, still does not know what is an Aston Martin or a gun with sileciador, or a Martini with vodka (there are two or three magnificent winks during the scene of the game on this topic), and in this prequel will discover all this for the first time. The idea to gather the argument completely Bond with the character pre-Bond and the first novel with a new change of actor is brilliant and gives a needed fresh air to the character which, moreover, gives us a magnificent and, again, entretenidísima film.</body>
</review>
