<review author="Dario Lavia" title="Blood creature" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film, by its origin, its absence of pretenciones and its visual daring approach, is just initiator of the subsequent cycle of Philippine terror.</summary>
	<body>Richard Derr - amateur science fiction of the 1950s film will remember this for WHEN WORLDS COLLIDE (when the worlds collide-1951)-, sole survivor of the wreck of an important freighter arrives to Blood Island, where a doctor (Francis Lederer) experiments with a Panther that, over fifty operations for two years, is gradually turning in an anthropomorphic being. When this beast manages to escape, their escape causes desolation and death on the island. Philippine version of "Island of Dr. Moreau" H.G. Wells, which is located a scale below the classical versions of Charles Laughton (1932) and Burt Lancaster (1977) only for budgetary reasons and aspirations. In fact, the director Gerry De Leon has a visual development, especially in what refers to the mobility of the camera, which is even a little ahead of its time. The problem is that, in the absence of cast and budget, we do not have a pack of men beast but only be monstrous (this therefore eliminates the interesting role of the "behavior of the law"), the romance between the Castaway and the mujer-pantera is replaced by the interest among the doctor's wife (the evocative and generous Greta Thysen) and the hombre-pantera, and there is no "House of pain", but just, an operating room where doctor Assistant (Oscar Keesee Jr.) sticks with a wood to the monster. Finally, the potential interesting dialogues are replaced by filling dialogues (although this is no longer the director fault), so that, after a superb initial appearance in which the murderous Monster two natives, the film crawls for hour and fraction until the outcome (which we also disappointed and fails to be equal to the beginning). Even so, the film by its origin, its absence of pretenciones and its visual daring approach, is just initiator of the subsequent cycle of Philippine terror (of unequal interest) who arrived until the mid-1970s. Note: perhaps inspired by the advertising tricks of William Castle (by then brand new), the film begins with a prologue in which it warns will that, given the nature of certain scenes, ring a Bell to forestall the soft and delicate stomach. During the movie, the bell sounds at the previous time that Francis Lederer is operating to the patient and the camera shows how his scalpel festively a what appears to be a piece of cuerina.</body>
</review>
