<review author="Sonia Esteban" title="Fragiles" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Balagueró should consider a Spanish cast of good quality if you don't have money to hire outside</summary>
	<body>Yesterday I saw "Fragile". I must admit that I am an enthusiast of Balagueró since I saw "Los Sin Nombre", with a fantastic cast and an atmosphere so suffocating that it left me colada to the sofa throughout the film. "Darkness" also I liked, and caused me that pleasant feeling of fear will not let me sleep in peace, feeling an invisible presence next to my bed.But "Fragile". buf, I expected much more. And he did it because this director me has been accustomed to a quality that does not match yesterday. Calista, undoubtedly, makes me laugh when I do comedy, but in this role is very "plastic", I never feel her real, but playing a series B horror film, which I believe was not the goal. I do not know whether by fault of the direction or the own talent of Calista, but the truth is that there are some details that bothered me enough. For example: when she begins to destroy everything you need at your table, I felt so incredibly unreal that he only managed to make me laugh, taking the "drama" that was supposed to broadcast the scene. Later, can someone explain me what makes a floor full of dust and crap on top of a hospital plant? It does not seem credible. Not to say that they had to hire a replacement for a couple of days to deal with 6 children. I expected much more, the truth, and maybe that is what disturbs me and dislike. Perhaps, if this film had been directed by someone else, I had overlooked errors.In short, neither many scares, many novelty, a rather mediocre player (fails 100% transmit your Chemistry with the girl protagonist) and some details out of site. I liked, that Yes, the scene of the lift. I suffered with poor children who break the bones. Besides, nothing. I think that Balagueró should consider a Spanish cast of good quality if you don't have money to hire him outside.</body>
</review>
