<review author="Pablo López" title="Sin city" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is without a doubt the most faithful adaptations of a comic (or graphic novel) to the film, and as such, we must understand its aesthetics, its history, its excesses and its shortcomings.</summary>
	<body>Having seen this film three times (one need, for commitment and the last by boredom) I think that I can show you fearlessly to doubt my most sincere opinion on this new work by Robert Rodriguez, who after the El Mexicano shit back through the front door in nothing (neither was very difficult, because the original was already very good and even more if the author himself co-directs).Leaving aside the polemics on fidelity to the comic of 'Batman Begins' I think we can say that this is without a doubt the most faithful adaptations of a comic (or graphic novel) to the film, and as such, we must understand its aesthetics, its history, its excesses and its shortcomings.On the stories. What to say, you may like more or less, you can move more or less, but there are, as Frank Miller devised them in his head years ago, are exactly as described the comics and not take any granting extra. the script went cheap to the Mr Rodríguez. Another aspect in which neither is esnucó was in the storyboard. With deficiencies may have the celluloid to the role in color themes and contrasts applies that aesthetics in general photography in particular are actually achieved, and is calcan levels of the vignettes of the novels here yes, giving some concessions on the color of certain scenes and characters.A Mickey Rourke makes himself, Bruce Willis in State of grace and a Clive Owen showing what is led by a cast of truffled star of new and old glories showing his side more hooligan and wild giving life to the sinful characters from the novels of Miller. Nobody stands out over others in this distribution of multitude of characters, because, ultimately, and although it is not politically correct, everyone loves to be bad.Finally, only point one thing all those people who has not read the books. An adaptation may seem more than one comic book, but I assure you that it is not, read books and comprobaréis, because Sin City is not an adaptation to the proper use, but a simple translation to images of this populated universe, because Sin City already was film before this project existed.</body>
</review>
