<review author="Pablo López" title="Batman begins" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film that is first and foremost people's fears, a dark, bleak, black, negrísima, film which confirms to Nolan as a great director and leaves a very good taste to the Viewer</summary>
	<body>Last night I had the opportunity to see this magnificent film by Christopher Nolan that I now turn to comment. How I already have precedents. I prefer those who have not seen the movie fail to read. The rest of humanity that has already seen her, you can continue reading.As Jack the Ripper would say: vayámos by parties. Comment everything in its proper place.One of the attractions of this film was its impressive cast, that even the most minor character had an actor, and I must say that this incredible cast. All stakeholders are very well characterized, and fit into their characters like gloves. The best of the film certainly Liam Neeson (Henri Ducard) and Michael Caine (Alfred Pennyworth), two actors that I feel weakness, and offered chilling and magnificent performances in this film, the first as a mentor of Bruce Wayne, and the second as the family's Butler. Gary Oldman (James Gordon) seems derived from the Batman cartoons. Year one and position on the screen without hesitation. Morgan Freeman (Lucius Fox) plays a little taken advantage of, but this not away emotion or quality to their interpretation. Katie Holmes is perhaps the only 'but' of the resparto. the girl is fine (both in its interpretation and the rest of things), but I does not credible, he is too young. Cillian Murphy (Dr. Jonathan Crane) gives a much more serious and stylish to Arkham aspect of that is you gave in Batman Forever. And the rest of the cast: Rutger Hauer (Richard Earle), Ken Watanabe (Ra's A Ghul. or not) and Tom Wilkinson (Carmine Falcone) are also very good in their roles. Me Christian Bale has never convinced me as Bruce Wayne/Batman, but I must say it makes a very credible and appropriate interpretation (although there are times it seems Patrick Bateman from American Psycho), but even so, nor felt me as good as the rest of the cast. Incidentally, goodness at the end there is nothing between the Holmes and Bale, because they do not stick or with cola.The dubbing. to say a film that changes all the recognizable voices of the actors by others? Because that really is fucking. To me has seemed very correct dubbing, but I would also like to see V.O. (always say the same thing, and in the end ná de ná). Only thing that me scraping is that when Bale is dressed in Batman, two: press you the suit, or catches cold throat, because get you a hoarse voice that there are moments that clears the absurd.Speaking of the music, the fact that two height composers Hans Zimmer and James Newton Howard to take over her was a big incentive, but without neglecting its unquestionable quality as score, it must be said that it could be improved, and that much noticeable influences of the other in some cuts from the soundtrack both a composer. Despite this, a wonderful composition and fits perfectly with the rhythm and the composition of Christopher Nolan as director.With regard to the direction, really nothing. the film speaks for itself, a few scenes, a few planes, a hair-raising pace, but we must admit mistakes: scenes of action (the fair, neither more nor less) are somewhat confusing, having moments that really is not a damn what is happening on the screen.The script, other ingredients star of the film. I went with the idea that was not going to like me, because what he saw in the trailer, it seemed too zen film, no, a species from seven years in Tibet with Batman, but Mr Christopher Nolan and David S. Goyer (author of the three Blades and Dark City) have done a really good job, a dark filmwith some brilliant dialogues, which excited, and some situations that drink directly from the essence of Batman. And the final nod. It puts the willies.In short, a film that is first and foremost people's fears, a dark, bleak, black, negrísima, film which confirms to Nolan as a great director and leaves a very good taste to the Viewer. Without a doubt, one of the best films of the year. Probably the best film in the Batman series. and perhaps, in time, the best superhero movie has been done.</body>
</review>
