<review author="Pablo L칩pez" title="Casino Royale" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The strong point of this film is not fairly Campbell or Haggis, but Craig.</summary>
	<body>This is the story of a resurrection. The resurrection of a saga that, as the genre of the western in their times, was starting to degenerate and not to take seriously to itself. And the man who unwittingly, became the incarnation more faithful of a myth for many years.This is the story of Casino Royale, which since its inception received much criticism since the election of the new Bond to the need that this novel to adapt. They were dark times for the production (of course with Tarantino and Brosnan interested in the project, few things could paint better), but cape칩 them with great dignity. Then came the day of the premiere.Casino Royale has what the three latest James Bond tapes left by the way: a history plausible (into what that means in the Bond saga) with an actor that lives up to. James Bond has always been a jerk, misogynistic, sexist, sarcastic, sobrado and thousand nicknames again, but, being the first British spy adventure, would be different and only major details on the agent. And so it is.Martin Campbell curra is a very successful and effective, discreet, direction that leaves all the weight in the action, a very well done, very well shot action and what the film is in its fair measure. Ojipl치tico I was to see that Paul Haggis was also amidst the screenplay for this film, a dash of something more notable than previous (and much earlier) delivery, but without us, that James Bond at the end and after all we all know that he is James Bond and can not be asked del olmo pears. But, although he could have become so, the strong point of this movie not be fairly Campbell or Haggis, but Craig.Un Bond much more visceral, physical, direct and without compromises, in short, a more humane Bond is which appears to us in this film, where we learn why Bond is thus where are all their deadbolt, customs, actions, thoughts. a kind of 'James Bond Begins' that brings us closer to the person than the myth. A human Bond shown close, sensitive, concerned and sincere. but little long.Eva girl gorgeous Green Bond illuminates the screen everytime appears, especially with those wonderful (although somewhat rambling) fighting linguistic facing Bond and Vesper. Mads Mikkelsen creates one of the best bad Bond in the series, without artifice 'Dominator of the world', simply of ricach칩n terrorist, who like all the rich, the more has more wants, with their problems, their plight and their shenanigans.Another characteristic of the 007 movies aspect are the credits and the songs that accompany it, where in this film there is also a change, because they aren't a Bond titles to use, but are cool a lot also, and Chris Cornell song I love, is not a Bond song to use, but as I'm not tired of repeating in this article. This is not a Bond film to use.Ultimately, and to end this article, a film much more close and understandable James Bond in a way because it teaches us why Bond is so, but certainly opens a new avenue of action for later sequels that revitalises the saga, that lately I was in cardiac arrest.</body>
</review>
