<review author="Dragon negro" title="El perfume" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Really well made and staged that despite running a time of downturn meets expectations and it did not disappoint the fans of the book, a shame from being one step away from being a great movie.</summary>
	<body>Jean-Baptiste Grenouille was born in the neighborhood more smelly and dirty Paris, amid the debris of a fish market and is abandoned by his mother. Collected by a hospice and brought up in the, soon realize that it is not equal to the rest of children. And it is that he has an extraordinary sense of smell that makes them special and different. Later sold to a Tanner of hides, passed his childhood and adolescence to survive in a bad way. One day, attracted by the smell of a beautiful woman, will discover that his mission in life is the capture the smell of things and preserve it. His eagerness to create the perfect perfume takes you to commit murders of beautiful women to use their smell, once distilled, as ingredients.Tom Tykwer is responsible for directing this European overproduction, with a great staging and characterization of a dirty and nasty Paris, also get, and was not easy to make credible, grim and distant to Jean-Baptiste, the interpretation of Ben Whishaw manages to convey all that and create a repulsive character and at the same time connecting with the viewer and awakens a feeling of worth despite their atrocities.Tykwer opts for a fidelity to the book worthy of praise, but that in turn is what makes the film at times somewhat weary and too long. There lies its virtue and its defect. Its virtue because anyone who enjoyed the book, myself included, are grateful has occurred the story as it is and suffered changes are really few. And failing because the adaptation of a book of such a scale is an excessive length, especially in the second half, reaching have moments in which one begins to look at the clock.This is because to fail to keep the continued interest on the film during its footage, as the film combines moments really achieved, especially in the first half, which is practically perfect and gets you to flying, where attended the birth and life of Jean-Baptiste and come to become adjutant of the decorative Baldini, with Dustin Hoffman in a short but great role. But it starts to wane upon his arrival in Grase, where he began his career of killings, which the film resolves rapidly and contrasts with scenes somewhat slow in their attraction to the young Laura, a young Rachel Hurd-wood of great beauty and precious eyes.As I am one who at the time enjoyed the book, I cannot, despite everything, pleased by the choice taken to be faithful to the book, above all to an end. A truly breathtaking scene and where it shows that the film is a European production, that I am quite sure that we had a final much more toned from being a Hollywood film, despite the fact that also did me something elongated and that it might be ridiculous depends of look at it, although to my I liked.A really well made and staged film that despite having some time in downturn complies with the expectations and not disappoint fans of the book, a shame from being one step away from being a great movie.</body>
</review>
