<review author="Caruco" title="El perfume" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Get that translation of sensations of the novel that precedes, but is the notion that is a film moments and details.</summary>
	<body>Lying them if they say that quite a few passages of "Perfume", the movie, not I became somewhat slow and pretentious. But it is more true that the fragrance of many of the images distilled by Tom Tykwer still accompany me, by its beauty, and its disturbance. what luck he was chosen rather than any other filmmaker applied and correct! The director of "Run Lola, run" dares to include curfews or very personal decisions. Risk in one of European blockbusters with more euros invested in recent years. And makes it aware that it will be on view, and olfateada, by millions of readers, fans or not, the highly original novel of the German Patrick Süskind. but the most interest for which we had to read the book, and who was not, to see how the film would solve the complicated task of adapting the universe of olfactory sensations evoking Süskind. the challenge also required an imaginative directorenemy of the mere illustrations for a novel large screen. Obviously the results are not always the best. Do difficult era, for example, avoid the? voice-over? (from John Hurt in the original), especially in their first sequences and to allow us to access best in what is cooked in the mind and such as well developed sense of Jean-Baptiste Grenouille (Ben Wishaw).But in just twenty minutes Tykwer manages since chain 4 or 5 scenes of impact.The artist and her world.Hyperbolic and hyperrealistic, there are strongly contrasting colors, the rapid progress of the camera, scene changes sudden, virtuous? circular close-ups?, ecstatic faces or inserts of all kinds of objects, food or human faces, intended to produce us a few immediate effect blows.Perhaps another director would have limited to abuse the close-ups of noses and nasal cavities, or to frame simple still lifes. However, Tykwer get images of a beauty and horror, plastically impressive, especially as regards the morbidity of its eroticism or as show bodies, chaste and grotesque pose, of the victims of this crazy and misunderstood artist is the perfumer Grenouille. A genius to the search of his great work, and a media that make it a killer.Theirs is trying to extract and preserve the well most precious ever known, and this only emanates from the skin and hair of young and virginal young girls that, denying the first to cooperate, eventually she and the other lifeless.Ben Whishaw is excellent as this insignificant man in the eyes of others, but with a superhuman gift. I do not think that Gaspar Ulliel when will it release, probably next year "Hannibal rising", is his height recreating the adolescence of other popular and fictitious serial killer: the Cannibal Lecter.Wishaw gets fully into that almost imperceptible being that does not identify at all with people and the world that surrounds him. A world that could be our current, but is of the pre-revolutionary France of the 18th century, indecentemente little scrupulous hygiene and the good smell. Where the aroma seems to only join noble persons, either of nature or social status. And where Grenouille seems one of the few elected to separate most of the mundane; to capture the beauty among so much misery; to reinterpret the world according to their codes. But neither occurs they imitate him!A nose, a baby and a redhead.Although the two hours and twenty minutes of footage not always scratch at the same height. There is irregularity, delinquency and artifice, and even one of the scenes most complex, crowning and expected, as it is that of the orgy, choreographed by La Fura dels Baus theatre group, resembling to that, too theatrical.Do do Dustin Hoffman keeps the mannerisms and? tics? many of his more recent films, perhaps why the weight of the clothes, makeup and wig are what prevent. "And Alan Rickman, sometimes great actor, has the audacity to not change the registration of his countenance in any, absolutely none of the scenes in which it acts.""The perfume" as film get that translation of sensations of the novel that precedes, but is the notion that is a film moments and details.And these abound. My favorite: the camera approaching the nose to move us to the past of Grenouille. The birth of the baby in the middle of the putrefaction of the Paris fish market. Or that superb air plane linking Grenouille tracking, sniffing, to its most coveted object, the beautiful Laura (Rachel Hurd-Wood); and as it flees on horseback, weather-wise by his father (Alan Rickman), the flight of his hat lays bare his gracious redhead mane.</body>
</review>
