<review author="Jessica Delgado" title="El perfume" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The adaptation is good, very good. But I think that some licenses that have been taken by the writers or the director were not needed.</summary>
	<body>"The Perfume" narrates in third person the life of Jean-Baptiste Grenouille, born in France in the s. XVIII in the midst of all the most detestable smells that may exist. I had an uncertain future, I didn't have much chance of surviving.It íba to entertain me to explain the plot of the film, but I will not. Because I have given much war with the book and the film. I prefer to discuss the impression that I have brought, I hope that you not bother that this time my criticism is that, pure and hard. Why it took longer to write it, because when I already thought to have it made, I decided to re - write it.The film begins with a scene that is situated almost at the end of the book, revealing a little filnal than him espra, or not, our protagonist. I will start commenting on my impression about the actors. A 10 for English Ben Whishaw. It was not an easy role, because before opening the film, producers already accusing the director does not achieve the olfactory effect won the author of the bestseller. And I think it borda.Another big film that outboard its role is Dustin Hoffman. Great its role as old glory perfumer, which takes advantage of the poor young "desodorado". Short paper, but enough to show it off. Reminded me at times to hook in "Peter Pan", another great character to which he gave life, therefore Baldini happens to be surprised by the young talent, to be sorependido to be delighted to end up being full. A repertoire of expressions, go.The young Laura is very correct in her role as "Miss", without wishing to offend. And it is coming from family well, everything in it should be correct. Thus, his character is just that. Anyway, I liked their faces of fear. Not all the actors know "be afraid".Found me the rest of characters, "normal". Not they caught my attention, for better or for worse.To tell the truth, yes I was surprised that the first victim was by accident, and after making a cast. The adaptation is good, very good. But I think that some licenses that have been taken by the writers or the director were not needed. And this is one of them. Not cost anything reflect the murder within the framework which describes the book. Like the second, I can't remember any passage from the book which explains how Jean Bautiste pays an prostutita to get to put the fat.Also I sorpendió that avoided that Madame Arnulfi was widowed, to dress in black and Druot was his lover and not her husband. Because, if I do not get to know the history, it would have not guessed it. It seems silly, but the author insists quite in that and how Druot treats the young apprentice.It is the only drawback (which unfortunately is repeated many times) in the film: that there are details that are not true to the book. And they are insignificant details that do not change the thread of the story, but make that adaptation away from the story that Patrick Süskind describes in his work.But that, only "complain" that have read us the book, because they do not affect the course of history.Although Yes it take less a scene writer reflects on the book in detail. And it is that when Jean Bautiste is in the mountains when discovers that it has no smell. But it takes several years to "discover" it. The writer entertains to describe each smell the protagonist discovers in the mountain, the cave or at the entrance of the same.Go down, there is no smell and this is evident, because they confuse him with a man of the mountains and even use him as an example of a study. I will not go in much odetalle, for those who are unaware of the work and may want to read it.That scene help much to understand why our protagonist becomes obsessed with the pursuit of its smell. Pity that they have captured in the film as something so temporary, for me is one of the most important.On the other hand, and having seen the famous and controversial scene choreographed by la Fura dels Baus, glad that I not caught in the casting. Not because it is not worth me, eh? But, not wanting to teach my beautiful buttocks, as they would say in more than one western.Honestly, in the book is very well explained why people are crazy of pleasure and is mounted a massive orgy. In the film, to the hear the comments from the people of my around, and after revealing that they had not read the book, it must not be well understood, something must be missing. Maybe Yes it is true that to see the film the Viewer is not able to "smell" that the director explains, something that does manage to make the author of the book.I can't find an easy task, the truth. Reading a book mind "plays" much to the imagination and is able to "fly" much and far away. Seeing a scene, narrowly explicit who is or by lot of information to give us, we are not able to imagine the same as reading the book.With regard to other aspects of the film, and leaving the script, "destroy" the affection, as say a friend of mine, I would like to praise the music. Chord with every scene. Really, it reaches pnerte tense when you have to be afraid, and produces you tenderness when you have to feel it. That is what a wait of a good soundtrack.The costume I found very detailed, very careful. And few special effects I saw, seemed very realistic. Because the baby was a doll, I hope. I suffered much in that scene, because if it is a doll to my me confused. And if it is a baby of truth, I do not know how the parents agreed that their infant shot so famous film surrounded by as much dirt as much as copper. It's a baby, man!In short, not her I destroyed as much as I thought it would. A Council, read the book before or after going to see the film, but do it. Will understand many things and in a better way. And you will enjoy the description of odors.</body>
</review>
