<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Lolita" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lolita, light of my life, fire of my bowels. My SIN, my soul, Lo-li-ta, the tip of the tongue embarks on a journey of three steps from the edge of the palate to support, in the third, on the edge of the teeth. Lo-li-ta.</summary>
	<body>1. The book of NabokovEran restraint and censorship times condimentaba art: law was hard and the artist, except some eccentric wanting to annoy lifting skirts to morality and to girls of good family, avenía to not bother too much: was left to pollute the modesty, by the previous sieve. He was the author sacrificed his freedom that their objet saw the light and show your creativity or, at least, a substantial part of it. Henry Miller, in literature, was the guru of sex, the eccentric with obstacles, with rod of command in the lyrics and in the scandal. Very smart and openly bitter readers with official power reveled with twisted, lewd and prose vaguely disturbed many authors whose name often appeared in the list of the damned. Nabokov, Lolita, deserved place of honor. Vladimir Nabokov creates the forties Professor Humbert Humbert, hereinafter HH or H, platonically in an "voluptuousness Supreme, always turned on", in his words, fancy to pathological extremes of Dolores Haze, Lolita, onwards, always use the terminology which the author marks in his book. Lolita is Sin adolescents, the prepubescent nínfula of the exalted loving imagination of HH for its passionate deviation not repressed, but encouraged, conducted ex officio. In those days timorous, a novel about a pedophile, and above one distinguished, cultured and refined until the unspeakable and correct treatment as a gentleman of Oxford Street was a bomb. And it exploded. The obscenity of the plot was as high as the quality of the writing. And Nabokov, aware of the risk, but knowing the deep subplot of his work, requested cries that read his book: there was no therein other pornography that the Suppression of who saw their page more run-away own desbocamiento, the anguish of suppressed and panic to the repressed material demonstrate, in the background, mental and sentimental poverty in their lives. That the aggrieved party, if you want to limentar his natural inclination to the offense, only needs a slight flight of a skirt, a warning of itching in the crotch of a teenager or a principle of hair in the armpit of a girl. And there it is, morbid, Plenipotentiary, imposing and massive, immortal, sin. However, Lolita is a perfect novel, a decadent novel, a complex novel like few in the twentieth century, hypnotic, difficult, but equally attractive reading because the events narrated are (and here opens the film motive for this page) filmable material, i.e. cinema in its purest form. Lolita appeared only seven years before the film and its social ROAR was infinitely less. We all know that the eye is faster than the brain shocked: that the image is worth a thousand words, a teenage girl sucking a lollipop in a garden is a representation of sin more powerful than a Homily of a parish Minister angry by the excesses of today's society. Aureolada damn novel, Kubrick resigned to encourage one greater cursed and delivered by the own script Nabokov erased the subversive elements, throwing a HH for younger and more Lolita. This concession allowed the film to be shot. This concession and another added: record in England, away from the disciplined, sober, severe film policy of the U.S. in the early 1960s. 2. The movie Stanley KubrickLa history of HH is a masterful lesson of guilt and Sin, the troubled beauty and unhealthy love. The own Nabokov splendidly illustrated his stylistic vocation to ensure that he did not write in Russian or in English, their languages of expression, but that thought in images. The instinct of the perverted teacher is making its way to elegant and sutilísimos, shoving on the confused and troubled society of Puritans and neighbors with pretensions of modern, represented by the mother of Lolita, Charlotte Haze, which is who rents a room teacher who only accesses to use when he sees (and we have here a fundamental part of the iconographic history of cinema with Lolita in the garden)(, disturbingly lying, wasting time in a two-piece tiny and chupeteando a pirituleta on the Freud have no doubt that it would draw material for two well FAT volumes) to his love to his sad thing and frivolona, to the thing whose greatest exponent of sensual pleasure is to eat a bag of popcorn and throw straw to finish one Coca light. Kubrick asked Nabokov that lowering the dose of eroticism of the girl: have that already in the post-production of Spartacus (196o) the director walked hooked to the screenplay of Lolita and obsession distracted you from his work in the film so that the production company called to order. Nabokov, for its part, warning the Pharaonic scale of the project of Kubrick, taking into consideration the advertising potential of his novel and making the scope of hearings of the film accounts, decided to publish under his own name and in his usual editorial line the script origin of the screenplay. Without ncaer in the searches that the book had, let us not forget that it was published in Paris by a publishing house devoted to pornographic hustling, Nabokov wanted more meat: more evidence of the sensuality of the niña-mujer and more explanatory elements of the love affair of HH and the motels who occupy very greedy part of the film by, as we will see later. Kubrick obvious this bait and focuses on more orthodox aspects. Cinema, after all, is a company that gives money and is not going to allow that him out of control project. Without going any further, Kubrick removed putting in scene the reasons that the book does well left clear and based the behavior deviant of HH. We do not see in the film no image that tell us that HH was fell in love with a young Switzerland and that this precocious love of adolescent, tragically, truncated permeated his libido, his aura as a sentimental and delicate, pathologically zaherido man spurred aimlessly to the tragedy and the failure, as we shall see. One of the levels of tension of the film is that the Viewer is never clear if HH wants to make love to Lolita or excites only with attenuated caresses and damped and mild warnings of very fleeting eroticism in a poorly placed garment or a distracted from her burning nínfula mohín. The novel is more explicit: HH will lie with the and toured the States of the Union as lovers, although they occur as stepfather and daughter. Admirable in Kubrick is the way that it disassembles the reality and raises a parallel reality, which overrides this to suit, and arroba the first substance, the basis for the narrative that we are witnessing. Example: it is HH already unhappily married to Charlotte and they rest, without touching on the conjugal bed. It seems that they are a normal couple and the scene is normal in its entirety, but Hh is extraviando his eyes in a photo of Lolita who chairs the bedside table. Here is the bottom of the narration: give light on what is hidden, but let us see what must not be considered significant. Kubrick was a master of divination, of concealed truth so that the spectator endeavour to come up with seem keys and thus reveals the always Crouching transcript of the story. Humbert Humbert lover is excessive, pathetic. And now let's talk about the capital letter interpretation of James Mason in State of grace incomensurable: a Mason abandons his tics of formidable Butler English, neat and tidy, Knight, and befriending catches with a profound character, allowing you to be a psychopath with white glove, a cabronazo illustrated with an indispensable point of madness and a few blades of social intelligence that enable escalafonar in crime, in its unquenchable vital purpose: love Lolitas, possess them, being spread by their gracejos, unpolished beauty. Quilty, the despicable Hunmbert antagonist, his shadow, his pursuer and his relentless impersonator, is Peter Sellers in its sauce: seizure, hilarious, almost demonic. Peter Sellers is Jim Carrey with twenty more years of tables. Sue Lyon was a personal stake of Kubrick and not disappointed, though his film career did not have similar heights. He wanted a girl and young not a woman already well turning by unpredictable random teenage hormones, but neither the producer nor the circumstances allowed him to go for one and had to go to this excessive, but convincing, moza before timidly his light, his churlish seriously and, in the end, with his nasty, full screen. Shelley Winters ago Charlotte, and moderately shines: living portrait of the homemaker pleased with his role in life, vecindona and plump, settled each night with his memories of the marriage which was extinguished too soon and of love was not continued in its outvoted nights under the stars of the city. Another aspect that all film lover pro recalls is the road-movie thrilling that Kubrick is marked in the third section of the film. Some who have read the novel knows that the film version is very simple and not recreates with the sordid world of curtains road motels with smell of stale nicotine and its empozoñado of cheap Gin and lotion shaving hedionda air. The love of HH and Lo, however, these motels is the part which I reviewed the film on at least four occasions, is the part that I like. The splendor of HH is his own perversion: laminated in his obsession with raise your spirit to the perfect paradise of their pre-pubescent muses. In fact at Humbert see you no forcing Lolita in no time: there is no evidence of a dominant virility. Already in the first scene of the film is very clearly warns the philosophy of all its poignant footage: see HH painting the nails of the feet of a young man. What press is a very fine eroticism, deliberademente never pornographic. The risk of Lolita as a film, has been compensated more than. Sexual fixation of the protagonist has placed a Word, Lolita, in our dictionary and in popular speech, which is the dictionary for immediate use and more robust reliability. We say that a lolita is girl newly marked pubescence which outlines in his gestures, in their ways, style, an erotic, not without provocation sensuality. That got Nabokov. Circumvent the sensura with this Sue Lyon already a little crecidita first was the purpose of the film. The code of the Catholic Legion of decency, a holy inquisition yankee of the era, ended up swallowing the moral of the film violence because Kubrick lowered still burden of carnality, and consented to give the character of Humbert Humbert a role of love, adult, deviant, but in love, finally and after. In the novel, because it is essential to see her after having seen the film or vice versa, Nabokov emphasises starkly insistently again the nature of the passion of the teacher, which is the girls, said crudely, and not love a specific girl, to a discovered in a house in Middle District Garden, innocently sucking a lollipop. Nabokov lie to HH with the: Kubrick does not dare. The decay of the novel and also, in part, of the film comes from this revelation clarified before time. Nabokov reveals a secret that promised greedy and long. Kubrick hides it longer and the game eventually lead us to feel that the secret lacks the importance we gave him truly. Lolita is stratified into five parts very well compartimentadas, although hiladas with brightness. Segment one: presentation of HH, the patient. Segment two: knowledge of Lolita and stay at home in the Haze. Segment three: HH marries the mother of it. He soon widowed. HH runs with the country. Segment four: will drain it and just pregnant, not of HH, and married a man gross and insensitive, just the opposite to his hero Humbert. Segment five: murder of Quilty, who chases him, obsessed by it. "Lolita, light of my life, fire of my bowels." My SIN, my soul, Lo-li-ta, the tip of the tongue embarks on a journey of three steps from the edge of the palate to support, in the third, on the edge of the teeth. Lo-li-ta. ", reads the famous first line of the novel." HH narrates in the first person his surrender to justice. The entire film seems to this: the confession of a defendant, guilty of lust, suspected of murdering another lush. Life, what bad is. </body>
</review>
