<review author="Plissken" title="El perfume" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A wonderful demonstration of power of the German film, which by the way gives us a Campion and teaches us that the secret of a good adaptation is, as good perfumes, in its essence: tells the story and respect for it.</summary>
	<body>In an end of year in which things I I've swallowed as 'Los Borgia', 'Alatriste' or 'The illusionist', he already played a film of time in which to look for something rather than the wardrobe or the picture. The German Tom Tykwer directs an afortunadísima adaptation of 'Perfume', the archifamosa novel by Patrick Suskind, than with Office of veteran has caught me off-guard or simply I loved. I think that the second rather than the first. Treatment of reasoning.For the two or three stragglers who have not read the book, 'perfume' has the life of Jean-Baptiste Grenouille, a kid who is given birth between heads of fish rotten in a suburb of the pre-revolutionary Paris. Hated by all without apparent reason and systematically beaten since the born, Grenouille has a wonderful olfactory gift, and an obsession: knowing all the smells, dissect the world in which they live through their aromas and odor. Grenouille is called to a mission beyond his own life (and that of others): find the perfect perfume, ideal fragrance.In one of the best (by faithful and cinematographic) adaptations that have been made in recent years, Tykwer establishes a strongly visual narrative code from the minute and leading to its logical conclusion, supported, that Yes, in a narrative voice-over in some moments (necessary, on the other part, and never abused). You will not find in this film cansinos explanatory dialogue, flashbacks offensive, nor spectacular script turns. the pace leisurely but firmly Tykwer, always counting, always showing, get the two and a half hours of footage to pass in a sigh, and keep you on the edge of the seat while you know the outcome in advance. Nothing mount videoclipero (well, a little bit at the beginning for rhythm), just a way of telling the story apropiadísima for the text narrates.Then there are the actors. Ben Wishaw is the perfect Grenouille, of nondescript appearance and andares simiescos, but a dramatic expressiveness. Help a lot this actor does not have to tell things with the voice-over, sometimes a simple smell him enough to understand the character. They wrapped him Dustin Hoffman at your leisure with the character of the decadent Baldini; Alan Rickman always Manor; and the young Rachel Hurd-Wood not at odds with the rest, which is already fairly. Special mention to the beautiful (further enhanced by the photo and makeup) and brief appearance of Karoline Herfurth.Todos the technical aspects of the film scratch at high altitude: photography and planning of Frank Griebe, at times, evoking the odors without words; music by Reinhold Heil, Johnny Klimek and the same Tom Tykwer supplementing the action perfectly; and the enormous artistic direction by Uli Hanisch (the art director of 'The experiment'), helped by 50 million of? budget, clear. All less Hanisch form the usual team of Tom Tykwer.Una wonderful demonstration of power of the German film, which by the way gives us a Campion and teaches us that the secret of a good adaptation is, as good perfumes, in its essence: tells the story and respect for it.9. By putting a but there is one key aspect on the personality of Grenouille which is not sufficiently well explained, in my opinion. My own things.</body>
</review>
