<review author="Plissken" title="El ilusionista" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One more failed proposals for the season, part of one material rather than interesting to leave half of footage to a mix of supernatural thriller and Danielle Steel novel.</summary>
	<body>Hollywood producers are milk: instead of making movies in original plan, they opt to copy neighbor, lest it storks and they are ridiculous. That is why we tend to have several examples of films "repes" (Robin Hoodes, natural disasters, Wyatt Earps.), in a season which one of them tends to be the "poor missus". This year he has played them the wizards, and 'The illusionist' part as the Cinderella of the pair. 'The illusionist', directed by Neil Burger, tells the story, almost the story of Eisenheim (Edward Norton on auto-pilot), a magician in the early 20th century Vienna leaves no one indifferent: nor to Sophie (stunning and somewhat bland Jessica Biel), his love of youth; or to the inspector Uhl (Paul Giamatti in another one of those roles that end up being the center of the function), an admirer and rival; or to himself Prince Leopold (credible Rufus Sewell until the final scene), evil aspiring Emperor and professional revientatrucos. What begins as a challenge between reason and superstition becomes a struggle for the love of Sophie, with unexpected consequences.Well, this would be, more or less, the official synopsis. What we really have between hands is one more failed proposals for the season, part of one material rather than interesting (the world of the magic of late 19th and early 20th Centuries) to leave half of footage to a mix of supernatural thriller and novel by Danielle Steel which has just bored by predictable.And it is, in a movie called 'The illusionist' in which the protagonist is a magician, because the average viewer say that it surprised not too when at the end goes what happens. But hey, better to not do much blood. Do let them in boring and previsible.¿Y why not do much blood? Well because as I said earlier, the film starts dramatically (great job in photography carried out by Dick Pope, in charge of Philip Glass music and art carried out by Ondrej Nekvasil), with a treatment of the perception of the magic by the profane very stimulating (all, ever, have wanted to be the smart people that elevates the secret of a trick). But the main plot comes into play and the charm disappears, leaving only a mise en scene, to make matters worse, devoid of history just for view pompous and tiresome.A penalty, truth, that not counted, simply, the adventures of a magician in love with a Princess. I think that it would have fared much better.</body>
</review>
