<review author="Elena Suárez" title="El perfume" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The biggest problem that arose me during the projection, is that for almost an hour and a half (the two hard movie) didn't know if before me was a story or a thriller.</summary>
	<body>Bothers me much when a creator (call director, writer or writer) confuses the fact of showing a new perspective through calculated plot twists with changing the rules at his whim, without order or justification whatsoever, unless the have no ideas either not knowing how to develop them. In the first case, the narrative jump usually us document on information that had already been shown but we had not been able to interpret (something that we could observe in a masterful way in the fabulous work of Michel Gondry forget me!). However, in the second case the feeling is that someone is cheating to justify a new element has been introduced almost as if by magic.As well, "perfume: story of a murderer" could be classified in the last option, although, due to my literary shortcomings, I do not know if the blame for this is the author of the novel, Patrick Süskind or, on the contrary, the director who has been commissioned to adapt it into a film, directed by Tom Tykwer, which would highlight the beautiful while it lasts history "the Princess and the Warrior".To start are abused systematically the Narrator figure something that, on the one hand, becomes bored and, on the other, suggests the lack of professionalism when it comes to the script. This is not a novel but a film and, therefore, we cannot do a fair use of the same figures. However, this small error is pleasantly subsanado if we consider the wonderful photography that typically surround the chronicler.The biggest problem that arose me during the projection, is that for almost an hour and a half (the two hard movie) didn't know if before me was a story or a thriller. On the one hand, I saw the detailed account of a brutal serial killer in the France of the 18th century, however, had components that I spouted the tangent reality (one thing to have an exceptional olfalto and another, very different, it is to be able to know by smell at the bottom of a pond frog eggs, another important detail is that odor emanating persons by very pleasant it is murky with the) (death). In general, there was a clear statement of the plane in which the story unfolded. We all know that within a fantasy can be a set of rules which make it more real and to the you upside down, in the strictest reality you can establish a parallel fantasy world that give us alternative dimensions. But what you can do is play the dismissal and make a homogeneous mix of genres so chaotically.I have to say that, ultimately all doubt dissipated before me when I saw the final outcome: had actually witnessed a great joke that had chosen the form of time of horror movie, detective, fantastic and all this sprinkled with scene that has nothing to envy to the images to which we are accustomed the photographer Spencer Tunick.</body>
</review>
