<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Los fantasmas de Goya" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Milos Forman does not seem to have been soaked enough of the brilliant artist hand and the character not just be convincing.  Entertaining, but no more.</summary>
	<body>That they roll today in day films on Spanish artists, whatever the time, seems to me something great. Especially if revolves around the figure of one of the greatest painters which has had Spain and the world in general. Although it is true that the fact that is shot in English, sincerely, subtract attractive, because nothing is more beautiful than an original work; something easy to understand especially if it is something related to an artist, as it is the case. And it is that dubbing, usually slightly distorts the films, by very good. Milos Forman does not seem to have been soaked enough of the brilliant artist hand and the character not just be convincing; the portrait of the black Spain which aims to reflect the film, lacks solid foundations, Amen their characters than ever give the sensation of possessing the characteristic attitude of the Spaniard of the time (with the exception of Bardem and the secondary Portillo and Ugalde), which is neither better nor worse than any other but is ours. Or at least it was.In general, Goya appears as a witness to the events of the time, with the Inquisition a toda mecha and Philip IV as monarch of a decadent Empire, subject to one omnipotent Catholic Church and resigned themselves to fall back on himself despite his external contests. The Napoleonic armies and the misery of the citizenship complete the framework in which aragonés performs his paintings of the so-called black era that adorn uncredited initials and finals. A pity that the improbability of the argument and the lack of mordant on the script not allowed its two protagonists do better work, because you have to recognize that both Bardem and Portman are two great actors, regardless of personal consideration worthy me of each one of them. Those who do not know enough history of the Spain of the time can enjoy more of the film, that cinematically it is not bad, but lack you rigour. Contrary to usual, the fact that the writer is the author of the novel on which is based the story, does not contribute to the adaptation to be more credible, and in my opinion, I have had the opportunity to read the original book, the film is far worse, without being a genius the literary work of Jean Claude Carrière. Entertaining, but no more.</body>
</review>
