<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Borat" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Cinematically speaking is unclassifiable because, to tell their despicable and pathetic story, that dirty realism is required.</summary>
	<body>"Borat", say from the outset, has moments absolutely repugnant and its efforts to shake the consciences and sensibilities of the spectators, espoleando the lowest instincts of those Yankees of a foot, common and theoretically, Sacha Baron Cohen, putative father of the infected creature, won't hesitate to behave like a real pig, racist, Digimundo and misogynistic arrabalero dog of the lower estofa. And what you get with this? What do it? "Supposedly to drag in their romps through the mud to the cream of American society: feminists, Baptist clergy, the high society of a southern town, University students, rough cowboys, sellers of second-hand cars, sellers of weapons and, in the end, to the very same and recauchutada Pamela Anderson.""Borat" is an atypical road movie that attached to the emerging genre of the mockumentary, is breaking the box office American, possibly because it is acid and cruel reflection of a contradictory and complex society. the apparent simplicity, stupidity and cretinism mental of much of its inhabitants, perfectly represented by that individual have as President. And is that not as laugh at others misery, when they are so close, to feel comfortable and quiet with oneself.Now, if as experiment pseudosociológico, "Borat" can be curious and striking, cinematically speaking is unclassifiable that tell their despicable and pathetic story, it requires that dirty realism, its planning based on a single camera that pursues the supposed journalist Kazakh everywhere, of his neglect in the details and all the dandruff that oozes the film.What is very clear is that the comedian Sacha Baron Cohen has managed to shape a character with popular pull very media, we do not know if it will have continuity (and success) in the future. It must be acknowledged that the 82 minutes of "Borat" are passed in a sigh, that they get tired or bored, that give rise to reactions in the viewer and giving for awhile to talk after the film. But certainly not going to revolutionize or history of cinema nor that of sociology.Music deserves special mention, a soundtrack full of the hottest sounds of bands zíngaras from Eastern Europe. "You can hear songs like"Ederlezi"and tunes of the famous Bulgarian voices in a lively étnico-musical medley that puts the festive counterpoint to much cutrez and dandruff.""Borat" claims the power of humor as a tool of social criticism, is politically incorrect and, as mentioned, gives rise to reactions in the stalls. It is not little. But it is not for burst lockers, the truth. Is symptom of any disease, diagnosed in our country after the success of torrent? We will continue to pay attention to Borat and Sacha, to see what happens to them in the near future.</body>
</review>
