<review author="Daniel Galindo" title="El camino de los ingleses" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In this suggestive and suicide formal bet coldness guides us by marshy land, emotional spaces that accomplice who trust in him comes the director with the help.</summary>
	<body>Feelings and painful memories, pirouettes risky with the camera and editing. Flags has made a difficult film but it is, that no doubt, his film.The most thorny paths are that, upon completion, give more satisfaction. It is this proposal new, different and difficult to defend against the purists. A flight of conventional makes the story of Antonio Soler shine with force on the screen although it is sometimes lost between daydreams and details. Easy to argue, difficult to contextualize in formal terms, the tape has in their top 5 minutes the best business card. A sequence in a hospital, with many elements anticipatory, keeps us in tension to make way for a more manners tale, 4 friends arriving in a swimming pool. After the sample of courtesy, filmmaker chooses to straighten the road and delete all halo of realism.We not raise the question of if a filmmaker must do a film for him, for the enjoyment of the majority, to make some with fewer ties to enter their world. We have the film more staff that can become an author, which travels through the land of emotions with the maxim, always present, looking back is painful.Permeates flags photography sadness and melancholy. They surround the imagined and therefore biased portrayal: you can't see the whole levels are foreshortening, abound insignificant details in appearance and play with the frames. Works with sensitive material, so its characters may be lost? and with them the viewer - in the existential anguish. Still points to the optimism that only they can count on enough courage not to deal with the destination, but to live to the fullest, precisely because the capricious fate imposed when it wants to.Domina poetic accent without that language is artificial. Translate metaphors in images, escape the costumbrismo, also of the action and perhaps sinneth spend footage to present the characters, but it is in fact nothing happens and everything happens. As Pablo Aranda in his novel the other city, its own city, with scarce set flags relating to foreigners and few anchorages at the time, have fairly with his interior and airtight, world away from social and political events. We know that is based on the novel of Soler, but that only persists the germ: everything is new on this nothing RESTful trip for a summer dominated by anxiety.In this suggestive and suicide formal bet coldness guides us by marshy land, emotional spaces that accomplice who trust in him comes the director with the help. This viewer will have felt the Canora that tells emotions, memories and dreams, making the pinch in the stomach does not allow to relax until the end, 10 minutes where the Swans sing his agonizing singing. In the skin of revered authors for their upset the film concept, why won't have to endure the comments of those who wait the typical generational film of young people seeking to make their way. Out by the tangent and thank many was you, maybe when you spend some time: poetic and evocative reflection will be like one of those gems that many recur years after having criticized. And flags, the director, will remain in constant search of his own way. You will see.</body>
</review>
