<review author="Berto" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A great resurgence for the series, with a new very charismatic Bond and that he predicts a new series of films, hopefully with the same style.</summary>
	<body>After twenty films of the legendary spy British, the producers of the series, after the downturn had the latest James Bond film starring Pierce Brosnan, attempting to find the series in a new direction, more modern and in line with our time and again that would attract people to cinema as formerly when the premiere of a Bond film was surrounded by an unprecedented expectation. Therefore, what better way to start again from the beginning? So they grabbed the first novel of his creator, Ian Fleming, Casino Royale, to start working with this new Bond. The novel had already been adapted long time, but anyone who has seen will know that the spirit of the classic Bond had little, with a Woody Allen script and played the spy by David Niven. Do now how difficult came from the election of the new Bond, after that Pierce Brosnan will dismiss the project for being too dated with his role as Spy, something funny, more than anything because in his next movie will do, then Yes, but spy? After a list more great that Goths Kings, chosen was Daniel Craig, actor quite discreet until then, although with good performances, and he broke with the typical Bond style of the twenty previous films. I acknowledge that when it was chosen as the new Bond nor I liked, but patiently wait to see it on the big screen and I do not pull directly to his jugular, as they did in all parts of the world, and now have to hide the head, because vista once the movie, Daniel Craig makes the best Bond since Sean Connery. Is not it may be comparable, because the style of Sean Connery is the typical English, conqueror and elegant gentleman, while Daniel Craig pulls in the direction of the medium and is more like any seen spy in a chapter of mission impossible, hard, relentless, without no remorse in killing, and rather disobedient with orders direct, although that also had the previous Bonds.En the beginning of the film, after teaching us how accomplished his famous license to kill (bone, in front of your spy number 00, 7) and continues with one of the best persecutions, walk that Yes, I have seen in the film. During the rest of the film level is still very high, although not everything could be as good, and in the final stretch the film loses bellows dangerously, focusing on love affairs, when normal and what I honestly expected more action was still. Even so is not too badly give certain human entity to the character, but dosed throughout the film had not been so bad.As regards the protagonists, Daniel Craig impeccable as a James Bond in its early days, too rough and easy trigger, and that gives a great example of entity character, after Pierce Brosnan, for my actor without enough charisma to embody Bond and that put the same face so you torturaran or was with one of the girls Bond retozando. Judi Dench in her role as M, very good, as previously since the saga and the evil of the day, Mads Mikkelsen, quite right, is not a Scaramanga, but not bad, that if the little something that cries blood is totally anecdotal, and a question that you arose me seeing it is for that lately the bad guys always must have some scar?default or something? Fixed that worldwide there bad most normalito. That if it had been a delight found us with a bad style Philip Seymour Hoffman in mission impossible 3. Eva Green, and consciously left to the end, thought me of it more light of the film, firstly because I do not think the typical Bond girl to use physically, thing that it falls within the normal watching the giro of the franchise, but not, has something which I am not convinced yet, both in its interpretation, and in the final twist that give your character. Anyway isn't bad actress, I believe in the Fund that is their problem, which is too good actress for this role, and despite everything comes out quite airy with its interpretation.In the script, then quite well, with that game of Poker as a backdrop and history quite closer to reality, in this case the bad is not the typical trying to conquer the world whatever it is, just a banker of terrorists, too fond of Poker and try, making them certain "accidents", bid up their investments.In short, a great resurgence for the series, with a new very charismatic Bond and that he predicts a new series of films, hopefully with the same style, which producers during the premiere already spoke positively with the damn Word, trilogy, for the rebirth of this Bond that we all know.</body>
</review>
