<review author="Elena Suárez" title="Ratónpolis" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Approaching the format of the goose that lays the golden eggs (animated films aimed at a child audience but with winks for adults), British not clear as much irony as others of its kind.</summary>
	<body>Are already here Christmas and the holidays of children, time that is tapped by the film producers to make films devoted to the children, something which seems absurd because not only in holiday children can go to the movies (another thing is that parents prefer to put them in front of the TV so that they can learn with educational series such as the Simpsons or Shin-chan)(, which comes on the other hand out them cheaper and also can feel proud when their monsters are almost so stupid like them).Approaching the format of the goose that lays the golden eggs (animated films aimed at a child audience but with winks for adults), British not clear as much irony as others of its genus (Shrek, monsters S.A, Ice Age or the latest and most fantastic incredible but true story of little Red Riding Hood). The fundamental reason is that, although situations and chistesdestinados to the older (terrific of the cockroach reading of Kafka's metamorphosis), the target audience for this story is more often.Following an infographic design very similar to the of Toy Story (simple textures and a repeated use of household objects that bring us closer to a contextual reality), the characters in this nice story will be almost in its entirety animal (humans only appear), and small (mice, frogs, slugs, etc.)The message is is the Association of individuals as the best vehicle to achieve a genuine personal development. Perhaps, the way in which it will not be very creative and missed some that another added value that implied the urgency to curiosity and research (our rodents are very courageous but barely make use of his imagination).Very important and interesting is the soundtrack of the film, played mostly by a cheerful slugs that will make us remember classics from the likes of Tina Turner. Not so interesting has been the idea of choosing players for dubbing (María Esteve shows us that not only does not know interpret but that either, is good in this double films).In short, look at the various options presented for this month (still enough to come) and choose the most appropriate (also may choose to place the baby in front of programs from the category of big brother or the search engine, total, if tomorrow is going to get beaten teachers and burn it on the mobile)(soon to be witless, much better).</body>
</review>
