<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Ratónpolis" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The cartoons are most human creations giving us cinema. Roddy, with its luxury Mansion is a perfect example of solitude.</summary>
	<body>British is not even remotely a boring film. In fact, it is a hilarious movie. But it has a few minutes that stays without bellows. Enough to uncover a detail.Roddy is a spoiled mouse of a wealthy London family. The family goes on vacation and he stays alone. An unexpected visit and an accident led him to give his bones in the sewers of the city. Then he meets Rita, a ratoncita who runs away from a mobster from a Ruby. The mafioso finds and steals Ruby, but Roddy helps you escape and signed a pact with her; She will help you get home and he shall pay for the work. Now comes the downturn in the film. The mafia continues to pursue her because the girl has been a cable that he needs for his evil plans.It is a blunder that small, Mann, and only lasts a few minutes. But it was also avoidable. The movie requires frenzy, so start with a Ruby, but when the bad get the Ruby should give you another excuse to the good continue escaping. Only need a man exit the stage and asked on his knees that we not go because he has another number. The spectators didn't want excuses to be there sitting, viewers thought that we were a few invisible witnesses something important. When the excuses become poor and they tell that they are excuses, viewers discovered that we are there in that uncomfortable seat, discovered that a man is trying to distract us with anything. We can even imagine giving laps in the lead, working extra hours at night to fill the next page of the script. It is then when you look at the clock.The cartoons are most human creations giving us cinema. Roddy, with its luxury Mansion is a perfect example of solitude. It has things but he has no family, is like an isolated millionaire, or equal to the great child of Hugh Grant. All the adventure which has lived serves to make us have a good time with us, but also to raise his life and make a good decision.</body>
</review>
