<review author="José A. Peig" title="El ilusionista" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Under its infuriating plain film keeps a too intelligent approach to an invoice so obvious in appearance. It is the typical film which tends to mislead many critics.</summary>
	<body>The magician profession fascinates by the image of the impossible made possible with an austere stage game, some small gestures loaded with symbolism and the rest gets the ingenuity and the illusion of the stunned tier is left drag in an equally playful credulity.The case of "The illusionist", is curious because what it does is interfere the structure and tone of the story in a line of naïve credulity, because the truth is that level argument not supported too, but the public--the public watching the big screen - wants to think that the wonderful illusions created by Einsenheim have something of realityin the last redoubt of reality is a space for the supernatural, whether for philosophical reasons or justify aversions or political phobias.Simplicity is the word that defines this film honest to the core. It only seeks to entertain, would shudder to a pablum, and therefore it matters little little plot consistency. It is a tale of cot for children to hear him next to a fire or before going to sleep without another objective that the amaze with very little sense of reality and with little sense of how fabulous. Claims are null and void, and likewise the idea on which it is based goes direct to the point: intrigue and sentimental story about a magician executed with obvious, with characters whose reactions are subjected to a mechanical, equal development that was happening in the other folletín of time that we have seen recently, "Goya's ghosts", only that here does not matter because it is the very essence of minimalist and austere tale both in the construction and treatment of their external structure in its contents, which justifies its obviousness. (said abruptly, does not lack that little Red Riding Hood is a complex character for his role as Captivate and pleases the listener).The story has an appealing simplicity, and this is its best asset. The realization is fluid and follows a logic focused on fair and necessary. The story culminates with a stimulating re-reading of the narrated. At the end, effectively, the illusion is ratified as part of reality, only is not the reality that although viewers most wanted, revealing is the film in its more hidden nature: a love story illusion that comes out winner using the illusion.So, ojito, because under its infuriating plain film holds an approach too intelligent for one it invoice so obvious in appearance. It is the typical film which tends to mislead many critics.</body>
</review>
