<review author="Silvia" title="Va a ser que nadie es perfecto" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We are all blind, lame and deaf, because we all have shortcomings, emotional and sentimental. Sometimes we are deaf to things that we must hear, blind to the things that we don't want to see, and lame because we arrived late to many sites.</summary>
	<body>Ruben is deaf, Carlos is blind and Dani is lame. The three friends meet to celebrate the hen of one of them, which will be the night that will change their lives. That night, each of llos will fail to fulfill a dream. Ruben (the deaf), sing. Dani (the lame), dancing in the water, and Carlos, (the blind) driving a car at full speed.The latest creation by Joaquín Oristrell brings to the table the problems of persons with disabilities, an unusual item in the screenplays (mostly in Spanish). The history shows some barriers (both architectural and social) that are people who hold some type of disability.An example of problematic situation for the protagonists is shown in the scene in which the Group of friends discusses the door film if they are going to see a foreign film in subtitled original version or if they will see it folded. What may seem like a minor detail is all a dilemma since the blind man, obviously, is unable to see the subtitles and the dull, if you do choose to see the dubbed film, will not be able to understand the movie to know the language, that can only read lips. Highlights for its quality performances by José Luis García Pérez, on the character of Fudd lame and Santi Millán, who - without falling into the cartoon - manages to speak as you would a person with hearing problems.But the interesting thing about the story is not then develops under a plaintive tone or victimism but with more normal. Albert Espinosa dares even to introduce humorous touches in the script, without falling into the lack of respect for the collective to which it refers. The fact that the writer is lame no doubt influencing the successful treatment of the history. Espinosa is already an expert to write on topics that people flees to speak and do it from the perspective of the comedy. He wrote an endearing story about children with leukemia (4ªPlanta) full of friendship, tenderness and in which not missed the humor, ironically on the death in 65 minutes and on this occasion speaks of disabled people, but not from the position of pity towards them, but with the intention that we see them as people not so different from us and as valid and capable as any other.As it is usual in some films that they populate our billboards, the trailer and the poster they do justice to will be that nobody is perfect because they sell it as a light teen comedy, when it comes to a product of much more psychological depth. Perhaps the public that expected a comedy where the laughs are a constant will be disappointed in this comedy drama impregnated.The message that is derived from the movie is, according to Joaquin oristrell that "behind anyone, there happens what happens, is a human being." "You have to look to that human being, not the disability." History encourages us not to turn our backs on people who are different from us because we all have some deficiency. The director admits in an interview what he liked the screenplay was the idea that we all have some kind of disability, at least some emotional. Oristrell explains: "We are all blind, lame and deaf, because we all have shortcomings, emotional and sentimental." "Sometimes we are deaf to things that we must hear, blind to the things that we don't want to see, and lame because we arrived late to many sites".A comedy that excites, entertains and serves at the same time to raise awareness of disabled people are first and foremost human: are people who feel, fall in love, have their fears, suffering, and have desire to have fun as anyone else, and even laughing from themselves.</body>
</review>
