<review author="Rafa Marin" title="Déjà Vu" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The film does not give Truce to the Viewer, get not rolling it in his statement, nor that cirríe the police investigation. We will feel a pleasant and appropriate sense of dèja vu.</summary>
	<body>There is a before and an after 11-S, and the feeling of helplessness of society to the disaster then boosted with the phenomena of the tsunami and for the United States, with the devastating effects of Hurricane Katrina in New Orleans. At least the first two disasters plan on the new film by Tony Scott, Deja vu, because the action takes place in the same place and is about a terrorist attack. The reflection that makes the film before shooting clearly towards science fiction and the temporal paradoxes, is what can be done to prevent terrorist sabotage, and if this is possible, what responsibility is towards the victims. Not far from the plot of this movie is that is for me the best novel by Orson Scott Card: keepers of the past: the redemption of Christopher Columbus. There are abundant elements of contact not as time travel itself, but to the responsibility and commitment of the observer observed and all the moral implications that can drag with them. With a devilish pace, a magnificent staging, one picture dirty shows the streets of New Orleans still not have recovered from the effects of the disaster or the effects of the Mardi Grass, without crazy camera or make exaggerated tricks montage of his penultimate film with Denzel Washington, the younger brother of Ridley Scottthat comes over and over again proving that isn't so small, it is able to put the viewer at the crossroads of gender and, without solution of continuity, take him by the hand and ensure that it is not lost in the temporal paradoxes that raises. The plot of the film is simple: a terrorist attack against a ferry loaded with sailors from farra launches police Doug Carlin (Washington) of the ATF (a government agency of which I had not heard before, by the way) to the investigation of the causes. A woman appears dead and tortured and burned on the Bank of the River, but an hour before the attack. It is then a government research group, led by a Val Kilmer that increasingly resembles more to Alec Baldwin, enrolled to Washington so help them investigate, and they show him alleged recordings of all that has happened in the city four days ago and a half. Bit it takes the Viewer (and Washington, which is a Lynx, the uncle), to understand that it is not of recordings, but the quantum technology allows you to open a window to the past and see in real time, but with this gap of four days, how develops the plot of murder and bombing. Ironically, the pirado patriótico-religioso who commits murder is not other but James Caviezel, i.e., Christ himself in the film the passion according to Saint Mel Gibson, who already participated in a similar film from parallel universes and changes in the timeline, this great little often understated gem which is Frequency. The film does not give Truce to the Viewer, get no liar in his statement, or that chirríe the police investigation of the principle with the inevitable time travel than Denzel Washington has to make to the rescue in the last fifteen minutes of projection. If not are you sci-fi fans, it will look like a proper film and it is even possible that the end surprised them. That we are already old in the genus dogs and love above all items travel in time and the paradoxes that these entail, will feel a pleasant and appropriate sense of dèja vu, and leave the film reflecting on how many times in total has traveled the good of Denzel Washington in the past trying to not amend the plan of the terrorist, but their own previous failures, and without knowing it.</body>
</review>
