<review author="Red Stovall" title="Déjà Vu" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A bad, greatly disappointing film in its realization. Move explanations, they forget characters and even offers a minimally decent show.</summary>
	<body>Is true that Tony Scott has not yet flown as high as his brother Ridley, but I have always defended him as a more than interesting director. Someone with personality to lead good tape of action. Does unfortunately has made it me go very wrong with things like?Do days of Thunder??Top Gun? or?Do fan?, but I've spent big with ribbons like?Love at point-blank range?,?The last Boy Scout? or?Do Spy Game?, and films like?Public enemy?,?The hunger? and?The fire of vengeance? they are decent entertainment. Do I was recently disappointed a lot with that entitled visual delirium?Do I know?, and when I saw the trailer of?Déjà Vu? I thought that Scott was returning to their good times.Because if there is something to note about the last film by Tony Scott is that your trailer is perfect, a masterpiece of mounting very intelligently using the plot of the film in the construction of the own trailer. It I not tired of seeing it and certainly got eager to see the film, good, as virtually all the trailers, but this in particular stands out above the average. Do so, last Friday, happy and satisfied, I went to the premiere of?Do Déjà Vu?, and after two long hours of footage left with a face of perplexity that still lasts me. This film seems the confirmation that Mr Tony Scott is lost, and nothing does predict that someday again to find the way.Do talk about the argument of?Déjà Vu? It would be cited a lot of plot inconsistencies, as well indicated in the comments on the post about the film made by my colleague Beatrice, we should not have in mind, something with which I agree to an extent. But come on, we could say that the film goes a nutty terrorist who wants to fly a ferry and a policeman who travels in time tries to stop them, at the same time that falls in love with a woman who died in the attack. Because Yes, because the writer has given out there, she had read somewhere that the great love stories are timeless and taken it to the letter.Everything that raises the film has been seen a thousand times in other films of identical theme of time travel. However, this would not be any default if all narrated were shown with a minimum of credibility and professionalism, something that does not happen at any time. It is as if the own writers of event, Billy Marsilii and Terry Rossio, not believe in the material that they have between hands, and what is worse, Mr Tony Scott not know material that staging. The film is hasty, with an irregular rhythm and would not taking no time to reflect on certain points of history, something which have been very well. Perhaps this is the case because so many viewers not would realize the enormous bug that has the ridiculous script, so in my opinion, the film is a little silly to the long-suffering public.There are two moments in the film that you can see the errors in a scandalous manner. First, the scene in which the character of Denzel Washington explain absolutely everything about the possibilities of time travel and whether you can change the past or not. This scene seems ridiculous that it is a comedy, and is also too long, basking in its own default. The other time is quite long, that we can say that it is from some intervention by the main character, the film will slope down at high speed and ends up crashing hopelessly. Move explanations, they forget characters and even offers a minimally decent show.Regarding the actors say that Denzel Washington is as always, or protesting at all. Jim Caviezel seems to shift a bit of registry, although personally I am not convinced that terrorist mixture of psychokiller and Rambo. And who since then is truly disastrous is the main actress, Paula Patton, with nothing drawn character despite the hours and hours passed noting her. This in my opinion is greatly missed some chances of history. Something that also happens in a Chase scene certainly original, although only the idea, that viewing by Scott is the weaker throwing land which could have been one of the most spectacular chases and sorpendentes of how many have been made.In short, a bad, greatly disappointing film in its realization. That Yes, I insist that the trailer is a gem. And by the way, is it entitled?Déjà Vu? as could you have entitled?Ham sandwich with sausage? or?Persecution at the time? or anything else, and they even talk about déjà vu, which has noses.</body>
</review>
