<review author="José Córdoba" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is a very intelligent and vibrant redesign of the character, in addition to an entretenidísima movie that leaves you glued to the seat for two hours and fourth.</summary>
	<body>Daniel Craig must be a happy man right now. After the entire campaign orchestrated against him by his choice to play secret spy most famous (curious contradiction) history, swords were high and the expectation was higher than the previous changes of face of the character. And the result was not disappointed, it is more is liking much.Much has been saying for the past year on which the series was exhausted, the character already tired than that which. I always found me funny this whole debate because the previous film, die another day (Die another day), starring Pierce Brosnan, was not only not a failure but that it wasn't the most box office film of the saga. So strictly speaking, made change was not necessary from an economic point of view. Although it is also true that the scale of the last project at all levels, it was difficult to overcome.Casino Royale was the first novel written by Ian Fleming of James Bond character, and already had two previous adaptations one for TV and one in the form of parody shot in the 1960s which had five directors, a cast where it appeared from David Niven until Peter Sellers passing by Woody Allen, and posed one of the most expensive Follies ever funded a large study. The plot narrates the confrontation of Bond, newly obtained his license to kill (the double zero), with LeChifre, a banker who manages the revenues generated by gangs of drug traffickers and terrorists. The plot is quite simple and easy to remain its peak the poker game that takes place in the casino that gives its name to the film.The new James Bond adventure is probably, and lack of seeing Déjà Vu of Tony Scott, the best film of the genre of Action released this year. It maintains Moreover all constants of the saga: stunning women, multiplicity of scenery, luxurious environments and scenes of action was. Changes, that there are, are not as spectacular as it has been saying. We have two women Bond, a vase (and quickly dispatched) and other intelligent that accompanies the hero in his adventures, as in other films in the series, you does not go very far, in the films starring Brosnan women were more than simple objects and throw-away. Perhaps Yes has gained in realism in the action scenes, nor too much at the end and at Cape is a Bond film, but has been dramatically reduced the use of spectacular Gadgets or more elements of a science fiction to film one of spies that runs today. Where he is most noticeable change is the main character. The film designed by way of a James Bond Begins is the redefinition of the character, telling their origins to begin a new series. Thus we are witnessing its first Martini mixed, not hectic, its first Aston Martin and a long list of details that will delight fans of the saga. This idea extends to the music section, makes mild notes of the theme written by Monty Norman and immortalized by John Barry, and only heard in its entirety in the last scene film. In this sense the film resembles Indiana Jones and the last crusade, where we discovered the origin of many details of the character.The Bond played by Daniel Craig is credible, hard and ironic, capable of falling in love and suffer. Appears to a human being, something which had disappeared after the secret service of his Majesty (film that keeps more than one point in common). The choice of the actor turned out perfect because it gives surprising charisma and a physical presence to the character. But the rest of the cast has not been neglected, starting with an intelligent and sensual but nearby Eva Green, and continuing with a wonderful Judi Dench as M or a very suitable Giancarlo Giannini. Perhaps the downside in terms of character her we find in the villain role, a character devoid of charisma and strength, than not takes advantage of its physical peculiarity (cries blood).Matin Campbell, who was director of Goldeneye and the mask of Zorro, again to show how the effective director who is, though not brilliant, not known to take advantage of the filming of the poker game where a best director, John McTiernam and Richard Donner, could have done wonders. Without embargo in the action scenes draw out all his potential but we should not forget about the work of the director of second unit and, above all, by Stuart Baird, probably the best editor of action cinema that has American cinema today.The script is agile and fun, with some surprise and some magnificent dialogues between Craig and Green, well-publicised, certainly by the chemistry there on screen between both actors. However the multiplicity of late and the long duration of the film do lose something of bellows in the last third.The picture is very correct, emphasizing the use of a magnificent black and white in the sequence pre-créditos which opens the film. The music of Arnold is functional in the film, zacchia or romantic as appropriate, but not especially remarkable, a far cry from the scores written by Barry and lower other endorsed as the tomorrow never Muere.Vuelve Bond and returned to stay. Casino Royale is a very intelligent and vibrant redesign of the character, in addition to an entretenidísima movie that leaves you glued to the seat for two hours and the fourth so it serves its objective outweigh. Long live James Bond.</body>
</review>
