<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="El camino de los ingleses" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>How not are you going to forgive Antonio that makes a failed movie, even though it is so pleasantly failed? So, finally, to the best sweeps up at box office and all.</summary>
	<body>We must recognize value to Antonio Banderas: to make his second film as director not only comes to Spain, when commercial prospects would be much higher in United States, where it is settled three decades ago, but it also makes a version very lyrical, barely grossing novel of a poet, Antonio Soler, for more inri undertakes solo script, with what the load poetics (sometimes touching the kitsch) of the novel wanders its shadow throughout the film. And it is that, although it seems a truism, not always a good book can be a good movie; in fact the experience comes to say quite the opposite. In addition, languages are not equal, and what works in a book (the voice of the narrator in film, generally resulting from more shocking: here is an example) does not have why to do it in a film. It is clear that fascinated the Soler novel flags: the atmosphere of the Malaga of the tardofranquismo, in the mid-1970s, just the time in which he was approximately the same age of the characters in the novel and the film, and probably also lived and met the same places in which the action of the book and the film unfolds. It is also true that the tone that has given flags (and his screenwriter Soler) to this "camino de los ingleses", between the poetic and dreams, with allegorical reflections (that initial, so atypical scene in modern commercial cinema), bathed in ubiquitous Antonio Meliveo music, with chords more reminiscent of the jazz to flamenco (better as well: not always the cinema in Andalusia has to resort to the jondo)(, although some people so creates it), is pure poison for the box office, not accustomed the public to such licenses. Said which will have to say that "The road." neither succeeds with the tone: history tells us is curious, albeit not precisely not going more than originality. In addition, flags, which has counted on a budget (EUR 7 million) than what is the it style in Spain for a production as this (without known actors, nor complicated special effects, and scenes of masses), seems that it has been self-absorbed in the beauty of the images, and so the film is too precocious, as if the director had regodeado in a dream to Malagacertainly only exists in his Magin and the of those who knew her, more than thirty years ago. All of which should not overshadow the merits of the film, the story of a boy with one less kidney, in love with a girl who in turn is tempted by another man of more possible than her boyfriend; It is also the story of their friends, the son of the rich who is forced to leave the girl who wants to, and the son of the "strip-teuse" that makes sex on stage in London. It is also the story of aspiring announcer of radio, perhaps a reflection of own novelist and screenwriter, Antonio Soler, although eventually his radio "speechs" remember more programmes of the fool of the Hill of the 1970s. And in addition to all that, why not say it? Antonio is the girl in the eyes of the Spaniards, and not to mention the Andalusians. His triumph in Hollywood so enjoy as their own, as in the 1960s with the successes of Manolo Santana tennis or now Fernando Alonso in racing. So, how does not gonna you forgive make a failed movie, even though it is so pleasantly failed? So, finally, to the best sweeps up at box office and all.</body>
</review>
