<review author="Jesus Lens" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It boasts the best virtues of the saga of Bond, the classic substrate of the cinema of scams, tiles and tocar, scathing replicas of all good war of the sexes that self-respecting and that spatial and technological geography that shows us that we live in a fully globalized world.</summary>
	<body>It is true that I am not a big fan of 007, but it is truer still that I (almost) always see his films and arrival screens, when round us the Christmas, the welcome with more enthusiasm than the landing of advertising lotera or almond-shaped the nougat.The Bond franchise, with his collection of spectacular girls, its refinement, the locations of your dreams by way of catalogue of luxury travel to the Condé Nast and its globalized sophistication offer a solid and well finished product, but comes to excite, is always interesting, fun, entertaining and relaxing.So, when it was announced the premiere of this "Casino Royale" already I knew that, even without excessive eager haste, a good day I would fall by the cinema to see it, with popcorn, coke and other gadgets suitable for the tasting of a film of these features.The prologue in black and white, cynical and stark, already started to call me the attention more than the Bond films is normally the case. And the closing credits, animated, witty, imaginative. to continue with a first persecution of hair, a free and wild race by a building under construction that manages to convey all the sensation of dizzying speed to apply the two contenders and that it will be resolved with a crude murder, blood cold. We are told that we we have another type of Bond, a bit different.Craig has been called the Bond labor, popular and other things for the style. I do not want to enter now open the debate on the different types of Bond in the film have been or, above all, engage in what that Sean Connery was the best 007 ever when seen with the passage of time, those movies have been more stately than the sheep's milk cheese. This is: I liked, and much, this Craig and that scenes like that that, emulating John Wayne "The quiet man", gets under the shower and the water soaked you white shirt, are beautifully resolved.And the bad, course, another of the topics unavoidable when speaking of a Bond. The portrays this time, is so cold and cynical as credible and perfectly adapted to the times: a banker, bleaching of dirty money from the satrap and dealer anda by the world, bleed their victims. A guy who cries blood and that will make you sweat yours our 007, which reach torture in a simple way as cruel and ruthless.Do I liked that, instead of leaning on the path of the franchise of mission impossible, difficult and crazy action, "Casino Royale" has chosen to the spectacle on the sets? that Montenegro, that Venice and its Palazzo Hundiente. - but on the basis of a more credible direct action. always bearing in mind that we are talking about Bond, a James Bond who, by the way, just use gadgets or ingenious toys in this story.Agitated, which mixed and scrambled, "Casino Royale" is not a very good film that has a very good movie that possesses the best virtues of the saga of Bond, the substrate classic film of scams, tiles and tocar, replicas scathing of all good war of the sexes that self-respecting and that spatial and technological geography that shows us that we live in a totally globalized. And why, when it finishes playing the classic series theme, once Craig says for the first time about Bond, James Bond, at the end of the film, gives you a regustillo of the most friendly and satisfactory.</body>
</review>
