<review author="José A. Peig" title="Déjà Vu" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A film with their points in favour, but too saturated with topics of superficiality, of Sci-Fi relamida, predictable resolutions. But it is also a good toy to have a fun time, widening a little movie fan manga.</summary>
	<body>The title of the film can be misleading, if we attend the implicit content that takes place along a narrative, as I would say, "to catch-up", but the truth is that the director and the writers never lose sight Essentials; narration seamless and bluntly, I would say. He said that the title can move to deception because what is emphasized here is another thing, supporting in repeated situations that referred to the common and strange sense of "this I have lived", which is no more than an excuse for structuring the story. In fact, it is one speech - another one - about God or the existence of a divine order, claiming the value of sacrifice within social and symbolic post-11 September. Film ideological, controlled and regurgitado by the industry and the propaganda apparatus that leads behind.The idea is very simple; Police thriller mixed with elements and characteristic of the science fiction themes. And that is what Scott wants to create; a serious film about the human condition in a specific context. The fantastic elements serve to marinate and brighten a little plot, a topical and relamida history in hundreds of films past and present. That Yes, in specific situations manages to be original in the persecution by road to two times. In other words, the only way to save the movie was introducing temporary travel, which isn't anything new. A word that defines the main problem of this film - and that is also the problem of most of the current commercial cinema - is the word "saturation". Topics and clichés, saturation saturation of "latigillos" of police suspense and the genre of science fiction. Both in the characterization and plot approach, everything is based on insubstantial clichés.The temporal paradoxes, the Patriot psicokiller, the ubiquitous secondary cast that has another function that the make of "stuffed", typical situations "in extremis". This same material, under a fresh and genuine look, could offer much more, but here insists on the pale portrait and the remake of genera conjugated rather clumsily. The Mise en scène loses one hand that WINS on the other: strong close-up and movements and electrifying changes. Serves as effective visual style that conforms well to the tone of the story, but, once again, we ended up in the saturation: Medley telefilmico, without a true aesthetic style. Under the electric pulse of the camera there is no more than inanity and dramatic trick. However, has its point of honesty since the story takes place, as indicated in a previous paragraph, fluently and with a more than correct dramatic sense, framing the Odyssey spatio-temporal agent protagonist in a process of philosophical pretensions (that Yes, very well-worn and little original) without the need to give explanations that disrupt the narrative flow. Each meaning emerges in each of gestures, situations and "clashes" with the destination, always maintaining the central idea that much is intended to ameliorate, change or introduce a variation that is essential in the ongoing storm, there is always an unalterable redoubt, an immovable upper order against the wishes of the human being. And there is a price to pay.In short, a film with their points in favour, but too saturated with topics of superficiality, of Sci-Fi relamida, predictable resolutions. But it is also a good toy to have a fun time, widening a little movie fan manga.</body>
</review>
