<review author="Rafa Marin" title="Casino Royale" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>After twenty films try to sneak us the dreadful trola not that Daniel Craig is James Bond but that is newbie, brutote, passionate and make mistakes, it is something that does not believe it Judy Dench or the own writers.</summary>
	<body>Since the George Lazenby said (in English) that of "Oops, this was not happening to the other type", fans of the film adventures of the best known secret agent in the world have developed particular theory that the saga of 007 not is telling us the adventures of a single agent, but many, and that both double acronym zero James Bond brand name as a cover to disguise the identitypast, and even the personality of the new spy that occupies the niche. Yes, I know, there are things that do not fit (pain in the ass that often give Felix Leiter in his different incarnations, for example; the different faces of Moneypenny; the widowhood of the Bond Lazenby inherited Bond Moore), but I would say stuff squeaking less than cocoa mental maravillao facing the top producers, which did not clarify, and now seeking with this new installment, Casino Royale, show us a James Bond. first-time! One is agreed in that, as the cat is yours, can fuck him as they wish, but after twenty films (twenty-three, if you count the television Casino Royale, the original parody Casino Royale, and a return to the fold of Connery with never say never again; do not have the cameo made the character of the hand of the same Connery in the rock) try to sneak us the dreadful trola not of Daniel Craig as James Bond (so)(, cuesta awhile believe it) but that is newbie, brutote, passionate and make mistakes, it is something that does not believe it Judy Dench or the own writers. How much easier would be to accept that there have been other 007 prior to those who have known (us and M) in the past, and now this fortachón rubio seems newly licensed with dishonor of the British SAS has been chosen to finger after Brosnan to fill the post. Talks halfway between M and Craig suggest, the own Judy Dench (Advanced series in interpreting for the first time to a female M and became crazy against Brosnan), said here a line of dialogue that seems to make a nod to the comment to already make the ex-Remington Steele in his first career: "You are a remnant of the cold war", snapped you then, while now, before the brutalities of here blonde blue eyes (above goes for free throughout the movie), says "How much miss the cold war". But no, they have not dared. There is nothing more cagueta that the owner of a franchise. And that there are elements in the movie indicating that the idea could be in the minds of the writers, the director (who reintrepretó the series with Goldeneye now eleven years ago) and the author of the soundtrack: it obscures all the time the subject of Bond, which does not sound until the closing credits; the final scene, the only one in the entire film in which Craig says "My name is Bond, James Bond" is hollow because all the time has named it people, when it would have been easier to be called only 007 so far to assume the personality of the British agent. Moreover, the film tries to escape the Bond scheme always but fails: when approaching the Bond of always (i.e., the action scenes) always remember something that has been made beforehand; damn Mania move the camera makes no look a damn in the fights scenes; and when you try to make a film of posh spies in decadent environments (i.e., the hour long that lasts the card game) it ends up being boring and sleeping. Is not enough to want to innovate: we must know where and why innova, and after twenty titles of franchise strikes me as an unsuccessful effort, an I want to and can't an ask del olmo pears. The bad guys are second category; the plot, silly, predictable and confusing: recognize that Casino Royale, the novel, is little film in its conception (also in comics is a bit pesadita), and is only saved the scene of torture and rescue in extremis. rescue which differs with the book, much more direct, wild and augurador of things to come (a subsection to remember that Bond is marked in the hand as a "Spy" and MI-6 has to remove a piece of skin from the temple to meet the mark detail Fleming undertakes to remember in all their stories). Craig is not a bad actor. But it is not Bond. Or it is not "our" Bond. Cannot be the Bond producers seek to will then be (especially because the story is "now", develops in a world post 11-S). It is not soft. It is too lethal, too sharp, without the sense of humor characteristic of at least four of its predecessors (Connery, Lazenby, Moore and Brosnan; I do not remember whether Dalton made humorous remarks too worried posing). More gross than a Guillemot, to understand us. It is clear that writing the script they had in mind to Brosnan, nor to Ewan McGregor, but with Jason Statham in Transporter (the scene of the fight in the truck recalls to the scene of the truck Transporter which in turn was a "tribute" almost level by level and stunt for stunt to in search of the Lost Ark). For true, what a silly scene at the airport: with which it is falling into the world, do you believe that they will submit a prototype aircraft? at night? Almost equally silly is the persecution giving jaunty manumaná of Middle Africa (a form of recognizing that Bond is now in Spider-Man and the superhero to his worst enemy in the box-office?). And how much this man runs throughout the film. Eva Green is enormously sosa, sosa. A more Bond girl whose history does not interest and does not love: it is incredible that such maromo change from being gross in history to drop the cursiladas released in the past and long minutes of the film. Judy Dench is good in his role of madrecita (enchufadora?) of 007, although it must be hitting a slap to the translation or dubbing: has No logical M tutee bond; that gives you a closeness to the relationship between both unnecessary and contrary to the tension that exists between the two. The deduction of the past of Bond which makes Eva Green, incidentally, contradicts the more or less official biography of the character, so once more we can point to a desire not consummate to tell us that this Bond is actually a new Bond that follows the wake of other Bond no longer. And all this roll tell a newbie Bond for, oh, Boggle because there are organisations of spies that MI-6 does not control (Smersh in the original idea). The same dare and at the end just to do a remake of Doctor No. Or live and let die, that is the next novel. Because without ideas appear to have been all all.</body>
</review>
