<review author="Caruco" title="Brick" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The look is respectful to one of the genres most moviegoers and more strongly encrypted. And also dignifies, and that way!, the subgenre of cinema for teenagers.</summary>
	<body>There are bad, very bad guys. But the girls still appearing are the worst, the worst. How should it be! Why this brick called "Brick", not by the peñazo but also by its? macguffin? in the form of ingot of coca, has the flavor of the purest? film noir?. The "Eternal sleep", "The Maltese hacón", "the postman always twice" or "Death among the flowers". The difference is that all the codes and recognized characters of the genus moved to an American Institute, and the Bogart, Lara Turner, Gloria Grahame, Peter Lorre, Sydney Greenstret or Gabriel Byrne on duty have teen face and dress worn jeans.The thugs of middling, drogatas, fatal women and dedectives disgusted and cynical move between the corridors, offices and plots of an Institute, between the streets taken by young people without cause, and even humble maternal homes. But that never appear on screen are classrooms. Subjects learn outside.To this we should add the commitment and the will of a rookie, Rian Johnson, of 33 years, with only $450,000 (about 360,000 euros), make that one wondering whether a film professional invoice can be done with so much.Dangerous subject.The answers ranged that he had to assemble the material in their home (which will of course be much better than mine) computer, or that we have one of the most pleasant and stimulating of the season proposals.And the operation has its risk. "It must be underpinned in some credible performances, are, and above all about working díalogos and test of pump, that is."My boys will investigate your story. Do "then you kill or hire", is the response that receives a protagonist smarter than hunger, Brendan (Joseph Gordon-Levitt), with the mission to avenge the death of his ex-girlfriend, Emily (Emilie de Ravin), when you try to win the confidence of The Pin (Lukas Haas), a cripple with an air of? dandy? do to what Truman Capote but candidate not to Pulitzer sinó to? capo? of playground.An autobiographical that will not cease to be shock, physical and emotional, in a journey marked by feminists; angelical face and devilish mind; the vipers who hide behind their malleability in the makeup and the arropajes of the theatre; or the handlers of disturbing beauty that same dress in Eastern plan or fashion more pijera while smoke their good ration of cigarettes, the case of Laura (Nora Zehetner). Find out who lunch one is indispensable to know the ground that step!With the teachers on the heels.Do to your around, caught by a luminous and naturalistic photography, moves a society where the agents of law and order have been indoles by steering some of this? high school?.Where the boys speak of having read Tolkien, while also the spirit of writers as Dashiell Hammett, Raymond Chandler, James Elroy or the Coen brothers. Even the ghost of Laura Palmer, or enigmatic notes of paper, to the David Lynch slip by one of its frames. Meanwhile, the mother of the villain serves your guests instead of a whisky or bourbon Apple juice.Do do do do there is no mental empanada, but it is a plot, as befits to a? noir?, twisted and full of surprises that make us focus our gaze towards these rebel classrooms, bad streets and fauna of? teenagers? you populate them.The look is respectful to one of the genres most moviegoers and more strongly encrypted. And also dignifies, and that way!, the subgenre of cinema for teenagers. If in addition helps to awaken the interest in one of the classics of film noir, then, better than best.</body>
</review>
