<review author="Moriarty" title="The holiday" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Something good from this tangle of vague attempts to reach our hearts?. Yes. A decent soundtrack, some not clear glimpses out of the script and any game without outline with the subconscious. And that's it.</summary>
	<body>We, oh surprise, have a navideño-amoroso hybrid and supposedly funny (?). The Holiday (vacation) is a squishy, topical, predictable and surplus production. With all the commas. And most unforgivable of all is that the talent pulled away is hefty. It is better to know it from the beginning, because although their appearance could remind recent successes of the type of Closer or even in another dimension, Love Actually (marketing does wonders), the viewer should be aware that you will not find with anything like that. Even in one-tenth.To begin with, the script lacks novelty (something common, so it might not be so serious). Two girls lovelorn and wanting to get away from its former undesirable partners, one residing in Los Angeles - Cameron Diaz - and the other in a small village near London - Kate Winslet - contact coincidentally (or causally) via the Internet and decide to exchange their homes during the Christmas holidays. Foreshadow you well, I to Boston and you to California, curiously in the Filmography of the Director, in modern plan but without the game of identities. Do without? chicha?, will.In just two weeks given time to overcome the trauma, to know new people and how not, to return to fall in love with. Until the pointer, the poor, manages to be happy. It is the effectiveness of a script by slightly more than two hours has been stretched without mercy. The iteration of the crucial arguments in addition to the history becomes a sort of carousel that never ceases to turn on itself. If the viewer has not heard to the fourth or fifth mention of that, for example, one of the girls was deceived by her boyfriend, it is left to pay attention, at least in the two minute. Somewhat likely thank you, among other things, to the tiresome overacting of all and each of the cast members that, instead get into his role, appear to move by him as if from a transaction is involved. Abundant light interpretation, and although this is not necessarily pejorative, some gags are really completely absurd to the Bridget Jones; absurd and unnecessary. If they had at least taken with an homage? I serious? the unforgettable Classics (telephone misunderstanding), the catastrophe would have never triggered. What waste.Do or everything is perhaps a lack of overall motivation compounded by cruel feelings crossing: seductive guapo - Jude Law - with pretty millionaire and? mona? do sentimental with? clown? Shorty - Black - Jack. Typical. The fact is that these four actors have worked throughout their careers more than acceptable, but certainly did not have a good day when they were shooting The Holiday. A penalty. As it is also the only salvageable plot, with many references to the film, goal with shoehorn. It wasn't difficult, yet endearing Eli Wallach was the most credible.Even we have come to believe the plight of personal law, as also we did, despite everything, with Penépole cross in back, with a daughter, certainly not think yours. The general conclusion is clear: Nancy Meyers didn't know what to do, if a drama, a mess or a pastelada, which it thus mixed everything. Some result, it gives them no, at least now. Something good from this tangle of vague attempts to reach our hearts?. Yes. A decent soundtrack, some not clear glimpses out of the script and any game without outline with the subconscious. And that's it.</body>
</review>
