<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Agitese antes de usarla" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Many grumosos jokes, and hundreds of naked women, which are attractive to Pajares and Esteso, which is why still find me science fiction films.</summary>
	<body>Sunday at noon, rebusco in the caspoteca and bag a classic uncover. "Are going to get that shit?" says relax my medium kiwi. "Only a little, to see that will" I answer in my role of man crouching ears. Begins the film, the three minutes I'm going to remove and she says that let a little, out of curiosity. Two hours and half we woke up all three, that good NAP covered by the golden age of the Spanish film.The film is a hospital that is almost in bankruptcy by the infamous. In these appears a new doctor (Pajares) which is actually a con man that gives you fear the blood. Providence drops the Minister of "incompatibilities" with a hangnail, which takes advantage of the surgeon Chief (Ozores) to enter and give prestige to the hospital. And the thing is entangled, appearing there Esteso, Arévalo, Juanito Navarro and many women in pelotas. A classic.It is assumed that we were a sour criticism of social security of the time, but reality more resembled a comic book Mortadelo y Filemón. Absurd situations resolved even more absurdly, based on a script without rhyme or reason. Many grumosos jokes, and hundreds of naked women, which are attractive to Pajares and Esteso, which is why still find me science fiction films.In short, very bad film uncover, whose principal virtues are the joy in nudes and sympathetic critique of Social Security. As pathetic as always gangoso Arévalo.Scene at random to give us an idea: the first, a girl that her boyfriend has cracking a tit. Esteso says there need to inflate, Pajares which make him a boca-teta and Ozores to be blowing covering the raja that doesn't come out the air that mess. A nurse enters and tells Ozores "you want something or touch their noses?" Jajajajaja, I is me mondo with these people.</body>
</review>
