<review author="Silvia" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mid tender, funny, surreal moments as life itself.</summary>
	<body>"In this life there are two kinds of people: the winners and the losers." Do you know what's the difference? "That the winners fighting for what they want".The father of Olivia (Greg Kinnear) has very clear what the alleged recipe for success. As a good optimistic dreams of his family to achieve success and therefore supports his small daughter of seven years in its decision be submitted to a beauty contest child in which the winner is crowned as little Miss Sunhine.Toda the film focuses on the bumpy journey undertaken by this peculiar family in his dilapidated van to California , place where the contest is held. But as in all roadmovie self-respecting, the trip will change the lives of the (perfectly interpreted) characters and will strengthen the relationship between the members of the strange family.A family in which live a shameless and funny (Allan Arkin) grandfather addicted to drugs, a suicidal uncle, a brother that makes strike of silence until do not allow you to join a school of pilots, a mother of innocent personality (Tonny Collette) but which serves as a main axis of the family and an obsessive father with success. Paradoxically, the person that shows more mature family is the small Olivia (Abigail Breslin).The girl does not seem to quite fit into the prototype of beauty they seek in the contest (it has separate teeth and used huge glasses) but his dream is to become a model and shall strive our utmost to achieve this. Although the illusion sometimes wane and the girl will fall into the discouragement and feel unsuccessful. His grandfather explains that she is not an unsuccessful because "the losers are those who resign to try for fear to not get it" and she does not cease trying. With one nod to Proust in another of his scenes, the film shows us the triumph in life is something relative and that it does not have to match the image of success in society. A critique of fierce, seemingly lightweight of the American dream, represented in the obsessive father figure and beauty contests. The competitiveness of society sees exemplified in talent tests which are subjected the participants of the contest. Because society compels us to demand us increasingly more than ourselves, and leads to frustration front the successes of others. As raised the character of the little Olivia's brother, "life is a contest of beauty after the other".Despite the indisputable drama suggests, little Miss Sunshine is a tender, funny, surreal moments as life itself. Because life is full of moments in which we feel a few losers, and others in which the greatest triumph is to be ourselves.</body>
</review>
