<review author="Yul B." title="Casino Royale" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This is not the Bond that the public expected. I do not mean because it is worse than others. It is that it is simply a different 007, which I think it disappoint many more purist fans.</summary>
	<body>This is not the Bond that the public expected.I do not mean because it is worse than others. It is that it is simply a different 007, which I think it disappoint many more purist fans.It is clear that the character of Ian Fleming has been reinvented to build a secret agent less subtle and more mercenary. Chivalry zero.What I don't know is if this change is that the parents of the child were already designed in advance a 180 degree turn in the franchise, without having chosen still the protagonist of the new release; or because they have been irresistibly compelled to do so by the final choice of Daniel Craig, an actor with aspect of bully. Safe to say that it has been the first thing.What is clear is that this transformation has had its victims: essential q. does an appearance at any time, and the efficient Moneypenny has been replaced by a Secretary with less sex appeal. This is logical, because the new Bond is now self-sufficient and not interested in loving jueguecitos. He's going to sack.However, this reinvention could justify the fact that we are before the first mission of the British Mi6 secret agent James Bond. By imagination, we would say that the boy is not yet refined.Its double zero category (licence to kill; and how kills) obtained after ruthlessly murdering two major criminals. And for his first work, Bond is sent to Madagascar to capture a dangerous terrorist named Obanno. After several investigations, and countless undisciplined actions that bring headaches to his boss M. (Judie Dench), get locate an international banker, called Le Chiffre (Mads Mikkelsen), whose occupation is to exploit financial resources to terrorist groups. Bond will try to ruin him in a game of poker millionaire held at Casino Royale in Montenegro with the assistance, inter alia, an agent of the British public Treasury, Vesper Lynd (Eva Green).During the first hour of footage, the film has a rhythm incredible, highlighting a frantic pursuit of Bond excelled, running behind the terrorist Obanno through the streets of Madagascar. Bareback, no cars or similar vehicles. The spectacular end of this persecution on an Embassy is the icing on one of the most vibrant scenes of recent titles in the series.Here is where we see the new 007 in all its splendor, and see that we we have James Bond another pasta. Wild and visceral.But once past those (approximately) 60 minutes, the tape drops significantly. He loses his initial pace, and becomes slow, predictable and with little interest. His lowest moment coincides with the plot developed around the game of poker in Montenegro, precisely the scenes giving title to this movie. The majority of external incidents occurring him bond during the game are implausible to seriously questioning me the words of Martin Campbell, director of?Did casino Royale?, referring to it as a tape that leaves behind the excessive fantasy of previous deliveries.As for the staging of this film, it is very similar to other titles, clearly influenced by the craft that Campbell has in this series Bond after being responsible for its resurgence with?Goldeneye?. Do the classic surrealist beginning of every 007 film has been devised for?Casino Royale? with an attractive style but without being a genius. I've missed the forced female silhouettes.As for the cast, Daniel Craig has done a good job as James Bond. And this must be qualified it. If we take as a basis the consolidated style that their predecessors have given to the character, Knight, conqueror, elegant, orderly in his performances, Craig unconvincing as 007. Here is where all the bad omens had since his election could have been confirmed as Bond.Pero is that the concept of the new 007 is different: is harder, impassive and uncontrolled. With this premise, Craig has built a very believable character, with great force, which you only recognize as Bond because he named his mission companions. It will be a matter of getting used to, but it not at odds on that line; However, I'll take Pierce Brosnan.Las interpretations of the rest of the main cast are not overly relevant. M. it has more presence in this film, so Dame Judi Dench has opportunity to offer longer his art, although in this case it is not too notable. Eva Green is correct and, for my taste, its beauty is not comparable to other Bond girls (I prefer the stunning murine Caterina, in the role of the wife of a terrorist that 007 bind.) (Delicatessen). And, with regard to Mads Mikkelsen makes an evil of the bunch, and the tears of blood are a story.?Casino Royale? I has entertained halfway, so with me has not achieved our desired objective. To make matters worse his end is intentionally unfinished, implying that the next installment, number 22, will be a continuation of this. If marketing maneuver flies?.</body>
</review>
