<review author="Iñigo" title="Transamerica" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Felicity Huffman is good, but nothing so great as some they cacarean</summary>
	<body>It is interesting to note how even the cinema itself is torn between different pseudo-oleadas converted into temporary fashion. It is enough that you one the first stone lance so the screen becomes a massive stone-throwing. "Like everything else in this world, it has its pros and cons.""Transamerica" plays a bit with all these factors surrounding supposedly sudden, innovative, bold and groundbreaking ideas. But as what prima in the film quality are other factors. get a little malparada. Firstly, those who think that the film is terribly original, only, about the issue of a transsexual, are very wrong. It is not even the real background of the film.What is really appreciated is the boldness and the self-assurance with which touches a theme so (possibly) controversial and contentious. But that is a double-edged weapon. What at first is a species of road-movie to use (but absolutely with all factors seen and hackneyed) with tone comedian true dramatic background, degenerates into a substitute for comedieta certainly pathetic family mess, and concludes, obviously as a drama sprinkled with small comic elements to entertain the Viewer.A so orderly progression as obvious and predictable. The problem is that it is so simple and topical, drama hundreds of times seen in film, you need a fun mask to do so somewhat endearing. And that mask is precisely that avoids that the story is told with the necessary grip to enable us to the Stanley/Sabrina skin with all the seriousness that requires.As I said, the self-assurance with which us speaks of a difficult subject for many is a plus, and really, it may be so if you are simply looking for fun in the cinema. But seeing his little originality, it is difficult to reach the film more than a passenger entertainment.We have all the ingredients of the comic road movies. The frustration of a parent to discover the existence of a child, until today, unknown. The coincidences which obviously lead to both match and to know each other. The journey undertaken, more that a trip is a clear McGuffin for a future redemption and a rediscovery of both.A trip more spiritual than physical, a journey that, much as Stanley/Sabrina search the element that will definitely become the woman that has always wanted to be, the only thing that will really look for is the acceptance and the meeting with his son. The history of redemption is in essence, does that flood the viewer in a continuous feeling of "déjà vu". The unspeakable secrets that are discovered throughout the trip, the traumas of childhood revive by the intolerance experienced against a sexual preference (or psychological, will not put me to analyze it) atypical, both in the family environment and the social environment. Fear of rejection and replacement of a son which was not given all the love required by its condition of transsexual (here is the theme that comes to us, but any other reason or condition is valid and applicable).A cluster of evidence that expensive too much the quality and originality of the final product.Because no, no mistake. Which tell us the story of a transsexual does not change anything. If a drug addict, a lost son, a coward to be home because everything is complicated, or a perpetrator, surely the film not reached such levels of public interest. It would pass unnoticed, because that really is what deserves.History is always. The only thing that changes is the sexual preference of its protagonist. But not. We must accept that it is the story of a transsexual and that is why there will be uproar. And unfair criticism. These are things that happen. If for this simple reason we have to brand peliculón, forgetting his true quality and making more case to the uproar it causes. go I no me up on that bandwagon.Felicity Huffman is also good, but nothing so great as a certain cacarean to nominate it or announce it trumpeted. Tad sobreactuada perhaps. For this reason, in short, it is an interesting work only as portrait of a transsexual and frustrations, fears and prejudices of their environment.While the story and its formal self-assurance are numbered in a tone so humorous that, sometimes, is a burden which prevents us posicionemos properly in the complicated skin of the character. the correct description is sufficient so that we come to understand the message that tries to send. Addition, it must be admitted that innocence, simplicity and lack of pretensions of grandeur with which the story is told is a fact in their favor. It follows the classical aura of tranquility of purely "independent" films that make presence, from time to time, in billboard and arriving to become something endearing.But let us not deceive ourselves. You can upload any integer, but never become a great movie. It is so topical, repetitive and obvious that it does not bring anything new. The only thing that changes is the choice of the protagonist, a little valid change to raise the quality of a film that has little to offer. It entertains, amuses and little else. We are not at the level of "Brokeback Mountain" film (allow me the comparison by the rapprochement between topics and to avoid a controversy that would be unfounded, incoherent and stupid).</body>
</review>
