<review author="Bloody Will" title="El perfume" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Neither found me month peliculón, nor the hodgepodge of the year. Give an approved.</summary>
	<body>I have not lído the book, starting out there. Why is that I lose something basic to see this movie, and it is check if the director, Tom Tykwer, along with the adapter writer, of course, has managed to capture the essence of the novel, or has at least brought diligently. It is well known that when we read a book our imagination flows until create us our own movie, why fuck much to come another to destroy the charm.At least tell you in what has cagado her this film, because comparisons are them going to his readers.The main failure is the silence. Ojito, not is that go me the movies where is cotorrea no sense constantly, though the verbiage of Kevin Smith is my favorite. It was simply intended to move to the screen the hundreds of detailed, thorough and devious descriptions that surely coparán the book, and that translates into images, images with no dialogue, and when there is no dialogue because you can not have them, the thing starts to become tedious. Of course I prefer to a script by Michael Bay, but as a regular reader I am aware of are where I tangando.Everytime the protagonist intends to commit some of their crimes make sure you about ten minutes in total silence, and fuck you supremely know in this silence, the auor of the book you are detailing with an impressive wealth odors, feelings, grief and desires of the protagonist. That there is no co ** put it on screen unless it is with a voice-over, and because we know that that may be worse than the silence.The history you know something. Jean Baptiste Grenouille, born with no body odor, has a gift: the distinguish all the scents of this world. This gift will be to turn the curse of the obsessive quest for the perfect essence. If we need to assess the work, first, of the director Tom Tykwer, I don't have any objections. The director has done best for the story and that is provide it with a photograph and a way to handle the camera you approaching how that scene in the book, has narrated brilliantly so you can guess that it has faithfully reflected the environment requiring adaptation. Perhaps what I am most grateful for is that it is a film of a murderer and see just a drop of blood. The director has not needed and already I think that is quite an achievement, seen in the film current addiction to red blood cells.The actor protagonist, Tom Wishaw, is has been encotrado with difficult ballot of try to transmit the world that Grenouille moves, and at least his eyes do a good job. I think it's an obsessive, because it acts during the film as such, and is well above the other actors in the film, Dustin Hoffman outboard not his best role precisely, and Alan Rickman nor has lines to show it off. The question would be if for those who read the book Jean Baptiste has been the murderer had hoped. I can not say, I hope that you can give light to this issue.I have a friend (that ricky) which says that there are books that are scripts and others who are literature. "Code Da Vinci" is a hyphen. Any of Grisham is a script. "The perfume" should I assume is the latter, because I know that they have omitted me tens of pages of the book, and that gives me a lot of courage. For the rest, or it has seemed the month peliculón, nor the hodgepodge of the year. Give an approved.</body>
</review>
