<review author="Yul B." title="El camino de los ingleses" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The visual and sound aspect of the film is dominated by overwhelming. It is a paranoia of Antonio Banderas, in the best sense of the word.</summary>
	<body>To understand and appreciate this film it is essential to go to the movies before knowing the following:?The camino de los ingleses? It is a paranoia of Antonio Banderas, in the best sense of the word. Paranoia caused by the writer and writer of the novel inspiring, Antonio Soler, by cinematographer Xavi Giménez, and by the composer of the soundtrack Antonio Meliveo.La Union of the work of all of them, with flags at the head, has resulted in a feature film of author, unconventional, and some surreal moments.If this detail is known in advance, the tape is seen from another perspective, with a different chip, and is judged better.Therefore, on the basis that we have a completely atypical film product, my assessment sobre?The camino de los ingleses? It is positive.The malagueño director/actor has been able to relate in unusual way, apart from the prevailing formalism in the film of our days, but in an attractive manner, the first loves, lusts and obsessions of a group of four friends - Miguelito (Alberto Amarilla), Babirosa (Raúl Arévalo), Paco Frontón (Félix Gómez) and Moratalla (Mario Casas) - during a summer vacation in the city of Malaga (Spain) of late 70.El visual and sound aspect of the film is predominant way crushing on tells the story. This is its hallmark: almost everything you see on screen is a game of colors, lights and textures, led with unusual, often short and intentionally descuadrados levels with no pattern camera movements and angles already forgotten in the current film.The continuous background music and the voiceover of a fifth friend,? the throat? (Fran Perea), poetic Narrator mode, gave the film a melancholic atmosphere appropriate to the dramatic touch that gives the lives of the Group of friends and their environment.On the other hand, the sexual component of this film is intense. Do however, is treated without chabacanería or Visual vulgarity (Word are inevitable), with? elegance? and an unusual artistic carefully in this field.With regard to the selected main cast, a success to one hundred percent. None of them at odds.Alberto Amarilla outboard the role of Miguelito. Do to my gone this grating image that had him for its portrayal of Rafa in the series?My lovely neighbors?. The rest of the group, Raul Arevalo (the more pirao, lover of Bruce Lee), Félix Gómez (posh) and Mario (left) houses, not get left behind. Fran Perea, unrecognizable, takes off his stigma of television product. With regard to the women's campus, it is explosive, sensual and savagely beautiful. María Ruiz (Luli), the girl in Miguelito, is a discovery; remember his name because we will often see in our cinema; and so far as Marta Nieto (the body), does honour to his nickname in the film.For veterans, Victoria Abril and Juan Diego fit short. Online its outstanding common (although Juan Diego prodigue shortly).Does the climax of the above signed the own flags to describe in a recent promotion granted to Spanish film magazine interview?Do Cinemanía?, and collected in this month of December's issue special supplement, what were its claims to the shoot?The camino de los ingleses?: "with this film did not want half measures nor save his own skin." "I know that me I played, but I managed to put my dreams on the screen".Do luck, because this film complies perfectly with the topic of? or you like or hate her?. It is the only conventional, that can be attributed.</body>
</review>
