<review author="Bloody Will" title="Déjà Vu" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Do we have a cross of?C.S.I.??Public enemy? and?Back to the future. ?Déjà Vu? It is a purely summer movie that has crept into the Christmas calendar.</summary>
	<body>Gentlemen, we are facing a crossroads "C.S.I.", "Public enemy" and "Back to the future". There is nothing. I wasn't very sure if the main premise of the film was to see Denzel Washington behind a terrorist plot, and at the end you realize that nothing at all: what really is travel through time. This film is a perfection of Tony Scott on the work of Tony Scott: fast, continuous action and the aesthetics of the best Jerry Bruckheimer productions. "Déjà Vu" is a purely summer movie that has crept into the Christmas calendar, and as such must be seen. Why was a box office failure?, perhaps help you understand after reading this criticism.To continue talking about need to know a bit what account Scott: Agent Carlin (Washington) is in charge of the investigation of an event that I will not disclose. This event is as cruel as inexplicable, by what the different tracks followed by Carlin carried it a new method of research of the Government that will provide the possibility of altering the course of the time the protagonist? and as I said that, here I can read.It is difficult to not gutting important aspects of the film, since otherwise a very broad synopsis you would look askance Scott intentions. When you attend the step-by-step story development going entering what really wants the director to the public: to accept that reality can be so fanciful as possible. Let me explain and return the thread of the three pillars and references of the film. "C.S.I.": investigation of Carlin is as accurate as the forensic television, and it shows the hand of Bruckheimer in these parts, not in vain is the creator of the cathodic franchise. It is a very effective remedy, but my "déjà vu" begins when I've seen too much Grissom to surprise me. "Public enemy": obviously the emergence of several mice library with predilection to monitors and satellites evokes in me the magnificent Seth Green film made by the own Tony Scott with Will Smith and now copy in a way obvious, but clear, is how is copied when you're the original creator?. And you tell it from "back to the future"?. Impossible not to remember it in the last third of the film. I shall count.The theme of the time travel is as old as cinema and this film will not discover anything new; However, play with this genus carries things the have very well tied until the end, and you could say that after more than half fairly consistent film, everything is going to hell in the last half hour. In the end everything with regard to 4 days and a half (you already know what I am talking about) is reduced to a couple of hours, which I have not come to understand. Many Capes are loose and the final resolution has been accomplished because there is no other way to end, but not because everything is explained.Quite apart from the always controversial topic of logical or not logical, other aspects of the films are undeniably entertaining. It is not a film of policy or of human feelings. Denzel Washington mauve a brutally real role in magnificent "El Fuego de la revenge" of the same director, and is now introduced in the fantastic solving the ballot in the same way. When Denzel gets seriously we know and avoid the role of poly hyperactive with liquid metal body. I must admit that I begin to tire of always take the same attitude of mujo I in his later works, but I will not put any but until that it's not really tedious. Least the villain of the film, which is superb despite not to disclose their identity, the rest of the casting is, as usual, erratic. Val Kilmer leaves enough to be correct, and Paula Patton is this discovery that we will see in the next few years starring in genuine blockbusters. Adam Goldberg takes over Jack Black and Seth Green left on "Enemy" and I must say that this actor has always been one of my favorites after embody the psychotic partner of Joey in "Friends". An efficient counterpoint to the always airtight Washington. maybe so many films a year make me a little more punctilious, but despite all the holes remaining at the end of "Déjà Vu", not you can discuss you action takes you in aloft until the 2 hours and 8 minutes to take you to Tony Scott tell a story that, as a good translation of its titledo, makes you remember a few more, and for this reason perhaps the public turn its back spot already thousand times, and this despite the fact that the mixture, rebozo and agitated applied to product finish leaving it new, tee?</body>
</review>
