<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Jackass 2" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One wishing to soak up this dreadful bullshit, go, sientése, assemble a stomach as a hangar of a Boeing 707 and leave dirty, literally, dark, stinky and cheesy shit.</summary>
	<body>Yes, I admit: I have fallen so low. I hardened in Jean Renoir, Fritz Lang, John Ford, have attended the ceremony of the unconscious and I lost time and peak of my life to verify, perhaps this is the last time, to what extent can degrade the human being for the sake of commercial claim. I admit that the savagery of the sketches has its point of hilarity: remind me of those videos of first, or as rang, amenizaban family dinners and nurtured mindless babies (by leaving Randhir, not to have little intelligence, come on) and mozalbetes with acne were recorded while replaceable someone is departing for the benefit of the community risotada.Jackass is a formula of success of MTV which probably has his hole in accelerated hearings, bourgeois of the cable, strong feelings that their lives are sufficiently grey and flat, Avid so devoid of emotion, that they require this artificial clamping system that his adrenaline is not die in your organic bedroom and feel between whack and others asquerosidada plus of adventure, a trip (armchair, with the remote in hand and the LCD 1080 full to all pixel) to eschatology, i.e. shit pontificada as artistic expression.In this thread of things, Jackass isn't film: it is not a film, but uses its mercantilist machinery and its industrial billing process. This Johnny Knoxville, father of the bastard son of home entertainment, has clear ideas: the ready kind seen in this stinking litany of prowess of the absurd is an easy method (the more criticized, more amortized) to fill the current account and create in the fifteen year old market (ay, believe that there I am extremely short) one candy fully addictive morons laughter and chabacanería amplified at full power.Read more: is nor warns that those who recorded this nonsense have any idea of how to handle a camera or how to mount movie. Everything is frayed, badly finished: seems that my cousin had returned to his eighteen years and camera on his shoulder, had recorded an afternoon of Follies in the town square. Kind of. Amateurism with sponsor millionaire: exploitation in cinemas around the world.If stepping on a hook on the cheek or showering with leeches is encouragement for a viewer, then Alfred Hitchcock is dead, Francois Truffaut is dead, dead Ernst Lubitsch, Clint Eastwood has died, has killed Steven Spielberg, in short, all those that have contributed to that cinema is an art and concite the unanimous opinion among his followers and addicts, that life can be, Yes, gentle reader, wonderful.One you want to steep in this dreadful bullshit, go, sientése, rearm (I insist) of a stomach as a hangar of a Boeing 707 and get dirty, literally, dark, stinky and cheesy shit. (Had to see it to, quietly, write on it: here are the sad role of responsible film critic)</body>
</review>
