<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Primera plana" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Wilder proverbially emphasizes the corruption of power. Front page lives in freedom, writes in freedom and is filmed without the homicidal corset of the censorship of the time filters...</summary>
	<body>Somehow, front page, very precariously summary, is a film by Billy Wilder, and she come together, also very schematically raised, the leivmotivs of the author, his particular interests in film, his way of seeing life. So front page contains formidable sentences, irony, sarcasm, bad milk good (not coarse, not cazurra), vertiginous dialogues, characters with a dramatic depth and a comic bis dozing spectators-proof.Wilder cinema is cinema of words, cinema in love with dialogue as an absolute asset to hook to leave that they steal two hours of attention to attend a story that happens to other people. What is the film, but this?The Wilder words pronounced them morons psychiatrists, corrupt sheriffs, journalists hacks of shoddy, mayors sponsored by a brand of sausages and poor of spirit that do not support more or less irremediable injustice in this world, but also the Wilder words are spoken by whores (ex officio that never leaves badly in the film of the Austrian master), journalists as a sequoia Cup, clerks with a cathedral heart and poor of spirit that they go away the shit of life and draw the nose to find on-air flawed by the stench, a point of honesty, aromas and beauty.Unlike the film of Howard Hawks that gives rise to this (new moon, 1940), front page lives in freedom, to write in freedom and is filmed without the homicidal corset of filters of the censorship of the time. Wilder proverbially emphasizes the corruption of power.Hawks makes a more dynamic film: Wilder, in the 1970s, forty years later, signs a more finely ironic work, with a draught of comedy more virulent because Wilder humor hurt when he hears concentrated. It is a caustic humor: acid and corrosive humor.Whatever that Wilder was a journalist in his early Vienna years, knows what will the thing and front page, the thread of this sort of lived event, becomes a monument formidable freedom of expression, the nobility of the art of journalism and their dignity as essential in the last trade (at least) two centurieswithout which runs.The argument itself is a satire thorough, methodical in its simplicity, but strong in the extension of field reaches. Walter Burns (Walter Matthau) is the editor of a newspaper of double circulation and abundant, but low in talent template because, apparently, will have to resort to his journalist star Hildy Johnson (Jack Lemmon) to cover the execution of a murderer in the local presidio. Everything is mess when Johnson announces, theatrically, with a clearly contemporary and intelligent comedy which abandons the work by marrying a Philadelphia concert and make a living as a publicist. You ranting against journalism, it is important that the press only read for awhile and the newspaper ends as wrapper of a few scrapes of herring in a dustbin. Walter Burns is, by all possible means, devious almost all, recover their man for the news, return it to the Office, avoid that he marry, mostly. Here we note the conventional script, the commercial, avenible party to the conventions and the usual gags, but below, ras of metaphor, late (powerful, sublime) desparpajo that Wilder portrays the role of the journalist as a notary of the reality, thus also very manidamente expressed.Much of what we see only happening in the Department of the presidio press. From his window, he then rotates, is the scaffold. Journalists there to drink, play cards and talk about frivolities and old raids have no scruples, not have honesty, have no difficulty in modifying the reality to your tastes and for the greater glory of the pompous and bombastic holder: seller.The Mayor and the sheriff are neglected and are a huge asset in the script of Diamond and the own Wilder, on a small play of Hetch. The two are degraded, converted to slag which measures (as you can) to the powerful Guild of the press (the serious, that is) so not aireen their desire, their sins legally punishable.Then there is the Eggelhoffer, the psychiatrist to interview the defendant Williams: one of the best side of Wilder, no margin of doubt. Rich in its profile caricatured, reduced to hyperbolic shadowing of Freud, which Wilder also ridicules. "Has the own Freud met the Wilder journalist in his native Vienna and that they were, shall we say, good tune.""Truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth", reads the slogan of the Examiner, the newspaper of yore. Movies and nothing but movies, I'd say. God, in voice of Trueba, was killed by modern cinema, the cinema less semantic, film eaten by technology fever.In the sky in which I do not think will be taking notes on the turbiedades of los Angeles. Bad times for the lyric, sang in the glorious eighties low blows.</body>
</review>
