<review author="Caruco" title="Ratónpolis" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The comical, not by simple is stupid, nor scenes of action, at full speed, whether in boat, blender or recycled toaster; become monotonous.</summary>
	<body>Go my vote for the best animated film of the year to "British", failing to see "Happy feet", and taking into account the relative disappointment of "Cars" (technically incredible) or boredom of "Ice age 2: the thaw" (how is he was a taquillazo in the world?).Entertaining is at least funny, and its footage is not stretched too. When you can start to tire come the final scenes and it ends. Another thing is that its leaders had decided that they were before a genius and they pulled the House out the window, spending $ 90 million, more 30 in advertising, going from the endearing and handcrafted clay and plasticine "Wallace Gromit &" or "Chicken run." "Evasion on the farm" to the computer-generated animation. An investment which will have to recover on DVD.Literally evacuated of her luxurious mansion to pull the chain of a water, its protagonist, Roddy (original voice of Hugh Jackman in English, with Fele Martínez in Spanish), English socialite mouse goes to an underworld of sewers; a replica in miniature, and rodent version of Londres.Babosas singing.There you will discover the adventure, the value, the company and of course love the whiskers of Rita (original voice of Kate Winslet in English, and María Esteve in Spanish), a reply to scale ratuna of Lara Croft.El evil of the function is the Toad (voiced by Ian McKellen in the original, Javier Gurruchaga in the dubbed version), a copy of its kind traumatized by an event of his childhood and also associated with Prince Charles (!)do, and is that winks to the Royal family are constant, good evidence that this is a product typically? british?.It could not miss any homage to Bond, even that appear conveniently caricatured American and especially French, to inspector Clouseau in the strokes of frog (Jean Reno, original voice). And there are more, but not abused, Nemo, Frank Capra?But the best is in the secondary characters as a bobalicón and huge bully, or especially the appearances of a few canals slugs, in the purest style The Platters, which like dare to sing the "Bohemian like you" from the Dandy Warhols as Tina Turner's "Proud Mary" or the "What? does s new Pussycat?" of Tom Jones.Aardman vs. Dreamwoks.Y, Hallelujah!, the comical, not by simple, is stupid, or scenes of action, at full speed, whether in boat, blender or recycled toaster; become monotonous. There are even trompazos and hilarious blows. Who I was going to say that to me? Enemy staunch as I am easy falls.Do the funny thing is that "British" without being anything intellectual or complex, but also rather on the contrary, a worthy? divertimento? for children and adults, has broken the Alliance of the Aardman Features with Dreamworks Animation, controlled by powerful Jeffrey Katzenberg. Not only because of lukewarm box office results, but also why Katzenberg wanted to include a more "American" humor, helpings and winks to other titles of the factory Dreamwoks, as "Shrek" or the less memorable "The espantatiburones".Katzenberg is business, about the Aardman more artistic vision and a possible agreement with the Disney/Pixar perhaps trusty us moments of greatest glory.</body>
</review>
