<review author="Kiko de España" title="Brick" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>You have to enter the game. If you can, you will enjoy as long ago. Fun but dense, slow but fast, original but a photocopy. Very good film today.</summary>
	<body>You have to enter the game. If you can, you will enjoy as long ago. If not, can finish leaving the room (that happens by doubt between Brick and why rubbing the legs?) Brick, the directorial debut of Rian Johnson is a conglomerate of noir by which they poke Houston, Welles, Hawks, Chandler and Hammett and leads one of the kids of things about Martians, i.e. of an experiment. And the experiment turns out to be a noir of the of all life, with his fatal woman, his criminal in the shadow, his private detective as hard as the rock and his Intelligent Assistant and a constantly present in the film Chinatown (see the knife attack and the strips in the nose of the protagonist) in Brick there is also a little elephantwith his AUL (film school where he studied the director) their teenage freaks and, above all, with his filming: 20 days. During this time Johnson banned the cast viewing of the gangster film, but if recommended them reading Hammett or Chandler and seen the results the kids broke squarely in her both as the director himself.I say above that you have to enter it from the beginning, because it may be shocking (although I don't know the reason, anything can happen in a movie, not is it that?), because see American Pie kids acting as Lords of Chinatown (for example) can catch you by surprise.A major success of the film is to demonstrate that, first and foremost, these characters, both the (anti) heroes such as criminals, are students of Institute living with their parents and that, in addition to the obvious pressure by the drug trafficking and murder (are criminals) have to worry about the lack of attendance, and that is fun, original and surprising.The truth is all you need high school is the Institute and the students, because the dialogues and situations are 100% Noir, becoming at times as dense as any other peli gender of fifty or sixty years ago. Understandable is that the tape could see in Sitges, because it is so pure (speaking of noir), which seems to scifi, such forms of talk (are you sure you want to be sure?) and these methods: the universe of Brick is a particular MicroWorld that the director has invented and is as real as absurd (the mother of The Pin serving milk "friends" of his son)(the head of studies talking about the protagonist as if they were in a police station rather than in the Office of the school.)The actors are great, especially that revelation who is Joseph Gordon-Levitt, which creates a Brendan that little has to envy to Sam Spade, a "strips" dim-witted nerd looking but that resources and stubbornness is almost a machine to kill, something normal on the other hand, because if not possibly end underground. Lucas Haas is The Pin, the man behind the crime, a character a little excessive, but fundamental, represents a connection between the world that creates the director and ours in a way that can not even the protagonist, that we only see the alarm clock of your home: The Pin lives with his mother and in the basement has a room where plays the role of godfather of the mafia of the kids in their twenties.Emile de Ravin (lost, they the hills have eyes) is the character that triggers the events and Nora Zehetner is the femme fatale. Shaft, I mean Richard Roundtree portraying the head of studies. A movie fun but dense, slow but fast, original but a photocopy. Very good film today. A 8´75.PD: very bad Alphaville theaters despite the "redesign".</body>
</review>
