<review author="Silvia" title="El ilusionista" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not only a story of love and magic but is basically a suspense film in which the Viewer may wonder if what you are seeing is real or is a product of fiction.</summary>
	<body>When we attend a magic show, often are afraid we learned the trick and leave behind this aura of mystery that surrounds all the games of magic. But in the illusionist, both the Prince in Prague and the police of the place are obsessed with discovering what are the secrets that hides the magician Eisenheim (Edward Norton). And it is that his tricks are so spectacular that they seem to result of some strange supernatural power.The story begins, as it is imaginable, with the magician Eiseheim showing his artistic abilities on stage, with a public encandilado before his mysterious tricks. From here, the movie takes place in a flashback that will explain the beginnings of the protagonist as a wizard from his childhood until his success.As a teenager, Eiseheim was madly in love with Sophie von Teschen, (played by the deadpan Jessica Biel), an unrequited love which is truncated but returns to stoking years later. As they are people of different class and social status will live a clandestine relationship to the purest style of Romeo and Juliet. They are forced to separate and are when they are adults but the beautiful Sophie was already the fiancée of the Prince in Prague (Rufus Sewell). Everything will be impediments to post magician that both the Prince and the police will try to at all costs find out his tricks. But the love story is the least developed element and that promised more from the beginning. Perhaps the fact that the film is narrated from the point of view of the character of detective police played by Paul Giamatti generates a distance from the Viewer to the couple, so that after a promising start, it is hard to be complicit in his passion and feel empathy for the characters.But it is not only a story of love and magic but is basically a suspense film in which the Viewer may wonder whether what you are seeing is real or is a product of fiction created by the wizard. With the death of one of the characters, the story will take paths of police intrigue, those in which the viewer can play guess the murderer.At the technical level should be emphasized a soundtrack and an atmosphere cared to detail that manage to perfectly recreate the atmosphere of light and shadows lived in Vienna from the year 1900. The script is correct although it suffers some ups and downs: after a promising start he reaches a turning point of narrative stagnation that extends until near the end. A final, which although it can guess, no ceases to amaze. History is resolved well in a way that in the puzzle of the film, the pieces end up fitting perfectly.Leaving aside the possible shortcomings, the public that most will enjoy the film will be willing to be lead, and believe that the wonderful illusions created by the wizard have something of reality. If we leave aside the logic gets to a point where no us blend-naremos tricks and can fully enjoy the magic shows. An entertaining story, a nice drama more unpretentious than entertain which magic show and get significantly its purpose. The story exemplifies the eternal struggle between logic (the reason) and emotion, illusion. But, as it arises in the film, will the illusion be the truth?</body>
</review>
