<review author="Matías Cobo" title="El camino de los ingleses" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We welcome the ambition of originality that exudes all the work of the Malaga, but both poetic desire as a whole becomes a wrapper of luxury too cold.</summary>
	<body>I applaud risks in sunsets in scene managers able to dip the visual lyricism to support their stories, and thus escape from the conventions of the, almost always effective, classical narrative. But I understand that go to recherché frames, images slowdowns or the shooting of dreamy sequences must be justified and must whether on the set of the film gently. Antonio Banderas director likes to take risks as demonstrated in this tape in which used narrative formulae diametrically opposed to those seen in his work as an interpreter. Notice you the tables of a gifted student who has learned in the best school possible, the American cinema, but perhaps lack the necessary restraint to balance form and content. To the camino de los ingleses, a tape that is a conventional story from a point unconventional view, they drag a few Visual excesses that perhaps have been more content or have sustained a history of larger vessels, would have completed a round film. But, unfortunately, the result of the second work as a filmmaker of the Malaga has been half way.The camino de los ingleses is an introspective portrait of youngsters whose lives cross by trance which mediates youth and maturity, a stage of elections, but, above all, resignations pushed by the icy clash with reality. The protagonist, Miguelito, you change your view of life a cultured man who will meet in the hospital during his hearing after a kidney operation. This man at the gates of death will be shown to Miguelito towards an inner world that give you access reading and poetry. To his departure from the clinic he reencontrará with his world, with his work in a hardware store and a late 1970s Malaga neighborhood friends. But something has changed in the relationship with them. It was determined to be a poet and will repeat it to those they see while walking his inseparable exemplary of the divinia Dante's comedy. His gang of friends also passes by existential doubts of mixed caliber, but sharing with Miguelito the desire for feel life with sparkling intensity of youth that still treasure. I.e., that front a reality that repeated them machaconamente what little that are and how little that will become, they cling to a burning clove to your dreams.The choice of a cast of young actors and little known is also a decision risks that, in this case, yes it has taken advantage flags by the implication that denote all of them in each sequence. Alberto Amarilla, last known television, and a great Raúl Arévalo, already discovered in the remarkable AzulOscuroCasiNegro, embody the main male roles, while newcomer María Ruiz and Marta Nieto assume the weight of the female cast. In addition, secondary luxury such as Victoria Abril and Juan Diego completing acting work, in general, bordering at high altitude. In the same way it happens with the score composed by Antonio Meliveo or precocious photography signed by Xavi Giménez. Both elements, along with mounting tape, the aesthetic frames of some planes or the repeated inclusion of dreamy sequences, become a personal bet that flags maybe has failed contain enough tape. As I said at the beginning, it is appreciated the ambition of originality that exudes all the work of the Malaga, but both poetic desire the set becomes a wrapper of luxury too cold.</body>
</review>
