<review author="Marta" title="El castillo ambulante" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>History fascinating and full of fantasy</summary>
	<body>For quite some time that did not see the film a film that I like. I would like to say that I liked really. Also long enough that he hoped the premiere of "Howl's moving Castle" (or "Howl's Moving Castle, or" howl no ugoku shiro ""), the last film by Hayao Miyazaki. Friday her they premiered, on Friday I saw nothing more return from the Congress, and now I cannot make long that I do not see a movie really liked me.First of all, a few details: when speaking of this man often mentioned as "the creator of Heidi or Marco". Or mentioned you, because for some years (especially thanks to "Princess Mononoke" and "The journey of spirited away") has begun to be known to the general public (among which I include myself). As you can see on my list, "The journey of spirited away" is one of my favorite movies. In 2002, he won the Golden bear at the Berlin Film Festival - making it, I believe, in this award-winning animated film, first and in 2003 won the Oscar for the best animated film.However, having said that, I am continuing. "The journey of spirited away" is a magical film, where each scene is a surprise. In fact, and as well he told me Guizmo at the time, is a species of "Alice in the country of wonders" to the Japanese. The first time I saw I liked, that when he finished me he upset not to continue with the story. For that reason, it had high hopes for "Howl's moving Castle" and as usual when you expect much of something, a little bit of fear that decepcionara me. Luckily, it wasn't like that. In an article by Supernovapop leo that the film "has been described as one minor part of the career of Miyazaki works". The truth, I have no idea of who has been able to say something, and it is not a subjective opinion, because any case, is nominated for the Oscar.En say what they say, "Howl's moving Castle" is a fascinating and full of fantasy story. You never know what is going to happen next, and this is a pleasure. As regards the protagonists, what should I say? The demon Calcifer, turnip-headed scarecrow, the Witch of the Landes and the own Sophie, converted into old woman, are great characters.</body>
</review>
