<review author="Cp" title="Déjà Vu" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The writer does not maintain a consistency in no time, the scenes are happening as you crave the Director, with the only justification that remain well, regardless of history.</summary>
	<body>Several days ago we had already gone to see Soraya and I, but not even I had motivated enough to write something about it. By that look so pessimistic, so that the film is a disappointment. Not at the level of director, the technical team or actors. In all such cases, is what you can expect anyone who has seen other films of Tony Scott and Denzel Washington. They work as normally do with their level of quality and the way they act or address to which we are accustomed. So that is a quite flexible film with action with Denzel doing his role as good (is the wrong, for other stories) and struggling to save the girl. Highlights are the performance of Val Kilmer, who is improving with age, the scene of the explosion (which we have already seen in the trailer), and how to shoot Scott. But all this is nothing, if everything build you on a defective basis. A time travel movie, camouflaged thriller, you need a solid script, without too many errors, or at least that go by connecting all the stories, the motivations of the characters and their actions of end fitting at the end. This is not the case. Seems the only writer thought to do a story of travel in time, where at the end the protagonist saves the girl, and if we have to do crap about it, including spoil all the previous history, because it is done and now this, what matters is that the film ends well. I am not going to get into the amount of crap on the theories of time travel, eye, not about the known science, but to the theories which have own tape. That is the problem, the writer, or the writing staff do not maintain a consistency in no time, scenes are happening as you crave the Director, with the only justification that remain well, regardless of history. A disaster, will. See Deja Vu I understand why so many millions of dollars are paid by a good script, increasingly more scarce.</body>
</review>
