<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Ellos" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Principals have made a rapid inventory of gender clichés and have gotten them into a tourmix: the resulting milkshake is them and has significant flavors, although the final aftertaste is harsh, bland, poor.</summary>
	<body>From the outset, this is a film of fear: everything is designed to produce fear. The trump card is to hide the nature of evil during almost the complete footage: do not know until the last minutes what threat pursues the protagonist couple. Would have been better not to know never – or know it from the outset not to have saved the eighty minutes of tape but to not bore us both. They get bored. The film enfanga in a few artistic pretensions that do not deserve to unfavourable criticism any. Everything is well written: images, the crescendo in fear, the final climax. History convinced visually, but this remarkable film writing isn't supported by a script that really appeals. Looks forward to the thing to conclude: know what is behind the noise of the silences. And at the end, when we know, we condone the idea that has not been worth riding both firework for a final Fireworks so mild.Non-profit-making gutting that Fireworks, mild, as say, the gentle reader should, however, spend those 80 minutes. It bored sovereignty, feel that maybe in the end everything is a huge joke, believe that you outside, on the street, rain or Sun or cars make a symphony with the cláxons or that a blonde calón mounts a chicken because her boyfriend just you confess he is with another, more blonde and more cannon. All that you can go you through the head, but should be given a chance, albeit to accelerate with the sprint are the protagonists, the couple suddenly woken up at his home, a huge, incredible, unusual House, i.e., not credible, by some noises that just taking them literally to the absolute horror. It would seem that principals have made a rapid inventory of gender clichés and have gotten them into a tourmix: the resulting milkshake is them and has significant flavors, although the final aftertaste is harsh, bland, poor. They have not gone ten minutes and we no longer have sweet tannins, the mouth perfumed by so many ill-fated emotion.</body>
</review>
