<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Ficción" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Fiction explicit as few films I have seen the difficulty of humans to express love, let it flow and not to control the effects of his escape.</summary>
	<body>It was very easy fiction, with a few very simple mimbres, fell into complacency, in that the navel-gazing in which many films of this intimate draught fall. And avoids it fiction almost always: lyricism that we see that cleaning of feelings, is sincere, but overwhelming sometimes, and you feel self-conscious before this formidable display of emotions so to ras of epidermis, of people (that no characters) so honest with his life. Fiction explicit as few films I have seen the difficulty of humans to express love, let it flow and not to control the effects of his escape. CESC Gay is portrayed in the film director: Eduard Fernández immeasurable, now, I have no doubt, in an actor of fundamentals solídisimos, able to lift itself, a film in this our Spanish film so needy of attachments of superfluous additions. It is the story of a man who runs away from the city and take refuge in the House of a friend. It is the story of a reconciliation: that of a man with himself. Then fiction is not articulated as classical history, but it goes on with meekness and the words, gestures, silences, the looks are (especially) which lifted the film. The script is very short: doesn't almost bait. The merit that we leave the cinema with the impression of having seen a film and not a boring concatenamiento of cuarentones in a country house talks is the poetic pulse of a director on winning streak (in the city, his previous film was also a notable movie, or Krampack) and a cast (it says so, but the word sounds to starlettes in a staircase of a musci hall)(see, we do) in absolute State of grace (and this final sounds to San Juan de la Cruz, wrap a verse in a mystical trance, metaphysical loneliness of his retirement).We don't know if the director seeking inspiration and spiritual peace finds some of these shortcomings. It is important little. What is is the love: and immediately recognizes. Ultimately, the love story is sad. And the film: a remansada, Nice, contained and almost warm sadness makes us ask ourselves, without the stridency of the urgency for life, by stimuli make us to withstand it, enjoy it, fear her, occasionally.Recommended film in these times of Vertigo and confusion aesthetic, although shock than the characters, except for the veterinarian who makes Javier camera, occasionally speak in Catalan. There will be things of the policy, and this is a page of cinema. The own Gay was "appalled" when the Distributor came to to turn the Spanish in full force. In short, this is a page (I insist) on film and not can, by extension, at the time, by wanting to get into these byways.</body>
</review>
