<review author="Caty" title="Saw 3" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I hope the producer, Lionsgate, not more installments of the saga, that with this brooch leaves him all tied up and well tied that not enough margin to either one single sequel more, but of course, when a tape is so much money, you know...</summary>
	<body>Darren Lynn Bousman, the director of Saw 3, declared in its day this new installment of the thriller that brought head half a world beyond by 2004 would appeal both to fans of the psychological terror of "Puzzle"(algo_que_predominó_en_la_excelente_primera_entrega) as fans of the rampant killing which marked the pattern of Saw II. The question is: could say that Lynn Bousman was right? Do the answer is that? almost.The first installment of Saw made really merits when presenting a plot steadfast, supported almost in a one hundred per cent in the construction of their characters. Saw 2 away something of this concept to introduce little three-dimensional characters, at the same time that boosted what, in its predecessor, just appeared: deaths and mutilations. In short: what previously was more well macabre, in this installment became something free. The result was not all bad, but it was clear that not reached or the soles of shoes of the first.Saw 3 we find elements of the previous two. The number of important characters in scene fell markedly and the script - once again signed by Leigh Whannel, one of the players by the way of the first film - gave place to both concepts. The plot follows equally bizarre and full of secrets, without forgetting the inevitable references to previous frames; that's why I notice that if not vísteis the first two, you are hardly going to learn anything. Try to see each other before to not miss in the midst of so many references. But of course, if the script returned to the characters psychological depth, mistakes in Saw 2 also campan comfortable here. The end result is that Saw 3 is greater than the second tape, even still distant from the first appearance of "Puzzle", the murderer who, if we see him carefully, does not become so. The story, as mentioned in the previous paragraphs, has many conexíones with (des them) Mr "puzzle" previous venturas. It would be impossible to crumble all the sub-plots without uncovering any surprise, so if you want to discover things for yourself, I advise you to keep not reading. When you leave the film back to these pages.If you continue here, so let's. First of all, a brief introduction to who is not very familiar with the universe of the film: "Puzzle" (portrayed by Tobin Bell) is a species of serial killer that has a peculiar habit of kidnapping people and involve them in a "games" whose goal is to run with life. Which fails to finish the game in the correct way, dies? and if concludes it (ignoring the bruises, some mutilations and some physical and psychological sequelae) comes alive learning to reassess the fact to live. Technically "Puzzle" may not be charged with murder, because that does not gets it dirty hands killing them, their "modus operandi" is manufacturing weapons and gadgets that the victims themselves who kill (or not) alone. The paradox is that "Puzzle" is considered a Savior, a man whose macabre ideas about death serve to redeem people.There are two new "victims" in Saw 3 and the novelty is that one depends on the other to finish the game successfully. The first is Lynn, a doctor who is dedicated to his profession, aside from his family and considered the best in their specialty? What leads her to "Puzzle", which is on the verge of death. Kidnapped by him, Lynn is oblicada to keep their dying existence at all costs: a full bomb around the neck collar is connected to monitor cardiac rhythm of her captor. If he dies, Lynn too it. But there is hope. "Puzzle" just wants to live until another game comes to an end. The alternative game is starring Jeff(Angus_MacFayden,_a_muchos_os_sonará_de_"Alias"), father of family, abandoned by his wife, lives only to kill the individual that, drunk, ran over and killed his son. Jeff awakens inside a large wooden box, and when you get out of it, is trapped in a casa-laberinto. You have to follow the clues provided by "Puzzle" to advance and reach the end of the challenge, where finally will be face to face with the subject that killed his son. Although we must not overlook one of the elements present in the trilogy: the character of Amanda, pupil of "Puzzle" and present during the three deliveries. Basically what I have said above could be considered the central line of the argument. There are other issues to explain, but nor is it of gutting it completely. As regards the direction of Darren Lynn Bousman, I must say that you exaggerated a lot the technical mannerisms. Mounting is accelerated and some camera movements are too rapid, have the feeling that some moments pass too quickly. Another problem is what I call "Scooby.Doo complex": with each surprise revelation, the director looks for the viewer all scenes which in turn gave clues to such disclosure, to show that everything was there, but we saw it not. It is as if Lynn Bousman had fear that the Viewer does not understand history and therefore feels obliged to explain things in detail.In short: personally I do not think that such "Puzzle" deserves to be elevated to the category of "God of the crime". In the first part, he went from being a dangerous madman with messianic aspirations. In the second, the script was to pigeonhole the role of "brilliant mind", of man misunderstood by society, of the Hannibal Lecter or John Doe and style in this third is a mix of both, but clearly specify. "It isn't that much, import the truth."Saw 3 "is worthily represented as a thriller tense, with a couple of really hilarious scenes (the scene of the operation and liquefied pigs) and also worthy ending for the crazy killer"Puzzle". I only hope that the producer, Lionsgate, does not make further installments of the saga, that with this brooch leaves him all tied up and well tied that not enough margin to either one single sequel more, but of course, when a tape is so much money, you know?</body>
</review>
