<review author="Jose Contreras" title="Happy feet" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Mumble Happy Feet begins as the ugly duckling. In a world of singing penguins, he can't sing, knows to move his feet. You will learn how to sing and be one Penguin or will demonstrate the value of their individual art? Okay, I accept that the outcome was sung.</summary>
	<body>Aesop, La Fontaine, Iriarte, the three liked do talk to the animals to thrill to humans, usually at the expense of morals. Morals are past fashion, those cocks dry, cigarette ashes, as it called Juan Ramón, already dislike. Cartoons bugs we enthuse with their journeys rather than their lessons.Mumble Happy Feet begins as the ugly duckling. In a world of singing penguins, he can't sing, knows to move his feet. You will learn how to sing and be one Penguin or will demonstrate the value of their individual art? Okay, I accept that the outcome was sung. But the film offers much more. "Happy Feet" is not only worth seeing because it exceeds the roll of la moraleja. It is interesting by the social background. There is a conflict between the singing penguins and other smaller breed that is bent by Cubans. And the conflict is narrated in music form. The singing penguins do ballads, while small bring mambo and Latin rhythms. So the leaders of the tribe were priests and defenestran to the mischief elements of the herd. Here begins the journey of the hero, a narrative schema which has not stopped working since the Odisea.La reading of the final is the most modern, speaks of the power of communication to change societies and transform the world.There are many things for an hour and a half, and a reasonable price. All calling us the movie is to forget what are all these dances and songs: are the result of a tradition that begins with Fred Astaire passes by the Beach Boys Michael Jackson and the Blues and comes to Ricky Martin. They are not voices emerging from inside of each Penguin and with which expresses its interior.</body>
</review>
