<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Harry poter y el caliz de fuego" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It is not perfect, it is not wonderful, but it is more than enough to have us attached to the Chair during their more than two hours and a half of duration.</summary>
	<body>Even recognizing that I've never been a great fan of the adventures of the young Wizard, I must admit that Harry Potter is one of the greatest social-century phenomena. On the one hand, Rowling books have managed to start to millions of children in reading than in the times in which we live is quite longer. And on the other hand, the film adaptations of his novels have dragged huge masses of not so children rooms.This fourth installment could be the more accurate translation of the book which is based, but perhaps why lack you certain connection between their scenes, which means that at times give us the impression of being a sort of stories that occur, instead of a whole. The central thread turns, as I guess that many already know, on the International Quidditch Cup, a tournament of magic to three schools and the return of Aquel-that-not-should-be-Nombrado.Es the first time that a British director Mike Newell (four weddings and a funeral), directs a film of this saga, and is noticeable in many respects, as a way of marking the tempo of the film. That Yes, if someone his remaining doubts, have to say that this is not a particularly appropriate for children film, as well as its predecessors. Moreover, the action scenes, full of epic, sautéed with great special effects and a few dialogues of considerable height are appreciated. Daniel Radcliffe (Harry Potter) continues to grow as an actor (obviously his physical growth), and the presence of Ralph Fiennes contributes to luster, once again, the adventures of the young Wizard. It is not perfect, it is not wonderful, but it is more than enough to have us attached to the Chair during their more than two hours and a half of duration.</body>
</review>
