<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Casanova" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Lacks it a bit of dynamism, what may be due to the little habit of Hallström to direct comedy, anyway, to have a good time, is an acceptable option.</summary>
	<body>It seems that the life of Casanova is one of these inexhaustible sources that supply the producers and directors to make one version after another. On this occasion, responsible for this has been the Swedish, Lasse Hallström, who already occupied this space a few months ago with "An unfinished life" and that he has a long career in American industry with famous titles such as "Chocolat" or "Las rules of the House of the cider".In carrying out its work, which we must not forget that this is a light comedy and not a historical film, has had an interesting cast, headed by Heath Ledger (Brokeback Mountain, the Grimm brothers or Knight's fate), Jeremy Irons (what about this giant of interpretation) and Sienna Miller, who garnered covers last year to be victim of infidelity of your partner, Jude Law, with the nanny. This time, the master of seduction and the costume is infatuated with a young Venetian writer who dedicated their time and efforts to distribute pamphlets feminist. The surprise, above all for himself, arises when Francesca refuses, which will cause the indignation of the character, which will try to overcome himself pursues one plan after another for approaching his beloved. Special mention deserves, as almost always serving, Jeremy Irons, who masterfully plays a villain of the time. With everything and with that, the movie lacks a bit of dynamism, what may be due to the little habit of Hallström directing comedy, that always moved more comfortable in genres more profound and far-reaching, though in the background behind a critique of moral hypocrisy of those who sought to Casanova by rake when reallyIt seems that it was more envy than another feeling which aroused in them, clerics and ultra-conservative to the world and depraved burghers in the intimacy. In any case, to have a good time, it is an acceptable option.</body>
</review>
