<review author="José A. Peig" title="Perros de paja" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Many inspirations and varied notes deserves and distills the viewing of this flawless film of Sam Peckinpah, an impressive construction of a social conflict of ideas and forms of principles against the instincts and what leads us to detach ourselves from any Convention.</summary>
	<body>"Straw dogs", shot to the convictions of enlightened consciousness and centuries of "humanizador" effort (why exclude violence of our psychological and biological background as a species if it has always shaped our humanity?), narrative earthquake in pursuit of sharp consequences in superb development of a specific atmosphere of indeterminate hatred, dehumanization in a loop of unfortunate and events sponsored by a climate of tense ambiguity. As when you presientes the hidden Wolf in the shadows and just to wait for the cluster of events to explode in a terrible truth. Urban nightmare, an unexpected hero, x-ray of violence history.Many inspirations and varied notes deserves and distills the viewing of this flawless film of Sam Peckinpah, an impressive construction of a social conflict of ideas and forms of principles against the instincts and what leads us to detach ourselves from any Convention.The idea part of something as well as a western urban, outlining a choral film in which occur within CITES different personajes-modelo: the American and his wife residing in a paragraph home, the gang of thugs, the mafia boss, the representative of the law, the victim and the verdugo innocent. It is astonishing to see as, even basing the typology of characters in very trite clichés, manages to overcome and enlarge this dimension to a range of gestures, thoughts and human emotions of enormous extent. The central character, the American WIMP played by Dustin Hoffman, strong supporter of law and rationality, this endowed with enormous complexity, complexity built with an ambigüo appear, an uncertainty in the confrontation against the adversities which progressively leads to an almost eerie metamorphosis, generated by an accumulation of acts of violence which oblige a makeshift restructuring of mental schemes. Shocking the subject is the path from the containment and initial coldness (correction in forms attitudinal and avoidance of conflict) until a final climax of authentic Madness (value and destruction, giving free rein to impulses).Significant in this regard is that the structure and the construction of the story are so millimeter precise that it gives the impression of inevitability, predestined from which at the beginning was already a potentially destructive situation (whose conclusion is outlined in a feeling after the death of a cat and the first takes of weapons to go hunting)(, a disguised but latent violence representation), and here reinforces the complexity of the central character, because it is difficult to determine to what extent their actions respond to a mere impulse according to exceptional circumstances either are the product of the repressed and ultimately released with a malevolent smile of satisfaction.In a film like this, the violence is not only staple of the action, is also a formal livelihood; Assembly used to assemble the sequence of the first frames already serves as notice with regard to what is approaching in the last stretch. And the same mounting already is starting, openly violent (a tomb, cemetery, children playing in the cemetery, a dog surrounded by children, tense and furtive glances, insinuated sex, etc). In the final stretch, this frenetic montage of faces, blood, grotesque faces, arms, transmitted what already home was latent and which likewise manifests itself in a corpus of images, flat Rapids, faces, eyes of hardness and uncertainty. The overlap that occurs between the montage of the first moments of the film (in which is hinted a potential development on later sexual and violent skirmishes) and montage in its final stretch is what gives the meaning of the same; It first outlines in power, culminating in fact. Containment is behind life and dynamism to the deployment carried out between party and party.The secondary cast, far from becoming a mere "padding", thanks to a masterful exercise in construction of characters, extends to a real and poignant humanity as life itself; see the scene of the rape, mix - happy redundancy - rape and true loving act, in which the same male instigator of the Act by a few moments, feels compassion and appreciation by and the situation of distress suffered by his companion, asking that not forced you to make use of the brutality, which will eventually give up and fold to a relationship that goes beyond a forced sexual act. And not to mention the dubious malignancy of a kept cabezilla motivated by the disappearance of his daughter.No topics, but a humanity encompassing all the x-ray of gruesome acts. Here, nor the bad guys are so bad, nor the good are so good, and why we we have a superb film in the realization, pace and Assembly, in the creation of a (rarefied) atmosphere of concern sustained from beginning to end, and in addition to all that (which is already enough), a Fund of enormous complexity, open to many readings and interpretations with regard to the law, the order, the defence of the oppressed, taking the law into their own hands, the debate about a possible use legitimate (?) of the violence.It is not a film that attempts to justify violence. It seeks neither to denounce. As it has been pointed out, the movie goes far beyond nailing their look in a scrupulous and comprehensive statement of facts (with a meticulous chain of causes and effects of a logic quite forceful, without denying that always can be discussed if the final transformation of the central character is believable or too much forced), pointing in many directions but manipulate the point of view of the spectator for none in particular what that final smile and disregard? by the unknown path?. The gaze of Peckinpah is an atonal harshness: things are simply, as they happen. Beyond everyone with his conscience. And without losing sight that is the sense of responsibility aware of the protagonist to the danger of beating of its rugged host what move you to use violence to protect him, in the name of reason and after the assassination of the sole representative of the law. Or that only an excuse?. Devastadora.para Finally, a reflection of part of a movie buff desperate: "Straw dogs" is commercial cinema, despite his intellectual maturity and the ambigüo of its ultimate meaning. It tells a story which in its more superficial lines can be understood by all types of public and keeps the suspense without ups and downs. And hence wanted to I go to stop; It is a perfect example of commercial film of high quality art, something very hard to find in the current Billboard. And from here I ask and demand the film God that punished the instigators of current conformism and banal mechanization that driving the process of creation and production of the film today, devoid of intellectual or artistic values. Tell interesting stories, but they are not more than the topic. "Straw dogs" is constructed with stereotypes, but managed with ease and multidimensionality. Is it so hard?. In our days, when one goes to the movies, has the impression that you are telling the same story with the same cliches. And I'm already sick.</body>
</review>
