<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Ciudad de Dios" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Holgado footage Meirelles leads with sobriety, without ever falling into free show a dramatic, unarmed context, instrumentalized and greedy violence for the accidental Viewer that creates watching a game of revenge.</summary>
	<body>The South American cinema road is paved with obstacles, but inevitably thrives, hangovers to the international balcony and ends up being desetiquetado film, orphan of parochial clichés, although his scripts to talk about what they have close and retraten life that have opposite.City of God is a masterpiece of South American cinema or the Brazilian film, but gives equal citizenship. Her would have liked theirs a Peckinpah high hours or the Scorsese with the Verve of the 1970s. We don't know if we are seeing a rapid cinema session of gangster to use or a western syncopation with urban scenarios of a 20th century already almost cancelled.More than three hundred characters of the novel of 600 and peak pages of Paulo Lins, I've not had the pleasure of reading, but I imagine addictive and deleitosa as tape, give to a loose footage Meirelles leads with sobriety, without ever falling into free show a dramatic, unarmed context, instrumentalized and violence greedy for the accidental Viewer that creates watching a game of revenge and shady environments to the Tarantino.Impresiona the likelihood of what we are seeing. One is very accustomed to watch American movies and to grant it merits, prestige and medals without any margin of uncertainty: City of God is probably the film more credible than this cronistahaya seen in a long time.Relates without modesty and restraint the birth of organized crime in the city of God, a neighborhood of Rio de Janeiro. The rapporteur, the omniscient eye, the demiurge of this choral, Greek, story times, is Buscapé, a child decides on the fringes of crime and who knows, in the background, sensitive, tender, artist. None of these labels at since well started the movie torcerán one iota: Buscapé fatigue the favela: a world of weapons of narco-trafficking bands subjected to strict codes of conduct and police purchased populate his universe.Articulated in three distinct parts, which can be seen without solution of continuity or rows in the plot that shows. That hopscotch oeuvre, the referenced elements come to a well known film, which feeds and to which taxed a tribute single, crude, almost invisible, but recognizable if they handled similar keys. It is the Italian neorealism (I saw the black-and-white films of De Sica in many episodes). It is the western (there is an epic of the revenge of the persecution of the destination as a single recognizable symbol in the lives of all her characters). It is Coppola, very tangentially, and his triumphant Godfather. Tarantino, it is inevitably with his urban Madness with its Vertigo of blood and grammatical thicket.Three decades ranging through the screen: all contain a label of the House: camera in hand, deliberate interruption of the consummation of a scene to finish later, desirability of artistic creativity and the Assembly. Buscapé is seeing how their world is crumbling: how your friends are falling and how Street ras is resolved differences among its neighbors. He only has a camera: his eyes are the camera and the lens is delivering us surprising, amazing images.Impresses, by unusual in European or (even more) American film contest of children and adolescents as vulgar thieves or drug addicts, or assassins. : Brazil it is the favela. In this lies the subtle difference between Hollywood models and the South American. The South, this being Brazil, there is also: and as we now know with more solid evidence, with a sharper truculence. Only there to follow the life of Zé small, one of the main characters of the story, to understand the hard life in the suburbs of poverty in this Brazil occupied by the misery and survival at all costs, with all risk.Lins has in his novel: "another, homeland without compassion, wind the laughter this soil gave me, this soil reached about men with boots and tools to measure everything, to mark the Earth." Then came the machines, which razed the orchards, frightened the hobgoblins, guillotinaron trees, terraplenaron swamp, dried up the source, and this became a desert (..) Emerged the favela, the cement neofavela, formed of mouths and sinister silence, with desperate cries in the run of the streets and the indecision of the crossroads "."Nature, was probably replaced by the progress. And with him, I conclude, came the gun, drugs, hate and darkness, although all paint with a huge, sharp, perfect, Harbor light of life.</body>
</review>
