<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Happy feet" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Tremendous film of animation that won't leave anyone indifferent. We will be able to excite us, rejoice, laugh, jalear, singing and dancing without blushing. Dare, so it will be well.</summary>
	<body>Come Christmas and the producers get their best clothes to fill the cinemas with our small shoots. Worse, in many cases, focusing on light peliculillas, not inciting adult accompany their children. With this film, you've got a mix that I don't have anything clear to convezca for the elderly or children. For children I think it gives something of fear and elders are not receptive to receive criticism. In the end.The film is about an Emperor Penguin which, although egg, is falling to his father. For this reason was born with a peculiarity, not can sing like the rest of their species, but has a gift for dancing. In the society in which he lives is not well seen, is marginalized and discriminated against. One day, by chance of fate, known to other penguins, who communicate in a different way.I loved this recording, and for several reasons. On the one hand, the graphic quality is impressive, brushing the perfection. In many moments, you can doubt if we see a tape of animation or a curious documentary. The soundtrack, aspect you never mention, found it me very suitable, of those that oblige your armchair companion to draw you attention to make sure to follow the compass with the foot. The argument is not loose, from a film Billy Elliot ending with the Lord of the rings epic style. In conclusion, I would like to highlight two aspects that make it a very special film, the subtle (well, not this is subtle) criticism to the organized and hierarchical religions, and on the other hand the review that gives to human beings as regards the maintenance of natural resources and conservation. Very large. Oh, I do not forget the "Cuban" friends that is, have a few dialogues to hear party.To sum up, tremendous film of animation that won't leave anyone indifferent. We will be able to excite us, rejoice, laugh, jalear, singing and dancing without blushing. Dare, so it will be well.</body>
</review>
