<review author="José Córdoba" title="El perfume" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A stimulating, very attractive, film with an excellent invoice and a great story which perhaps lacks depth.</summary>
	<body>Comment on a film as the Perfume, the new work by the German filmmaker Tom Tykwer, is a difficult task. Since its publication in the mid-1980s, the work written by the also German Patrick Süskind has become one of the most sold and books dear history, with a huge Legion of fans, in addition to having livestock inadaptable fame. I would like to have me read the book before seeing the movie because I believe that it is necessary, not to analyze the film strictly but because subsequent reading of the novel is inevitably marked by the memory of the film adaptation. On the other hand, the prior reading of a novel often damage the viewing of his celluloid version, because our desires are usually seen disappointed. During the history of the cinema, we have witnessed countless adaptations, which usually meet much more entity has the most failed novel tends to be the film version and vice versa. Thus, films such as the godfather or shark outweigh to novels that suit, both in quality and in the memory of the people, while others such as La history forever are failed and insufficient in comparison with its literary original. A separate case would be the code da Vinci, then a novel which was supposed by many (not by me) little more than a script ready to be adapted in soon, became a film tedious and unpleasant, although that itself extremely faithful to the book, as screenwriter only bothered to adapt the novel to the film field.Thus, with so many previous negatives, Tykwer film had the losing and fortunately did not happen, because although I can not compare it with the novel, the German film is very estimable and satisfactory, with an excellent Bill and not dependent on the original text.The Perfume narrates the life of Jean Baptiste Grenouille, a young orphan in the 16th century holder of a sense of special smell France. We are witnessing its birth and growth, while you go for an owner to another and discovers and develops its amazing capacity for odors, until finally discover a perfume which becomes obsessed.They say those who have read the novel, which the author get you stay that describes in the book, using only the words and the power of the imagination. Tykwer also get something similar to basis of enhancing other two senses: sight and hearing. Thus, the director is set much details, making very close levels, maximizing what we see on screen, as wanting us to show its essence. While music, composed among others by the director himself is ethereal and obsessive, very inspired and with inspiradísimos moments. Tykwer approach in general is very classic, flat long and leisurely mounting, without resorting to the saturation. It also splatters the narrative with some oniric Visual moments, making more fluid the narration in a film that lasts about two hours and a half. The address only falters in the film's most controversial scene: the orgy orchestrated by la Fura dels Baus. This sequence is surprising and unexpected, but failed in its resolution.The script on the other hand, while it is not outstanding, does have the virtue of being 100% film, without paying excessive tolls on the translation of the novel. The positive level highlights the presentation of characters, drawn well are and in the negative, perhaps, the shallow waters. We never come to understand to Grenouille, the motor of their actions and the viewer has to put something on your side, not too, to complete certain gaps.Level performances Ben Whisaw meets more than in his difficult role of Grenouille, as well as the beautiful Rachel Hurd-Wood as his object of desire (though does not have too much scope to adequately develop the character beyond his imposing physical presence). Two stars Dustin Hoffman and Alan Rickman function also comply with its tasks, especially the first, because her character has a greater weight and the physical matter of the American actor is well suited. While Rickman can do little with the character.The technical sections are excellent, excelling the artistic direction (which gets you forget that the film is shot largely in Barcelona), such as music, magnificent, one of the best works of the year no doubt.In short the Perfume is a stimulating, very attractive movie with an excellent invoice and a great story which perhaps lacks depth.A final highlight detail is that the film is a co-production of several countries, Spain between them, running as few times usually do this kind of products, which are highly affected by tensions between the various producers.</body>
</review>
