<review author="Taliesin" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A Bond as cool as always but much less sophisticated revives the series from its ashes.</summary>
	<body>I declare I fan of the James Bond films. I admit. It brings me memories of my discovery of the film from the hand of Sean Connery in from Russia with love and it makes it far more tolerant than the rest with these rants which was suffering from the series. However, I think that I am quite just if I say that this is the best Bond in years and the rest of views that can be found in the network of networks as well attested.The arrival of Casino Royale in theaters has not been accompanied by the advertising noise that came before the premiere of the previous films starring Pierce Brosnan. This, together with the presentation of Daniel Craig as the new Bond, blond with blue eyes, predicted the final thud of the series. However, both the new protagonist and the new air that has taken the Bond universe have been shock and we can talk better delivery of the saga long. Daniel Craig plays a first-time agent, but with the hardness which requires the post. Everything remains as cool has to be Bond but with much less sophistication. Ended the Martini shaken but not removed and the poetic flirtation with the Bond girls. The dialogues as the character, bleeding more than usual to be James Bond, are credible. This does not mean that the film itself is credible, because what you see is one of the premises of the series to be incredible. What happens is that there are differences between this is incredible but both gives me and this is incredible. Damn that it fails! Casino Royale has a few scenes of those that make you grab you into the arms of the Chair and that means that the character has come to you and that you are living through their eyes.Accompanying a surprising Daniel Craig, we have Eva Green (dreamers of Bertolucci) as Bond girl, that this time is more than just a pair of tits with legs. Turn maloso is Mads Mkkelsen and is very convincing, especially in the scenes of the game of poker. Otherwise, the rest of clichés that one can expect from a Bond movie are here: a burst of infarction, persecution, explosions, cities and twists in the plot. It is not that the script is a prodigy, but it meets the expectations and is not long, which was the case in the previous installments. I miss the appearance of R, but it is one of the weights that have been left behind to lighten a package was becoming too heavy.In short, the good of Pierce Brosnan seems a Grandpa when compared with Craig Bond, much harder and less sophisticated. The bet of responsible for Casino Royale has been down to the get smart of the altars and give him a beating from reality, and the result can not be more promising.</body>
</review>
