<review author="Lara Croft" title="Syriana" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>This film is not for prizes, not fuck</summary>
	<body>When I saw the trailer for Syriana thought two things, that was a very political movie (item missed in 2005 in the films in general) and hopefully not tinted of the American self that would lay it to lose. Therefore either by Fortune or not, were not fulfilled none of the two things.It is difficult to make a summary of the story in a few lines? An American Government agent accidentally "loses" the whereabouts of a missile, a corporation of United States ago everything is at your fingertips to merge with an Arab oil and when I say everything is everything. Turn interconnected with a succession in the Government of UAE and occupational and personal avatars are an investment advisor that destiny wanted that it was planted in the middle.Syriana is the typical film in which each two or three scenes appears at the bottom of screen printing indicating the place of the world in which the action takes place, needless to say that gets to a point where you cross fingers to keep the pace. It of course as all political thriller which should explain many things and delimit the sides, the number of dialogues is thick. At times it seems that it will be water at any time but it is not, that one put the necessary concentration. Sometimes one falls in the satisfaction to see pass through the screen into the large casts, in Syriana, George Clooney, Jeffrey Wright, Matt Damon, Christopher Plummer and Chris Cooper are available and each one does exactly what he has to do. Although I regret the fact that the characters are so guys and not complete outline is never know very well what is the real driving force that generates the actions, whether they are good or bad, that reflection is not at all bad.The major point against which I can criticize you is the core of the script. As I read in United States the best reviews of the film were by the crude history and for showing courage a furious behind-the-scenes on the handling of the oil. It seems that they are the only inhabitants of the planet that were unaware of it, so from that point of view any thing stating is risky. At this point the story is guilty of pretentious.A scene that found me excellent is when one of the bosses of the company discusses with the lawyer that hinted you that the "favors" and pressures are not so good ideas as they seem to be responding to that: "corruption is our protection." Corruption is what keeps us safe. Corruption is what you and I are strutting here rather than fight between us by scraps of meat in the streets. "Corruption is by what we earn it."That Yes, this movie is not for prizes, not fuck.</body>
</review>
