<review author="Txapulin" title="Renaissance" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An interesting experiment that less complex and more understandable structure with a script would have been better.</summary>
	<body>I saw this film in the Art Futura, and it seems that it has no release date yet in Spain, although in France months ago is on DVD. The first surprise I took is that the supposed "original version" that we passed was in English, and the closing credits featured Daniel Craig (Yes, the new Bond), Catherine McCormack, Jonathan Price and Ian Holm. I surprised because I thought that this movie like A Scanner Darkly was filmed and later rotoscopeada, but no, the movie is in 3D, using motion capture for movements and a special renderer that creates the black and white effect. If we go to the page of the wikipedia of the movie, we see that Daniel Craig only has done the voices in English, a such Patrick Floersheim, French voice and Robert Dauney movements. Nothing more and nothing less than three actors for a same character. The effect is visually, awesome, although just tired the view.The movie is like a futuristic James Bond, no wonder the choice of the voice of Craig for the English version. In the year 2054 scientists seem to have discovered the fountain of eternal youth, and a company wants to keep the secret to use it for their own benefit. Our protagonist, inspector Karas discovers things that the company will try to avoid that they come to light.The plot is complex and is explained in a somewhat confusing way, and, despite the amount of (good) action (impressive persecution of cars to the Bank of the Seine) and that does not pass 1 h 40 &#8242;, made me long. The use of the technique of black and white in maximum contrast (i.e., no grayscale) seems just as free as the Rotoscoping in A Scanner Darkly. But accepting the technique as a novelty in the world of 3D animation, I want something more. Also, it must be said that there is a restricted use of the grey (in transparencies, for example) and some colors perfectly justified in certain moments of the movie.An interesting experiment that less complex and more understandable structure with a script would have been better.</body>
</review>
