<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>If the next Bond is led by a director of the good, of those who have personality, I am sure that will be the best Bond of history.</summary>
	<body>From the beginning I defended the election of Daniel Craig as the new James Bond, provided that that implied a change of course in the series. "Well, once seen"Casino Royale", the sensations are good, and despite the shortcomings, one clear conclusion: habemus Bond.""Casino Royale" is, first and foremost, a new beginning of the character and very well could have been titled "Bond Begins". As Nolan's "Batman Begins" here also shows the desire to do something different and original character. There is a special care to give a sense of narrative to several of the typical elements of the series: the initial adventure before the credits or the use of the harmony Bond at the right time.The big difference with the tape of Nolan is just that: the director. Martin Campbell is very very far of Christopher Nolan and that the film so note. Isn't Campbell do so bad, in fact it is possibly his best work, but with another director we could be talking about something big.The film is divided into three major events clearly differentiated. In the first of them almost all the action of the film is concentrated, and although entertaining, does not break the spectator, proving almost too long. That Yes, we must recognize that it is very spectacular (and why not use the typical gadgets).The second act is more leisurely and develops the characters. Do not think that it is more boring because it is not. It is a pleasure for a follower of the Bond series, attend their birth, feel more real, more credible, without losing the aura of legendary invincible get smart.The third act is the conclusion of the story and what I least like the film because the final climax is not as successful as it should be, there is some confusion in the action and any decision defícil to understand. That Yes, the last minute is priceless and leaves one eager to see a new movie with Craig as "Bond, James Bond".In short, with this film something happens that should not surprise us. There is a good writer giving the final touches to the screenplay (Paul Haggis, signatory of the scripts of "Million Dollar Baby" and "Crash") and a few good actors (among those who would deploy Judy Dench, Eva Green and an inspired Daniel Craig).In the equation of the great film only need a good director and that is where they have to throw the other producers. If the next Bond is led by a director of the good, of those who have personality, I am sure that will be the best Bond of history. "Casino Royale", if it is not, stays very close.</body>
</review>
