<review author="Silvia Giner" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Casino Royale takes place with good pace, maintains an interesting pulse with the viewer during the poker game. A very successful script to show us as James Bond became.</summary>
	<body>Director Martin Campbell, which we already entertained (and long) with "The mask of Zorro" and "The legend of Zorro" among others, surprises us now with a new sequel to the most famous secret agent James Bond. Previously he already led quite less fortunate "GoldenEye" than the current "Casino Royale".Sincerely I went to the cinema to see this movie practically forced, that in addition to not like me at all none of the previous 007 (specifically GoldenEye seemed colossal boring), but I have to admit that I found a pleasant surprise.Martin Campbell has left the skin in this film (imagine after the shit from the previous sequel), told us the story of a young Bond which premieres as a double agent zero, with its mistakes his sweat in the chest (arf arf), anyway, more humane and what I always say "believable". and who is the new macizorro? AI nenas is Daniel "pout" Craig (aaaaaa I have weakness for the blondes), an actor most secondary cases, with 47 movies under his belt, still had the opportunity to show its splendour as in this film. If my daughters is making bread and wet? Since then and with great distinction the best James Bond who has known this legend (although that carries the movie becoming pout).And who is the companion of this Stallion? (do anda? that you are willing to start the despelle) as Eva Green! Recovered from baldness who flogged his tree in "The Kingdom of heaven" becomes a pavisosa bond girl. Eva is a great actress, we like, we respect, we fell in love with in "Dreamers" has a peculiar beauty (I will skip the part where I say that we can play quietly on his forehead to pelota), but? honestly it is not the type of actress I had chosen as a bond girl, not paste anything, we are going and much less since that has thinned so much that he has that look of "I'm doing a diet that you shit and I want bread bread bread" i.e. the eyes desencajados by hunger, much better in "Dreamers", Eva, we like with curves? This role was for Evangeline Lily (lost) or Vahina Giocante (Lia says), this had been an espectacularísima-bond girl, above all for playing Vesper? anyway maybe is that Martin wanted to give a touch of sosez to this character.Casino Royale takes place with good pace, maintains an interesting pulse with the viewer during the poker game. A very successful script to show us as James Bond became. Finally note the impeccable Judy Dench, an actress who should honor urgently and that repeated along with Daniel in the continuation of "Casino Royale" whose premiere is scheduled for 2008 and which will bear the name of "Bond 22", yet by confirms bond girl and rest of cast.</body>
</review>
