<review author="Silvia" title="Borat" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I do not know until that point is worth spending the money of a film entry to see such canallada. Borat: Do the new stream of Kazakhstan?</summary>
	<body>Perhaps I expected a more damning criticism of the traditional American system. Perhaps he hoped laugh more with this surreal story that is sold as a politically incorrect comedy but is not much more that a succession of escatological gags that fall in the absolute ridiculous and evil like (even to remember me Jackass at times).For which do not yet know, Borat Sagdiyev is a fictional British television character played by Sacha Baron Cohen. Borat is considered the second most famous journalist of Kazakhstan which sent to the U.S. to learn about their culture and its political system. Thus starts the surrealist movie, whose ultimate goal seems to be criticized more traditional values and deep Americans. A more peculiar type whose hobbies are based on ping-pong, wrestling, dance music disc and shooting dogs.Borat is a controversial character, especially because it constantly expresses his anti-Semitism, his blatant misogyny (women are only for him meras prostitutes his intolerance and lack of respect for any kind of collective (dares to get even with the diminished).) However, Sacha Baron Cohen is Jewish. That is why Cohen defenders say that the attitude of Borat is not racist but that embodies a parody on anti-Semitism in American society. What isn't so clear is if majority public that will go to cinemas to see the movie, teenagers, will take it as a parody or if history will help to reinforce stereotypes and prejudices that may have with regard to the countries of Eastern Europe.Personally, what I liked most was not so much humor escatólogico nor the antics, but the fact that Sacha Baron Cohen, with his character, exposes the hypocrisy that it breathes in American society and serves as a vehicle for reflection on what we consider as a civilized society. The scene in which Borat is in the midst of deifying holding a meeting of Catholic fans is for shudder is if we stop to think that they are the same individuals who vote to Bush in the presidential election and that exasperated against Islamic fanaticism. The irreverent interviews system adopted by the atypical reporter manages to bring out the lowest misery of Americans.The last joke lies in the contradiction that the film is sweeping at the North American box office, precisely the place that history turns his criticism. The truth is that the character can not leave anyone indifferent, but I do not know until that point is worth spending the money of a film entry to see such canallada.</body>
</review>
