<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Brick" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Rare piece of contest of end of career for a talented director and Vice to assemble what, in principle, it seems extremely difficult: classic film noir and Youth Institute to the American cinema.</summary>
	<body>Brick is teen noir, rare piece of contest of end of career for a talented director and Vice to assemble that, in principle, it seems extremely difficult: classic film noir and Youth Institute to the American cinema. Brick does not exhibit the stridency of the predictable being an amateur play (almost) and for raising a very risky speech. It is supplied of a very solid approach to black, truffled film of acne of the youth hormonada with the lapel pins and posters of idols of the rap sheet in the box office of the Institute.More than the aesthetic quality of Brick, interested here in his gesta, his single Ministry of fulfilled purpose: there can be no maledicencia when assessing its depth in public, although one know, for certain, that these deviations from the norm will not make box or engolosinar producers eager to silver which are prequels and sequels, merchandising of t-shirts for August in all these products of new design whose end result is (always) puzzling and burger bar.The Viewer won't either make last in your memory this parade of thugs, rich girls and people in general, openly sinister (the character spielbergiano Luke Haas, already renewed in adult with prospects).The ingenuity of Rian Johnson makes the very abstruse investigations of its protagonist twisted sometimes seem us more important than the discovery of the reasons why his girlfriend has appeared dead. Unfinished, imperfect characters: young people without lyricism, frozen in a society without emotions in which will be leaving live, burdened by not guess what dark vices, perceived as a forced extension of adolescents talluditos, hooligan, irreverent, back lot film and without having lived still barely anything.Let it fall, without wanting to, the last stone in the pond: Brick is a creative film: appears clear and turbid, unpleasant: sacrifices the elementary exposition of events by a drawing disgresor of social class that strives to portray us, desfiguradamente.Well look, not excited, and could well be. I understand who this failed experiment he has reported Jubilee and entertainment in the same lot. To me, on the contrary, produced me an intense anxiety, boredom at times, only pleasure moments.Up the mcguffin guess incompetent. It will be that I did not have arrests for letting me lead by its bizarre argument.</body>
</review>
