<review author="Caruco" title="Grbavica" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Perhaps we do end up with bent head, but vale spending 90 minutes of our lives.</summary>
	<body>Still lingers in my memory that tragic final scene of "Germany, year zero" (1948) Rossellini. With the emotion contained, in color, and leaving the procession to go inside, we run into this Bosnia and Herzegovina, year 11, a country under construction, marked by the still recent aftermath of a war that left more than 100,000 dead, nearly two million exiles and some 40,000 women raped by the ultranationalist Bosnian Serbs.And among its ruins, human, and real estate in this Germany of the postwar period, begins a reconstruction that will affect entire generations.Do not expect any film feast in "Grbavica", rather its images are grey and everyday, that go come and go in the neighborhood of Sarajevo that gives title to the film. This and the lament of a Director, Jasmila Ebanic debutant, that not even could get a 35 mm camera. and a laboratory that roll and make the post-production of the film."The price of a trip.""Grbavica" definitely not mark any new generation of moviegoers. It is made with more desire and commitment to media and imagination. It is the cry not for quiet, less sense on a violent past and a difficult coexistence, marked by humiliation and resentment.Its history is as simple as a mother, Esma (Mirjana Karanovic), widow of war, trying to do the impossible to collect 200 euros is worth a school trip for her daughter, Luna Mijovic (Sara), of twelve years. Do a fee that would go you to half price if he could certify that her husband is a? shahid?, a martyr of the war, but that she, by some mystery, can not get.And it is the story of a rebellious teenager with cause, Sara, he begins to notice the first effects of love in a script that, on the other hand, eludes the Vulgarisation of this aspect in which fall most of commercial production of consumption fast.Essentially portentosa is the interpretation of Esma, usual actress of Emir Kusturica, who can convey all the details of affection, weariness or outrage that entails. Especially in some revealing moments of his character.Thousands of Esmas.Esma, a still attractive widow, which nevertheless refuses to erotizar, as advised a him companion of the nightclub where he works, to attract men or clientele. ESMA, a dedicated mother, but that appears to not bear too well physical contact with his daughter, for instance, lying on the ground while playing, or when the girl decides to cut the nails. ESMA, a fragile woman but which reacts however enraged against her suitor, the bully Pelda (Leon Lucev), when he defends it of aggression, because she hates violence more than anything.And like her, thousands. Although only show us a few, which meet at a local in the neighborhood to try to exorcise nightmares that I hope none of us need to wake up ever."Lost between their faces, that girl of twelve years, delighted to have a gun in his hands, kissing for the first time to their noviete, but it also begins the painful path toward understanding, and that also means maturity.""Grbavica" is one of those movies that perhaps makes us put an end to the bent head, but it is worth spending 90 minutes of our lives.</body>
</review>
