<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="The holiday" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>When the film takes a vacation. Christmas fever Ray in the collective madness, and the Mecca of cinema, as broadcaster for American values sometimes, is dedicated to sell to the rest of unhappy his vision of the festivities.</summary>
	<body>Some months ago we warned of the need to create a new genre or subgenre in cinema, the Christmas films. Before the Chronicle, and if continues much more will become terminal, lack of original ideas in Hollywood (either by lack of original proposals or because no one dares with them), all kinds of prefabricated films proliferate like mushrooms. In United States by the Christmas fever Ray in the collective madness, and the Mecca of cinema, as broadcaster for American values sometimes, is dedicated to sell to the rest of unhappy his vision of the festivities. A vision where everything is pink color, people laughing in the streets and there is no hint of despair or concerns.And for more inri, if responsible for that message in a movie is Nancy Meyers, known pastry, the end result can be truly devastating. In his previous work, when least you as you wait, showed his ability for sweetening a tape during its first hour was entertaining and rarely, fun. It is unlikely that perhaps, just perhaps, Jack Nicholson and Diane Keaton collaborate in the potability of the film. But back to what now concerns us, these holidays; Amanda (Cameron Diaz) and Iris (Kate Winslet) are two women who have virtually nothing in common, except that both have suffered recent disappointments in their relationships. Through the internet, they exchange lives, taking a well deserved holiday. The proposal is rather simple, as it was hoped, the script there is no where grasp it, lacks of grace, which in the case of a romantic comedy should not be cause for astonishment. Characters of encephalogram flat, not to mention the situations, as predictable as if the viewer has a crystal ball in his hands. As if few were the incentives to run and not look back, more than two hours of footage are able to break down the viewer more hardened in such combat the height is everything around the character of Elli Wallach, a real subplot of helping one's neighbor and improvement made in USA. Against such background, they can do anything Cameron Diaz and Kate Winslet, absent from beginning to end, or a lost Jude Law.Pero must acknowledge a point in favor of holiday. Before the proximity of food excesses of the holiday season, those attending the film will end up with so dulcificadas arteries, which the only seeing a few candies or marzipan cause them cold sweats and a few impulsive desire to put land of through.</body>
</review>
