<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Camino a la perdición" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Road to perdition is film noir. Pure cinema. Sam Mendes appears when you make a film, you do it big. And to tell the truth, it succeeds.</summary>
	<body>The film is precisely characterized by an art where abound all kinds of genres. Historias.hay many. And also of all kinds. And in what regards the film noir, of course that there are. But, how long it was that he did not write and above all ran so well a feature film as well? And with these fantastic interpretations?Road to perdition is film noir. Pure cinema. Sam Mendes appears when you make a film, you do it big. Do and to tell the truth, the consigue.¿Por what? Because it has an interesting plot. Because it accompanies a proper soundtrack. Because it has an excellent picture. Because he knows all the resources. Because you know you do.And while the home may be rather slow, since the time the story begins, this leisurely pace has moments of great intensity and emotion. The details are great. Fans and non-fans of the genre will enjoy her because Mendes knows how to combine the prevailing severity of the film with touches of brilliant, own of the greats, with a paterno-filial relationship that drives the story, and that despite the marked coolness, manages to thrill.The way of shooting and the story is so perfectionist, it leads to believe that the director really made with the film he wanted, as he saw in his mind: he took advantage of to the maximum the screenplay by David Self, and gave him a longer personal touch, because after seeing your last address in Jarhead, can say that the footprint of the director is considerable in his films. And the truth is that precisely wrong not him he's gone: it seems that you can make each film to lead, magnificent works.And it is one of the pillars of the film is the interpretations section. It has a luxurious cast, in which each of the performers outboard its role. Excellent Paul Newman, Jude Law great and very correct Daniel Craig. But without a doubt, the best of all is the incredible performance of Tom Hanks, which marks their best record to date, full of expressions and gestures truly admirable, convincing, and that not everyone can be reached. A pleasant surprise. A success.Because in reality, we have one of the best black films of recent times. A luxury. A work of art. Cinema of truth.</body>
</review>
