<review author="Iñigo" title="Truman Capote" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Up the own Truman Capote reaches bore</summary>
	<body>A new biopic comes to the big screen. And another biopic, as it would not be otherwise, an Oscar winner. It seems that there was a strange deal with the Academy which had to go forced per year, at least, a film of such characteristics. It has already become a constant which, incidentally, he starts to get bored. Amen to be indicative of a worrying lack of ideas that it denotes, the truth is that many of them, usually arrive with a very dubious quality, only underpinned by the presence of a striking interpretation or recreation of the famous character in question.But maybe with "Capote" is a little different. Although, really, not so much. Once again, the biography (or some portion of it) a famous character or that arouses curiosity, tells us in a way that is dangerously near the telefílmico tone. The truth is that the person of Truman Capote was eccentric and curious enough to arouse curiosity and interest in an audience eager to obtain data to explain the reasons for their actions. For this reason, "A cold blood", the well-known book created by the character before us, could be an ideal accompaniment to the film for squeezing juice from Capote to the maximum. Unless it is a staunch interested in knowing in detail the ravings of the man, really, is don't need the book to guess the future of the film. Truman Capote was not as eccentric or unpredictable as he made us believe. It was, simply, a self-worshiping complacent who grew up with the abandonment by fellow elevated himself to a status already, and as much as he intended to identify with people that made him remember his terrible childhood to earn greater recognition, not allowed change to the position of the affected.With the automasturbación as a standard bearer, Capote had allowed (rather was in a position to do so) manipulate which puppet to those people who were part of the lower society, killing each other for survival. I could use them to increase their already disproportionate ego and achieve a story that would never be forgotten and posicionaría his name in the annals of analytic history: narrating more sobering reality with all kinds of detail, surpassing even the most fierce fiction.Really, the movie is filmed in a way somewhat cold and dry, which manages certain aseptic character and not her positions on any side in particular. The camera observes and analyzes the confessions of their protagonists. But it is also true that, in an effort to try to understand the character, falls a little into his own trap. Capote is portrayed so well that we cannot avoid feeling different feelings toward his person.From the deepest revulsion to be so selfish and opportunistic, until some pity. Although he fails that their acts are covered with the blanket of their uncertain fate. A destination, on the other hand, very predictable. Because, in essence, is not more than the umpteenth mantra facing the poor and to the rich, while confronting their feelings and being sentenced at the same time, by the same.It was not surprising that someone so unstable emotionally as Capote ended succumbing to the weight of the alcohol and the condemnation of their own acts by betraying their deepest feelings towards to elevate his pride above the average. And Philip Seymour Hoffman details in a remarkable way the dramatic construction of Truman Capote.El actor performs a minimalist and study detailed almost until the perfection of the character. Concluding with a closeness so amazing as dangerous, due to the risk of being labeled as simple mimic. Anyway, work is obvious and Oscar more than deserved, not simply for this role but by the final recognition of his amazing and versatile career as a exceptional second. Who does not remember the great and amazing gay in "Boogie Nights" or nurse "magnolia". Paul Thomas Anderson has always recognized the immense talent of one of the best and most versatile actors of the current panorama.In short, and if with the exception of the work of Philip Seymour Hoffman, the film isn't in a mere interesting document which is, surely, the most important vital portion (for consequences) of the character in Capote. The other characters are not properly profiled and the history is a little diluted with the analysis of the protagonist. Everything ends in a ballast devoid of interest and too flat, cold and, in essence, failed. As the movie and its irregular construction causes a bump a bit difficult to overcome in relation to the "tempo" of the film. Up the own Truman Capote becomes bored.</body>
</review>
