<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="El Pianista" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A gem of a film. One of the best films of the last decade. The conjunction Polanski/Brody make that "The pianist" is one of the best films and performances of the last decade.</summary>
	<body>Few are films nor books, that have been made about Jewish stories of the nazi era. But despite this abundance, the truth is that we are particularly and with the permission of the rest, with two big films. One of them is "The list of Schlinder" by Steven Spielberg. The other is "The pianist" by Roman Polanski. While the two are true cinema, I tend towards the second.It is curious that both managers have Jewish origin. Or not. But the truth is that, thanks to this facet, both get deeply connect with the spectator. "And regret that the subject invites ello.es undoubtedly its quality as directors what comes to qualify them as such.""The pianist" is cinema in its purest form. It impresses you, hits you, makes you sentir.vivo. Numerous and well-known are the stories of Jews who lived through the Holocaust. But there are many possible ways to transmit them and Roman Polanski has done the best possible.Polanski tells the story of the great Polish pianist Wladyslaw Szpilman (Adrien Brody) who, like millions of Jews, suffered the consequences of Nazism. The film shows, from the vision of a single person, life in the Warsaw ghetto and his subsequent survival. Without loss of detail, all the cruelty we show as what they are, or were, reality.Viewed from inside, ghetto with his hardness. It is inevitable to not feel a strong connection with the protagonist as the story progresses. Not only for the great performance which saw Adrien Brody the Academy Award for best actor and his consecration as such, but also to see situations that has soportar.que must live and the director has managed to translate so brilliantly, taking him to also get the Oscar for that address.Uses their own experiences to add more details and realism to the film because many of the scenes featured in the film, when Szpilman and his family moved to the ghetto, were lived by the own Polanski.La film can be divided into two halves: the first, magnificent, more focused on life in the ghetto, in trying to convey how it was, through the experiences of our pianist and his family. In the second part, equally splendid, Szpilman becomes the center of the story: we see the passing of the events from their eyes, we heard by his ears (something in what the director intended to emphasize, as when momentarily loses the hearing to a nearby bomb), ultimately, makes us feel what he feels, live what he lives.And you get it. And not only with the technical and personal direction that the director gives, but also by having an actor of the stature of Adrien Brody, who took the role, who learned piano to interpret some fragments of the works of Chopin which featured in the film so seriously lost 15 kilos and even sell part of their property and live alone to feelat least in a manner roughly, who lived Spilzman. Gestures, the voz.tantos are the details that Brody plays so brilliantly that they make the film win integers, although them already had won.Music deserves special mention. The soundtrack of the film is exclusively of works by Chopin, whose romantic and drama-laden notes add the perfect touch to the already on its impressive setting of the film. The melodies of the composer are fantastically performed by Janusz Olejniczack, and fits in each of the situations experienced by Szpilman, to the point of getting a perfect identification between the two.In short: the Polanski/Brody conjunction makes "The pianist" one of the best films and performances of the last decade.</body>
</review>
