<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="La vida es bella" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A point of view different from the Holocaust... not too credible but that it is a hymn to life.</summary>
	<body>I had heard wonders of this film, and to tell the truth, it is a gift, especially at this time so commercial and superficial.eso Yes, in a sense, and much to my regret, they disappointed me some things, because expected me a real masterpiece and I found a beautiful film although not so well mounted.To tell the truth, it is a story of impeccable script in its content and its way to present it. Without a doubt, the title of the film shows the message: the most beautiful film is flawless and commendable attitude of the father (great Roberto Benigni, showing its good do in comedy, in a role which earned him to get the Oscar for best actor), which manages to create true emotion in the Viewer.But precisely what let me down was the way in which mounted: there are certain scenes which note too that we have a film to fiction, and I do not think that this is what precisely locate the film. Let me explain: does not seem certain reactions are shown to House too exaggerated? little natural? I am referring to some as the constant of Dora, wife of Guido, surprise faces when it makes its appearances: as if only a map which shows the face of surprise was shot, and then continues the film. The truth is that it doesn't fit, and does lose a little. The touches of comedy have his grace, although the vast majority are predictable, which is not to say that you lose, because as I have said, as a whole the film is great.Also consider certain things to be little credible: that never found the child (even when he escapes and is in the area where they have working Jews), who get to speak for the megaphone without any guard. And the truth is that the film does not want to show cruelty to the Jewish people during World War II, at least not as much as in others (read two works of art like 'La Schlinder list or the pianist').In fact, and again I repeat, 'life is beautiful' is characterized by being a beautiful film, using much of the scenes of the child to make us truly feel admiration for the figure of Guido and an incredible shame about the situation that have pass. It's an essential film, which could have become a true masterpiece if they were not so exaggerated and pretentious at times.But seriously, I can assure you that I liked enough, especially dealing with the history of the Holocaust from a totally different point of view...so much so that it seems so they have to spend Guido and his son does not affect the whole of the Jewish people, but that focuses exclusively on them.</body>
</review>
