<review author="Txapulin" title="Brick" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We must save the small obstacle of the use of a narrative structure of film noir already in disuse that, addition, does not fit with the scenario of secondary of the film school, but at the same time, this is his greatest achievement and originality: return us the memory of the great films of the 1940s and 1950s.</summary>
	<body>We have a movie in puzzling even for those who are accustomed to seeing film noir classic. It is not difficult to imagine a lone private detective, no family and few friends, or a femme fatale self-destructive. These characters are normal in an atmosphere of film in black and white of the 1940s. But when they set us the history at a secondary school, with issues of drugs, murder and revenge, as it bewilders. It is hard to believe how the class nerd gets to investigate a murky issue in which his ex-girlfriend has gotten with the bad of the class. Clear that her could have explained to us as an episode of Beverly Hills, 90210, but if we have a history of film noir and a few characters in film noir, and above, an homage to the classic film noir, we do because we have to tell the tale as if film noir, although we are in the environment of a secondary school. The narrative point of view also is very classic, we know exactly what he knows the main character, and that is why, at the beginning we do not understand anything, then the plot is somewhat complex, but the puzzle is solved masterfully and everything fits, especially those hidden motivations of the characters to guess to understand them.To highlight the script, performances and the beauty of Nora Zehetner, photography and the use of so many details (hear the synchronized sound of footprints in a Chase just prior to our protagonist remove shoes or insistent comparison of lyrics between the post-up our protagonist receives) that invite a review to discover what else offers this film.Total, that we must save the small obstacle of the use of a narrative structure in disuse that, moreover, does not fit with the scenario of the film, but that, in turn, that is his greatest achievement and originality: return us the memory of the great films of the 1940s and 1950s.</body>
</review>
