<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Nausicaä del valle del viento" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Another film of Miyazaki's essential viewing for children, to see if they can avoid the inevitable. The years have not cheated a shred of validity.</summary>
	<body>There are films that have a life outside the same projection which gives almost to another film. For example, this is based on a comic of seven deliveries made the teacher many years ago. They managed to persuade him to take her to the film, only the first two volumes. Reached Spain and the Legion do censors? He decided to shorten its duration, cutting more environmentalist party. Not content with this, they decided to give him enhancements to the theme, how to change the name to the protagonist calling Sandra instead of Nausicaä. By the way, to see it whole, in Japanese (that if, subtitled).The film is a girl that travels in a glider powered device and delves into a strange forest. Toxic clouds and insects as ones campan by rampant. In these it is a kind of shedding of an insect like a House and takes home the cornea. While he discovers the owner and manages to talk with him. Later going to the village, we discovered that she is a Princess and that the world is cursed because of the usual human beings.Watch that it is years old tape and this genius already spoke of such modern terms such as ecology and respect for nature. Through this recording shows the worst of the human race and in a crude way shows what the planet can result. While this goes to hell by our fault, we are still fighting everything with the force. The animation is correct, especially taking into account that the recording is 70. And the argument very interesting, though very hard, with a dramatic, although viewed with tenderness and optimism veneer. Perhaps up too.In short, another film of Miyazaki's essential viewing for children, to see if they can avoid the inevitable. The years have not cheated a shred of validity.</body>
</review>
