<review author="Rafa Ferrer" title="El código Da Vinci" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A good way to translate a bestseller on screen. And now also widespread.</summary>
	<body>It is difficult to talk about a film when you take a couple of days reading criticism, some better, others worse, but not leave you indifferent, when I entered the room, was almost as "pig to slaughter" by dragging feet and thinking that I was not going to like what I was going to find, and what is worse than the 13? input (mine and that of my companion) would not deserve the show referred to on screen.Nothing could be further from my intention, the tape I liked, some changes are logical for the narration on screen (of a book to film things change does that not?), but in general terms the tape like convinces and Moreover, to finish at my meeting more than one has escaped a round of applause.Tom Hanks restrained, nor much or little, go, that it outboard or convinces, perhaps most his partner Audrey Tautou, who still see as "Amelie" (mention besides that insufferable dubbing with French accent that sometimes was ridiculous), Jean Reno, its online, as always making the role to which we are accustomed, Alfred Molina normalito, my two favorites Paul Bettany (plasma a Silas as he imagined it when I read the book) and Ian Mckellen)(which although does not make us forget his role as Gandalf), is the character most vivacious of the film.Quite achieved special effects, special mention when Langdom gets to "ruminate" or mixing of the Flashback with narration which I loved; and another thing to note is the excellent score of Hans Zimmer full of melodies that give the film a mysterious air.A good way to translate a bestseller on screen.And with regard to the extended edition: once seen the film, and now, with the DVD Edition, and Recalling my Moon of honey by Paris and London (scenarios where the action takes place), I have been pleased to find me with places where I was 3 months ago.The film quite beats the scenes added, giving another view the characters a lot more deeper and closer to the novel, as I said at the time, the transfer of the book to the film always is complicated, since many things are left in the dark. Finally, a way to revisit this film thanks to the DVD media.</body>
</review>
