<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="El último tango en París" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The last tango in Paris is authentic film, although I don't know exactly what this mean: perhaps it is authentic because it gives no answers to open questions. This is the life of any form.</summary>
	<body>What happened to the last tango in Paris is reasonable unmatched in any other film of quality: they prevailed in some images in our collective memory and the rest are erased.The elevator where lovers are a vitamin lúbrico has been. Pubic very black and roughness of Jeanne (Maria Schneider), its often body, short legs, her face of girl and her big tits has been. The humiliation of the butter has been. The sunny apartment, his half solitude and its stark empty has been.What has been lost is a symbology, the spirit of Utopia, his literature. The background of his characters has been lost: the madness of his exisencia, the sad beauty of the stories that, in line with the meeting of the lovers, are composing the portrait of a world in decline, ridiculed by Bertolucci in the figure of the amateur director, filmmaker Jeanne pedante-novio, which represents what the own Bertolucci hated: the slimy filmpedantic and realistic at the time. Has someone thought about Goddard?The political commitment of Bernardo Bertolucci is dressed in the echo of the French may of their student revolts of the cultured and solidarity innocence of their liberated young. They were times in which culture was handled, perhaps for the first time in the 20th century, as a weapon and the words were thrown as bullets. What makes Paul (a cool Marlon Brando) is to talk about: their inner torment is verbalized, shamelessly informed the niña-amante that has been found and shared with him the loneliness, anonymity, as if they were ghosts.The last tango in Paris is authentic film, although I don't know exactly what this mean: perhaps it is authentic because it gives no answers to open questions. This is the life of any form. Paul is a tormented, a be vandalized (has enviduado; his wife has committed suicide, and does not want to build a new world) and a soul in continuous punishment that does not need to redeem itself, but that lampa to find someone with whom letting die, who entrust their most intimate litany. And then it appears when the sex and is in his grammar of sweat and silences where Paul and Jeanne achieved a full communication. Eros and Tanatos, embroidered on sex, as I said Serrat in the ' COPLA ' of their gigs the span, the eternal story of good and evil, of light and its reverse, not scary necesaramente life and death: this is what hides under clothing lovers, on the ground of the Parisian apartment with sunlight invading the screen."Amazed that the years have not subtracted one iota of strength to this film: a love more visceral by expereincia which means viewing has overcome its message, although it has all the papaletas to lose because it is very fundamentally, a need of a precise time film and understood that viewers who saw him in his Premiere were one greater amazement, a deeper reverence,.""Fucking God," says Paul under a bridge while a train passes. Paul does not want to know anything about the past of his casual lover. There are no names. There is no story. There is epidermis. There is a reshuffle has given enough headaches to the repressed and the prevailing censorship to have this film as the head of sin, with the voluptuous image of Jeanne in the bathtub, enjabonado by the hieratic Paul, burned in a winter afternoon tristísima and beautiful.Not shocked as then, thanks to the God beneath the bridge that Paul insulted, but leaves a sediment of anguish, stinging in the soul, which is where most escuecen all things.Words of philosophers of mesa camilla as nihilism and Existentialism to a simple remembrance of a dramatic Erotica or erotic drama film, but sex is the vehicle so that these characters touch the sky or touch bottom and end up in glory or hell. It matters little. Paris, however, taking many films, have this as a firm of its aura of decadent romantiscismo flag. Chapter necessarily apart is the Arch of social influence that the film produced at that time: I'm still fascinated by backed, parochial pathos of those españolitos in perpetual erection (Franco had missed inhibitors of the libido in the marshes was inaugurating) which were to the South of France to see a pussy and tits, sorry for the semantic recess, moreover, very useful. And above they spoke in French.These now are different times and others are the patetismos, provincial or not, that we inhabit, but one was paradigmatic of a situation embarrassing, obscurantist pollítica. Seems, in any case, the delay is already being souvenir in our history and all are in these days of openness in social and moral good awards for the liberal talente of our Government. Time was. Time will in future probably not distant to assess if we ran much or in the race we lost something valuable. It is then very difficult to us back, reandar the path and sharpen the view to see what lost.This is a simple film critic, a note about the past, not a furious editorial on the progress and their vices in a newspaper with circulation much editorial.</body>
</review>
