<review author="Taliesin" title="Crash" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The best that has gone through the cinemas this year</summary>
	<body>There is nothing new that made film products in USA are low hours. There are only a handful of titles that manage to get us out of the boredom that tend to produce us remakes, salads of clichés and commercial cinema. These titles often come from more or less new directors, few are the gods of cinema capable of doing something different. This is the case of Crash and its director, Paul Haggis, who comes from the world of television and has made his debut with this film that was shot during 2003 (after having written the script for Million Dollar Baby). Crash is situated in Los Angeles, one of the cities with greater racial mixture of United States (and may that worldwide). This mix causes conflict on a daily basis among white, poor blacks, rich black, Arab, Hispanic, Oriental. It's communities with many differences that are forced to share the same vital space and survive day to day face the adversities. The protagonists of Crash are walking stereotypes: the Black Brothers, dedicated to the crime; the racist white policemen, one of them pair and the other is not; Arabic, which is not willing to integrate into the Western culture; the rich black, which can be more racist than a white; the white politician, who only sees the black community as a sack of votes. All of them will live different stories that at some point will intersect at some point in the streets of Los Angeles. Depending on the situation, each of them will be the worst or the best carry inside, what the director seems to want to say that different people are so many things that unite them as separating them. Aesthetically, Crash reminiscent Traffic, which also shares the rhythm and the development of the different stories. Although some interpretations are remarkable, especially Matt Dilon in the role of police and Don Cheadle in the detective, the strong point of this film is the script (not in vain Higgis have more tables as a writer than as a director). If you have to put a but, is that it starts with a crude realism and is transforming into a history of almost happy ending more sweetened, losing some of the credibility on the way. Crash is the best who has gone through the cinemas this year and plays an issue that increasingly have more news in our societies: the mix of cultures and racial. Paul Haggis shows ability that are many differences separating us, but to a certain level are also many things that we share and that should be the starting point to move forward in the right direction. In short, a film with a subtle moralina which could perhaps have maintained the level of realism with which starts, but that in any case keeps the interest until the end with enough solvency, which is not little.</body>
</review>
