<review author="Rafa Martín" title="Happy feet" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>George Miller wants to return to the good cane. Someone you a script to match.</summary>
	<body>The film needs to George Miller. If you want to get an idea of what is to be the best producer in the world in a time and place determined, I recommend the screening of two films of this extraordinary Australian director: Mad Max 2 and the oil of life. You can share a couple of features as his fellow countryman Peter Weir, including inability to biological make a bad movie, but unlike the second, much more focused on the characters, the sense of the epic of Miller knows no rival. It is not an intimate epic which we are accustomed the director of Master &amp; Commander or single witness, but the great sense of entertainment that can be enjoyed on the big screen. By very children film than Happy Feet, and very bad that she feels in the stomach the tremendísimo downturn plaguing the film halfway through footage, when this film explodes (because that is what happens at certain times) reaches the level of classic animation, reasoned that the incredible images of Miller are complemented by an animation game. And when I say game, I say level a millimeter below musical Pixar.Parte, part adventure on snow, part ecological message, Happy Feet is the story of Mumble, son of Memphis and Norma Rae. As penguins emperors who are their parents (and here I creeré what tell me the movie because I have not simply, or slut), couples places Court through the songs. In the first scene of the film, Norma Rae, sliding between the penguins males to the rhythm of Kiss, Prince, is instantly subjugated by an impressive electric version of the Heartbreak Hotel of Presley (Jackman practically devours this film). The two fall in love, fornican off screen and lay an egg. It is a full scene of rhythm which marks the rest of the songs that appear throughout the footage: have the same energy and vitality to Moulin Rouge, but hellish epilepticus Assembly or the medley.On the verge of passing a bad drink.And vale which is a wonderful way to start a film, and predicts good omens, but is the second sequence that you have recorded in the retina: thousands of penguins male (females leave home during the winter to hunt) they guard the eggs, glued against each other while the elders of the clan shout words of encouragement, under an incredible storm at sunset. It is this the type of things that used to make Miller before, taking every opportunity to use its visual strength, and so create images of enormous power (hopefully many agree Mad Max, contemplating the lights of the refinery from atop a cliff before the fall overnight). Accompanied by epic choirs, it is really sensational, and it seems that he is about to escape from the genre of movie for kids, but not the case. And that, if you are that you like to involve you in depth with what you see in the film, is almost a disgrace to see what lies ahead.Thus, this type of impact not be repeated many times throughout the film: is too routine in the moment that becomes a metaphor for equality when we discovered that the son of Memphis and Norma Rae, Mumble, can not sing. It is its exceptional ability to dance tap which will become the engine of the film (what you're thinking: tries to sing, fails, throw you / will, discover world and returns done best Penguin). Despite the fact that it is a perfectly natural plot, begins to fall to lead halfway through the film, as soon as Mumble meets a clan of penguins. of the race "estereotipus cubanus" (experts in dance, clear.) (Because all the Cubans are experts in dance, right?) and it is not only predictable, but that is boring; include before the second great moment of the film, with all the penguins singing version George Michael in Wembley of the Somebody To Love, of Queen, is a reminder of bass that falls after the film. Fortunately, there are a few action scenes, including the attack of a terrifying Leopard seal (never thought that you would write something like "terrifying seal"), courtesy of the Spanish artist Miguel Angel forts, or the fight against a couple of hungry killer whales, which are very dynamic, and are very well made, but it is clear that Miller wants to take another path. The last twenty minutes show us, when the ecological message of the film and where, for the first time from it for a long time, someone has the eggs of integrating digital animation with characters of flesh and blood. Is it effective? Part: it is clear to see millions (literally) of penguins dancing at the same time, in the final scene of the film, it is a visual delight, and the coexistence between humans and animals is a simple, but powerful and well-intentioned message. But there is also something that just does not fit, and is that Miller completely changes the message of the film. If the second act is boring, the third is abrupt, seems another different movie, and changes the direction of the film almost radical shape (and get me the feeling that if Happy Feet collects $ 200 million will not be by what the film wants to count, but because children want to see dancing penguins).Breaking the track.However, the delight is there, despite the fact that the script of "painting with numbers" lastra to the film, its director raises the level above than expected, and even more. If only it would have found something more in what nail nails, we would be talking about the best film of the year, but seems that the pela remains the pela and that feed the children films as the iron giant is a thing of the past. Happy Feet is impressive to see how a National Geographic documentary, is animated in an exceptional way (Mumble movements were captured from the great tap dancer Savion Glover) but a film with aspirations may not include secondary infectos (Robin Williams lends his voice rather than one or two, but three damn bugs) or so forced and pointless action scenes. It's simple: George Miller wants to return to give the good cane. Someone you a script to match.</body>
</review>
