<review author="José A. Peig" title="La joven del agua" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>M. Night Shyamalan gets naked to show us their fantasies and their intellectual cowardice in this new fairy tale, the most straightforward and honest of how many they had filmed to date.</summary>
	<body>D. Night Shyamalan gets naked to show us their fantasies and their intellectual cowardice in this new fairy tale, the most straightforward and honest of how many they had filmed to date. And this time there is no trap. It is not a dramatic trick to confuse the viewer at the time that history gives the dazzling turn to us into a fabric of metaphors and philosophical, anthropological and sociological reflections, as in the case of "The forest". After the titles of the home, shows us that we are entering the realm of myth and the enchanting, not leaving the Viewer no choice but to the of lull in the armchair as an innocent child willing to believe the fairy tale, emulating one of the scenes in which the brilliant Paul Giamatti strives for transfigurar his nervous and insecure pose in the image of a child's cradle in the presence of the Narrator. And that is the only way to enjoy the film. All part of the myth of the nymph of the waters, creatures from another world that ensure the inspiration of humanity unless it is turned, came the wars, inequalities and struggles between social classes. The world, in short, lost its communication with the magic and enchantment, with innocence. and men knew not to listen to the wisdom that sprang from the depths. It is like the myth of the golden age in which humanity lived in harmony get same and with the elements of nature. The significance was lost, thus. Shyamalan camera introduces us to the real and current world from a dark corner that pounces Mr Cleveland, the protagonist of the story, to end the life of a bug that frightens residents. Cleveland is the Regent of a block of apartments, stuttering, something aseptic and disoriented, lives between his solitude and chores with their tenants, all of them with some "tick" of personality: a boy who wants to be special to increase the muscular mass of only one half of his body, a pedantic and deadpan film critic, an old silent it passes the time watching TV sitting on the coucha group of jipis, a retired writer and an essayist with great pretensions. All have claims to be something special, do not know, but are about to embark on a mission to save humanity. They are the synthesis of a routine world, a micro universe of beings and views that flutter around a blue central point: the swimming pool, the omega point from which will emerge the extraordinary, the fairy with a face of porcelain doll who will come to give meaning to the lives of all of them. Who can doubt that this is a story about how the routine and the disenchantment of everyday life is going shedding with a progressive leap of faith in a tale of old on sea creatures who come to the world to redeem it and restore harmony, this chimera of collective consciousness, believing that first and foremost was idyllic and that if he stopped being what was for a purpose and following the guidelines of a universal plan that us? It will guide everyone toward a new world?. He is God and the faith that Shyamalan tries to dissect pulse of fantasy and micro costumbrista drama, picking up the current state of fear in a troubled world. Not in vain, there are occasions in which shows us the TV on in the homes of the residents of the apartment block - which is almost only scenario of the narration - constantly repetitive broadcast images of the war of Iraq. At another time, one of the protagonists, says plainly something like: "originality is nonexistent in today's world". And clear, Shyamalan rubs hands doing his peliculón, a waste of megalomania very full of pretensions. Nothing new, on the other hand, coming from the author of "Signs" and "The forest". As it is advancing the history, magic is taking shape real and palpable, at least in the mind of Cleveland and the Group of dreamers who walk in search of faith in something of a transcendental sense to their lives. One of them has the real singer voice, a político-sociológico writer of trials of nature which, according to the vision of the fairy of water, has written a book in the hands of a future leader (a preacher for a new was, go) will promote a change of planetary proportions, the return to the golden age. There is a prophet, a group of brothers, a guardian who doblegará evil creatures that threaten the life of the fairy. Cleveland gets seduced by the dream and seeks a correspondence in the real world for all the iconographic elements of what should not be more than a fiction for children from cradle. Need the existence of such correspondence to make possible the salvation of the fairy and for the redemption of humanity begins its first cycle. Everything is an act of faith. Thus it often happens, probably provided that a humans embarks on a dream. And this is, according to my sensitivity, the most heart-rending aspect of the film: beats a deep anxiety to the reality of a world on the eve of the Apocalypse. Rather, beats a wrenching fear at the possibility that everything is a fantasy to escape the harsh reality. There is, accordingly, a desperate to believe in magic, in the gods, beings higher in the designs of the universe planned by "energy" and "forces" that we like to think that we do not understand, but, somehow, and everything it to maintain hope, should exist. Not because it comes from the hand of reason and logic, but simply because we need to believe. It is pathological to search "signals" in the vision of the boxes of cereal on the shelf in the kitchen or a crossword puzzle of a weekly magazine. It may be excessive, but Indian filmmaker shows it us openly and let soften in the wonderful sequence in which Cleveland and yours surround the affirmer girl of water, between skepticism and hope, while Cleveland embraces her in tears of pain. The only hope to your pain is the faith in the resurrection of the girl (to what sounds to me this?). It is the sign that he needs. Definitely, d. Night Shyamalan is crazy by his audacity and desparpajo. A round of applause for his daring creativity, but something squeaking in this platform antropológico-religioso - Mystic (takes longer!) brings between hands. I have to say that "The young of the water", at first glance, I liked less than "Signs" and "The forest". Those two were a good balance between claim to entertain and do think the Viewer. It dominated, perhaps too much, philosophical and other, claims making it less fun than his previous works ("The protected" not speak because I have not yet seen). Yes, I love the multitude of subliminal messages behind during the footage I love that Shyamalan is a mystical filmmaker, but I also prefer the impression of excess verbiage and, perhaps, having missed a little more than lyricism and mystery around the young protagonist, what is said deeper into your profile to be mythological, but without falling into too many hermetismos. More dangerous and controversial of all is the intellectual cowardice of the speech: everything is in the hands of the belief in beings and supernatural things. Shyamalan does not support the reality and wants the world to reach the good through the intervention of the magic, the superstitious thought and other entelequías of the New Age have become part of the culture of masses as a reaction to the chaos and the post-modern loss of values. While in "The forest" we tackle the reality descabezando myths and facing the civilization in the hope placed in the goodness of the human being, everything is in the hands of fanciful hopes. Therefore, notwithstanding, this it is a pure and simple fairy tale, and as such must be assessed it. But at this point we encounter the great flaw of the film; a story about fantasy elements that slip in a world everyday and boring can be counted, but what we cannot do is ignore the dramatic sense that, in such circumstances, provided the line that separates the real from the imaginary and fantastic, normal of exceptional, and signaling, and the effort of the characters to cross that line. Shyamalan does not use this mixture for an emotional inciático trip in which characters can take the decision to believe in wonderful, what is beyond the limit of the real, but that it melts everything, hastily, in a same texture of elements. This stripping emotion and drama to a story that aims to be full of humanity and need to dream. Therefore, the result is both cold and history does not procure the lyrical and emotional intensity that suggests the story. On their behalf I highlight that, as I said at the beginning, there are no trap or dramatic twist that makes Squeak the plot, already from the beginning you know that you you will enter a world of fantasy in order to test the faith of the protagonists of flesh and blood. On the other hand, the film is intended to be tender and sensitive, and indeed succeeds without ever falling into the kitsch. The narrative brilliance of Shyamalan remains in force and demonstrates, despite comic books themselves, are nonsense because only he is them believed be weaving, knows moving in the ground with their own fears and fantasies. "Girl with the water" is the least commercial of his films, and for this reason will be - being already - hard de both by the public and the critics. For something is the most misunderstood filmmaker today. </body>
</review>
