<review author="Manel Juanico" title="Supervixens" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Not only the girls have big breasts in Supervixens, men have "Superpenes" of more than half a meter!.</summary>
	<body>Today I will tell you of Supervixens, a small classic film series b, which perhaps not be entirely known as it should be, but certainly all the mold-breaking at the time. Supervixens has everything, humor, love, violence, action, sex. everything that you could ask a film is here, together with a frenetic pace as rarely seen in a production of this style.More than one considered this movie as a crappy, it is not a conventional film, humor that has is very acid and macabre occasionally, feminists could find macho for the way it has to teach sex female, always with the breasts outdoor and willing to open the legs at all times. But nothing more from reality, the absurd form that shows all this makes you take it with humor and did not give him importance, Russ Meyer only want us laugh exaggerating all actions of the girls appearing during the footage to the limit.Well, first of all should be commenting a bit that goes Supervixens. We already know that it has girls, many girls, and very despelotadas, but what more there is a part of girls?. Supervixens is not an erotic film, although it contains several scenes of sex and as I said before women as God brought them to the world. The plot revolves around Clint, a gasolinero that is married to Superangel, a lush women huge breasts. The couple does very well and they have many discussions. Following one of those discussions, Harry, the police, brilliantly played by Charles Napier, makes a visit to his house to investigate what happens, Superangel seduces him and takes him to bed. But Harry paid not to the expected level, Superangel is rie, and this feels very angry, so much that he does not hesitate to electrocutar Superangel when it is taking a bath. Clint is accused of the crime and must flee. Harry chases him, and here begins the adventure with a myriad of persecution. Else better discover it yourself.Supervixens has an exemplary Assembly for a film of this type, giving a pace frantic that does not breathe the Viewer, the truth is that it is a very entertaining film laughter are assured, that Clint will be harassed by a lot of girls during his escape, all with huge and eager breasts so Clint make theirs. The problem is that some of these girls have husbands, and upon hearing that Clint has been with their wives won't shake hands precisely.Not only the girls have big breasts in Supervixens, men have "Superpenes" of more than half a meter!. It is the way that teach the sex scenes rather seem animated, the Stallion the fly with a snap down and takes his manly member, which we see reflected in a shade in a kind of sexual parody, with music little seen in this type of scenes, better to watch it to understand that I mean.Russ Meyer was conceived and I think this film he could almost say alone. He did everything from the script he wrote for six days in a hotel in Hawaii, until the direction, through photography, with some interesting landscapes shot in the desert of Arizona, the production and the Assembly. So here we have a product that reflects exactly that type of film wanted to makes this director, no one put obstacles is a film 100% Russ Meyer.Nos are faced with a copyright film, with their strengths and their weaknesses, you can like it or not, but no one can deny his originality in the staging and the personal and unique style that the director gives to Supervixens. It is really worth seeing her. As it isn't edited in Spain on dvd, and find the tapes on vhs is somewhat complicated you can download a montage I made with the original dvd and the sound of my tape vhs. Here this the result. It was my first mounting of this type, so it may be a bug is synchronization, hope will not notice much.He later following this style, Russ Meyer directed Up! (1976), entitled Spain Megavixens and Beneath the Valley of the Ultra-Vixens (1979), here "beyond of the Valley of the ultravixens". I guess someday you comment something of these two films, which are also quite interesting, especially Up!.</body>
</review>
