<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Creep" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Creep is a combination of all the defects that can suffer a film: is ill-structured, the idea is simple and vulgar and actress on which rests the entire weight of the script does not give the stature, not even close.</summary>
	<body>Always liked more film of suspense that horror, inter alia because except Honorable exceptions, it tends to be quite superior to plot level, and also because for a time this part horror films, are mostly, a parade of viscera, desmembramientos and any imaginable topic; at least in United States from films and many countries of the old continent who have seen the unique chance to win share of screen in the "Americanization" of their work. It is very possible that part of the budding success of Japanese cinema is due to this cause, that until very recently you could count on the fingers of one hand the Japanese productions of this type are shown in Spain. Creep responds perfectly to the stereotype before commenting, as his script is a magnérrima simplicity; virtually all of it takes place in the underground of the London underground, where a strange creature (more a monster seems a guy that you have missed a cauldron of oil boiling over) is dedicated to bring to his Lair to anyone who is. To make matters worse evils, the stranger be emits sounds resembling those of a eunuch off-key in the choir of the Church. Creep is a combination of all the defects that can suffer a film: is ill-structured, the idea is simple and vulgar and actress on which rests the entire weight of the script does not give the stature, not even close. And Franka Potente, however much that some want to pay tribute, is a monument; but a monument to the inexpressiveness and lack of claw before the camera.	As in almost all films of this type, the following question arises: finish why heck never off the bad when they do at their mercy?. In short, a film to wear her students of film schools. In order to be clear what no of to do.</body>
</review>
