<review author="Manel Juanico" title="The rocky horror picture show" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I present?Do The Rocky Horror Picture Show?, what you leeréis then will change your lives? or rather cross-dressing them? you do not dream, live it!</summary>
	<body>When this blog was born, will be the film that really inspired me something more than one year now has done was "The Rocky Horror Picture Show". It is certainly my movie favorite inside of what I call "Other cinema", these cult films, different from the rest with a legion of fans who worship them for being what they are, be special, some fans that feel bugs rare to see this type of cinema but they feel proud of it. The film of which I speak today is the summum of this type of film, the epitome of what we might call cult film, his followers would kill for her, his love for the film is such that gather to see rooms upgraded, full of balloons, toilet paper, gloves rubber, confetti and transvestism. Watch this movie is a joy for the six senses, if I say six because with the five not enough to taste this wonder. I present "The Rocky Horror Picture Show", all that leeréis below will change your lives? or rather cross-dressing them? you do not dream, live it!Well, in principle give for granted that those who read this do not know much about the movie, if you're an expert in it I do not think that you find much new information, anyway you would encourage to continue reading and I encourage you to leave here a comment that contributes more than I can say, I'd like that this post reflect everything about this film. If instead you've never heard talk about this film, or sounds, but you have not seen, then I must say that you have to continue reading, do it by me, by the "other" film and this blog. Made this sort of introduction, something more long than usual (as required by the subject), then move on to item. We find ourselves in 1973, a musical is reaping success in the theatre "Royal Cort" in London. This work was what would be in the future "The Rocky Horror Picture Show", written by Richard O´Brien and directed by Jim Sharman. It is gradually becoming a cult work, i.e. viewers are going to see the work more than once, know the songs and part of it. A few months later it opens in California and is also very successful, which encourages producers Michael White and Lou Adler to propose to take her to the cinema. I would like to talk more about this work but the truth is I am not sufficiently informed to treat the theme, the argument, as the film was about two students nerds left in a world of decadence, rock´n roll, sex and science fiction. In a documentary that comes as an extra in the dvd released in Spain are some anecdotes of the work. I remember one that is when Meat Loaf attends the theatre to rehearse for the first time and meets with Tim Curry, who plays Dr. Frank b. FURTER, which later will talk further, dress with stockings and a leather suit. Meat Loaf has no idea that is going to work and leaves the theatre, saying that he does not want to participate in something so. Luckily at the end so convinced and later played a great role den film. For more stories similar I recommend you see this documentary and interviews that come on the dvd, there are really weird things, some them comment on here, but it is impossible to say it all. Let us focus then in what is "The Rocky Horror Picture Show", the film. We are going has make a kind of synopsis, without disclosing much but not hide anything. Brad and Janet are a couple of very simple, she very prudish and he quite seriously. After attending the wedding of a friend Brad asks marriage to Janet. His return is lost with the car and go to a strange mansion where is this holding a strange Convention. There get them Riff Raff a mysterious Butler and Magenta a maid of more eccentric. Invite them pass and they are in a room where there is a kind of party, everyone goes in disguise with strange costumes, hats of colors, glitter, facemasks, to Arab costumes. They begin to sing a song and dance. Frank will appear ´n Furter, the owner of the mansion dressed in leather and fishnet stockings, is presented to the guests and invites you to attend the presentation of their "work" is not more nor less than a sort of "Frankenstein" blond and with many muscles that he has created for your personal enjoyment. From here the in adventures that Brad and Janet will be living in the mansion they discover their sexuality hidden until then. MMM, missing much argument in this synopsis, more than all that there. We have other characters, Dr Scott, Eddie, Columbia? It is now when have to dig a little deeper. Here I will reveal some things it is better to not know before seeing the film, although for me the most important thing is not the argument itself, but everything else, the music, the choreography, the aesthetics. Visually it is really shocking and musically even more, so gaps that may exist of script are totally needs. So let's first of all, the "nerd" wedding, what nerd? As wikipedia defines as "traditionally is a very intelligent person, fascinated by knowledge, particularly scientific, characterized as a lonely person socially and socially awkward." Today, the term refers equally socially normal one, which presents a great knowledge of a topic not dominated by the common people. Many features attributed to a certain type of nerd usually go also United with Asperger syndrome, a form of mild autism, sometimes confused with sense of humor, and vice versa. ". So we have two nerds who attend the wedding of a fellow nerd University. We are in the city of Dentex, a curious Church, created expressly for the occasion, I understand only built the front for the making of the film, the interiors were filmed elsewhere. At the end of the wedding the bride throws the bouquet that will stop to Janet. Janet is performed by a young Susan Sarandon in one of his first performances for the big screen, and if I have not misunderstood, the only one in which he sings. In principle this role came to him by chance as he attended the casting only to greet Tim Curry, who was his friend. He was told to sing, but she said that she didn't know, his father was apparently a singer, but she not dared even to sing along. Still lost the shame and sang and went it so well that she got the role. The Janet character was defined by herself as "the fever of Saturday night of the naive version". Already presented all the characters and having an idea quite clear where we would have to conclude this species of monographic section of the film, but before I would like to provide a few more data, curiosities, or facts that occurred during filming. His voice is funny, very acute, which you've heard some of his songs in the movie you know what I mean, also you can listen to it for example in the video that I put below. Well, going by the of the bouquet, which I don't want to lose me as much information. It is then when Brad, played by Barry Bostwick, this already more experienced in musicals and well-known for his more than 50 characters played in television series, today in day proposes to Janet to her giving him a ring. Both this and Susan Sarandon had not participated in the play and with Meat Loaf form the American trio of production. Then begins the first musical number and is when some of the characters who will later come in the mansion. At this time already we see that it is not for nothing in a conventional musical, both the music and the choreography are totally different to that seen until then in musical type "Grease" or "West Side Story", although it may have some similar more with "Saturday night fever". Here's that first number musicalEn the scene later found the couple in a car, in the middle of a storm, listening on the radio to the resignation of Richard Nixon, something that is not at all random and places us in a time of transition deliberately. Many things are going to change? in the life of Brad and Janet. The car breaks down, and under the storm they envision the mansion and they sing a song that my particularly I love, especially when it appears out of the window the character of Riff Raff. Here is when did not find the mansion, one of the points most forts of the film and that it is of great importance in the aesthetic outcome. It's a mansion in ruins found the Interior Designer Brian Thomson and the artistic director Terry Ackland on the outskirts of London. The mansion was used on several occasions to shoot horror films. They did a great job adding modern elements such as an elevator, which was not really such, but a hydraulic system which gave the pego. All the decorative elements were carefully selected by the art team. You can see the video of this first contact with the mansion here. It is now when the door opens Riff Raff, the character played by Richard O´Brien, composer of the musical and true architect of this wonder. Curiously this was the first musical writing, and that is noted especially in the freshness and originality both lyrics and choreography. Richard O ´Brien has been very versatile during his career, being singer, songwriter, playwright and actor among other things. When Jim Sharman suggested him to write the music for the theatre wasn't it twice, so he wrote a damning, groundbreaking, controversial and of course fun. Rex, David Bowie, Sweet or Roxy Music, which certainly inspired quite Richard O´Brien in the creation of the work. Glam rock had a short duration, and while few have been groups that have gone down in history within that genre, was given much to talk about at the time by the daring of its costumes and staging. Remember, groups such as the New York Dolls, for example, one of my favorite bands. And here is when it really starts the fun, but first I want to submit another character from the film, Magenta, played by Patricia Quinn, who embodies a kind of Maid of the House. This actress has participated in another film that I love "The meaning of life" of the Python monthly. When he was offered the role he accepted because he was told that he would sing the song of the principle "Science Fiction" one of the best of the film, look at the letter that has no waste, a homage to the film series science fiction 1950s B. Because it is at the end he did not sing the song and has only four lines in the film, which says when Brad and Janet enter for the first time in the House. Patricia Quinn finally was satisfied that Jim Sharman suggested him to record his lips singing the song in a sequence that will go down in history and is one of the best known of "The Rocky Horror Picture Show", the introduction of what will be this huge reto-musical. The video is required viewing and what you can see below. As said before here it is when the fun begins, Brad and Janet are invited to go to a room where a strange Convention, are about the words, the choreography of the dance is superb, we studied every movement to the millimetre so stay perfect, I I never tire of seeing it, look at the characters in as moving at levelsthe colors, the props in general, is simply masterful, only to see him happy day, seriously, but you think try yourselves. (of course that the same is not see him here in small to see it in a film, I would pay whatever to see in the cinema, or a team home cinema sound to the fullest). And now is when he makes an appearance for the first time Frank´n Furter, this kind of Dr Frankenstein regalia that leaves no one indifferent. Brilliantly played by Tim Curry, it's one of the most endearing characters has given the world of celluloid. Tim Curry machismo cost him find the tone of voice to play Dr Frank´n Furter, it is said that until that not putting the socks could not catch the appropriate tone. Either way it was a brilliant role and his voice is impressive, both moved items and those who must express feeling. And what is this festival which is organized in a strange mansion, full of colorful characters?. Then to attend the birth of Rocky, the work of Frank´N Furter, who represents the sexual ideal, a blond boy, with a perfect body, a kind of modern Frankenstein intended to satisfy the carnal desires of the doctor. The art Department's work was very important in the birth of Rocky, Rocky is born within a kind of coffin with a liquid, the idea was being all colors of the Rainbow that was achieved when the doctor drops a kind of paints in tubes. The order was strictly decided by Ferry Ackland, artistic director who told Tim Curry which should whet to give this tonality. Birth of the creature, wrapped like a mummy, they sound these two songs. At the end of the second appears Meat Loaf, playing Eddie, nephew of Dr Even Scott who is brutally murdered by Frank. As a curiosity to say that Richard O´Brien wanted to eliminate that song because he said that it was impossible to sing it because it had too much lyrics and nobody could sing so fast. Meat Loaf did and I am perfect. The entry with the bike scene was extremely rugged, a member of the team broke a leg, which towards specialist dropped the bike over, Meat Loaf also fell with the bike, broke a camera, a disaster. Good luck in the end was so good. Say the videos that I do not have subtitles, not I could find them and I did not get to upload the videos to youtube having them there, I put these videos just so you see aesthetics and music, is essential to see the movie whole subtitled to fully enjoy it. I am missing three characters by presenting and I'll quickly in this paragraph. On the one hand have to Columbia, performed by Nell Campbell, who has an interesting tap dance dance in the opening scene. You will then have an important role during the development of the film. On the other hand this Dr Everett V. Scott, former Professor of Brad and Janet, which will prove to be a researcher of the Government that is dedicated to investigate aliens. Its role is really important, is the uncle of Eddie goes to the mansion to investigate her disappearance and the corpse is found in a scene which was very curious. In this scene they are dining almost all the characters in the film, a very special dinner in serving the meat of the corpse of Eddie. Well, as it turns out that in this sequence, at the table where they eat, below is the body of Eddie's own. The director they said nothing to the actors and when Frank takes the tablecloth is his mutilated body. The expressions of the faces of the actors are real and the scene stayed very well. The last character I want to make is that of the Narrator. "The Rocky Horror Picture Show" is narrated by Charles Gray and perhaps is what I least like the film, it seems to me that although this is a very personal opinion breaks the rhythm, a little. Who tells the story, it seems a serious character although he sometimes gets to dance as the characters. It is curious and sometimes even fun, but I am saying that I do not I just like. Already presented all the characters and having an idea quite clear where we would have to conclude this species of monographic section of the film, but before I would like to provide a few more data, curiosities, or facts that occurred during filming. E.g. Frank´n Furter character, apart from having clear references to Dr Frankenstein, according to director were based also on Ivan the terrible, snow white and Cruella Vill? There is nothing. More things, because in the studio shot where they had no heating, no toilets, the conditions were very bad. To complain of this Susan Sarandon who had to go in underwear throughout the film she was told "these American stars always complaining". Susan Sarandon caught pneumonia therefore their complaints were not unfounded. The problem was that they had to spend many hours of shooting that the makeup required long. Finally say that the film was a commercial failure, people were scandalized and left divisions, projections lasted very little and not even raised it had cost. The success he has come later, released in small cinemas where projected different films, such as "The night of the living dead" or projected in universities, was gradually forming a kind of cult film that has come down to today. Each year are festivals throughout the world paying homage the film to my I'd love to be able to attend one day one. Here I leave a video of one made in Madrid. Here is the blog of this representation. Well, I know that I have leaving the film halfway, missing tell many things that occur in the second part, but is not plan to tell absolutely everything, so if someone has not seen it probably has more to do it. Say that "The Rocky Horror Picture Show" was a continuation in 1981 "Shock Treatment", directed by Jim Sharman and many members of the reaparto of the above. The truth is that I have not seen that movie, by the images that I have seen on the internet does not seem to have all the quality of the first part, although the soundtrack I still enjoying it very much. I hope that this special has been to your liking and this time that I let some comments, I like you aportarais things that I have not said, or fixing bugs in my review, I have taken much time gathering information and can some thing her has been badly. Anyway almost all the commentary stems from my personal experience with this film, I've seen so many times that I no longer remember. </body>
</review>
