<review author="Rafa Martín" title="Brick" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Pure film noir directed by Rian Johnson with a mostly stable, but sometimes irregular, pulse, taken out of context and inserted into an Institute today, directed by an immeasurable Joseph Gordon-Levitt.</summary>
	<body>Occasionally it is a delight to be able to take a look at the current independent film. It is at the moment in which it departs from the contents classic for this type of film (drugs, problematic family relationships, social complaint and similar conaza) and focuses on revitalizing a genus of life. The recently released Hard Candy is an exercise in suspense. Brick, for its part, is pure film noir out of context and inserted into an Institute today, starred by an immeasurable Joseph Gordon-Levitt and directed with a mostly stable, but sometimes irregular, by Rian Johnson.A pulse characteristics despite the flat long combined with Moloney Visual effects, natural photography and the almost total absence of soundtrack, with which the indies lead us wow / torture since the 1990sBrick complies to strict standards: there is a victim, a fatal woman, two sides of mobsters, a representative of the order, and an anti-hero smarter than hunger, who knows all the moves and possesses an undeniable practical spirit and a dose of above-average intelligence. The major asset of the film, as we have said, is to put all this panda enclosed in an Institute. It is a great idea but it is even more: is a brilliant development that extends during most of the film until his last scenes, in which breaks slightly the balance when we entered the field of fire.Brendan and his girlfriend Emily (Emilie de Ravin). Common sense versus desquiciamiento paranoia.However, the forces of Brick lie elsewhere: dialogues and actors, is called. While the outlines of the plot occasionally too reminiscent of the Coen brothers masterpiece mentioned in the holder (if, Fargo is very good movie and Arizona Baby is funny, but death among the flowers plays in another Division), are talks between the characters and the conviction with which all interpret them making a Brick into something more than a simple experiment Mondosonoro balls. I do not usually do it, but I recommend that you see the film on dubbed version because it is incredibly easy to miss: history is incredibly twisted limits and the dialogues seem to machine gun fire, plagued of replicas of the flag (in particular, for example, "you have given this guy to see as she is what they zampaban, not like you what you eat").It is easy to convert that phrase into a joke, but not when tells Gordon-Levitt, an actor well ahead of the rest of his generation and has survived to films to his credit as Halloween H20. Brendan Frye, the protagonist of the film, is three-dimensional thanks to Gordon-Levitt, combining weak human (the trigger for the film is the murder of his girlfriend) with mental agility of pantera and above all, the disdain for the rest of the human race which he shares with the great detectives private gender. The rest of the cast is almost swallowing, but Lukas Haas, Noah Flynn (in his role as mafiosetes of middling) and Nora Zehetner should be mentioned, in particular this last, which makes wonders with her role as femme fatale.Brendan and the Femme Fatale. The photo does justice to the big eyes of Nora Zehetnera.Lo said here extends to the particular vision of Johnson on the Institute, where again all groups are perfectly differentiated (the cool, the hanging, the snobs, the nerds, the abandoned) but they move at the same time in an almost surreal environment (the Roman Feast where Brendan arrives by chance). It is the touch of alienation that breaks the routine practically at every level of the film, which however never leaves that history will hand, supported in a couple of scenes of action, inserted at the right time, quite surprising and shot with energy.However, if Brick inherits all the virtues of film noir (as a constant tension: is virtually impossible, with a good story behind, bore the Viewer) also has some weaknesses, and some drawer: the end, x-rays, it is not that it is a little unsatisfactory, but leaves a slightly strange taste. That no one expected a climax, but a kind of quiet end, where all the pressure ends up yielding almost at once. Johnson seems to realize this and try to get an emotional component (without specifying more unwanted pregnancy) that was not necessary before being introduced, and which in my opinion seems a bit forced, because with what there is behind (the famous "Brick"? title do brick?) is already more than enough. In any case, there are reasons enough to lose an hour and a half of our time: it is fresh, original and there are more chicha that appears behind a brilliant idea. And a brilliant idea is a finding, the problem is that it only gives a short.</body>
</review>
