<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="El extraño" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Subtlety in details, superb performance and a magnificent setting showing talent neither be bought nor sold.</summary>
	<body>The truth is that I feel a little intimidated when I think that I shall make a critique of a directed and starring film who is my particular Olympus of celluloid with Joseph Cotten and Jack Nicholson. Orson Welles was a strange, Bohemian, Maverick, eventually fought with all the American film industry, which was virtually ousted by ultraprogresista ideology in a United States dominated by Semitic and conservative capital. The stranger belongs to its golden age, next time Citizen Kane and the third man (feel chills only to write these titles), shortly before that his enthusiasm for Spain take you to spend great seasons in our country together with one of his great friends, Antonio Ordóñez, on whose farm lie the remains of the great filmmaker.In the strange, Welles plays a nazi that after the war leads a quiet life under a false name in a village of America, and that a "Hunter" located in large part thanks to the fans to the clocks of the former SS, he occupies his time free to fix the Bell Tower of the town clock. Charles Rankin is the name under which hides Franz Kindler, and which will seek to catch Mr Wilson, which gives life a monster of the interpretation, as it was Edward G. Robinson. The characterizations of the characters reach insurmountable heights in the dark and gloomy appearance of Welles or the affability of the detective Wilson, who comes to make some friends with the orondo and nice clerk of the warehouse, which in turn uses to obtain some information. This contributes to the tempo of the film is slow, but at the same time dynamic in a difficult combination of factors that rarely are. The simple details of the way in which the Nazi pursuer convinces the real identity of Kindler is a subtlety unmatched. All this without forgetting the rest of the cast that shines also to a high level (especially Loretta Young, the ignorant and naive wife of the ruthless criminal). But in any case, and remain outstanding in this section, the interpretation is not the most important thing of this film.From the technical point of view it is also impeccable, and used often chopped and contrapicados of images, with a superb management of lighting and shadows, creating an atmosphere of tension and suspense of enormous intensity. These "ventures" with a depth of full script of second readings and political messages are make the stranger (also known in Spain as the alien) in a real masterpiece and inevitable reference to subsequent productions of similar Court, framed in what came to be called Film Noir (film noir).I am aware that I've done an enthusiasm disproportionate in these lines, but the fascination that has always exerted on me Orson Welles prevent me from moderate me when he is. And especially if we are talking about a wonder as this film.</body>
</review>
