<review author="Jose Luis" title="Brokeback mountain" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Apart from any dispute shall be conducted in the heart of many people</summary>
	<body>By how much scandal for a movie of two gay Cowboys? Is it that we are not so liberal and open as we presume be? I think Yes. On all whereas the so carried and brought film is not so much about homosexuality or sobre as males who are the Cowboys of the American West; It is simply and before all these things, a sincere love story.Ennis and Jack are hired to take care of a huge flock of sheep in a mountain away from any civilization, there in the midst of loneliness, begin an affair which unknowingly runs for his life. A love that will have to hide, knowing that homosexuality in those places is punished even with the death penalty.From the opening scene is given one account is not to tape as "gay", a few simple shots on an also simple scenario accompanied only with a couple of chords of the minimalist but effective music. We have a simple and realistic, tape that does not require large elements to tell their story. The main feature of the film is the economy, in all its aspects, the music, the scenery, costumes, the captures you, everything is simple, at least in appearance. As well as performances, especially that of Heath Ledger as Ennis Del Mar, who goes to a character who speaks little, but with its silences expresses much, breaks, the gestures, everything helps you build a tormented but realistic character, which I believe, will be remembered for a long time. The script, as sober and simple, tells a story that extends for several decades without any qualms, skipping days, months or even years with just a cut, which makes it very easy to follow the story with a rhythm and quite unique detail without many problems. For that when you almost reach the end and the events occur with more calm suffers a bit slow, which at other times of the film was more enjoyable. Ang Lee, all a consummate artist, build an excellent film, that beyond all the alleged dispute will be carried in the heart of many people, both gay and heterosexual regardless? as it should be in all.</body>
</review>
