<review author="Matías Cobo" title="Eragon" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The lackluster and predictable result is a direct result of the unbearable inertia of the Americans to conceive the film as a single industry.</summary>
	<body>Eragon is to cinema what McDonald's food. Fast food for easy digestion and poor nutritional value. I do not would save or as event Mall cinema popcorn maker/family. Because, in this case, the producers of this invention marketing have a face as long as left brain. They decide to do a hodgepodge copying the notable trilogy of Jackson, that time be located in a place privileged as epic entertainment film, and the dull and recent the Chronicles of Narnia. The lackluster and predictable result is a direct result of the unbearable inertia of the Americans to conceive the film as a single industry. Because, even if the tapes are precise to sustain the bloating business and thus produce smaller works but infinitely better, reniego of the overabundance of films of this type and of the advertising and commercial paraphernalia that bring with them. In the end, more films are being franchises for sale of video games, toys or derived from a roll of two hours and a half instantly forgettable t-shirts.The film, as I say, not worth or to be entertained while one eats the pipes. The story is decorated with the typical elements: elves, dragons and heroes face a dark evil that sojuzga them with the iron hand of all medieval warlord. The good must fight against evil, and a chosen, that now instead of an Elf a ring bearer is a madder chosen as the last copy of Dragon Rider, will be the hope of men. The young blond hair meets an egg and it was born a baby Dragon which, in a pair of flapping and raids by the field, becomes greater and is able to telepathically talk to the waiter. As it is "chosen", although all you antojen an esmirriado for so much horse, the forces of evil will go after him to kill him. But without hardly training, the night the day, the boy pilot to his dragon as Alonso a F-1 and begins to do spells without or Pope of the world of magic elvish language. And this cross between Aragorn and Gandalf, with the invaluable collaboration of a Court of Knights and Amazons willing to give his life for him, is the hero built with this scandalous lack the originality.But not enough to shoot a story so trite and bland, it was also filmed by copying? in vain? the style of others much better and plagiarizing sequences and levels of blatant way. Have we how many times have seen a group of riders dressed with long layers ride through the countryside while the camera from an aerial outlet gives a 360-degree turn at high speed? Many, right? As Eragon serves us another serving of more of the same. And why is it that the fanfare of Fund who officiates soundtrack sounds having heard, but in versions infinitely better (such as the Shore), other dozens of times? I do not know if even Mann is the involvement in such a project of actors of the talent of Jeremy Irons and John Malkovich. Vale who take out a few extra milloncejos almost without disheveled in the commercial cinema from time to time, but perhaps they should think a bit before putting their names in the credits of this nonsense. Because, honestly, his performance is in line with the poverty of the rest of the cast. And the film is not that I have disappointed, since he did not have high expectations, but yes it has bothered me, as it is clear in these lines, because it is a joke of volume and spine. I don't think I to again it take in the aftermath of the forthcoming Christmas.</body>
</review>
