<review author="Mario" title="Eragon" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>I do not think it fair to judge something that I could do better (or worse) but in this case I am obliged to propose my first suspense for this film, as forgettable as his literary reference.</summary>
	<body>Christopher Paolini is the human test of the American dream. A Californian young, passionate about Harry Potter and the Dragonlance (this I do not know but what I guess) Decides to write a book to a whopping fifteen years. After reviewed and Remiro pamphlet, family resolves to be support in everything to his son to become the USA version and machulera of J.K Rowling, and thus change its foul caravan of the suburbs by a mansion properly in Beverly Hills (like I am exaggerating, but something) the papaítos abandon their work to take the child by the State, and later throughout the country, so get someone publish you, and his book, Eragon, to finally become a bestseller.Broadly speaking this is its history, another example of triumph in the country of opportunities and, as said, good test of the American dream.The plot of the books, the movie follows erratically, is not but the overused initiatory journey tolkieniano surrounded by dragons, elves, and Orcs (although these last is call úrgalos) often plagiarized and repeated. The formula for success that raised the British writer has been shot without complexes on countless occasions, but even with everything, the plot that raises this barbilampiño author I was very bland, hard to read, to the point of abandoning the ship well advanced half of the journey. I can assure you that I enjoy as a dwarf in each installment of Harry Potter and I had fun with, for example, Dragonlance legends, so I do not pecaré pedantic when I say that I do not understand that they have seen you so many millions of people to this boring and bland manuscript of which I do not think it can rescue absolutely nothing.Due to the bestseller of Eragon and Eldest sequel - apparently there is still a third installment, because someone had said that it was obligatory to do the stories of three in three if it does would be Tolkien? heroic fantasy - Fox didn't get rights and launch for a production that take advantage of the slipstream of the film more laureada historyThe Lord of the rings. The shooting of the film began with a cast of actors reputable in a hateful smile leading profident child and low hours (please Jeremy, enough already).Once done, little can be said a tape that, despite the misunderstandings that may carry the trailer, it closely follows the wake of dungeons &amp; dragons. Is true that comparisons are odious, and that any production of this kind cannot help but overshadow before the project of epic dimensions filmed Peter Jackson, but, even so, building on the success of medium-sized and Orcs, well it is true that might have arisen products more than worthy and with different points of view to which they saw in the drama trilogy - something like this as what happened in Seattle following Nirvana, in another field that Yes.It is not the case in this case; What we have is an infantiloide film devoid of any kind of consistency, sleeping and (despite the million) with a painted very but very shabby.Most interpretations give embarrassment. The exception to a minimally decent Robert Carlyle, which gives life to the escarizado shade Durza, or the beauty of Sienna Guillory, the rest is for piss and no echar gota.The child, incredibly clean and always smiling, might be more irritating than Jar-jar Binks, on all when Lisp magic words or sounding epic phrases. This is leaving aside the outlandish mental conversations with the Dragon.Jeremy Irons, trying to recover from D &amp; D, fails but crashed into a parody of himself certainly frightening, with a character who drags his foolishness in crescendo until an ill-fated final, so unusual that I narraré not here to not deprive you of some good laughter if you decide to waste our time with this movie.And not to mention people like Djimon Hounsou, strolling through scenes outrageously silly and disguised as a humorous way, with a poker face as perplexed as mine.The budget of the film is barely appreciated, the CGI are heap by pulling to bad and there is a total absence of creatures created in the workshop (have not bothered or horns to the úrgalos) also the twisted imagination of the production design will show us throughout the movie good samples of psychedelic pop designs, as the appalling guess in his Lair, the pompous and jewelled sword of Brom, with this Boulder in the grip of the version more kitsch of Sara Montiel, or the final fireworks in the shelter of the vardenos rebels who live in the caves of Altamira and dress as Kings Magi from the East. A tacky festival OT style.I do not think it fair to judge something that I could do better (or worse) but in this case I am obliged to propose my first suspense for this film, as forgettable as his literary reference. Because at the end and after that what are dreams not? that most of the time end up forgetting.</body>
</review>
