<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Eragon" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It will be a promotion of the love of good cinema, that suckers that fall into their networks, the next time that they heard about it, will be locked into the nearest library to view the work of geniuses such as Bergman, Fellini and Kurosawa.</summary>
	<body>Immersed as we are in the maelstrom of the holiday season, cinemas are preparing for a tough battle to decide which movie will be which reigns in this holiday time. Traditionally they were tapes of animation, but that changed five years ago when became two of the most important cinematographic sagas of recent years: the Lord of the rings and Harry Potter. And seen the huge benefits that reported the trilogy based on the works of Tolkien, Fox brings Eragon, a new épico-fantástica story that attempts to continue such good box office data.The film is based on the novel by Christopher Paolini, a teenager when he started writing, he jumped to the fore in the same year released the return of the King. As the great Groucho Marx, what a coincidence that would say coincidentally occur so many coincidences, because the work of Paolini (still unfinished, because that lack the third volume of the trilogy) is first cousin of the great work of Tolkien. The story takes us to Paolini, a fantastic land where governs the cruel King Galbatorix (John Malkovich). The few who oppose him are his hope in Eragon (Edward Speleers), a young farmer who is chosen to be a new Dragon Rider, the only person who could challenge the cruel King. With similar mimbres one would expect an exciting epic tape, but the reality is disappointing. Say that Eragon has all the teen, even children, is staying short and insulting the intelligence of children. That the film is destined for children is evident, even though producers, in a spectacular Pirouette, have worked hard to sell it as a fast-paced story of fantasy and adventure. The argument of an insulting simplicity bored so small as to older, and will cause more than one strategic retreat in the middle of the projection. Stefan December, former technical of the Industrial Light and Magic, before such monumental hassle opts for the simplest way, and instead of looking for innovation in the Visual aspects, is limited to copy (many levels are identical) the work of Peter Jackson the Lord of the rings. If the torment outside little, unknown Edward Speleers contributes enthusiastic and remarkably to prolong the agony of the spectators with his unbearable performance. Jeremy Irons, John Malkovich and Robert Carlyle best nor spoke.It must be admitted that Eragon will be a promotion of the love of good cinema, that suckers that fall into their networks, the next time that they heard about it, will be locked into the nearest library to view the work of geniuses such as Bergman, Fellini and Kurosawa.</body>
</review>
