<review author="Ricard Marcet" title="Lilith" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The profound legacy of a filmmaker unparalleled</summary>
	<body>Two years before his early death from diabetes, Robert Rossen signed what would be her last film: Lilith. Four decades after its premiere, its dramatic complexity and his lyricism reach us intact, with the same capacity to challenge the Viewer.Vincent Bruce (Warren Beatty), a young veteran, returned to Maryland, his hometown, with the intention of working in Poplar Lodge, a nearby psychiatric centre. His predisposition to help will be responsible for the Centre do not hesitate to accept him among its workforce. It will soon set in Lilith, a beautiful and intelligent sick he has built to its around an imaginary world, with a language and a logic of their own.Since the beginning, thanks to the Mise en scène by Rossen, the viewer also feels curiosity by Lilith: first without seeing his appearance, it will show to the internal from the window to monitor the movements of Vincent, and will not be until a few minutes later, after hearing much about it and have fuelled our desire to see her, which, in the first Exchange of words with VincentRobert Rossen gives us a closed level of his angelic face. Through its beauty and a special sensitivity which takes you to contemplate, without rest, the flashes of light in the flow of the River, Lilith will become before our eyes and Vincent, a kind of nymph or also living in harmony with nature. It won't be until that she spit from the bridge, causing the laughter of the companions of the Centre, which we will draw from our reverie and will return to reality. However, Vincent will be captivated by Lilith and apañará them, convincing policy-makers of the psychiatric hospital, to pass the as long as possible with her. At his side, he will forget the ghosts that you torture, such as the death of his mother and memories of war, and contagiará his Joie de vivre. Thus, despite having rejected it once by his caregiver status, its principles will go overlooked and will be delivered to the enjoyment that proposes Lilith: after being crowned as medieval kings, in a scene that symbolizes the final approach to the world of the beautiful sick, consumará the desire of both. Framing in nature and relating it to the flashes of light in the water, the sex to be the couple will be shown by the director as something sublime, both fleeting and eternal.However, Vincent, defined by the own Lilith as a "worshiper of pain", not settle for love which offers the young and enfurecerá to discover that he has sexual intercourse with Mrs.Yvonne (Anne Meacham), another internal. Unable to accept the fact of not owning Lilith exclusively, it enloquecerá by jealousy. Its most destructive instinct it ending with what both longs for owning. After the terrible outcome, you can just return to the psychiatric hospital as one patient.With this hopeless end, Robert Rossen will close his filmography. The director, who was vapuleado by the power of their own country before the Communist alarm, defines the moral imperative, expression of the desire of power, such as cancer of humanity. Rossen, it is the man himself in its desire to possess (in this case, possess himself) that is overriding a fierce moral that governed his life. Judging from the story of Vincent, as well as her married friend (less developed but not insignificant), that morality which aims to define the limits of good and evil, able to delimit the madness, punificar sex or send one to war, just causes frustration men and carries it of remorse. To all this, the American filmmaker puts Lilith, possessed of a moral permeable and characterized by its natural goodness. With a mise en scène that deals with kindness the personal world of the young sick (the details of the flashes of light, as well as the travelling that follows the reflection of the couple in the water, betray the will of the filmmaker to be close to it) will be through his martyrdom in the hands of Vincent Robert Rossen will reach the viewer its profound legacy: as says Mrs.Yvonne at a time of great lucidity "principles should be examined constantly".</body>
</review>
