<review author="Ibán Manzano" title="Babel" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Babel is universal, jumps from continents, change language and flies through the air any kind of borders through a visual terrorism which injects oxygen to the image at a time called the libertarian reductionism.</summary>
	<body>One might think that the third movie Alejandro González Iñarritu is the poorly resolved synthesis worst defects of his previous works, Amores Perros and 21 grams greater, or that even Babel is the wound heal a film again cut the butterfly effect that leads to the more exasperated limits of their own realityunder the excuse of a world globalized, interconnected to the force and definitely disoriented. In fact it would be easy to assume that the Gallery of alien suffering vignettes that make up Babel follows the logic of a whimsical script which explores the border last as possible, instead of responding to the probable.But what separates Babel of films, including Crash, which shares form and Fund (the fear in our days), is that his manipulative collection of coincidences finally responds to a plurality of responses, pronounced in a multitude of languages alive (and killed), for a number of quasi-infinity of cultures; Meanwhile, that for its part, of Haggish devenía in sole and simplistic response under the illusive mirage of that same plurality in their interrelated stories. The director of Amores Perros has shot the climax to a trilogy about the pain marked by rewriting in modern key of Greek tragedy through the fractured narrative with Babel. But his latest work has a fundamental difference with the previous two, is not out of necessity but by vocation polyglot, i.e. that despite the torture that took their characters is deeply hopeful.Babel is universal, jumps from continents, change language and flies through the air any kind of borders through a visual terrorism which injects oxygen to the image at a time called the libertarian reductionism. His stark story joins the vital adventures of his characters in a point of multiple readings and many more directions under an inviolable axiom: the only way to escape that which we call fear, is through love and true pain. Something shared by all cultures speak the language they speak.</body>
</review>
