<review author="Francisco Bellón" title="Mia Sarah" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>MIA Sarah is a tender story and sweet, that at no time falls in the easy or the acaramelamiento cheap. This mixture should add the originality of the proposal and its development, intelligent humor, and a touch of magic that makes the tape in a modern fable, a romantic fable.</summary>
	<body>In the film, as in all the arts, could be argued that you're all invented, or at least almost everything is governed by unchanged rules that leave little to the imagination of everyone. There are some film genres which seem at first glance a nightmare for originality, which do something different and new seems to be punishable. The romantic comedy is one of those genera whose exponents today appear to be photocopies of photocopies. Perhaps for this reason, the romantic comedy as we know it is not one of the most exploited genera in recent Spanish cinematography, by limitations that offers. There are always some exceptions, and Mia Sarah, newcomer Gustavo Ron, is one of them. Marina (Verónica Sánchez) is a young girl that brings caring to his brother Samuel (Manuel Lozano) and his grandfather Paul (Fernando Fernán Gómez) since the death of their parents three years ago. Since then, Samuel suffers from agoraphobia, and has not taken to the streets. Provided that Marina Gets a new psychologist to visit his brother, this manages to frighten him. Everything changes when appears Gabriel (Daniel Guzmán), the new psychologist Samuel. From the premise of a romantic comedy, Gustavo Ron makes a beautiful and cheerful, film that is overflowing with good intentions. It is a sweet, and tender story that never falls on how easy or the acaramelamiento cheap. This mixture should add the originality of the proposal and its development, intelligent humor, and a touch of magic that makes the tape in a modern fable, a romantic fable. To maintain the illusion, the film relies on its actors, especially on a masterful Fernán Gómez, as always, and a sweet and adorable Verónica Sánchez. MIA Sarah is not never heavy, but is seen with a smile on the lips from the beginning until the end, and is of those films that comes out happy, that you comfort to one spirit. Unfortunately, by the time that opens, and pos low distribution, few will be viewers who enjoy the first small jewel of the Spanish film of the season coming.</body>
</review>
