<review author="Caruco" title="Eragon" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A telefilm without hint of some, ideal personality to any desktop on Saturday or Sunday.</summary>
	<body>What can expect from a novel written by a still immature young man that has came up with the idea at age 15, and saw published the book 20, together with what you can do some Hollywood screenwriter, which tend to treat viewers as if they should have no more than 12 years?And if the project is responsible for a Director, Stefen December, Rookie, and pulling to mediocre. What is the result? Well: "Eragon", the start of an (ahem!) new and great Trilogy for the Navidades.Pero'm going to skip the usual criticism for asserted another comment to game mode. So turn on tiptoe by saying that Stefen December is revealed as a filmmaker without spark, a mere Illustrator totally denied to use the floorplan and both for the action as the more intimate scenes. Or that used the Aerial panoramic landscapes and to place the characters became fashionable Peter Jackson with "The Lord of the rings". Although December used to stun us.Or that photography is a monotonous tone, and that everything that happens, dialogues included, is a topicazo that pulls back. On top of all this, I suggest the relationship that follows on the points in common with a trilogy that obvious, I will not mention the title.Star dracs.The beloved producer 20Th Century Fox is behind the project, and the protagonist is a young farmer orphan who lives with his uncle. It is also blond and seems endowed with a special value. And is not called Luke Skywalker sinó Eragon (Edward Speleers). Eragon hears fascinated by stories of a glorious past on riders and Dragons fighting against evil, go! as if were the Jedi in the? Clone Wars. Jeremy Irons, who recites his dialogue as if it play to Shakespeare, Brom, an instrument clear of Obi-Wan Kenobi.Arya (Sienna Guillory), although it did not unveil even in this film, is an elven Princess. And the young Eragon will be took by its beauty through dreams and visions (which not hologram), has, and will be launched into her rescue. Hence we have to Princess Leia Organa!Robert Carlyle portraying the fearsome sorcerer Durza. Perhaps to express themselves better after the weight of its make-up, Carlyle, with its huge risotadas clear us, if we didn't, is the villain of the function. Belongs to the category of the "it shadow", but it is really an excellent copy of sith.John Malkovich is King Galbatorix, the great evil that has been done with the power. It would be like the Emperor, but perhaps his (alleged) charisma you closer to Darth Vader.Hay a base for rebels, the vardenos, that are not hidden on the fourth Moon of the planet Yavin sinó in a rocky area of difficult access. Their leader, Ajihad (Djimon Hounsou), resembles Lando Calrissian.Se talks about the "magic" as if it were "the force". Some sword is very similar to the light sabers, and there are flashes instead of laser guns. Not missing a scene of career through a narrow passage. And reference is made to "fear", not as what can lead you to the dark side, but the courage (that not everything is going to be the same).The ancient dragon.R2D2 and C3PO have they have left them, but I understand that in the novel, not in the film, appears as a dwarf Orik.La dragon Saphira, the real star of the function!, strikes me as a kind of version of the Millennium Falcon, but endowed with life and with the capacity of hablar.¿Y Han Solo? As the projection progressed me towards this question. And I have to say also appears, Yes Sir!, in the forms of a young boy of black hair.Finally, I retomaré criticism for insisting that December is terrible in its decor, especially in combat sequences. "E fails even in important moments as this is the first time that Eragon rides to the Dragon (? and rhubarb any easy joke in this regard!).""Eragon" is a telefilm without hint of some, ideal personality to any desktop on Saturday or Sunday. And as it brings more sequels, a couple in portfolio, the question is if the second appears to Yoda. Taking into account the desparación of one of the characters, I would say Yes.If someone wants to contribute, or correct me, into something more, I appreciate his collaborations.</body>
</review>
