<review author="Caruco" title="Réquiem (El exorcismo de Micaela)" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>It must be acknowledged that Sandra Hüller does very well, but when the movie gets interesting, VA. and ends.</summary>
	<body>Best film and actress in the Sitges festival critics award. Silver bear for best actress, Sandra Hüller in Berlin. 82 points out of 100 is the average American critics in Metacritic. And I that I have everything ready to go on pilgrimage to Lourdes, because this species of "The Exorcist: before the start", in version "Breaking the waves" (this Yes, masterpiece), found me a suckling pig Championship, and that which does not last and hour and a half.It had been sold, I don't know if for advertising reasons or less materialistic strategies, as the response in verismo key to "the exorcism of Emily Rose", of Scott Derrickson. Although it is not necessary to specify that any proposal is more "realistic" than a film intended for mass consumption.It was inspired by the alleged case of possession diábolica documented and recognised by the Church, of the young Anneliese Michel, who died in 1976 in the town of Klingenberg, malnutrition, exhaustion, wounds and practiced exorcisms.Fantasy vs. Realidad.Y what in the movie Derrickson, another peñazo, with some effective scene, was the popular and fanciful, version where the religious author of the exorcism was good; Here, and dealt with otherwise, version of author and close to the facts, the young priest speaking rather da grima, let's go! a doubtful fan. In contrast, also appears other cure, veteran and focused on its tasks.At a time when neither science nor faith could perhaps help her too, disease, or bad, Micaela (are epilepsy, schizophrenia, paranoia?), attacked the nerves and the mind in such a way that it not only has problems to adapt to University life or sex.It will also affect the rejection of Catholic conservatism that has instilled him, above all, his possessive mother, and that sense of sin and punishment, which makes it feel a martyr.If she believes see (or see) demons, souls in penalty and santas, is that education, which if had been born in some Asian country, instead, that would appear you would be pale girls long hair scratching walls and floors.A propósito de Schmid.El German Hans-Christina Schmid, Rookie, filmed a psychological test that refuses the special and sound in favour of a purported effects more emotion and authenticity.And you do 'dogma' style, that is with photography the most natural possible, camera carrying? zooms? seemingly improvised, abruto mount, and everything by way of documentary to bring us better in this remnant of life (fateful). And although the dogma productions have given very good results, is not the case of "Requiem (the exorcism of Micaela)".It must be acknowledged that Sandra Hüller do very well, especially when it marking the hands by the nerves, or that creepy that conveys when he can not approach a cross, or takes the language to his mother. But when the movie gets interesting, goes and ends. And I said, have attended a (cracked) piece of life, but without that will move us its history, by sleeping, and leaving means to develop both in the treatment of the script as the secondary characters.For the time being, what the procession to Lourdes like me I think and instead put two candles to Santa Catalina, in which Micaela felt devotion. ' Réquiéscat In Pace' (rest in peace).</body>
</review>
