<review author="Emilio Calvo de Mora" title="Eragon" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>The problem of Eragon is not Narnia, which seeks repeated comparison: is the Lord of the rings. Popcorn, dragons and franchises...</summary>
	<body>The problem of Eragon is not Narnia, which seeks repeated comparison: is the Lord of the rings. Case that this trilogy by Peter Jackson did not exist, Eragon would be an absolute Epiphany for the calenturienta, by fantastic, mind of a teenage fact to take hours to well-nourished pages books and to lose in mythologies of Elves, elves, magic and dragons. As the machinery of Hollywood is relentless, we have to impose on Eragon several corrective actions even though none of them the film get demolished in excess.The stone found in the forest by a young and then it be egg of a prophetic Dragon under whose nose chisperreante hides the destiny of a people subjected by a despotic and barbaric King is the foundation stone of the magic of all the tales of magical kingdoms and Heroes which is deposited, in a sort of arcane, the future of the justice or the happiness of a people.All this explicit with ease in the film, but the problem is that we have already seen arguments so similar and narrated with equal or better fortune than this, for late, is irrelevant.This family film of popcorn and discreet amazement not spare. What is more: should be hosted, powered, become common currency for American producers giving green light to these taquillazos, meagre occasionally in quality, but sweeping suggestions and amenity. There are already so few films really worthy for whole family feels in the seven row and gets carried away by the magic of the big room (now leave the well-trodden argument of the desirability of the domestic film) are grateful for all that den. This rudimentary, flat and populist film is born a spectator, now young, who then paladeará other works. This is the end of my criticism. Out of that connection, Eragon is one franchise film again, Christmas, spurred by a book by massive sales and driven with ex officio, but without charm, a director once expert in special effects (Terminator 2, Master and commander, the perfect storm, save the soldier Ryan) and that here complies, without more. It is not possible, proverbs popular ask pears at del olmo said. Above, this is a very simple pear.The epic that require these stories is burdened by some short-sightedness in the scenarios, although shine (and how) in the majestic flight of the Dragon and in the final battle, which is very successful. The actors, better not speak. Jeremy Irons, curiously based in the world of the dragonería (dragons and dungeons, verbigratia), makes as it involves in its work of the young apprentice of Salvador guru, but he notices lost in a role that won't you and that does not give any actor with character mark, that is, limited to overact, providing too seen tics and gestures very greedy old Wolf in sheep (paste) to bite his already learned tooth.Robert Carlyle is a shadow, a villain of órdago, adlátere, however, the demon king and reason for all the fuss fantastic, a John Malkovich that leaves little and which, apparently, seems to saved for a sequel (Eldest). The third (Empire) this geniecito cuasiadolescente still (Christopher Paolini) that has managed to shadow his Tolkien amadio and rethink what to deliver to the youth audience, is already said, Avid these candy medievalists, pure entertainment. And will also soon make dolls and plastic dragons to fill the shelves of Toys ' r Us of half the world and the McDonalds of the other means. They are very clever todos.p.d.: my daughter, who has read the billet was defrauded, in the bottom of his heart. You had esquimlado average book. Or more. Or everything. Anyway...I return to that matter, in any case: family film. How nice.</body>
</review>
