<review author="Enrique Colmena" title="El perfume" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Version with packaging, well narrated and performed, even a Dustin Hoffman we know have a tendency to the overacting.</summary>
	<body>The novel by Patrick Suskind "perfume" is one of the big titles of masses of 20th century literature; published in 1985, was an almost instant success, mainly because its subject matter was really innovative and stimulating: the history of an inclusero, born in the 18th century, equipped with Orleans of an unparalleled sense olfactory, what will use out of the hell of misery to which his humble cot had been confined to him; but the obsession to achieve the final perfume, one that would be able to go crazy love anyone who perceive it, also, will be in addition to the sense of his life, the need to kill to get it, obtaining each Virgin woman's body the essence of the thirteen basic perfumes. The director, the German Tom Tykwer, was announced a few years ago with its certainly more than funny and groundbreaking "run, Lola, run" (whose poor digestion by some, it is true, has spawned some other Monster; see, for example, "Crank: poison in the blood"), has become now the adapter film based on a novel that has had more boyfriends in the last two decades. Even the own Stanley Kubrick came from among their projects before his death. Did not win anything with imagine what could have done the perfectionist maniac (but to which adore both) of Kubrick with this juicy literary material; better to stick with what presents Tykwer, who is a very solid adaptation, perhaps sometime too much debt in the original text (does this voice, which, especially in the beginning, does not do any favors to the cinematographic language: another thing is it is very difficult to explain the story without resorting to it?), but in any case a version with packagingwell narrated and performed even by a Dustin Hoffman who we know has a tendency to the overacting, and more in a European production like this, in which he is the only star of global dimension. Tykwer leaves the most difficult subject that arise from the novel, how graceful offer images of odors, allowing the word of Suskind, in the literary reader Magin, columbrar the most extraordinary fragrances. The director and his writers opt for the formula to show the effects of these effluents, since stricto sensu aromas can be displayed: the discovery of the Nirvana by the protagonist to smell its first female on the streets; the total and absolute orgy from the scene of the alleged execution of the murderer; the physical eventual demise, the closest thing to a bride in search of love. It is not bad formula, especially until that Odoroma, that invention of joke that took John Waters manga already makes the stack years, is not sophisticated enough? Another thing is that, perhaps for the sake of not receiving restrictive qualifications of the censors, the authors of the film have opted a pudibundez in the nude certainly shocking: while the bodies inánimes of the thirteen maidens, and hundreds of naked bodies appear in a square in the penultimate scene appear, what is sex itself does not appear virtually nonefor which has been resorted to more characteristic of buskers to actors or Extras acrobatics? Finally, the rampant Sanctimony, in cases like this is more striking than the presence, with total naturalness of sex of those that appear on the screen.</body>
</review>
