<review author="Bloody Will" title="Eragon" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Eragon is a real disaster. A genuine heresy committed against the original by Paolini.</summary>
	<body>Apparently, "Eragon" can raise already as a genuine heresy committed against the original written by the young Italian Christopher Paolini. The trilogy of "The legacy", whose first book is who now jump to screens with a worthy of a Harry Potter marketing, is called upon to deal with the Christmas calendar of Hollywood industry during the next four years, and will have much to see their numbers at the box office this weekend, or what is the same: your support, and now I see no just happy?The truth is that, in terms of plot development, "Eragon" is a real disaster. During the first half hour everything is abrupt and without hardly any explanation. Scenes can basically take two seconds, from one to another with a real rush to remove the run-up to the history in the middle and go directly to what you want to the púlbico: battles and more battles. This has a direct consequence: not connect with anything. The magical ability of the protagonist appears without ton nor are there any initiation. There are characters that run more on foot a Dragon flying and ending situations of real danger practically out the door without any opposition. Crazy.I must confess that the beginning of all this mythology is pure "Star Wars": Eragon lives on a farm with his uncle, after there being left by their parents, and before an unexpected destination, you will find his mentor, which shall guide you toward the rebels and will start it in their powers and the future that awaits you. Not you sorprendáis because finally Galbatorix, the villain in the film says "Eragon, I am your father"?.Drinking clearly part of the universe created by Tolkien (spoken in the film of Elves and dwarves), aesthetics comes to be the same, and that is a handicap for the film. With the exception of that home as Luke Skywalker, the rest of the story returns to be about tyrants, junior sorcerers and rebels against the dictatorship. With a fregadito there and there, everything is converted into a product halfway entertains, but not dazzles. Of course, not look the film through the eyes of a reader predisposed to analyze the adaptation, as I have not read the original work, and from this distance I can appreciate that, in order to convert the legend of Eragon in a commercial product, its leaders have extracted passages with more action, perdiéndo in the way other aspects that would have easily been able to remedy if not for the regrettable length of the film: 1 hour and a half in which to condense all the beast.Perhaps the best choice made by the director and his team of casting lead actor himself. The boy does not hurt, and is at least not as clueless as our friend Daniel "Potter" Ratcliffe in her first film. From there to make it an Elijah Wood is a stretch. Jeremy Irons in his line, passing the procedure, although much is far from the English actorazo that caught our attention in the 1990s. I have lost the respect and that is fatal to my opinion. At least most is who captures screen time, that to John Malkovich we nor smell and Djimon Hounson appears just 2 minutes. Book them all for the sequel. Mention aside for Robert Carlyle, in his role as the villain Durse is the only view consistent with the whole of the film.And could give the approved the film for special effects, specifically the Dragon had been the novamás. Well nor by those that Sephira, the Dragon in the film has enjoyed a CGI of all one hundred. With the time that has elapsed since "DragonHeart" or "Harry Potter and the Goblet of fire", and I think their dragons better made than the main claim of "Eragon". It will evolve in Pokemon blue?, already we will check.Ultimately, poor management, dialogos enclichados, a mediocre costumes and some special effects in the middle of a direct to DVD movie. "Eragon" has been sold as the event of the year and is everything but the future fantastic trilogy. 9 To 13 years preteens will like, but to decepeción largest to seek an Uruk-Hai and encontarme with soldiers with mask. To pass the time, but by God, not us engañéis with comparisons, which in the end are not odious: are aniquiladoras.</body>
</review>
