<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Déjà Vu" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>One film more than passable, with a last minute absolutely entertaining with their strengths and weaknesses (I think that equally), and nor do I believe it to be remembered.</summary>
	<body>Since then, increasingly is they are wearing more with the translation of titles (and subtitles) in the latest film releases of Spain. His latest "achievement" is Déjà Vu (changing the past). I know I seem very demanding, but it is that this subtitle there is extra. "Déjà vu" means "already seen" and not "changing the past". But let's go to the grain. The new film by the brother of the prodigious (occasionally) Ridley, Tony Scott, has returned to his own: frenetic pace with a shocking picture, but, however, with a simple script and several deceptions (to the public). It is not that Déjà Vu is a little credible film, but is directly a hundred percent amazing film. Although it is true that the director nor intends to have us we believe. OK, clearly that feeling already seen or lived is a mental effect, but by God, about the program to the Minority Report (but visionando the past) isn't any trick of the mind, it is simply bullshit. So we could say Déjà Vu presents a mixture of genres, for my taste, too abusive: science fiction, thriller, action, adventure, drama and romance (these latter two quite away from what could be expected of the director of the fire of revenge). But well, on the other hand thank you Scott the balance between all of them, as much as some may appear inadequate to me. Of course, if you find defects to the film would find you, and several. Let's start with that so stimulating program for the protagonists, which allows them to travel in the past through a theory (or paranoia) that has invented such a Terry Rossio and Bill Marsilii. If one intends to shoot a film with fictional touches, that does not abuse. And it seems that Tony Scott has not understood yet. I think that the idea of dealing with that feeling so exhilarating of déjà vu and then add an invented program that allows you to travel in time of one it is really nothing credible is already good enough. So much of the film (in particular, the first hour) relies on this silly nonsense that you mess and makes the film a quality quite lower which would have had if he had avoided. Another defect is the false drama, Yes. In the fire of vengeance had dose in abundance of pure and simple drama, which were fairly credible. Here, Déjà Vu, they are completely unrelated to our feelings. Let me explain: the film can't you convey the feeling of despair the protagonist and much less the victim (one inadequate, in artistic terms, Paula Patton). So that the main shortcomings of this film are based on abuses of genres or terms that a tape of this kind, is better to avoid them, either because it is more credible and entenedora, and therefore more enjoyable, or by the simple fact that sobran.But we must also congratulate the brother of Ridley as to convey the sense of déjà vu excellently and provide us a tape entretenídisima (especially in the last hour). This last part is based on the outbreak of the plot, in a less credible way, on this occasion, makes you, at least, entering the game. No more destriparé the plot because but finish by explain this interesting end. And another good aspect of the film is, always nice to see, performance by Denzel Washington (authentic collaborating director). It is not to have a brilliant interpretation, that its role is not to be much, but it's nice to see him make these bromillas always and provide its Doug Carlin a little more of humanism. The subtraction of the cast is simply correct, although the semi-protagonista, Paula Patton, is really bad. He can't cry, he can't provide credibility. In short, that would have greatly improved with the magnificent Ashley Judd. One film more than passable, with a last minute absolutely entertaining with their strengths and weaknesses (I think that equally), and that I do not think it is remembered, at least that her return to feeling.The phrase "Atentos, are about to witness a murder".</body>
</review>
