<review author="Ramón Balcells" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Authentic wonder of entertainment. A tape full of authentic and realistic action that, despite their long duration - 144 minutes - is not heavy.</summary>
	<body>Myself, I am always left with Roger Moore, not afraid at all to Daniel Craig. Moreover, I wanted to him change the face to James Bond, after some ridiculous movies starring Pierce Brosnan which on science fiction. Because now, the most prestigious agent of Great Britain has become, more innovative, real, mature and imperfect, but with a twist of plot, already to the new adventure based on the first adventure, written by Ian Flemming and titled Casino Royale. The fact that a film is written by Paul Haggis and IE, and much. The double Oscar-winning and nominated by his perfect dash of Million Dollar Baby, brings to the main script of the film (written by Neal Purvis and Robert Wade) one touch of seriousness, realism and Brutalism. And the truth is that you notice, and much. The new Bond is an agent with defects, mistakes in their work, irony, and above all, very gross. The film opens in a black and white precious, with a rich contrast. James Bond, an agent without a license to kill, is loaded with a pair of shots on a snitch in his Office, although having previously explained how ended his contact (tuned to the blurred scenes of the bathroom, shot with an unpublished sadism in the last Bond). From there, start the magnificent opening credits, with mixtures of games of cards and guns and characters in movement formed by ACEs, diamonds and hearts. The fact is that Casino Royale has a top hotel, hardly seamless, attractive. The rest of the film will be better that can see it you, because but loses the grace (has already well, lost with what I said now). We are going to talk about Daniel Craig, then. I have to say that I am absolutely satisfied with the election of this actor, say what, actorazo. Nobody better than he could have interpreted this hard type, although a tad Ghost (but not pull vacuum by a swamp, not), with irony English, elegant when it does lack and beast and sadistic when also does. Also in this new installment, secret agent maintains a love affair long, nothing passing, as it used to happen with the previous ones, so the feature of embobado by this delight is Eva Green also has noted. Anyway, that this English actor would say that it is the perfect Bond. Let me now turn to the Bond girl. Eva Green, highlighted by his performance in dreamers, Bertolucci, also might be the perfect Bond girl. The why? The truth is that it has several reasons: tie, so to speak, with the protagonist, that creates such picaresque including Chemistry two (at the beginning of their relationship) which makes that Vesper Lynd (that is how it is called), is a woman of strong character and nothing, a weak symbol, as it was the case in the other Bond. Here, both Bond and Vesper are symbol of strength. In short, both are the Bond and the perfect Bond girl, and this makes Casino Royale Casino Royale. Another strong point of the film are the numerous scenes of action. All of them, from which opens the film, located in Madagascar, they are really dizzying, full of tension, long, but however nothing heavy. You could highlight each one of them, and is that the already named Madagascar, both, the Venice airport or which is located in the Museum, for not letting me hiper-tensos intermediate between each poker game, make the film shows his more adventurous and more realistic side. And it is that Casino Royale not lacks nothing. We have spoken of love and action, which is why I need the drama. The tape has many touches of this genre, so many, I will highlight some of them: the heavy conscience that it has stuck in the head Vesper, seeing James fighting on the ladder of the casino, makes immerse themselves in the shower of the hotel to forget about the past, it so Bond, how not, her help sitting beside her. Or in that same piece, do not miss the agent bleeding as a desperate and a half crying for have been uploaded to this pair. That Brosnan would never do it, come on, that neither despeinaría fighting. Attentive, SPOLIER. And finally, the last scene in which appears Vesper, drowning in the submerged lift of a Venetian building and Bond with her trying to get out of there, although knowing full well that he is saving the woman who has betrayed. This scene is, quite simply, the best of the film. End of the SPOLIER. Finally, within the more artistic aspects of the film, highlight the evil Le Chiffre, played by Danish Mads Mikkelsen. In all the James Bond movies, the villain of the function always had intended ending the world, either destroying it (view to a kill or die another day) or liquidating it (all the others). In Casino Royale, the evil is not intended to do this sort of thing. Its intention is his work, arms trafficking, and rather than submit to Bond to machines that rub science fiction, what torture with a whip directly (attentive to that scene.) (It is terrible and sometimes ironic). Well say that Mads Mikkelsen is superb in his role, crying blood as making crying tears to his enemies. Within the technical aspects, Casino Royale is not devoid of detail. Music, superbly carried out by David Arnold and Chris Cornell (in the magnificent main song, You know my name).And of course, the Visual effects, that without past thread (here die another day), are incredibly credible (as the scene of the collapse of the Venetian building). In short, the film by Martin Campbell is a true marvel of entertainment - good-. A tape full of authentic and realistic action that, despite its long duration - 144 minutes-, is not heavy, or much less. Do not miss Casino Royale, although you are not fans of James Bond. I would say that this is better still.</body>
</review>
