<review author="Silvia" title="La noche de los girasoles" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A story that makes us reflect on the coincidences, bad luck, how you can change lives in a single night and how many people's lives can change following a single circumstance or as a result of the actions of a single person.</summary>
	<body>The night of the sunflowers is an original rural suspense story, set in a quiet village in which seems that it nothing ever happens. It is the story of a night in which the lives of some characters changed completely after living an extreme situation that marks all in one way or another. A film of intrigue, of police suspense in the wake of a murder in which a series of coincidences are involved a group of people unknown among them.Pedro (Mariano Alameda) and Stephen (Carmelo Gómez) are two cavers arriving in a village in a mountain area to explore a cave. The bride of Stephen, Gabi, accompanies them up there but does not come with them and decides to wait in a nearby spot, at the foot of the mountain. But when the espeolólogos return, they find Gabi dam of an anxiety attack. As soon as they have the opportunity, the boys decide to take revenge on the person who has frightened to Gabi but mistakenly kill another individual that has the misfortune of appearing at the wrong time.The story is structured in a puzzle in which parts are slowly fitting throughout history. Each chapter of the story leads for a label that can give us clues about its protagonists (the man in the motel, the cavers, the man of the way) and does not follow a linear order but that the director plays to explain the story by leaps in time or flashbacks so that the story is told from all points of view of the different characters. However, despite knowing the end of some sequences, the interest of the Viewer to know how the story remains intact. The plot is fully explained but left some loose. The director knows dosed tension throughout history even though it is from the turning point involving the murder when the viewer never ceases to surprise and not left to guess about what is happening. The shortage of light helps foster that intriguing atmosphere, in a manner achieved an environment where everything seems possible.Apart from a suspense film, it's a drama of development of characters and even a costumbrista history reflects the concern peoples by its almost inevitable abandonment. The directorial debut of Jorge Sánchez-Cabezudo Spanish has as protagonists with Carmelo Gómez, Judith Diakhate, Celso Bugallo, Manuel Morón, Mariano Alameda and Vicente Romero. Interpretations are notable as a whole, but perhaps the most disturbing role it embodies the Chief of police (Celso Bugallo). The character of the Chief of police is located in the dilemma of choosing between acting according to dictates his professional ethics or according to their own interests.The filmmaker explained in an interview that interested him much further in the psychological development of the characters: "they are ordinary characters faced with extreme situations, and perhaps one of the major objectives of the film is precisely the consider how that ordinary people can result in a situation so complicated and dramatic;" What are the circumstances, and the psychological, personal and emotional mechanisms that lead to do what they do and above all justified in their actions to continue living. "It is not a film of good and bad, it is a very human characters.A story that makes us reflect on the coincidences, bad luck, how you can change lives in a single night and how many people's lives can change following a single circumstance or as a result of the actions of a single person. A drama that leaves an aura of sadness, fatalism, because what is narrated from the fiction can bring much to our reality.</body>
</review>
