<review author="Silvia" title="En la ciudad" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>In the city is the story of how little that sometimes we know although we convivamos together: how us deceive ourselves about our lives and how to deceive others to make our lives a little easier or just pride.</summary>
	<body>Barcelona. A big city that hides a multitude of small stories. In this urban scenario, a group of friends open us the doors of their homes and their lives to leave us to witness what happens to them in their day to day. Characters that silent much more than what they say. Characters that show much less than hide. It is the story of one group of thirtysomethings friends who are daily, share all their experiences but that hide an important part of their lives: their most private feelings. Only the viewer will be witness of everything: their lies, secrets, hidden desires and infidelities.Eduard Fernández (member of the cast of Alatriste) - and that won Goya Award as best supporting actor for his role in this film - embodies the character of Mario, a tormented type who suspects that his wife, Sara, (Vicenta N?)(Dongo) tricks and who will fight throughout the film to try to confirm your doubts.Irene (Monica López) shows an attitude of rejection and avoids seeing her friend of faculty that is reunited after years without being. Their marriage does not work while her husband Manu (beloved Chisco) constantly strive to satisfy their desire.Tomás (Alex Brendemünl) also hides something: its relationship with a minor, which on top of that is the niece of his friend Mario. And finally, Sofia (María Pujalte) dam of a relationship with a Frenchman whose posturing tries to constantly justify against the demáspor not be like a spiteful.The story full of deceptions reminds Tapas, although in the latter drama is disguised as comedy in an attempt to downplay the issue. In the city is the story of how little that sometimes we know although we convivamos together: how us deceive ourselves about our lives and how to deceive others to make our lives a little easier or just pride. Easy to empathize with these characters because, at the end and all, as como dice says one of the protagonists: "we all have secrets, huh?".</body>
</review>
