<review author="Alberto Concepción" title="Brick" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Set of good intentions... it stays in that, in purpose.</summary>
	<body>From time to time, raises one sees what kind of film. It is likely that, or either commercial (although many times is often confused with conventional) either 'of the understood'. I'm not who go to mess with the personal way that each have see movies. But after (I) given a chance with Brick, think that this short introduction has enough to do. Brick is an unconventional film. Of these intended to (especially intended to) be not only a film. And this is very bien.hasta some point. Brendan is a fairly atypical student (he and his entourage) received an unexpected call from his ex-girlfriend, Emily, of which virtually nothing known. But we do know that she is dead. In this way, the film shows that resulted in her first scene, to return two days ago, tell all? What has happened and the final consequences. Look good, right? To me also. But it is that, on the basis of this premise, the thing does not end March. And one knows when are ten minutes of tape: all is full of good intentions, and perhaps that which makes him to continue watching the rest of the (somewhat excessive) footage. But it is wrong. Or perhaps marche with that slight feeling of permanent casting. In my case, I have it clear: the cause of this run-rún of my brain was seeing too many elements 'for connoisseurs', with a not too defined and insufficiently clarifying rhythm: an 'aura of postmodernism' I did not finish curdling. I like to occasionally leave a stream of fresh air that prevents that the air vicie too in this film: how many times you said: ' go, what typical!, and you've complained about something so when you see a movie? Probably this not you go with Brick. But also it is likely let you something indifferent, unless you're a understand or want to be him (although in this latter case, within tí know definitely he is not so). That Yes, I like to be the idea that the film is bad. Because it is not. At all. It has its virtues (originality, different approach), but perhaps not sufficient as so that run-rún continue playing. In addition, interpretations can be liked by many, although they do not pass the simple 'meet'. Ultimately, the film debut of Rian Johnson holds promise. It has perhaps been too pretentious to be 'different' or alternative; or it has failed to bring us into the history of the most appropriate way. If what is rewarding are the ideas, then bravo. I only hope that, with some more experience, this director (who is also a screenwriter of the film) trusty us good movies. I trust in this, because talent is no doubt that it has.</body>
</review>
