<review author="José A. Peig" title="Eragon" rank="1" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>We are not going to waste time explaining the hows and whys. To say the least, and thus we are reassuring, Eragon blatantly copy clichés of other more fortunate productions, productions which also merit the category of classics in their field.</summary>
	<body>Frankly, it is bad but it is not so bad. Say what is bad but until vomitivas dimensions. It is an insult to the Viewer, it is a putada.Maybe what is happening is that you enter us the neuro as the genre of epic fantasy is one of our two or three favorite film genres. And I stress "film" because I've always thought that epic fantasy, if it is well made, has a greater power of fascination represented on the screen than in the written letter. But not, but seriously, but esto.pero esto.pero esto.pero this what is?. Ye, for the donkey you are asking for pears to del olmo. It is Christmas, pardillo, cinema one adventure very much in the use of these dates of magic and illusion. Opportunistic product that lands star in a bad historical moment. We stress the historical context.But, damn, boy this (bad actor, what asco's uncle) blonde makes crumbs with dragons and nymphs has followed Luke Skywalker and Frodo Baggins, two characters of luxury for the fantástico-épico genus, authentic Archetypes of the adventure film such as Odyssey and metaphor for our lives, of good entertainment film, ostia. Because, come on, do not fuck with me, or Marc Hamill Elijha Wood were great actors, nor nor interpreted especially complex characters, but how well-defined and represented were in an environment of ideals, hazards, and profiles of a splendid characterisation and sense of how wonderful, allowing even than two characters flat as folios have ease, the dimension of the real and true development along an adventure that goes from point A to point B. (more) (afternoon or more early we hincaremos him the tooth, under the point vision of "Images and words", the saga of George Lucas and Peter Jackson trilogy, and they give me chills only of thinking in the resultado.y how much we have to learn). Hey, Eragon entertains, right?. Shit. Why?. Because that is the worst thing, so the bad vomitous entertains us. And you have a fitting end to the end and all, than it is to tell a story for children. But "E.T" was not something that same, and "The Goonies"?. Exact, here comes the tragedy. That one and the other are the same but Eragon nobody will be agreed within twenty years and "The Goonies" and "E.T", around thirty, still selling like the rosquilletas in successive editions and being revised with permanent I enjoy year after year. Those were the times of good cinema innocent, for children and parents, but done with a heart at the height of the illusions and live magic in everyone, adults and children. Children and parents today deserve the same. Eragon could be a more than passable work distractora in dates of illusion, but is such the unwillingness and lack of talent...absence of.?. No, it is not, that is the worst thing. Not me I think that talent is over. The effectiveness and ability to James Cameron or Richard Donner, both equipped with a modest master of entertainment film, is not so difficult to achieve. Let us not talk of Spielberg, an individual with film in the veins that, in specific cases, was able to raise it to anthologies, mystical, proportions even. It is is is that you watch that it has bémoles. and I me cago in tó. what I talking about Spielberg, Donner and Cámeron?. Nostalgia. We grew up with them and thanks to their small jewels of recreational and leisure movie fan sensibility, today many love the film throughout its range or route that quality is concerned, since Mel Gibson to Ingmar Bergman, from Roland Emmerich up M. Night Shyamalan and everything what we throw. Come, we relax. And seriously, "Eragon" meets justito in its role of Christmas film, can be seen with pleasure has its good moments, I would venture to say that it is correct and honest because it gives what it promises. The uneducated Viewer - cinefilamente speaking - enough. But there is a canon established and known to all those who we love and mamamos Luke Skywalker or Frodo Baggins. Not I am assessing Eragon based on stupid comparisons with "The Lord of the rings" or "Star Wars" (because such a comparison would be stupid). We are pointing out the difference between what is well done and what not this well done in the field of fantasy and epic or the sword and brujeria or as you want to call it.We are not going to waste time explaining the hows and whys. To say the least, and thus we are reassuring, Eragon blatantly copy clichés of other more fortunate productions, productions which also merit the category of classics in their field. Behind this plagiarism there is some uniqueness. Blame already know who he is. Stefen December?, to be devoted to something else. Work­the, to crack her.</body>
</review>
