<review author="Jose Luis" title="Casino Royale" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A new Bond, one more realistic that will help to keep the saga live for a long time.</summary>
	<body>From the beginning the new the 007 adventure Casino Royale, you know different, the traditional shot toward the camera that can be seen in all previous tapes in the first few seconds is absent, only to surprise, minutes later, when they tell us the genesis of this shot is to this day the personal brand of the legendary spy. These kinds of surprises this fills the tape number 21 James Bond.Claro that, when you make any move, ends losing something or rediscovering things that one believed lost and that perhaps is what happens with the move that made the producers and director of the film, who give us a new bond, after closing a cycle with another day to dienow is returning to the beginning, on the basis of the first novel written by Ian Fleming on the super agent and presenting us with a bond more young, novice, impulsive and therefore one more human, one that is wrong and that bleeds, as any mortal.The tape begins when Bond completed the requirements to become a 00 agent, i.e. to have licence to kill and he is given his first mission, capture a terrorist who roams somewhere in Africa, which will give you the clue to a banker of terrorists has become a millionaire thanks to acts of terrorism more cruel in recent times, but to stop him, Bond will have to overcome it, not using force, if not their skills for the poker.By what this time, is not surprising, that some of the scenes more weather of the film are carried out on the table in a casino, relying on the work of the actors to create a tension that will keep the Viewer to the edge of your seat, as well as the successful good and intelligent action sequences, that inject you adrenaline to the tape.But perhaps the main ingredient that detonates the exciting adventure is the performance of Daniel Craig, who focuses not only on posing and modeling the esmoking, if not to give to each scene the fair measure, that transforms it a persecutor and murderer beggarly to a seductive, a cynical rival, or a man torn between good and evil and finally lost in the love of a womanso much that it threatens to leave his life of martinis and weapons to one side.Judi Dench as M, this back, printing his style as the head of Bond, willing to keep it at Bay to as place. Eva Green is the Bond girl, who far from being a spy, is an ordinary accountant with the mission to avoid Bond wasted the money from the Government, but with the charm necessary to carry the Spy to his doom.Although the director Martin Campbell, tries to put serious towards the end, lengthening and resulting the third act and thus weakening the closure, succeeds in creating a realistic Ribbon, which away from the action and technological fantasy cheap, gives a new air to the saga, which will undoubtedly help to keep alive for 20 new movies or more.Only left me a question for filmmakers: where the Earth were the silhouettes of naked women in the opening sequence of titles?</body>
</review>
