<review author="Jose Luis" title="Hijos de los hombres" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A tape it brings something new to science fiction, proving that not only gender is made to deploy special effects. A work master, futuristic but realistic, painful but very enjoyable.</summary>
	<body>Visions film about the end of the world there are many and of all kinds, from nuclear disasters, deadly epidemics, even the most improbable as alien invasions and robotic rebellion. But that suggested in children of men, is one of the most realistic and creepy that I've seen in a long time? And if the man is his own executioner? and that perhaps if one day the human species loses the ability to playback? As such the person young man of the world is 18 years old, no more babies or children across the globe and schools are abandoned buildings and thing of the past? If you lived in a world where there is no hope and know that every day you live humanity is dying? Scary isn't it?Much more if we consider that the story takes place in the near future, the 2027, and the world is in crisis with outbreaks of generalized violence; do one day like any other, humanity cries the death of Diego, the world youngest person, Theo (Clive Owen) walking desolate without hope, until his ex-wife gets in touch with him to ask a very important favor: to help you get a permit to transport a young woman into a city in conflict? a young woman who is miraculously pregnant.A script concise, direct, intelligent and brilliant; goes us to this scene of desolation, focusing only on the human point of view, where they are not scientific to explain us reasons women can not pregnant, or tests that they are carried out to resolve the crisis, nor military us explaining that most of the cities of the world are involved in endless conflicts. On the contrary, we see through the eyes of ordinary people, like us, are you not interested in listening to medical explanations, who prefer to evade the issue and try to forget that. An exact script which small doses will revealing us the complete picture that is the world, which gives us a moment of joy before that, with infinite cruelty, we restriegue in the face that this is not a happy film.The picture is borne by Emmanuel Lubezki, one of the most talented Mexicans from the scope of the film, who we have come to beautiful images, this time undertakes to portray the chaos, with the expression of the word, recreated by an excellent production design, masterfully, detailing both the time and the mood of the film; every street is crowded trash, each wall is striped and on the verge of collapse.This year, the three Directors Mexican, best-known worldwide have released one tape, Guillermo del Toro (El Laberinto del Fauno), Guillermo Arriaga (Babel), Alfonso Cuarón (children of men), and on the basis of these three tapes, I can assure you, that the most talented of them all is Cuarón, who with this excellent staging reaffirms as a directorwho alongside the brilliant technical aspects gives your tapes with a deep emotional and thematic. Carrying out this time, tape it brings something new to science fiction, proving that not only gender is made to deploy special effects and that can address such serious issues as the expected loss of humanity, symbolized by the lack of children worldwide.When I was a kid, me ill and I had to inject, my mother approached me a pillow and told me that her it bite very hard to not feel so much pain, there were several moments in this film that I wanted to have a pillow to bite her, as in the pesadillesca and long, long sequence, in which the protagonists have to cross a city in war, in which the camera almost flush with the floor moves, like the characters, hiding where possible, even blood splatters the screen and far from "correct" detail, the drops of blood are there to make us more painful sight.</body>
</review>
