<review author="Jose Luis" title="Infiltrados" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A detective story that Scorsese transforms her into a memorable sample of the genre.</summary>
	<body>If ever going to give a prize Oscar Martin Scorsese as best Director, and finally acknowledge his excellent career, should they give it once, for his excellent work on the infiltrators, the tape that some consider already a masterpiece and a classic crime film? And perhaps these assertions are not so risky.On this occasion Scorsese, puts his masters to the order of a story that takes place in the streets of Boston, which could be one city, which succeeds in creating a direct dialogue with the public, rarely seen in his film.Based on the Taiwanese movie Internal Affairs, the story is about the rise of two policemen, one (Di Caprio) infiltrated the lines of the bloody Irish mafia, commanded no more and no less than by Costello (Jack Nicholson), and another (Damon), whose career rising is not more than with the intention of passing information to your own boss; Costello.A long history is narrated as each of the two characters they are involved in more complex situations, taking them to live trying to conceal his true identity constantly and playing his own skin every minute.The task force could not be unbeatable, Jack Nicholson, as the omnipotent mafia boss, filling his character of a cynicism bordering on fun, becoming an antithesis of the godfather of Marlon Brando. Leonardo Di Caprio performed the best performance of his career, far above his celebrated work on the Aviator, becoming the absolute protagonist drove the audience to the bag with just a few scenes. Matt Damon, his counterpart, completes the trio and Boston city, its streets, its various locations are backed by a very good cast that includes Mark Wahlberg, Martin Shen, Alec Baldwin and the beautiful ribbon, Vera Farmiga.La, become a character more, an atmosphere perfect for that the actions take place in the proper environment. And is there where passes one of the scenes more memorable, in Chinatown, where the characters of Damon and DiCaprio, very similar each other chase each other, trying to discover.With this tape in addition, Scorsese returns to the usual violence used in their first tape, this type of violence which in less than a minute, several characters have died with their heads reventadas bullets and that verbal violence that allows that the word fuck repeat 236 times. And it is also one of their tapes with a resulting rate and an overwhelming energy, which seems to be dedicated to all those who believe that he is a boring director.The only detail that many could refute him, is the end of the tape, which surely divides to the public in two, those who loved and those who hated and that could certainly be the subject of a lengthy discussion.In short, what appears to be a simple police story that someday has in channel five a Saturday night, is actually a complicated, intense and intelligent thriller, a tape that without doubt will be remembered for a long time, in the hands of any director may have been a rehash any but in the hands of a wise and experienced artistbecomes in a memorable and essential work.</body>
</review>
