<review author="Jose Luis" title="Babel" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>A spiritual tape that to understand uses several unforgettable images.</summary>
	<body>A Mexican Nanny in charge of two American children have to decide between do their job or attend the wedding of his only son. A couple of American spouses who walk by Morocco suffer from what appears to be a terrorist attack. A Moroccan pastor is to raise their children. And a young Japanese sordomuda strives to communicate with his father and with his environment, at the same time that is desperately losing her virginity.All this believe it or not is part of a single tape, it's Babel, the third tape in collaboration between the screenwriter Guillermo Arriaga and director Alejandro González Iñárritu and as they threaten will be the last, citing creative differences. Separation artistic that leaves a big challenge to Iñárritu for their upcoming projects alone, without already having the depth, the force and the emotionalism of the greater Arriaga.Y scripts challenge yet, after this third film, in short the most stylized, tidiest, more poignant and although sounds weird to say it, the more hopeful.Both have these stories as a pretext to talk about globalization and the growing lack of understanding between Americans and Mexicans, between the Americans and the potential terrorists, but also between husband and wife, between father and son, between brother and brother.These several story lines that are sliding one between the other, different pace and time, while that history to the history of the now mature actor Brad Pitt and the beautiful Cate Blanchett is happening in a couple of hours of Adriana Barraza, in one of the performances more realistic I've seen in a long time and whose class is easier to find in theater and not film ithappens in 24 hours or more, but this is not any impediment so that stories can narrate a few among others.With a slow and leisurely pace, we skip the Moroccan deserts desert border between Mexico and United States, then a big leap towards the colourful and noisy streets of Japan. Flooding the tape with long sequences without dialogues, but intense all and poignant, highlighting two particularly, whereby some characters discover some place unknown to them, like a pair of children who visit for the first time Tijuana and are surprised at the intense images see behind crystals of their cars, or as the Group of tourists who come to a desolate village of Moroccowhose conditions are far from his comfortable life.And although it's accessible for all types of audience tape, this find history too slow and less chaotic and climate that loves dogs, are more suede tape contemplative and artistic, but somehow, there are some parts unnecessarily long on the Japanese side, although he intends whatever the most sublime, in fact, is the story more weakconcentrated in its artificiosa form partly neglected his Fund, greatly contrasting with the rest of the tape.Santaolalla music, Rodrigo Prieto photography and design art of Brigitte Broch, Iñárritu usual collaborators, make Act of appearance, with the difficult task of giving cohesion to this shredded tape, quite truthfully portraying the way of life from various regions of the world, including their rituals? Know how is a Mexican village wedding anyone? They do not have to look further, see this tape and will discover it.And as if the different languages spoken in the tape were not sufficient, suddenly the silence falls between their characters, of those intense silence that uncomfortable, painful and move, moments that uses very well the director showing that he is owner of a flawless technique. And declaring that, sometimes, to really understand us, the words are not necessary.</body>
</review>
