<review author="Jose Luis" title="Pequeña miss sunshine" rank="5" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>An independent, brilliant, tape being debated between the intelligent hilarity and more honest drama.</summary>
	<body>The father is a loser trying to sell its formula for success, grandfather inhaled cocaine and advised her grandson be promiscuous, son wants to be a pilot Aviator and as they do not allow has vowed to remain silent until it is achieved, gay Uncle tried to commit suicide because of a broken heart, the small daughter and plump wants to be a child beauty queen mother tries to put order in all this chaos. And all they are mounted in a, just as chaotic journey, aboard an old van Volks Wagen yellow in one of the best and funniest films of the year.Although regularly insist much on the screenplays of tapes that I see, in this occasion I have stopping me to talk about it further, I believe is one of the brightest I've seen filmed in a long time, from its simplicity, its accuracy and spontaneity, apparently, without great effort goes destornillante laughter, but smartwithout falling into the typical Gringo and silly, comedy to deeply poignant moments, without making dramatic fanfare. A script that is not wasted, nor is wasted, gives each character, its just time your break, and who will step by step building a whole full of color and intensity.But for a film it is not enough with an excellent script, we need an extraordinary address, and this ran in charge of the authors of the script, it's Valerie Faris and Jonathan Dayton, those responsible for an impressive amount of music videos for groups such as Red Hot Chili Peppers and r. e. M.'s iconic, them together, were in charge of the simple but fair implementation of the tapeacrobáticamente balance several opposite tones which has the story.But without a doubt the greatest success of his work, it is the acting ensemble, to get to the right actress for each character and the actor and also, put them to work forming an excellent team on screen, a real family, rarely seen in the film. From Toni Collete as the mother, Greg Kinnear as the father, Steve Carrell as the suicidal guy, until the grandfather and the more young, all performing outstanding acting work, always highlighting the irreconcilable differences between each of the members of the family and taking the limit her adventures? And misadventures!In this way the directors erected a story about the nature of the family, the search for authenticity and at the same time an incisive critique of the Yankee life that aims to make everything that touches in a beauty contest, as one of the characters screams; is life a beauty contest after another high school, the University? A life in which it is assumed all should Peel for being winners and a country seen as losers and "freaks" to all those who do not try to. But as the story progresses you end up wondering: who is really normal or "freak"? Who is really a loser?Do and although it may seem complicated perhaps the complete film can be summarized to a single scene, great, fun and meaningful at the same time, that that, once the vehicle in that travel it decomposes, everyone has to push him to throw him to walk and one uninterested between jumping and racing? What this is not be part of a family?</body>
</review>
