<review author="Tito Chinchan" title="Eragon" rank="3" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Film aimed at a teenage audience, with dragons, swords, wizards and magic, Kings tyrants and plebeian malcontents, resistance and invincible armies, heroes and villains, etc. Facilitated something to do between polvorón and marzipan.</summary>
	<body>Today I will roll cultural and I will tell you that this movie is based on a series of juvenile books, so it was intended to compare it with Harry Potter, Narnia, and the Lord of the rings. Well, it seems to me that it has very substantial differences, this is first focused towards youth audiences as Harry Potter, not as Narnia was more child (and for me I wear white) or the Lord of the rings which is more adult. On the other hand, is one short film not as the others. Perhaps too short. And the theme addresses if it is of the style of the others, magic and fantasy with a type that without knowing as he comes his time in life. Its momentazo I would say. In comparison I think it is the weaker of the first four parts, but it is not bad.The film is a kid who suddenly dropped a gem like a giant melon in the hands, so, without more. Living in a difficult time, in which a King took command of the world (or the country or the region or that are I) thanks to the Dragons then destroyed to stay as the sole holder of one. Total, which is that the giant gem is not a gem (was obvious) if not an egg of dragon that you chose him so he gallop. So a loins of a Blue Dragon named Safira has to destroy the evil King that and to its powerful army of ugly guys and evil and dark magicians. The repanocha, right?Being the very original approach, the film is enjoyable. We know that at the end we won the good and the bad, lost in all of this style, but we have to do as they do and special effects used to reach that end. The environments are quite well done, with landscapes of those who put the willies. Special effects we are not too good and it is that you aside from the Dragon (Dragon, forgiveness) and the final battle, there is little else. The actor protagonist is to turn boinazos to expel him from the recording, but as it is the axis of history, we have to hold us. As default the film would put that development is a little hasty, as if they were putting many things in the hour and a half long. If it had been longer had happened nothing.In short, film aimed at a teenage audience, with dragons, swords, wizards and magic, Kings tyrants and plebeian malcontents, resistance and invincible armies, heroes and villains, etc. Facilitated something to do between polvorón and marzipan.</body>
</review>
