<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Fresas Salvajes" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Bergman in its purest form. At the same time sensitive, tough cryptic and heartbreaking.</summary>
	<body>The day I started to see "Source of the maiden", Ingmar Bergman was a little scared as to expectation after hearing comments about cryptic of the great Swedish cinema. When the screening ended, I stayed a while in silence, reflecting, and it was then that I decided to continue discovering the work of the Nordic director. "The seventh seal" first and then "Wild strawberries", which is the film of which deal with these lines.Wild strawberries introduces us squarely in the mind of a doctor who attends their retirement and that along the journey up the University where the honors will be developed (which decided last minute to perform in car after a strange dream) makes a tour inside by what has been his life. A life full of contrasts, like any other person. A great man for the majority, but not to his son, who always judged harshly. NI for her daughter-in-law, or even the person that seems closest to him, to be his housekeeper. Bergman shows us the twilight of a superb, disciplined and hard man, but it also evokes moments of tenderness of his youth, in his summer home. It is a duality which probably lies within each of us, but that is difficult to portray with mastery and sensibility that Bergman makes here.So, halfway between the real and surreal, shows us a man strong, severe weaknesses, but that at the same time provided as it has escaped the life of hands without having demonstrated that he is as capable of love as any other person. All this adorned by an extraordinary interpretation and a magnificent handling of shadows and lights at a time in which the media, obviously, were not those of now. And finally, the end open, typical in Swedish. Although perhaps lack a bit of consistency to the script in general. As if you were things in the dark. Something that would most likely move so that the spectator reflect on these small gaps that seem to exist.At least, this is what has seemed to me, although clear, sure that escape me many things, because, why deny it, Bergman was a director to which cost work understand in its entirety.</body>
</review>
