<review author="Oscar Cantero" title="Volver" rank="4" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Finally we see an Almodóvar which portrays scenes of real life, unadorned, without extrañezas. A loa to the women of his house in the background are the backbone of our society gets upset who gets upset.</summary>
	<body>It is not that I do not like, but I admit that I've always thought that Almodóvar is a director overrated. I particularly enjoy more with Garci, Trueba or Julio Médem, but as I said my grandmother, something will have water when they bless. And that is if we talk about film blessings, this manchego, almost as universal as the cheese, them all. None of the major festivals of cinema of Europe or America has overlooked in its work.The truth is that return is the film that I liked how many they've seen him, which have been almost all. And I think that it has been the case because in this film presents a more realistic view of the world. It is a story that has greater veneer of verisimilitude, and that finally it has detached excessively histriónicos characters that usually pulular pos his films.Return is a film full of sensitivity, where the women return to be the pillars of the work removing arrests for bills with life and move forward with everything. It is a tribute to the Spanish woman from his home. That which does not aspire to the cover of Vogue magazine or to be received by Zapatero. That woman who is which maintains homes, families, struggling every day and that seems to embarrass much zagal converted to yuppie desagradecido (and unfortunate).From the impeccable, technical point of view. The silences that speak for themselves, changes in level, the close-ups and the subtle game of lights where there.And interpretations, only praise. Carmen Maura IMHO it shines above the rest, and possibly she and Almodóvar do know, although the Maura is already everything and looking back to a possible nomination to the Oscar, Penelope Cruz sells more. All this without diminishing one iota the interpretation of the latter, which despite not being my devotion to his usual inexpressiveness santa, performed a commendable work. Perhaps this is the greatest merit of Almodóvar: get that Penelope Cruz is convincing. Chus Lampreave and Lola Dueñas, seems that even they are acting, natural that get them every gesture, every word, every move.Return reflects everyday life. That life that many people want to flee desperately but that sooner or later you just hoping precisely that, again.</body>
</review>
