<review author="Jeremy Fox" title="Déjà Vu" rank="2" maxRank="5" source="muchocine">
	<summary>Two hour thriller with certain doses of action, not much for a weekend afternoon entretenidillas</summary>
	<body>Tony Scott is, in my opinion, a correct director with some skill to the frantic Assembly. Sometimes offers the best of himself and come out you good films like "The last boy scout", "Love at point-blank range" or "Spy Game" and sometimes get you worse, but in general, qualities as yours one can only aspire, it is no longer little, directing commercial tapes of those who entertain for a couple of hours and then forget. "Déjà vu" is of the latter.I will not go into details about the synopsis of the film. Let me just say is research Doug Carlin (Denzel Washington) carried out to stop the terrorist that exploded a ferry in new course Orleans.Por, the title already gives clues about this, the time travel will play his role in the film. But that nobody will break the head thinking about travel in the time seriously because it makes no sense. We are before a Hollywood product that aims to entertain and not a treaty physicist or mathematician. And as a result, although simple, it works.Despite this simplicity you mention, it must be acknowledged that not missing the story elements of a certain originality. For example we are witnessing one of the most peculiar persecution that have been. At least on paper, because in images is shot with disdain and simple correction losing all the strength of the idea. The same could be applied to the rest of the film.With regard to the actors say that Denzel Washington meets in its role of police like so many other times, Val Kilmer shows that it is perfectly interchangeable with Alec Baldwin, Paula Patton is very pretty but little else and James Caviezel reminds us that the Platypus and pirado fan is a role that likes to interpret.Not me roll it up more because it's not worth. Two-hour entretenidillas thriller with certain doses of action, not much for a weekend afternoon. If that is what you want, in "Deja Vu" you will find it.</body>
</review>
